I have been investigating the murder of Professor Odagiri from one year ago.
But if you keep the voltage at max and wear it for more than five minutes...
...then it will be lethal.
Kusakabe is not here.
He isn't?
His computer is not at his desk and
we haven't been able to contact him.
I got it. The truth behind the case.
Is the murderer the Professor's assistant, Kasai Hitomi...
...the imprisoned convict Nishihori Kouya...
...or the isolated Public Safety officer, Kusakabe Akira?
Or perhaps...
Why was Professor Banno
Episode 4
planning the Global Freeze?
Just who is the murderer?
Kaisai, Nishihori or Kusakabe?
The culprit is...
...none of those.
What do you mean?
First, the night before the Professor died.
April 7th, 2014 (Monday)  9:32 PM
Irritated with the Professor, Nishihori increased the voltage of the machine.
And the day of the incident...
...as revenge for plagiarizing her work...
April 8th, 2014 (Tuesday)  6:05 PM
...Kasai put a medicine that would place an intense strain on the Professor's heart into his cup,
with the intent of murder.
April 8th, 2014 (Tuesday)  6:48 PM
But Kyu spilled the contents of that cup, and so it has no relevance to the murder.
Professor!
So then the cause of the Professor's death must be...
Nishihori raising the voltage on the machine.
But you won't die unless you wear it for over 5 minutes.
I see! The Professor died on the night of the Global Freeze.
You got it, Gou. You're pretty sharp.
What happened?
Put simply, the moment the Professor put on the helmet...
The Global Freeze happened.
Did it break?
What is going on?
What is this?
I can't move my body!
So there is no murderer.
It was an accident.
But isn't the culprit still Nishihori?
It's because of him raising the
voltage that the Professor died.
No, Nishihori couldn't have predicted the Global Freeze.
He never deliberately attempted to kill the Professor.
I see.
What's wrong, Gou?
There is still something I don't understand.
You felt it as well?
Yeah. What Kyu said before.
He said that he used to run into Banno a lot during his walks.
They even met after he died, apparently.
If this case was an accident, does that mean Banno is unrelated?
Wait.
The name Banno was written in the Professor's planner.
And one more thing.
The Anima System's data was not found on the Professor's computer.
So even if his death was an accident...
...someone did wipe the data from his computer.
An accident?
So why was I working so hard to find a murderer?
But the case is not over yet.
Huh?
It's from Kyu.
I recovered the data from Professor Odagiri's computer!
Yes?
This is Kusakabe.
It seems you have solved the case.
Yeah.
So did you bring the recovered data from the computer?
We didn't recover the data.
What do you mean?
It was all a plan by the Special Crimes Unit to lure you out.
The planner Professor Odagiri left behind...
...the research he was conducting...
A system to upload the human brain into the network.
...and his actions.
He said that he used to run into Banno a lot during his walks.
They even met after he died, apparently.
It would be impossible to meet Banno on a walk if he was already dead.
But if the Professor's walks were in the network world...
...then it wouldn't be strange for you to notice him there.
What are you talking about?
Stop playing dumb!
Then how come you knew of Kyu's email, which was only sent to the Special Crimes members?!
Show yourself, Roidmude!
I'm surprised you figured it out.
Kamen Rider.
Brain!
Where is Kusakabe?!
I eliminated him.
He became aware of the Anima System, took the data
from the Professor's computer, and deleted the original.
Kusakabe did that?!
We were watching his every move. And then came the Kamen Rider.
You contacted him.
We had to avoid the Anima System
being spread throughout the world.
So that is why you pretended to be Kusakabe and tried to keep us away from the case.
Kusakabe Akira knew too much.
Unforgivable.
Why did you kill an innocent man like Kusakabe?!
Are you ready, Shinnosuke?
Yeah. I will avenge my comrade!
Good! Start you engine!
Transform!
DRIVE: TYPE SPEED!
You're coming along for the ride!
SP-SP-SPEED!
Kamen Rider, I do not intend to fight you now.
Professor Banno.
You intended to use the confusion of the Global Freeze a year ago...
...to borrow the Anima System to take control of the Professor's body.
So you could escape the network world.
But then the Professor accidentally died.
And your plan to capitalize on the Global Freeze...
...was crushed by the Global Freeze itself.
Ironic, isn't it?
Thanks to all of you, this case was solved successfully.
My deepest thanks.
I don't get it!
Is there still something missing?
Why are Kyu and Otta in the Special Crimes Unit?!
Oh, about that.
Kyu was scouted for his work with computers and the internet.
Exactly! Correct.
So Officer Otta?
Isn't it because he was in charge of the case a year ago?
And that's why he came to the Special Crimes Unit.
Well, yes.
Seriously, that's it?
Ah... that puts my mind at ease.
Knowing the truth also puts me at ease.
I'm totally not at ease.
You just used us to figure out
something you wanted to know!
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
This was just a test of your competence as police officers!
You're acting as suspiciously as always.
W-What are you doing?
That hurts,Shinnosuke!
It can't hurt! You're a belt!
Why you!
Ow! Ow! Hey! Hey!
Ow!
Secret Mission
START YOUR ENGINE!
The rain stops, there's a break in the clouds
The blue sky's calling out to you
Alright, it's almost time to head out
I don't need anyone else's advice
I've gotta trust my own instincts
It's high time I found my own way
Fire Up, Ignition
The heavy pressure's on
Slam the accelerator and power through
Surprise, the whole world's got drive!
(It's faster than ever)
Feeling high like you're finally awake
(Show me your Drivin')
Once you're on the road to destiny
(Keep chasin' forever)
A C C I D E N T !
There's no way to go in reverse...
All we need is Drive!