You're coming along for the ride!
I bet you're wondering why I'm fighting Brain right now...
It all started with this one case...
The story I'm about to tell you is the origin of Special Crimes Unit.
And an investigation into a murder.
Secret Mission
START YOUR ENGINE!
The rain stops, there's a break in the clouds
The blue sky's calling out to you
Alright, it's almost time to head out
I don't need anyone else's advice
I've gotta trust my own instincts
It's high time I found my own way
Fire Up, Ignition
The heavy pressure's on
Slam the accelerator and power through
Surprise, the whole world's got drive!
(It's faster than ever)
Feeling high like you're finally awake
(Show me your Drivin')
Once you're on the road to destiny
(Keep chasin' forever)
There's no way to go in reverse...
All we need is Drive!
One Day in April, 2015
I've been thinking about this for a while now...
How exactly did the Special Crimes Unit assemble this wacky cast of characters?
I think it's rather simple. We're all involved with Kamen Rider, somehow.
No, I get why everybody here is on the team.
You were rescued by a Kamen Rider,
and Rinna knew Krim before he died, right?
But...
Well, aside from Shin...
Hey, don't just gloss over my part!
What I'm asking is what's the deal with Kyu and old man Otta?
Episode 1   How was the Special Crimes Unit assembled?
They've got no connection to Kamen Rider, right?
Now that you mention it...
How about a little story, Krim?
If you're curious...
You'll need to look into a murder from one year ago.
A murder?
So, here's the outline of the case...
April 4th, 2014.
Professor Odagiri Masahiko of Shinkyo University's human sciences department mysteriously died.
The estimated time of death was between 7 and 9pm.
There was no sign of a struggle, the cause of death was recorded as cardiac arrest.
But the professor's assistant, Kasai Hitomi, went missing around that time...
Missing?
Huh?
Wait a minute, that date...
Wasn't that the day of the Global Freeze?
So, what does this have to do
with the Special Crimes Unit?
You'll understand if you can solve this case.
Sounds like fun. I'll solve it at mach speed.
You're showing your negative traits, Gou.
What about you, Shinnosuke? It will look bad if a detective gets one upped.
Why don't we race to see who can figure it out first, Big Bro?
Well, when you put it that way...
You're on.
Come on, Gou! Not so fast!
Honestly, don't turn this into one of your weird competitions!
Come on, you should be interested too!
If this case really does involve Kamen Rider...
Then Krim is probably hiding something.
Maybe you should do a little investigating of your own.
I mean, you did try to transform into Kamen Rider once, right?
Transform!
DRIVE: TYPE SPEED!
It's no use...
It seems that I'll need to find another candidate...
How did you know?
Well, I'm off to do some investigating!
You're Mr. Kusakabe Akira, right?
Metro Police Public Safety Detective
Kusakabe Akira
That's right...
You must be the Tomari I've heard about.
About me?
You're somewhat of celebrity in Public Safety.
You're the one who got
Superintendent Kirihara locked up, correct?
You're a bit of a celebrity yourself in the Special Crimes Unit.
You were investigating the murder of Professor Odagiri Masahiko, right?
Yes... that certainly was a bizarre case.
There was a device I had never seen before in the professor's room.
But I found nothing suspicious
when I checked his computer.
His cause of death was recorded
as acute cardiac arrest.
There's no telling what the truth is.
But apparently the Professor had an existing heart condition.
His heart...?
Mr. Kusakabe, you're with Public Safety...
Why were you on this case?
We were running surveillance on someone that was in contact with Professor Odagiri.
Who was that?
The man you arrested... Nishihori Kouya.
What's the connection between
Nishihori and Professor Odagiri?
I couldn't tell you. You'll have to ask the man himself.
But I'm not sure how cooperative he'll be...
What's gotten into you?
Having them look into a case from a year ago...
This case may have involved Banno...
Banno? You mean...
Your collaborator from your human life?
The man who created the Roidmudes? That Banno?
Yes, the late Professor Odagiri's calendar...
Banno's name appeared on it multiple times.
Why would he...?
Dear me, such a troublesome, tedious, tiring matter.
This is your fault...
Professor Banno.
Working on a cold case is rough, isn't it?
It's part of my duty as a police officer.
According to the files, Professor Odagiri had an existing heart condition...
Huh? Oda...
Oda?
If he had a heart attack...
maybe his medication wasn't effective?
Huh? Medication?
According to this...
His assistant, Kasai, would dissolve his medication in water once a day so that he could drink it.
Professor...
Thank you.
Heart medication...
Have you ever heard of Professor Odagiri, Saijou?
He seems to have some connection to the Special Crimes Unit.
Nope, never heard of him...
Little lady... why are you looking into that case?
Lt. Otta!
I went to go check on some records, and I heard that someone from Special Crimes had taken the file.
I'm the one in charge of that case.
Really?!
But why would you need the file now?
The girl who went missing last year...
Kasai Hitomi has returned.
Ex Criminal Psychologist
Nishihori Kouya
You must be really stumped if you're here to see me, Tomari Shinnosuke.
Let's cut to the chase.
What was your relationship with Professor Odagiri Masahiko?
Nothing complicated...
I was simply curious over some troubling rumors I'd heard about him at the time.
What rumors?
Apparently he made a habit out of plagiarizing his students' research, and taking the credit.
A similar M.O. to you and your copycat crimes...
I think I made contact with him...
The night before you arrested me.
What would a criminologist want with me?
April 7th, 2014 (Monday)  7:02 PM
I was simply curious about your habit of plagiarizing other people's work...
Shinkyo University Human Sciences Dept Professor
Odagiri Masahiko
Plagiarizing...?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to hide it from me.
I've actually been imitating other people's crimes for a while now...
In other words, you and I share a bond.
Ridiculous, I'm nothing like you.
I am doing research that people like you couldn't even fathom.
And I've achieved my goal.
With the Anima System...
Mankind will be free from the limitation of death.
I am nothing like some common plebeian that mimics others...
You could never understand.
Are you mocking me?
I'm a busy man. Please, show yourself out.
Don't tell me... that's why you killed him?
Wait, you mean he's dead?
What did you do to him?!
Just punished him a little.
I don't know what he was researching...
I increased the voltage on his little invention as high as it would go.
April 7th, 2014 (Monday)  9:32 PM
He had a weak heart!
Is that so?
In that case, I guess I must have killed him.
At the time, I still didn't realize...
...the truth lurking beneath the surface of this case.
Shinkyo University Human Sciences Dept
Kasai Hitomi
Professor Odagiri died...
...because of me.
Two suspects, both claiming to
have committed the crime...
Banno...
The ties that bind so many people to this case...
But what is the truth?
Who's the real killer?
Secret Mission
Is that even possible?
It is...
With the Anima System he created.
Switch on!
Why don't you tell me how you know Professor Odagiri?
If this case involves the internet,
then the Roidmudes could be involved.
Cores lurk within the internet, absorbing human emotions and spreading across the world.
Keep digging and someone is going to die.
Episode 2  What is the Anima System?