How were the members of the
Special Crimes Unit assembled?
If you're curious...
You'll need to look into a murder from one year ago.
That's how I ended up investigating the murder of Professor Odagiri...
We were running surveillance on someone that was in contact with Professor Odagiri.
Metro Police Public Safety Detective
Kusakabe Akira
Who was that?
The man you arrested... Nishihori Kouya.
Ex Criminal Psychologist
Nishihori Kouya
Just punished him a little.
I don't know what he was researching...
I increased the voltage on his little invention as high as it would go.
It seemed like the case was closed after Nishihori's testimony...
Until...
Professor Odagiri died...
Shinkyo University Human Sciences Dept
Kasai Hitomi
...because of me.
The professor's assistant, Kasai Hitomi, confessed to the same murder.
Who's telling the truth?
Which one is the real killer?
Secret Mission
START YOUR ENGINE!
The rain stops, there's a break in the clouds
The blue sky's calling out to you
Alright, it's almost time to head out
I don't need anyone else's advice
I've gotta trust my own instincts
It's high time I found my own way
Fire Up, Ignition
The heavy pressure's on
Slam the accelerator and power through
Surprise, the whole world's got drive!
(It's faster than ever)
Feeling high like you're finally awake
(Show me your Drivin')
Once you're on the road to destiny
(Keep chasin' forever)
There's no way to go in reverse...
All we need is Drive!
Professor Odagiri...
He... plagiarized my research.
He plagiarized it?
I had my computer protected with a password, but...
Episode 2   What is the Anima System?
He found a way to bypass the login through the network connection...
And then he stole my research data...
Is something like that even possible?
It is...
If he was using the Anima System.
Anima System... What the heck is that?
It allows you to dive into the internet and move about freely...
That's how he described it.
That research he stole was everything to me, it was my life's work...
That's why I couldn't let him get away with it.
But the Professor had no signs of trauma.
How did you do it?
He... had a heart condition.
Since he was so busy with his research, I prepared his medicine every day...
April 8th, 2014 (Tuesday)  6:05 PM
But that day...
After I found out what he'd done to my work...
I prepared a different medicine, one that would put an intense strain on his heart.
Professor.
Thanks.
After he drank that water, I'm sure he...
Shinkyo University Human Sciences Dept Professor
Odagiri Masahiko
That's a hell of a thing you did.
We can't be sure she's the killer.
Shinnosuke?
Wait a second, Tomari!
What do you mean by that?
According to the autopsy, there were no
signs of poison found in the Professor.
You don't say...
But if that's the case, then how did he die?
Another person has confessed to this crime.
What?!
Nishihori Kouya.
Ta-da!
Awesome...
I recreated Professor Odagiri's invention.
Nishihori said he turned the voltage all the way up, right?
Yeah.
Then we'll do the same thing...
Okay, time for science!
Huh?
No, no, no...
What if it kills me?
It'll be fine, trust me! Kiriko?
Ready!
Hey! Wait, wait! Stop that!
- Here comes the helmet.
- No, stop it!
There we go!
Come on, I'm begging you...
Okay...
C'mon Kiriko, let go!
Switch on!
W-Wait...!
No, I can feel it...
It's happening!
Huh?
Well, how does it feel?
It kinda... tingles a bit.
Okay, experiment complete!
Now we know that turning up the voltage isn't lethal.
Even if the professor had a weak heart.
That means...
Nishihori couldn't have killed the professor.
So that means it wasn't Kasai or Nishihori?
No, that doesn't rule anyone out...
Nishihori said something strange...
Professor Odagiri sounded pretty proud of himself...
With the Anima System...
Mankind will be free from the limitation of death.
That's right! Kasai Hitomi said it, too...
It allows you to dive into the internet and move about freely...
That's how he described it.
If a network connection is a clue in this case...
Then the Roidmudes may be involved.
Roidmudes...
You said they were born on the internet, right Krim?
Yes.
When Banno and I were working on the android technology...
None of their actual development involved the internet, but...
Banno hid a malicious artificial intelligence in the core.
As a result...
The leaders of the androids exhibited individualistic will.
They called themselves Roidmudes, and they killed Banno and myself.
In order to aid them in the war on mankind, they took their malicious cores and
created 108 Roidmudes, releasing them into the digital abyss of the internet.
The Cores roamed through the network,
absorbing human emotions and spreading all over the world.
Ultimately converting their code
into physical form as Roidmudes
What if the Anima System really is
connected to the Roidmudes, somehow...
What is it? You said it was important.
Please enlighten me.
What was your relationship with
Professor Odagiri, who died last year.
Who? I never heard of him.
Really? Well that's strange...
I was talking to a student from Shinkyo University...
And it seems that someone unaffiliated with the school was seen visiting the professor.
Now do you wanna talk?
I just wanted some advice...
Advice? About what?
The internet stuff the Professor was studying...
How did you meet him?
There's an SNS anime community...
What was he researching?
I don't know! Enough already!
Sorry, not so fast.
Why did you lie when I first asked you?
Mr. Kusakabe!
Mr. Kusakabe?
I tried calling you a few times.
Did you get my messages?
Yes...
I was occupied with other matters at the time.
Such troubling, idiotic, tedious matters...
Well...
I was hoping to ask you some more questions about Professor Odagiri.
Anything would help.
Do not dig any deeper into this.
Consider this a warning.
Any further and someone is going to die.
What do you mean?
Do you understand?
Yes?
There's trouble! Hurry back to headquarters!
What happened?
It's Saijou...
Kyu?
Stay back!
He's hiding something about Professor Odagiri.
Calm down, okay?
That's right kid, we're not gonna hurt y—
Stay back!
What exactly happened?
Kyu...?
It was me...
I killed Professor Odagiri! I did it!
Secret Mission
I don't know who...
But I think someone is after my research.
He said that he used to run into Banno a lot during his walks.
Professor Banno was already dead, though...
How could he have seen him?
It might be Kusakabe.
His attitude was completely different from when we first met...
You can commit a murder without leaving any evidence.
I think we might be closer to the truth than we realize.
Episode 3  Who killed Professor Odagiri?