How were the members of the
Special Crimes Unit assembled?
If you're curious...
You'll need to look into a murder from a year ago.
That's how I ended up investigating the murder of Professor Odagiri...
We figured out that neither Kasai, who we thought was the culprit...
...nor Nishihori were responsible for Professor Odagiri's murder.
The investigation was at a dead end.
Meanwhile...
Officer Kusakabe from the Public Safety Department, who was cooperating with the investigation, suddenly said this:
Any further and someone is going to die.
I killed Professor Odagiri! I did it!
Just what connection does this case have with the Special Crimes Unit?
What secrets lie hidden?
Secret Mission
START YOUR ENGINE!
The rain stops, there's a break in the clouds
The blue sky's calling out to you
Alright, it's almost time to head out
I don't need anyone else's advice
I've gotta trust my own instincts
It's high time I found my own way
Fire Up, Ignition
The heavy pressure's on
Slam the accelerator and power through
Surprise, the whole world's got drive!
(It's faster than ever)
Feeling high like you're finally awake
(Show me your Drivin')
Once you're on the road to destiny
(Keep chasin' forever)
There's no way to go in reverse...
All we need is Drive!
Episode 3   Who killed Professor Odagiri?
What do you mean by you killed Professor Odagiri?
I'm sure...
It was me...
Are you sure?
Probably!
Maybe...
I'm not totally sure though.
Uh... Kyu, you're getting less and less confident.
Professor Odagiri took medicine for his
heart every day, right? I didn't know that!
Please calm down! Put the weapon down.
I had been helping the Professor with his research.
With research, do you mean the Anima System?
What exactly was that research?
A system to upload the human brain into the network.
What?
I was giving him advice on that day...
April 8th, 2014 (Tuesday)  6:48 PM
Recently...
I feel like I'm being watched.
I don't know who... but I think someone is after my research.
No way! That couldn't...
Just now! Did you hear something outside?
No...
Who's there?!
Professor!
I didn't know that his medicine was in the water!
It's my fault! The professor died because I spilled the medicine!
You did well, Kyu.
It wasn't his medicine in the cup on that day.
He... had a heart condition.
Since he was so busy with his research, I prepared his medicine every day...
But that day...
After I found out what he'd done to my work...
I prepared a different medicine, one that would put an intense strain on his heart.
So that's why they didn't find any drugs in his system during the autopsy.
Relax. It wasn't your fault the Professor died, Kyu.
Yeah! I thought so!
You changed your tune quickly!
Hey, I want to ask one more thing.
What?
Did Professor Odagiri talk about anyone called "Banno"?
Well?
Yeah... many times.
What did he say?
He said that he used to run into Banno a lot during his walks.
They even met after he died, apparently.
Professor Banno was already dead, though...
How could he have seen him?
You don't think it could have been a random guy with the same name?
I'm glad though.
About what?
Kyu.
If he went any further, Kusakabe's warning would have come true.
Warning?
Yeah. Actually...
Do not dig any deeper into this.
Consider this a warning.
Any further and someone is going to die.
His attitude was completely different from when we first met...
That's strange.
You don't think...
Where are you going?
I think we might be closer to the truth than we realize.
Oh, right. About the Professor's machine...
I found out something new after running a few tests.
I told you before that you won't die
even if you raise the voltage to max.
But if you keep the voltage at max and wear it for more than five minutes...
...then it will be lethal.
If the current continues flowing
through the body for a long time...
...it will stop blood flowing from the heart, resulting in a condition called ventricular fibrillation.
So if someone made it so the Professor couldn't remove his helmet...
...and kept the assistants busy for five minutes...
You can commit a murder without leaving any evidence.
This is Tomari from the Special Crimes Unit.
Could you put Kusakabe on?
Kusakabe is not here.
He isn't?
His computer is not at his desk and
we haven't been able to contact him.
I see. Thank you.
The Professor's estimated time
of death is between 7 and 9pm.
The suspects are Kasai Hitomi and Nishihori Kouya.
Oh, Kasai is innocent.
Huh?
She was caught by a security camera trying to board a bullet train at that time.
Then Nishihori?
No, he is innocent as well.
I arrested him a while before the incident.
So then who...
It might be Kusakabe.
Gou!
I called up the Public Safety Department. Looks like he has suddenly disappeared.
I'm having them look up what Kusakabe Akira was doing on the night of the Global Freeze.
That's right! It was the night of the Global Freeze, so people couldn't move!
So how was Professor Odagiri killed?
Global Freeze?
I increased the voltage on his little invention as high as it would go.
I prepared a different medicine, one that would put an intense strain on his heart.
If you wear the helmet for more than five minutes it will be lethal.
Why can't I move?!
Wait... that's it!
I got it. The truth behind the case.
The key to all these mysteries lie in the Professor's estimated time of death.
What do you mean?
Now then!
A question for the people watching this on TV.
Why did Professor Odagiri die?
If you have been watching Kamen Rider Drive since episode one...
...then you should know the answer already.
I don't follow.
Give us a hint.
Then let me give you a huge hint.
Do you know about the multiple Secret Mission episodes...
...released in the Kamen Rider Drive series so far?
Take a look at the type name of every title.
There is an important hint hidden in those titles.
Now then, can you solve this mystery?
It's time for Type Tokujo's unraveling quiz!
Choose the reason why Professor Odagiri died from these options.
Access the Secret Mission website to participate in the quiz!
Put you brain in top gear! We are waiting for your submissions!
Secret Mission
I see! So the professor died on the same day as the Global Freeze.
Did it break?
The data was deleted from the Professor's computer.
We were interested in his contribution.
I understand.
The truth behind the case...
Is the murderer the Professor's assistant, Kasai Hitomi...
...the imprisoned convict Nishihori Kouya...
Why was Professor Banno
Episode 4
planning the Global Freeze?
...or the isolated Public Safety officer, Kusakabe Akira?
The culprit is...