Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Animal!
And so, the theme for this installment is animals!
But that doesn't work with the gimmick.
We gave up on that!
That was fast.
New
Member
Announcement
Starting today, we have a new member!
That's rather sudden.
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
New
Member
Announcement
Pam-pa-pa-pam!
It's me!
What's Lucoa doing here?
We don't have enough material
with just three of us.
So blunt.
And so, we've decided
to introduce Lucoa as a regular!
Yeah!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Cat!
Meow!
Meow-meow!
Ah, that's kinda cute!
Meow-meow-meow!
Lucoa, your "cat" is pretty half-baked...
Huh?
That's not true.
Meow, meow, meow, meow.
So cute...
Huh? What? What is it?
You puked?!
Cats will be cats.
Does our audience want to see this?
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Bear!
Bear.
Bearie-bear!
This is pretty good, too.
Bearie-bearie-bear!
Lucoa, you haven't changed at all.
Huh?
I'm all bear.
That's just ears!
Ah, I forgot something!
Is that necessary?
Wait, it's alive?!
Can't even see your face.
Hey! Ahh!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Sea Otter!
You don't have a single trace of sea otter.
Huh? Yes, I do. See?
I have the clamshells.
No otter is like that.
Oh, holding hands! How cute!
These just won't open, will they?
What a pain.
Show some perseverance!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Bunny!
That's not really an animal.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Dragon!
That's just redundant!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Koala!
This one... could work.
Wait, where's Lucoa?
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Dairy Cow!
* Circumstances require some areas to be censored.
Your boobs are completely exposed.
They are not. This is body paint.
Arrest her.
Huh? My time is up already?
And with that, we've completed our quota for this installment.
Quota?
All right, don't miss our next Dragon Something!
To be continued
But I've already had enough...