Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Battle!
We have some newcomers this time. If you please?
It's Fafnir!
Introduce me, too!
Me too...
Nah, never mind.
Some more fresh faces, huh?
The fans were asking for one of them,
so I invited them over.
One of them?
All right, let's get started.
Y-Yeah!
I guess I can tag along.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Western!
At last, it's time for our showdown.
Bring it on!
Stand back-to-back,
count off three steps, then shoot.
Got it?
Yep.
One...
Why did you shoot?!
You're not supposed to shoot
until we've counted to three!
You didn't think I'd actually follow your rules, did you?
You crooked...
Saw it coming.
Count to three, then shoot.
One...
Two...
Three!
I'm glad... you weren't... the one to die...
Nonsense.
No snappy one-liner?!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Ganryujima!
He's not coming.
We agreed to reenact the duel here.
Looks like he stood you up. Figures.
Sorry to keep you.
No problem. I got here five minutes ago.
That's because you got an early start.
Seriously?
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Kung Fu!
Is this Tai Chi?!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon RPG!
Tohru
Elma
Faf
Takiya
Devil King
..............................................................................................................................................................................................
Welcome to my lair,
heroes!
But you will regret
having come here!
Even in death, your
eternal suffering will
scarcely be enough to
Please, just shut up.
Devil King
......................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................
Tohru's attack
99999999 damage
Ah, that's over.
I'm hungry...
What, no item drops?
I mean, it was the final boss.
Well, that makes sense.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Battlefield!
Enemy attack!
Take it outside!
You haven't had one proper battle yet.
Isn't that what human battles are like?
Want to let loose?
Sounds good. Let's give our audience
a proper battle between dragons!
If you get out of hand, I will stop you by force.
Uh... See you next time, I guess.
This is incredible!
To be continued
You get used to it.