Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Wedding!
Duh-ragons, assemble.
Come to think of it, this is the first time
all of us have gotten together.
Makes sense for the last installment.
Right, I guess this is the last one.
Everyone, let's end this with a bang!
Yeah!
It's finally over.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Pure White Dress!
I'm the groom?
Whatever.
I'll never allow anyone else
to marry Miss Kobayashi!
Hey, calm down. This is just a bit.
Here comes the bride.
Sorry to keep you, Kobayashi.
What do you think, Kobayashi?
It suits me, doesn't it?
Your "veil" isn't veiling your horn.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Sacrifice!
Oh?
What's this?
Hey, there.
Sorry to keep you.
Is this a wedding?
In the land where I used to live,
it was customary to offer
a human heart as tribute during ceremonies.
That seems terrifying.
Why don't we offer something else?
Something else?
That should do it.
Huh?
Okay, a little bloodletting bonus, then.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Matryoshka.
A matryoshka?
Spasiba.
Sorry to keep you.
What is this? I want to take her home...
Marriage
Registration
Marry me.
Marriage
Registration
Huh?
Fill that out.
Bye.
Yeah, very businesslike.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Wedding Aisle.
Oh, that's a good way to end things.
Sorry to keep you.
At last, it's my turn.
Miss Kobayashi, what do you think?
I think it looks good on you.
Now then, the vows.
Do you take each other in sickness and in health,
And when lounging under the kotatsu,
and when gods descend upon the earth,
and when this world is brought to an end,
I vow that we will keep on loving each other!
What does that mean?
Miss Kobayashi vows it, too!
Don't vow for me!
Now then, the ring exchange...
Hold it! That thing is definitely cursed!
It's all right!
It can never be removed, that's all.
No way!
Finally, you may kiss.
Kissing is such a bother.
Let's move right on to the honeymoon night!
Just stop!
Okay, that marks the end of the
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Something extras.
Good work.
It's been fun.
We really went off the rails, didn't we?
Good work, everyone.
And to those of you who sat through them with us...
Thank you so very much!
The end
Bye-bye!