Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Sports!
Welcome back, Kanna.
I'm back.
When considering popular demand,
I settled on these cast members.
There's no "demand" for these.
It seems I've been chosen by this "popular demand."
Elma, you're standing in for Lucoa.
What was that?!
You got a problem with that?!
This segment is about sports.
Kanna, you just keep things rolling along, huh?
All right, let's get things going!
Yeah!
Soccer!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Soccer!
Kanna, pass!
Oh, no you don't!
Disqualified!
It isn't like that!
Just put your horn away.
Volleyball.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Volleyball!
Lady Tohru!
Take this!
Oh, no you don't!
Over the net.
Oh, no!
Again, just put your horn away.
Swimming!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Swimming!
The water is my territory!
No one can beat me at this!
Wh-Why, you...
Why does this keep happening?
Like I said, your horn...
What an idiot.
Lady Elma is a fool.
Kendo!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Kendo!
Horn!
Point!
What?! Horns don't count!
Horn!
Point!
But I just...!
Why are human sports all so difficult?!
For the last time,
if you put your horn away...
Never mind.
Cheerleading!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Cheerleader!
At last, I found a sport that I can do!
What does this accomplish?
Would you mind getting down, already?
What are you talking about, Elma?
This is your time to shine!
R-Really?
Lady Elma, you're so cool.
I-If you insist, then I guess I can keep this up.
Typical duh-ragon.
Okay, that's it for
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Sports.
We'll see you again next time.
Come on, wrap it up...
Elma, now's the time to really tough it out!
Everyone's cheering for you!
Fight! Fight!
To be continued
You really blow me away, Elma.