Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Uniform!
What's the deal with this project?
It's just an exposé of lust, isn't it?
Well, that's the kind of extras these are.
That may be true, but...
Hey, she's already stripping!
Huh?
Like a fish to water.
Anyway, let's get this installment started!
Yeah!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Nurse!
Your shot.
Your IV.
MEDICINE
Miss Kobayashi, all of your bedpan needs!
I'm not old enough to need that!
MEDICINE
Lucoa's properly dressed for once.
How are you feeling?
Well, not too bad, I guess.
Ah! Miss Kobayashi, I asked you
to please stop pinching my behind!
It's naughty!
But I didn't pinch you.
Time to take your temperature.
No, not like this—
Emergency! She has no pulse!
Rub rub.
Beginning CPR.
Wait, wait, wait! I'm alive!
Okay, now for mouth-to-mouth.
There's no need anymore!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon High School Girl!
Good afternoon.
I'm late, I'm late!
That's wicked.
Hmm, Kanna, you're too cute. That's wicked.
So anyway, I'm, like, mega stoked.
Huh? How come?
When I'm with Miss Kobayashi, I literally can't even.
That's mad wicked.
Miss Kobayashi's just too epic.
You should, like, make her your bae.
But if she friendzones me, I'll be highkey devastated.
If she does, we totally gotchu. We're bros.
Totes.
You guys are my squad.
This isn't what I wanted to see.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Cabin Attendant!
Attention, please.
Fasten your seatbelts.
We'll guide you on your
journey through the skies!
What's going on, Lucoa?
You're keeping your clothes on.
We will be taking off shortly.
Ma'am, is there anything that we can get you?
No, nothing.
Ah! Ma'am! If you pinch my behind again,
we'll need to escort you off of this flight!
Again, nobody's pinching you.
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Police!
Bike squad, move out!
Stop, or I'll shoot.
You're under arrest!
Tohru, that's not a uniform,
it's a variety show costume.
Miss Kobayashi, you're under arrest!
I'm telling you, I'm innocent!
Okay, now to execute you.
At least hold a trial!
Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Maid!
No change here.
Miss Kobayashi, leave all the housework to me.
Leave it to Lady Tohru.
Kanna, you're really not interested.
And Tohru, this is how you usually are.
Oh, I guess so!
Sorry.
I'm late.
Nothing but an apron?!
Circumstances require some areas to be censored.
I figured, since there were maids like this...
There are not!
Maid, dispose of her!
As you wish.
Huh? Again?
This is the same ending as last time, isn't it?
Good grief, Lucoa never learns.
We should really stop inviting her for these.
Don't worry. Someone else is taking the next shift.
There are shifts?
And so, we'll see you next time,
for Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Battle.
To be continued
Come on, don't spoil it!