Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Something!
What's with the "something"?
Please insert a word that ends with a "D."
Just like how "Maid" plus "Dragon" makes "Maidragon."
Why do we have to do something so random?
It's a project.
A project?
We have to create some extras.
Something to differentiate the BDs
from the broadcast episodes.
What happened to dignity?
All right, let's get started!
Band
Band.
Miss Kobayashi's Bandragon!
We're all over the place.
Why is my attire so plain?
The important thing is what we play.
Let's think of a direction to go with the music.
Then do the costumes even matter?
Yodeling.
Who wants that?
Idol!
That's not a band...
Enka!
Due to creative differences, we're disbanding.
We haven't even made our debut!
Mermaid
Mermaid.
Miss Kobayashi's Mermaidragon!
We're mermaids.
You're backwards.
Miss Kobayashi, you're my prince!
I told you, you have it backward!
Let's dance!
That's completely unrelated.
Here is a gift.
That's a dud, isn't it?
C-Can't breathe!
You breathe through gills?!
Indo
India.
Miss Kobayashi's Indragon!
The "India = curry" idea is pretty weak.
Namaste.
Iceland
Iceland.
Miss Kobayashi's Icelandragon!
Too literal.
New Zealand
New Zealand.
Miss Kobayashi's New Zealandragon!
Enough geography.
Avocado
Avocado.
Miss Kobayashi's Avocadragon!
Just like it sounds, huh?
You split?
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do.
Miss Kobayashi's Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-dragon!
Out of ideas, huh?
Nude
Nude.
Miss Kobayashi's Nudragon!
You're under arrest.
Next time, we'll fill in the blank space again,
with Miss Kobayashi's Dragon Something!
To be continued
To be continued!
We're making more?!