Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Scary!
People are Turning into Trees!!
On that day I was kicking a stone down a
country road where canola flowers bloomed
Birds were flying high in the sky
It's so cold!
-Why don't we have lunch here?
-Alright.
-Hurry...
-Help...
I'm sure I can hear human voices.
Water, please...!
Please help us...!
Where's it coming from?
This way, daddy!
Look at that, daddy!
They look like people, don't they?
It's the trees talking!
Please... help us...!
No, it's unbelievable!
Are they haunted!?
-Let's go back, darling!
-Right.
Who are you!?
The name is Alseides!
Alseides?
And what... do you
want with us?
You're gonna join GOD's guinea pigs!
-Darling!
-Daddy!
Run, quickly!
You can't escape!
Mommy! Sis!!
After him!
Is anyone there?
Help me! Anybody!!
Hold it!
Shouldn't we stop him, sir?
Sooner or later, everyone
in Japan will be a tree.
My experiment's already a huge success!
You fool!!
Your experiment is a failure! Their bodies
may be wood, but their minds are still human.
If you cannot suppress their minds,
then your plan must be postponed.
But, Supreme Commander--
Alseides!
You have new orders: Eliminate that
boy before the day is done. That is all.
Don't just stand there!
Bring me that brat already!
Hey, kid! What happened to you?
What's that? People becoming trees?
So a monster turned this
kid's family into trees...
Chief, you think GOD might be behind this?
Don't be silly! You think GOD
can turn people into trees?
He was probably daydreaming!
It wasn't a dream!
Please, rescue my daddy and mommy!
Hey! Where are you off to?
Mt. Hyouta.
Well, fine... C'mon, kid!
-Pass my jacket?
-Here.
Hey, why don't we tag along?
Sure!
I-it was this way.
Mt. Hyouta's just over there.
-Thanks!
-Take care, ok?
-Ok! Bye-bye!
Hey, Keisuke!
Hey, hold on a sec!
I can't believe we're
taking this kid seriously...
Right here! This is where
they got turned into trees.
I don't see anything that
looks like a human tree...
Weird, I'm sure
this was the place...
-You're really sure?
-I told you he dreamt it up!
Takeshi!
Daddy!
Where did you get to?
You know better than that.
But... didn't you get turned into trees?
That's quite a joke!
What are you saying? Were
you daydreaming again?
He probably fell asleep!
Well, I'm just glad it turned out ok.
Sorry for your trouble.
-Thank you so much.
-It was nothing!
See? Just like I said. Let's go.
Didn't fool me for a second.
Chief!
So...?
Follow me, but stay out of sight.
They don't look well...
They turned into trees again!
And you're gonna join them!
Help!!
-Come on, Takeshi!
-Run for it!
Stay out of this!
Darn it! That brat's slippery!
Takeshi!!
No one learns GOD's
secrets and lives! Die!
Hold it!!
I knew GOD were behind this!
Keisuke!
So, Jin Keisuke's here! Get him!
Let go!
Help, Keisuke!
Set Up!
There you are, X Rider!
The X Rider's here!
Here I come!
X Rider!
Take him!
Go!
Take him up there.
Let go!
X Rider, make like a tree!
Look up there, X Rider!
Help me, Rider!!
Takeshi!
If you want the brat to live, drop
your weapon and surrender!
What!?
You've got 'til I count
three to answer, alright?
Help!
He won't survive a fall from that height.
One...!
-Two...!
-Darn it!
Enjoying the view, Jin Keisuke?
Where's Takeshi?
I'm gonna hold onto him.
What? You're going
back on your word?
Light it!
I want you to enjoy every
second of your death!
We're leaving!
I've beaten Jin Keisuke! Now to take
Apollo Geist's place as senior officer!
What did you just say?
If it isn't Apollo Geist.
I've finished Jin Keisuke off!
What?
You don't believe me?
Of course not! The X Rider
can't die so easiy.
Only I can defeat the X Rider!
I'll just have to prove
it, then! Come on!
Darn it...
It's you!
Where's Keisuke?
-That way!
-Alright!
Keisuke!!
-You ok, Keisuke!?
-Keisuke!
Chief, put the fire out!
Curses! Still alive, Jin Keisuke?
Wait!
Alseides... This really
isn't bad for your work.
Quite the interesting little
show you're putting on.
Even Jin Keisuke can't lift a finger!
Keisuke!!
Say goodbye to Jin Keisuke forever!
Now we're leaving!
Jin Keisuke is dead...
and now it's your turn!
Are you ready?
Wait! Kill me first, if you have to!
It's the Rider!
The X Rider's still alive!?
Chief, look after Takeshi.
Right!
Cruiser Jump!
I knew the X Rider would
give up! We lost him!
Hit the brakes! What are
you doing!? Stop already!
Apollo Geist!
Idiot!
Hold it!
Apollo Geist!
Alright, today we settle
this! Let's go, X Rider!
Bring it on!
Apollo Change!
Wait, Apollo Geist.
Let me handle this!
You're not worthy of
facing the X Rider!
Shut up! I owe him!
Let me do it!
If you're that confident,
then have at him!
Alright, come at me!
This time you die, X Rider!
Have a taste of my whip!
Rider Shock!
You'll pay for breaking my whip!
Ridol Crown Splitter!
Daddy!
Darling!
You're alright! I'm so glad!
But what happened to us?
Daddy! Daddy!!
Takeshi! You're safe
too! Thank goodness!
-Mommy!
-What a relief!
But what changed you back?
I... don't have a clue either...
Isn't it obvious?
The X Rider beat the
monster and broke the spell!
Huh? What in the world
are you two doing here?
-Well, you see--
-It's like this--
You got turned into
trees too, didn't you?
Well, maybe...
That's dangerous! You can't just do
what you like without telling us!
-Sorry!
We should apologise for putting
you through so much too.
It's the X Rider!
Thank you, X Rider!!
The X Rider has crushed GOD's
awful plan to turn people into trees.
But they have another plot in store.
Will the X Rider be up to the challenge?
Do it for us, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
A black cat spreads a mysterious virus,
transforming city residents into cat-people.
Beware the black cat!
It's an agent of GOD!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Scary! It's GOD's Ghost Cat Plan!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider