Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Immortal Water Snake Monster, Hydra!
No dumping
Hey, Youjirou. What's that?
What the heck!?
It must be the guardian of
this lake! Let's get outta here!
Hydra!!
Enough playing around, water snake Hydra.
Excuse me!?
You've got a more important mission
than meddling with ordinary humans.
Damn, I can't stand that guy!
Water snake Hydra.
GOD Supreme Commander!
Your mission is to disrupt Tokyo's economy.
Proceed with it at once! That is all.
It's him!
Hey! Hey!!
Yo! You doing well?
Yeah!
How's your leg?
A lot better! I should be out in a week!
Good to hear!
Here, this is for you!
Toss it up!
Catch!
Thank you!
Well, be seeing you!
Bye bye!
Up you go.
How is it? Any pain?
No. Oh, mom asked me to tell you
she left this week's fee money.
It's on the table, so you can take it to the office.
Yes sir!
Whats wrong?
A lizard! There's a lizard there!
They creep me out...
I'll take care of it!
It's glowing!
The money and the lizard disappeared!
New Victoria
A lizard!!
The money's gone!
Toyland
Pinocchio
I'll take this, please.
Sure, that'll be ¥500.
My money just disappeared!
M-my money's vanished!!
-Mine's all gone too!
-What happened?
The plan's off to a great start!
Let's move on to the second phase!
Not a yen left in town...
It can only be GOD, can't it?
But they're probably trying to upset
the economy rather than make money.
Yeah, good point.
And they're bound to aim for
an even bigger payoff next.
An even bigger payoff...?
Tokyo Central Bank service entrance
Thank you.
Sir.
F17 here. They just set off as planned.
Roger that.
Turn around, turn around!
After them!
Work in progress - Detour
What was that?
Let's go.
-What's wrong?
-Strange, the car's stuck.
No good!
Alright, I'll take a look.
A monster!
You damn freak!
Alright, unload the truck!
It's him again!
I knew you guys were behind
the disappearing money.
So you're Jin Keisuke?
Ignore him and unload the truck!
Set Up!
X Rider!
X Slash!
Accursed X Rider, I'll send you to the afterlife!
Ridol Stick!
It's you, Apollo Geist!
You must think you made
short work of Hydra, X Rider!
What?
Surprised, X Rider?
Hydra's head won't stay cut off.
He's immortal!
Why, you...!
Die, X Rider!
Damn, I was so close!
Hydra!
Don't waste your time.
You've already made one mistake!
The plan's going smoothly!
What mistake!?
Are you blind? Over there!
That boy at the hospital
witnessed every bit of your plan.
What!?
Darn! So that's where the money went!
Accursed brat...
Another strange incident has just occurred.
Several hundred million yen was stolen
from a bank transport vehicle.
See, I wasn't lying!
Yeah, but it's hard to believe...
A snake monster, melting people?
I said I wasn't lying!
What's that blue stuff?
The snake monster!!
I feel bad for you, but you've
gotta die now you know our secret.
Kamen Rider!
Are you alright?
Yeah!
X Rider, curse your interfering ways!
X Rider, they threw the money in the lake!
The lake?
That's enough out of you, brat!
Nurse, get Satoru out of here.
Right!
Hold it!
This time I'll make sure you die!
Rider! Take a look over there!
How's that feel, Rider? Just try moving!
Darn it...!
Die, X Rider!
Rider Shock!
Rider Shock lets the X Rider instantly pass a thousand-volt
electric current through the surface of his body.
The enemy is shocked and sent flying.
Curses!
Ridol Stick!
Long Pole!
Damn you, Rider!
X Kick!!
The water snake Hydra is immortal!
That's him alright...
This must be the lake.
Curses...
Hydra!!
I see, so this is where you hid the money!
You'd come all the way down here!?
Whatever it takes to bring that money back.
As if I'll let you!
Bring it on!
Ridol Stick!
How about that, Rider?
Damn!
Stop!
One last time!!
X Kick!!
Useless.
Supreme Commander, I'm afraid Hydra has fallen to the X Rider.
It can't be helped. Await reinforcements.
Sir.
Yo.
You're all better?
Take a look! I'm walking already!
That's great. Keep it up!
Yeah!
See you around.
The X Rider foiled Hydra's plan to disrupt the economy.
But it won't be long before GOD are active again.
Don't lose, Jin Keisuke - X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD's Chimera kidnaps a girl with the power
to bend spoons and see inside boxes.
And when Rider X tries to save her,
he falls into Chimera's trap.
Even the famous spoon-bending boy
Sekiguchi Jun makes an appearance!
Look forward to the next Rider X:
"Kidnap the Psychic Girl!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider