Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
'I Want Bloood'
The Leech Monster of Corpse Swamp!!
Pitiful humans! GOD rules
this world, you'll see!
Die! Die, humans! Die!
Come, my darling pet!
Drink your fill of young maidens' blood!
Die! Die, humans!
Good news, your temperature's gone down!
But you shouldn't be moving around yet.
I'm so bored!
A l-leech!?
What's wrong?
There was... a scary old
lady... at the window!
I don't see anyone!
I'm not kidding! She was
frowning at me, all creepy!
That's not possible!
What a silly thing to say...
For one thing, we're three floors up.
How could anyone be at the window?
You're just a little delirious.
C'mon, you need rest!
Young lady!
Why don't I read your fortune?
It's free! Come, sit down!
How old are you, my dear?
Eighteen...
So young!
Here, pick a card...
A leech...!
Not just any leech! They
feed on human blood...
...and they look just like that!
Monster!!
Go now, and drink your fill of that girl!
Was that a scream...?
I'm sure I heard something...
I'll show you, Jin Keisuke...!
Yes, drink her blood too!
Michiko?
Is something wrong, Michiko?
Michiko...!
Won't you offer your
blood to my darling pet!?
The chief said he didn't
want you getting bored, Chiko.
Thank you!
Maybe some music'll help you rest.
-Well, I'd better be going.
-See you!
Wait... You're mistaken to think
you're unbeatable, Jin Keisuke!
GOD...
Keisuke...!
Stay here.
Who's there?
We want bloood!
We must drink blood!
-We want your blood!
-Are you three crazy?
We want bloood!
Those girls have had their blood
drained by the blood-sucking leech!
Now they must wander
in search of new blood!
Who the heck are you!?
Hold it!
Pitiful humans! GOD rules this
world, you'll see! Die! Die!
Darn it!
I am Leech Dracula, inheritor
of Count Dracula's blood!
Give your blood to
my leeches and die!
Leech Dracula's leeches
can melt human flesh.
Die, Jin Keisuke!
My leeches, melt Jin Keisuke's body!
Great Transformation!
Try this, X Rider!
The real terror is yet to begin!
Leech Dracula, how is your plan progressing?
Sir! Just wait and see
what horrors I unleash next!
Somebody help me!!
I want to drink your blood! Your blood!
L-leave me alone!
Your blood! Give it to me!
Stop! I need your blood!
Is anyone there!? Someone help!
Blood...!
Help me!
What's the matter?
Let me... drink your blood!
Help! Help!
-Please save us!
-Vampires!
-H-hurry, quickly!
-Boss!!
Huh? Say what!? Really?
-Chief?
-Keisuke! There are vampires at Chiko's hospital!
Blast... So that's what Leech Dracula meant!
What are you talking about, Keisuke?
Th-th-the TV!
A leech!
Tachibana Toubei! Jin Keisuke!
There you are, GOD monster!
Those who have had their blood drained will
hungrily seek out the blood of others!
Tokyo is now a hive of vampires!
What are you after?
Deliver your pieces of the
RS Device's blueprints to me!
What? You expect me to
give you the blueprints?
It is the only way to cure the vampires!
I will await you at the banks of Corpse Swamp...
Chiko! You've gotta save Chiko!
Chief, check out the hospital.
Make sure Chiko's safe.
What about you?
...I'm going to Corpse Swamp.
Don't tell me you're--!
We can't let anyone else become a vampire.
I have to go!
Jin Keisuke shall die! He shall
die here in Corpse Swamp!
-There you are, Jin Keisuke!
-I kept my word.
Then you have the blueprint pieces?
Here.
All five of mine.
Hand them over!
The genuine article!
With that, I'll take my leave!
And what about the vampires?
Do you really think I care?
Die!
Corpse Swamp is bottomless! Once
you go down, you don't come up!
Writhe in pain!
Leech Dracula, you've truly proven
yourself by eliminating Jin Keisuke.
And now, King Dark, those bloodthirsty
humans will take care of the rest...
-I want blood!
-Give me blood!
-Chiko!?
-Boss!!
-I want blood!
I want blood!
I want bloood!
-I want blood!
-My body's melting!
-The pain...!
-Boss?
-Alright, we beat them!
What in the world?
I get it! It was the salt
you threw at them!
-Salt?
-Yeah!
Of course! Leeches can't stand salt!
-We've gotta get to Corpse Swamp and tell Keisuke!
-Right!
King Dark, the blueprints.
Excellent work! Your peers in the
Villain Army could learn a lot from you.
Dracula's descendant has no 'peers'!
W-what's this!? Look at those blueprints!
I-impossible! They were there a minute ago!
Imbecile!! They obviously
used disappearing ink!
Deal with Jin Keisuke properly
this time, Leech Dracula!
Curse that Jin Keisuke!
Have you drowned already, Jin Keisuke?
Great Transformation!
Take this!
The salt brought by Tachibana Toubei
melts Leech Dracula's leeches!
My leeches are melting!
You're a quick one!
I'll never live down bringing
those fake blueprints back! Die!
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
The Vacuum Hell Wheel is a deadly finishing move that reduces
the enemy's offensive power by rolling them through the air.
After that, they're finished with an X Kick.
Hell Wheel Kick!
Accursed X Rider! Next time,
we'll send him to hell itself!
Leech Dracula's vampire plan has been foiled.
But King Dark will use any means to get those
five blueprint pieces. Fight on, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
In search of the rest of the RS Device's blueprints,
Lizard Viking targets a young girl in the Nasu Highlands.
And of course, the courageous Kamen
Rider X takes a stand against him.
Next time, look forward to GOD and X Rider's battle for the
blueprints in Nasu Highlands:
"Arise! King Dark!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider