Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Apollo Geist Strikes Back!
X Rider, Beware!!
Intercepting one of GOD's secret messages, Jin Keisuke
finally infiltrated their base: the Palace of Apollon.
But the formidable GOD Agency foiled Keisuke's plan.
Not only is the X Rider challenged by a
fierce enemy in the Death God Chronos...
...But what are the two scientists working
on beneath the Palace of Apollon?
Who or what is laying on this operating table?
X Kick!
I've... won...!
Darn it...
After the X Rider!
This is the GP. X Rider currently entering
palace. Initiate level one security precautions.
Do not be concerned.
The Palace of Apollon is two hundred metres
underground, its corridors labyrinthine.
The X Rider's capture is but a matter
of time. Now, begin the surgery!
Yes sir, Supreme Commander. Initiating surgery!
Is this...?
Apollo Geist, Chief of GOD's Secret Police.
I've only ever heard his name.
But what are we to do with him?
He fell in battle with the X Rider.
GOD cannot allow him to die like this.
GOD still has need of Apollo Geist!
As such, he requires reconstructive surgery.
Understood. I'll infuse Apollo Geist's
bodily tissues with the strongest cells!
And I'll upgrade Apollo Geist's mechanical parts.
I put my faith in your skills, doctors.
Have you seen him?
Where can that accursed
X Rider be hiding?
Look harder!
My shoulder'll take an hour to heal...
and I need to stay hidden somehow...
Well, seeing as I'm already here...
May as well take my time looking around...
We've had orders from the Supreme Commander.
Have Kerberos initiate the Fire Plan while
we contain the X Rider in the Palace.
This is the tape with the Fire Plan?
Fire Plan?
What can that be?
GOD have all the bases covered...
I've gotta get out of here.
We've thoroughly examined all
sixteen of the Palace's blocks.
He has no hiding places left.
The X Rider can't just have
vanished, and yet... Curse him!
-Did you find him?
-Negative!
Check rations, weapons,
and medical sectors!
Medical's in surgery,
we can't just barge in.
We certainly can!! The Palace's
security is our only priority!
Captain, you're bleeding!
Bleeding...?
Someone's getting surgery?
That must be what GOD
wants with the two doctors!
Alright, I need to see this for myself.
Geist Double Cutter.
Apollo Magnum.
Darn it, where's this
surgery even happening?
Almost done.
That was Dr. Kawakami's voice...
There they are!
Can't see who it is...
A trail of blood! The X Rider
did come this way!
We've got him!
Uh-oh! Found me at last, did you!?
Apollo Geist's reconstructive
surgery is complete!
Good work.
Well, how does it feel to live again?
Most refreshing! My thanks,
Supreme Commander.
Direct your thanks to the
doctors Kawakami and Miyamoto.
GOD provided these two with vast expenses!
It's only natural that they did their jobs!
That's the Chief of Secret Police for you.
You have been reborn with powerful
new mechanical parts installed.
Let us test them at once. Some
training will help you master them.
You see, I have a present for you.
A present...?
There he is! We've got him now!
This is bad...
Jin Keisuke!!
Apollo Geist...!
Jin Keisuke... I see, so you're my
present from the Supreme Commander!
I thought you were dead!
I won't die until I've killed you! You
should get used to the sight of me!
Let's test how quickly my
new equipment takes your life!
The Apollo Magnum.
It fires three 22 calibre shells, enough
to scrap a heavy tank in one shot!
Transform into the X Rider! I get
no joy from fighting a human!!
Set--
What's wrong!?
It's no good...
Apollo Geist! I'll fight you
without becoming the X Rider!
Geist Double Cutter!
It's been a whole day since Keisuke left.
I hope he isn't--
...No, no chance.
Mr. Tachibana, the coffee--!
Welcome back, Mako! What's that?
Someone just asked me
to give it to the boss.
This job's tough, isn't it?
What, what? Something for me?
Yep, here you go!
A present for the boss...
Must be from your girlfriend.
Show your elders some respect!
Sorry...
What a strange doll...
-It's that doll!!
-What's the matter?
That's the matter!
What's wrong with it?
Is this one of GOD's dolls!?
Watchdog of Hades, Kerberos, heed
the Supreme Commander's orders.
Sir, you need to get out of here! Hurry!!
Not until I've heard the
Supreme Commander's orders.
GOD!! Hey, run for it!
-We'd better hurry!
-Right, let's go!
Let us go!!
Let go!
Sir, your orders?
Apollo Geist has GOD's enemy, the X Rider,
at his mercy in the Palace of Apollon.
There is now no one on Earth capable of stopping the acts of GOD.
Implement the Fire Plan at once! Reduce Tokyo to
a sea of flames by overloading its electrical grid!
Begin the operation at Tachibana's coffee shop.
Yes, sir! Everything is in readiness.
As you heard, Tachibana's coffee shop
is now an asset of GOD's operation!
Don't give me that! I won't let you!
-Boss!!
-Hang in there, hang in there!
Did you see that? Fifty thousand
volts flow through my body.
-You won't get away with this!
-Jin Keisuke will save us, you'll see!
You won't be seeing Jin Keisuke again.
Tie them up!
Jin Keisuke... I'll wait for
your wound to heal.
But that will be the end of you!
I can't do anything to stop
GOD
's Fire Plan like this...
But I'll have to get out of here first.
Apollo Geist has ordered me to
assess Jin Keisuke's wound. Open up.
You--! But your wound--!
One hour was all I needed.
You can thank Apollo Geist for that.
Get up!
GOD does not brook failure!
You two must be executed!!
Wait! I brought you back to life!
Wow!
Is this the time to flatter me!?
We have a security breach!
Assemble all Palace
of Apollon personnel!
Elevators are off-limits.
Look! The Supreme Commander
has orders for Kerberos!
Good work. Occupying Tachibana's coffee
shop will guarantee GOD's victory this time.
Tachibana's coffee shop...
Go ahead.
They've occupied Tachibana's coffee
shop? Hold on a little longer, chief...
In ten minutes, every wire
in Tokyo will overload.
When that time comes, your lives will end.
You monster!!
Give up, Mako...
Don't say that! Justice
has to win in the end!
Naive, so naive! There's nothing
stronger than evil in this world.
Just wait until the X Rider gets here!
Where is Jin Keisuke now!?
Our security is flawless. Catching
him is just a matter of time!
No attempts to contact the surface?
No, sir! Just one agent who left with
orders from the Supreme Commander!
Idiot!! That was Jin Keisuke!
Get after him at once!
Apollo Change!
Set Up!
Cruiser Big Turn!
I warned you, didn't I? Your life
ends once you become the X Rider!
Apollo Geist, did you forget
the X Rider defeated you once?
Silence! I'm no longer
the Apollo Geist I once was!
No matter how often you come back,
Apollo Geist is no match for the X Rider!
Try this! Magnum Shot!
Geist Cutter!
Cruiser Jump!
Sorry, Apollo Geist, but I haven't
got time to fight you. Another day!
Curse you, X Rider!
Begin the Fire Plan's countdown.
Maybe it really is no use this time...!
Kerberos! The plan to burn
down Tokyo is suspended!
Suspended!? No! I just--!
This is an order from GOD's
Supreme Commander!
No... That's not the Supreme
Commander's voice!
Where are you? Who are you? Come out!!
-The X Rider!
-X Rider!
Blast! How did you escape
the Palace of Apollon!?
-There, didn't I tell you?
-He really did come!
-Quick, save us!
You fools think the X Rider can
save you? You're all going to die!
Hold it!
X Rider, this guy's got fifty
thousand volts running through him!
Did you enjoy that, X Rider?
Touch my body all you like.
Burn, Tokyo!!
Whats going on!?
I cut your little circuit.
Then I'll just have to kill you too!
Come and get me, Kerberos!
Here I come!
Ridol Rope!
All I have to do is kill
you and resume the plan!
Come on!
X Kick!
Darn it...!
I'll just get electrocuted
if I attack him directly...
Long Pole!
Fifty thousand volts isn't
such an advantage in water.
His greatest weapon turned
out to be his greatest weakness.
Escaping the Palace of Apollon, the
X Rider saved Tokyo from a fiery crisis.
But the revived Apollo Geist will terrorise
the X Rider with more challenges.
Keep fighting, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
The sounds of people in pain and sorrow
carry on the wind through a quiet forest.
GOD's monster Alseides has begun a
horrible experiment to turn people into trees.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Scary! People are Turning into Trees!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider