Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
But Nanbara escaped GOD and tore the blueprints
into nine pieces to entrust to his old colleagues.
GOD has stolen one of the pieces,
and the X Rider holds three.
Thus does a deadly race for the
remaining five pieces begin!
Behold!
X Rider's Great Transformation!!
Oki Institute of Biology
Good grief! That makes thirteen!
At this rate, GOD's gonna kill
every scientist in Japan!
Chief... Take a look at this.
It's a portrait of Napoleon, right?
Right. The same one was found
at the scene of all these crimes.
Then that begs the question...
...who's next?
Nonaka Youichirou
Chiko, wake up! It's a burglar!
A burglar...?
...Weird. There's no one here...
Oh, it's just you two!
'Just you two'!? Is this any
way to treat your guests?
Really! You shouldn't be playing pranks!
Just tell us you're coming!
But we heard a strange noise, so--
You too, Youko?
You heard the same thing?
Mom, there really is someone else in the house!
Look!
His shoes are wet! Something's seriously wrong!!
Where is Dr. Nonaka?
M-my husband's in America! Wh-who are you!?
My deepest apologies, madam. You may address
me as Spider Napoleon, of GOD's Villain Army.
Now then, madam... Won't you give
me the blueprint sent to Dr. Nonaka?
I-I don't know anything about it!
Madam, I am a gentleman. I
could never raise a hand to a lady.
Would you like to try one, madam?
My cute little babies just love beautiful
ladies! He seems attached to you, madam.
Let my mom go! I've got the blueprint!
-The boy!
-Itaru!
Where's the blueprint?
Please stop! I have it here!
Keisuke!
You're alright now. The
chief told me you were here.
So you're Jin Keisuke? I've
been looking forward to this.
Your life is mine! The word
'impossible' means nothing to me!
But for now, I shall settle for this blueprint.
Darn, where'd he go?
I can't let him get away!
I know all your weak spots!
Try my Vampire Spider!
Within minutes, you'll
be a desiccated corpse.
That's more like it, X Rider!
X Kick!
Something the matter, X Rider?
You're wasting your time, X Rider!
X Kick!
Blast... What's happening
to me...? I can't move...
Haven't you figured it out, X Rider?
My web drained all of your energy!
Your Rider Kick's useless now.
What...?
Spiderweb Jungle!
No...!
Struggle, struggle! The more you
struggle, the more energy you waste!
No use... Strength... fading...
-Die!
-Hold it!
Who are you!?
You don't know who I am? That says
more about you than it does me.
W-what!?
They call me... Kamen Rider V3!
Kamen Rider V3, eh? Alright,
I'll kill you too! En garde!
W-where did you go, V3?
...Just wanted to draw me out,
did you? Show yourself, V3!
Calm down, Spider Napoleon. I don't have
time to fight you now. We'll do this later.
Come out, V3!!
Get this on you...
Chief...
I have to operate on Keisuke.
What?
The only thing that can stop Spider
Napoleon is... Mercury Power.
Mercury Power...?
Fool!! That blueprint was a counterfeit!
That's impossible!
You must have been tricked!
Tricked...?
Let my mom go! I've got the blueprint!
That brat! He really did have it!
The Mercury Power will allow X to perform
the Vacuum Hell Wheel technique.
But it can only be used with
a Mercury Circuit installed.
As such, it requires a
transfusion of all one's blood.
I'll give you every drop
of my blood if I have to...
Shirou, big trouble!
GOD's got Itaru.
Itaru was hiding the real
blueprint all along.
-I thought they already took it?
-No, that was a fake!
A fake? But... I have to stay
here until the operation's done!
...Shirou, look after Keisuke.
Chief--!
Chief...
We're being followed.
What? Well, let's see how
they like a Spiderweb Jungle...
Hello, gents!
I'm running out of time... If I don't
install the Mercury Circuit now--
Speak! Where have you
hidden the blueprint?
Like I'll tell you! I promised
my dad I'd keep it a secret!
I see, I see... Then I'll
have to ask less politely.
Watch carefully now...
Alright... Now all he needs is
a shock to bring him out of it.
Of all the times!
Help! Help!!
Do you feel like talking now, boy?
Dad! Mom!!
Keisuke, are you ok? Please hurry!
Keisuke!!
Blast you, GOD!
Someone help!
-Wait, I'll tell you!
-No! Don't do it!
-The blueprint is--
-You can't tell them!!
It's in Itaru's...
Dang it...
Transform... V3!
V3!
Why, you--!
Curses!
-V3!
-Get Itaru out of here!
-Right!
Hold it!
I believe you owe me
a match, V3! En garde!
Curses! Spiderweb Jungle!
How do you like that, V3?
Can't move, can you? You made
the same mistake as the X Rider.
Finish him!
Hold it!
Keisuke...!
Jin Keisuke? You're alive!?
It'll take more than that to kill me.
I'm not the same man any more.
Get ready, Spider Napoleon!
Great Transformation!
And!?
Vampire Spider!
No, d-don't tell me--!
You won't get me with that again!
Then what about the Spiderweb Jungle!?
Die!
Try this!
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
How does the Vacuum Hell Wheel work?
This special move uses an
enemy's power against them.
First, it reduces their offensive power by rolling them
along at high speed, driving their head into the ground.
After that, they're thrown into the air and fall back to earth with a bang.
Finally, an X Kick clinches the victory.
Hey, Keisuke!
Kazami, the Mercury Power worked!
You don't say? Good work, Keisuke.
With the fourth blueprint piece as
good as yours, you can afford a day off.
Hang in there!
Same to you!
Why, you--!
Jin Keisuke has been powered
up by Kazami Shirou.
You've gotten stronger, X!
Now crush King Dark's ambitions!
To be continued
Next episode
King Dark and the X Rider continue their
deadly race for the mysterious RS Device.
GOD sets their sights on a blueprint piece hidden in a young ballerina's pendant.
Go, X Rider!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Mortal Combat!! X Rider Versus X Rider!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider