Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
Why did Keisuke's beloved Ryouko side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
Kamen Rider X fights against the mysterious agency known as GOD.
The Terrifying Human Genius Plan!
That's the twenty-third person.
Twenty-three elementary and middle school
students have jumped to their deaths.
And not an illness among them!
I can't see what GOD would get out of this.
Who cares what their plan is?
Who's making these kids jump?
While you're wondering what GOD are after,
these incidents keep happening!
Cat got your tongue?
No, it's just...
You just reminded me of my dad.
This is no time to talk like that!
Who knows who they'll target next?
Yessir!
Jump!
Jump, Ayako!
With that white silk cloth,
you can fly in the sky all you wish.
I can fly...
With this silk cloth, I can fly in the sky...
Be careful! Hey, you!
Get out of the way! Can't you see that girl?
Icarus Death Smoke!
Only death awaits those who stand in my way.
Now, jump!
That makes twenty-four.
Icarus, prepare to receive orders.
GOD Chief Commander!
The first stage of your plan to drive children
to suicide is already a splendid success.
Proceed to the second stage at once!
Drive Dr. Daimonji into an abyss of despair.
Wreck his human genius research and
recruit the doctor into GOD.
Roger!
Daimonji
Ayako...
Look...
They're cattleyas, your favourite flowers.
The cattleyas you loved so much...
Doctor, Fuyoko is...
Sister! Sister, why did you have to die?
Stupid! Stupid sister!
It seems this Dr. Daimonji has been researching
'human geniuses' for ten years.
My dad told me about him.
Apparently his research can increase a human's intelligence
tenfold. He only uses good-hearted children.
It'd be terrible if it fell into the wrong hands. This time
the victim was Dr. Daimonji's daughter Ayako.
Chief, I'll investigate.
What are these pictures here for?
They're the recipients of my human genius research.
And...
All of these already intelligent elementary and middle school
students took this mental stimulant I created.
That's who the children in those pictures are.
Dr. Daimonji, you don't think--?
I can't help but worry that these children's
mysterious deaths were a side-effect of this medicine.
Even Ayako, doctor?
Ayako died of unknown causes too.
Only one child who's taken my medicine has survived.
Come on, Fuyuko.
That's Seyama. An outstanding assistant.
Fuyoko seems to be falling for him.
She talks about getting married when she's bigger...
but she's still a child.
I just don't know how much longer Fuyuko has left.
Doctor, do you mean--?
Take a good look at that list.
The only one to have survived my
medicine thus far is Fuyuko.
But that also means that Fuyuko is...
If you keep crying you'll stick that way.
Come on, dry your tears.
Dr. Daimonji, that won't happen.
I swear I won't let Fuyoko die.
Lord God, by your mercy grant
this faithful soul a peaceful sleep.
May your holy angels watch
over her grave as its keepers.
Free the soul here interred of all its sins.
Let her come before the Heavenly Host, and--
Fuyoko's gone!
Doctor, could Fuyuko have wandered off in her shock?
Find her! Please, find her!
Help me!
That's Fuyoko!
Help!
Icarus Death Wing!
Let's go!
Help!
Set Up!
You're--!
X Rider!
X Rider?
Icarus Death Smoke!
Ridol Stick!
Had enough, did you?
Fuyuko!
I managed to keep her out of trouble.
Kiriko, you always seem to show up after Ryouko.
Won't you tell me who you really are?
Why did Ryouko betray me and my dad?
Please, tell me!
Ryouko is my elder sister.
Your sister?
We're twins. But we grew up far away from one another.
Keisuke, please console yourself with the fact
that my sister is still your fiancee.
Fiancee?
I can't believe that.
If it's true, then why did Ryouko--
Keisuke, I'm your ally.
I'll leave Fuyoko with you.
Where's Seyama?
Seyama?
Seyama, don't die!
For me... you did this for me?
Fuyoko, Seyama will be fine now.
Please get to bed.
But... but he got like this fighting for me.
If I don't stay beside him...
Seyama has a dream that someday he'll fly in the sky.
He never stops talking about it, even while helping dad.
We don't think it's a fairytale that humans might fly one day.
Icarus! Icarus! This is GOD's Chief Commander.
Your orders are to kill X Rider.
Also, we have no need for Dr. Daimonji if he won't join GOD.
Kill him at once!
Understood, Icarus?
Die, Jin Keisuke!
Your stories are always so wonderful, Seyama.
People flying in the sky without planes...
It's so romantic!
Do you know why angels of all
cultures wear white as they fly?
It's because white is the colour of a pure heart.
So that's why they can fly?
Right! White has no dirtiness to it.
That's why I love these white flowers so much.
Me too!
Smells nice!
Icarus...
GOD Chief Commander.
In accordance with your orders,
Jin Keisuke has been eliminated.
Good. You will next kill Dr. Daimonji and Fuyuko.
Roger!
Darn...
What do you want?
Move aside!
Seyama, what's going on?
Doctor!
Keisuke, what's the rush?
Be careful, doctor!
This guy's really Icarus!
So you knew, Jin Keisuke?
You're quite right!
The rest is up to you, Combat Agents.
Have at them!
Quick, run for it!
What were they up to? And why did Icarus take off?
Oh no!
Seyama, this is a present from me.
An angel flying in the sky.
I wanted to see your face when I gave it to you! Here!
Thank you... Fuyuko, will you
come to the lab a moment?
Fly... You will fly in the sky...
With the white silk cloth, you can fly free, free...
Don't die... Don't die, Fuyuko!
Careful, Fuyuko!
Fuyuko!
Sister!
Kiriko, please take care of Fuyuko.
I'm going to take out Icarus.
Icarus is probably after Seyama...
Fuyuko!
Seyama! Run!
Icarus, I won't forgive you!
You killed twenty-three innocent children,
including Ayako, and you'd even kill Fuyuko!
Did you see Fuyuko die?
Don't bother, Icarus!
Come at me, Jin Keisuke!
Seyama! Where are you?
Get rid of that disguise!
Hurry and get rid of it!
Seyama!
Icarus, show your real form to Fuyuko!
It's up to me which form I fight you with!
Where are you?
What about now?
Darn!
Set Up!
Take him!
Ridol Stick!
Revolving Kick!
Seyama!
Icarus Death Wing!
Ridol Rope!
X Kick!
Seyama was Icarus...
Icarus is beaten.
Seyama said he was happy to meet you...
and that he's gone to a far-off place.
Thank you, Keisuke. It's hard for Fuyuko,
but I think she'll grow from it.
I believe in her.
I've stopped my human genius research for now.
Maybe human growth is best left to nature.
I'm glad I know that now.
I think that's for the best.
I'd like to think I'm going to be the last modified human.
The X Rider thwarted the evil
GOD Agency's conspiracies again today.
You're the only one who can protect the world from GOD.
Ride on, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD has its sights on a new energy source and orders its monster Atlas to disrupt the research.
The responsibility for the research's security falls to Keisuke.
But what is the mystery of Ryouko and Kiriko,
who've helped Keisuke in his fight against GOD?
Look forward to the next episode:
"Bizarre!? Little Earth, Medium Earth, Big Earth"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider