Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Run, Cruiser! X Rider!!
Jin Keisuke's father, Professor Jin was killed.
His father was killed by the great evil organization GOD's pawns.
And Mizuki Ryouko, Keisuke's lover, was the one who guided GOD.
Betrayed by his lover and his father killed,
Keisuke also died once from GOD's attacks.
And with his father's skills Keisuke revived as a modified human, a Kaizorg.
Kamen Rider X was like the sea, however...
...Keisuke's heart was distressed,
as his body was now no longer human.
Keisuke just kept riding his motorcycle...
And now, it seemed the only way he could calm down...
...was to ride.
Ryouko!
Why are you running away?!
There's something I really need to ask you!
Ryouko?
Please wait!
Why?
Why is Ryouko...
You're...
I'm Kiriko.
Why do you keep following me?
Keisuke.
You even know my name!
You're not a normal human anymore.
You don't have time to be depressed about the death of your father...
...or to follow your lover.
I can decide what I want to do.
No.
You're everyone's X Rider.
Everyone's?
Right now, you must have witnessed those many people with tools in their hands.
But, yet you were obsessed with that woman, Ryouko...
And you forgot about those people.
If they committed a mass murder...
X Rider, you are to protect the civilians.
Who...
Who are you?
Stop it!
What's wrong here?
Why am I here?
A pickaxe?!
What is this?!
All of you were probably hypnotized.
Hypnotized?
Please recall.
Did anything strange happen to you before you lost consciousness?
When our exchange meeting with the apartment next door was done...
We went out to the streets.
I remember, until that part.
I remember. It was a flute!
A flute?
That's right. I do recall the sound of a flute.
Right?
Yes.
I heard it too.
It was a flute!
That's it!
That's it! That sound!
Crap! How dare a child hypnotize adults!
Wait a second.
That child is merely playing the flute.
He's a lone boy who lost her father in a car accident.
To say that he hypnotized you all...
There's quite a distance from the apartments.
How can this sound be heard from there?
All right.
There's no use hiding!
Come out here!
GOD Warfare Agents.
I knew it, it was you guys!
You lost your father, it seems.
What a nice song.
My father...
...died as well.
This is my father's flute.
You must have loved your father.
We were always quarreling.
I really loved him...
Yet, I kept disobeying him.
Susumu!
I don't care if I look shameful!
I'm crying because I want to.
You don't look shameful.
I feel the same as well.
But... there's something I need to do.
That's why, I won't lose.
Let's enjoy life.
GOD General Commander.
Give Pannic the following orders.
X Rider has started moving.
Kill him.
And kill every human in Japan...
You make sure the devilish homicide plan succeeds!
The sound of a flute...
It's the same melody as before!
Up there, huh?
Set Up!
Jin Keisuke, with his Redizer and Perfecter, Sets Up into Kamen Rider X!
Ridol Whip!
X Rider!
They did this to us again!
We were going to kill people!
It's because of that flute. It's Susumu's fault!
Yaokichi!
Are you still going to cover for that kid?!
I don't understand.
I was going to kill my customers.
Catch that kid!
We need to do something about him!
We'll be forced to kill people!
Catch that brat!
Okay!
Go!
Wait!
Pannic.
GOD General Commander.
My plan is proceeding well.
With using the flute...
...they'll be able to commit murder.
Hurry.
Use those foolish humans...
...and kill X Rider!
Wait.
What's that flute?
It can't be that Yaokichi is...
...him?
You saw it, didn't you?
Wait!
Run!
I'll do something about this.
You again?
What are you doing?! You're part of them as well?!
Please calm down!
Susumu is innocent.
Someone else was playing the flute.
Shut up! You should die!
Stop it.
I don't want to fight you guys.
What did he do with that knife?!
He's not human!
I'm not human anymore?
Susumu!
Liar!
You're not human!
Only robots can do that!
Robots don't have fathers.
That story you told me was a lie!
Susumu!
How dare you! You lied to me!
You told me that you just lost your father!
Please listen to me, Susumu.
Shut up!
You're a robot! Don't pretend to be a human!
You're wrong!
I'm not a robot!
Am I really not a human anymore?
I've arrived...
I've arrived, father.
Just now, I... was hated by a child.
He told me that I was a robot.
A robot.
If it goes on like this, I don't think I can protect children.
Because children run away from me.
But, father...
I'm still a human, right?
When I'm Jin Keisuke, I'm a human, right?
Keisuke. You aren't a human anymore.
You weren't affected by Pannic's flute...
...because you're a modified human.
Have pride in not being a human!
Not being a human?
Right. Who else is out there that can fight against GOD?
You're the only one...
X Rider. Be a person who can have pride...
...in being able to resist something no human can.
You're a great modified human!
Keisuke.
It seems that I miscalculated something.
I wanted to be of use to you, to be able to fight against the great GOD organization.
But it was a mistake!
The existence of this Jin Station has the ability of making you a weaker human.
I don't want you to come crying to the Jin Station every time something happens, Keisuke.
F-Father, I...
Keisuke. You know this, you must fight alone.
Without relying on anyone, with your own powers.
Keisuke. This Jin Station shouldn't have existed for you.
Father.
Farewell, Keisuke.
Father...
Thank you, father.
Surely...
I'll surely become the X Rider you told me to become.
Watch me.
Ow! Ow!
I'm telling the truth!
It's you!
What did I do?!
I didn't do anything!
Hey!
Hand me over that flute!
Give me back my father's flute!
Nothing strange with this.
Which means...
...that it's not the flute's fault.
It's not the flute?
It must be the kid himself with his strange powers!
That's right! He must be some kind of devil!
Three wives in the apartment have disappeared.
It must be his fault!
Yes.
No! I didn't do anything!
Shut up!
Hey everyone! What should we do with this kid?
Kill him!
Yeah, kill him!
Yeah!
Kill him?
No! No!
No!
Don't do it!
Kill him!
No!
Wait!
This is bad!
Come here!
Wait!
What are you doing?
Are you going to kill Susumu?
Look at who was playing the flute!
Eh?
Yaokichi!
So it was you all along?
You made us believe it was that kid!
Show us.
You're a cyborg of GOD, right?
It seems this time has come, Jin Keisuke.
I'm an elite of GOD, Pannic!
Everyone, run!
Attack!
Set Up!
Ridol Stick!
Let's go!
Don't move!
If you move, I'll take his life!
Cruiser!
Rider!
Cruiser Attack!
No good.
It's sometimes good to not be a human.
Keep this safe.
The reason why you weren't affected by Pannic...
...was because your ears were accustomed to the sounds of your flute.
Thank you!
Keisuke was able to grasp confidence and pride in this fight.
He's the one person able to fight against GOD.
The one person capable of destroying GOD, again...
...is him.
Where is Ryouko?
And what is Kiriko's true identity?
Go, Jin Keisuke!
Run, Kamen Rider X!
Until the day the GOD organization is annihilated!
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"Assassination Dark Spider Operation!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider