Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
A Terrible Weapon Targets the Three Riders!!
Hong Kong
Dr. Amamiya, I presume?
Wh-who are you!?
Tiger Nero, of GOD's Villain Army!
Chief?
-That you, Keisuke?
-Yeah!
Ichimonji Hayato sent
us a private telegram.
What's it say?
Someone called Amamiya has the ninth RS
blueprint piece, and he's flying in to Haneda today.
Amamiya? How will we recognise him?
Apparently he'll have a red attaché case.
A red attaché case...
-Mr. Amamiya?
-Yes...
-Is something wrong?
-I think someone's watching us...
That's bad. Let's hurry.
Doctor!
-The blueprint?
-Right here.
What are you doing!?
You've done your job. Die!
Surprised, Jin Keisuke? I, Tiger Nero, have
inherited the blood of the tyrant Nero!
Now, be a good boy and
give me that attaché case!
I don't think so.
I don't have time to play with you.
We'll settle this some other time!
Wait!
Don't tell me you really think
the blueprint piece is in there!
What!?
I've got the real attaché case right here!
Bring him!
Finally, Jin Keisuke is our prisoner!
Milord.
Well done. You truly are the Villain
Army's ace in the hole, Tiger Nero!
I'm humbled by your praise, King Dark.
And what of Amamiya's attaché case?
-Right here!
-Open it!
Milord!
It's actually here!
Let me see it...
Milord.
It's the genuine article! That makes
two pieces in my possession.
The remaining seven are with
Jin Keisuke; Kamen Rider X.
I had Jin Keisuke's body searched,
but he didn't have any more on him.
Find them! Use any means necessary
to secure those blueprints!
Keisuke's still not been in touch...
I wonder if he managed to
meet up with Mr. Amamiya?
Now hear this, Tachibana Toubei!
Who are you?
The ace of GOD's Villain Army, Tiger Nero!
-Tiger Nero?
-Behold!
-Keisuke!
-Keisuke!!
All it would take to hang Jin
Keisuke right now is one little push.
-Why, you--!
-There's only one way to save him.
Give me your seven blueprint pieces.
-He didn't give them to us!
-Do you think I'm blind?
I'll give you one minute
to decide. Just one minute!
Take any longer than that
and Jin Keisuke is dead.
What are we going to do, boss?
Keisuke's only got one minute to live!
-Boss!
All we can do...
is hand them over.
We've got no choice.
Even if they have the blueprints, at least
Keisuke will be alive to get them back.
Pass me that.
If the worst happens to Keisuke, we
won't be able to protect the blueprints.
But I know he'll pull it off.
-We're here to escort you.
-Fold up those blueprints and come with us.
Looks like you've got everything arranged.
Did you bring the blueprints?
Right here.
Chief, what are you doing!?
What do you think? I'm
not gonna let you die!
Silence! Now, give them to me.
Untie Keisuke first.
That was the deal.
Alright.
What are you doing!?
Alright, they're the real thing.
Then let Keisuke go!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What?
Jin Keisuke is GOD's archenemy.
Naturally, he'll be executed.
B-blast you! We had a deal!!
GOD doesn't make deals.
Do it!
Stop!
Execute him!
Who's there?
Kazami Shirou!
Shirou! You're here!!
Transform... V3!
Hurry, chief!
-Keisuke!
-Chief!
-There!
-The chains, chief!
-I can't transform with my hands tied!
-Got it!
Those chains are made from a
special alloy! You'll never break them!
Darn, I can't--
No luck, chief?
V3!
Ok, let me try.
-Thanks, V3.
-Hey, look!
They're not getting away.
Great Transformation!
Tiger Nero! Hand over those blueprints!
We'll settle this another time.
Tiger Tornado Hell!
-Blast...
-He's gone?
All the blueprints? Don't lie to me...
Milord... Behold!
Excellent work, Tiger Nero!
Milord.
The RS Device blueprints, at last...
Once it's complete, I'll promote
you to GOD's chief executive!
I'm truly honoured, milord.
Begin production of the RS Device at once!
Understood.
I don't know what to say...
One slip-up, and now they
have all the blueprints.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
There's still a chance we
can get them back, right?
Well... It'll take them some time
to put the RS Device together.
The first thing we need
to do is find their base.
I did manage to plant a tracker on one
of their agents when they captured me...
Really!?
Good going, Keisuke!
Their base is as good as found.
This way.
-Aren't you done yet?
-We just need to install the core.
-King Dark awaits. Hurry up!
-Yessir.
Just a moment, Tiger Nero sir.
There's an unidentified radio
wave transmitting from this room.
What!?
Alright, nobody move!
That Kamen Rider...
Brainless fool!
-What's wrong?
-They must've found it.
-What?
-But we've got the direction.
Let's go!
Hey, look over there!
Welcome, Kamen Riders X and V3.
We've been waiting for you.
What?
Don't move! Just watch.
-Is that--?
-The RS Device.
Surprised? Thanks to you giving back
the blueprints, the RS Device is complete!
Dr. Nanbara's horrifying RS Device can instantly
break down any matter on a molecular level.
Even the H-bomb can't compare to
the energy unleashed by this process.
What do you think happens when
I switch on the RS Device?
It can obliterate anything from an industrial
complex to a major city in a flash.
Why don't I give you two a test
run first? Control energy output!
-V3...
-We have to stop that device.
Are you ready? Prepare for activation!
-Kamen Rider V3, the rest is up to you.
-What?
I lost the blueprints. I'll destroy
that thing if it means my life!
Hold it! That's a job
for my generation.
-But I have to--!
-Alright, together then.
Fire!
W-w-what happened!?
Who are you!?
Kamen Rider #2. Ichimonji Hayato!
Ichimonji, when did you get here?
I infiltrated GOD's lab a
while back, just in case.
The vital blueprint for the
RS device's core is right here!
Dirty spy! Take him!
Allow me to show you my transformation.
Transform!
#2!
Come on!
Tiger Tornado Hell!
Ran away, eh?
Over here!
Here I come, Tiger Nero!
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
Thank goodness... We destroyed the RS device.
I will have that last blueprint piece, Kamen Riders!
You'd do well to remember that!
King Dark...
With unexpected aid from #2 and V3,
the RS Device has been destroyed.
But King Dark has sworn a terrible revenge.
Fight on, Kamen Riders!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD have finally gathered all of Dr. Nanbara's
blueprints to complete the RS Device.
The X Rider will risk his life to destroy it, but
the gigantic King Dark seems insurmountable.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Farewell, X Rider"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider