Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Terror!
King Dark's Vengeance!!
Just a dream...
...Still gave me a fright, though.
Help!
GOD!
What do you want with this girl?
Run!
-Are you ok?
-Thank you!
Wait, you look just like--
She's the daughter of that famous Dr. Yáng?
Seems so. Dr. Yáng probably has a
piece of Dr. Nanbara's blueprints.
GOD have already killed him and his wife.
So what do they want with the girl?
They must think she's got the blueprint piece.
Hey, chief... How'd it be
if she stayed here a while?
Oh, sure! I'll look after her.
Alright folks, the young lady's
staying with us for now.
-That's great!
-We're gonna have fun!
-Yes!
She's so cute, it's gonna be like
having a blooming flower in the room!
Hey Mako, don't you think she's
having a little too much fun?
For real... But that's Keisuke for you.
He wants today to be all about
spoiling Dr. Yáng's daughter.
Someone sounds jealous!
Here, cool off with these!
-Thank you!
Enjoy yourself, Jin Keisuke... It won't last!
How about we eat lunch here?
-Seconded!
Hey, where's Keisuke?
That's weird, he was with us before...
-Whatever, let's eat!
-Right!
-Keisuke!
-Hi! Sorry, I had to check something.
Hey, what's wrong?
What's up? Are you ok?
-Just a bit dizzy...
-Dizzy? We'll get you to a hospital.
No, I'll be alright after a little rest...
Rest, here?
Keisuke, you should let her use yours.
My room?
Of course. It's the closest. C'mon.
...Alright, sure.
Take care!
I think I just need some sleep...
You can leave me alone now.
What's this kid up to?
-She's a thief!
-No way...
-So, now you know...
-Wh-who--?
How lucky you girls are,
seeing my true face...
-Help, help!!
-Someone, quick!!
Welcome, Jin Keisuke!
GOD!
Indeed, I am Centipede Yáng
Guìfēi of GOD's Villain Army!
Where's Dr. Yáng's daughter?
Dr. Yáng's daughter?
Let me see... Why don't you give me your
blueprint pieces in exchange for her life?
Big talk! If you want them,
come and get them!
Alright... Take him!
Great Transformation!
Cursed X Rider! Be assured
I'll have my revenge!
Imbecile! Did I tell you to get the
blueprint pieces with brute force?
I wanted you to deceive Jin
Keisuke with your beauty!
But... King Dark...
It's obvious I can't rely
on you lot any more.
I'll have to take Jin Keisuke's
blueprint pieces myself!
King Dark, are you--?
Centipede Yáng Guìfēi! Lure Jin Keisuke to the Devil's Cemetery at once!
Blast you, Jin Keisuke... This time
I'll crush you with my own hands!
How's it going? Any clues
to where the girls are?
No, not even one.
Help!
There she is!
The fool has no idea he's
walking right into a trap.
Help me!
Help!
-Keisuke!
-So this is where you've been!
-Yeah...
Jin Keisuke, you've fallen right into my trap!
Shut up! I came here on
purpose to see your hideout.
Dr. Yáng and his family have been in Geneva for the past week.
And this is his daughter!
Good work, Jin Keisuke. But you still die
if you don't give me the blueprints!
Don't make me laugh. You'll
never find them without me.
Very well. Then I'll just
have to make you talk!
Poison gas!
Keisuke!
-Can't breathe...
-Keisuke...
Are you ok!? ...Darn it, I can't
let King Dark have his way!
Great Transformation!
There's no point transforming, X Rider.
Those girls are as good as dead!
What?
Where are the blueprints?
Alright, I'll tell you
if you turn off the gas!
Certainly! Now, out with it!
The blueprints... are inside Cruiser.
Cruiser? Alright then, call it here!
Looks like I've got no choice...
Cruiser!!
-V3!
-Hurry!
Curse you, V3! I was so
close! I will be avenged!
Thanks, Kazami. The blueprints
are safe thanks to you.
Good. I came running when
I heard you were in trouble.
-We're saved!
-Yeah...
It's all thanks to Kazami!
Don't start celebrating yet!
Keisuke!
Chief!
Give me that blueprint if you value his life!
Keisuke, don't worry about
me! You can't hand it over!
Blast...
Keisuke, there's nothing else we can do.
We'll have to give her the blueprint.
But--
Well, what say you? Quickly, now!
#2!
Who's that?
Curses! Another interloper!
Keisuke! Shirou!
-Chief, I was really worried there!
-Yeah! Don't scare us like that, chief.
Honestly, what would you do without me?
I... just figured I'd take
myself out of the equation.
-Chief, is this person--?
-Yeah, he's a Kamen Rider like us.
My senior: Kamen Rider #2,
Ichimonji Hayato.
Just 'Ichimonji' will do.
You must be the X Rider.
Jin Keisuke. It's
good to meet you.
Three Riders all in one place!
There's nothing to fear now!
Right!
Laugh while you can! The three of
them are going to hell together!
Look out! Run!
Don't dawdle, Centipede Yáng Guìfēi!
Take the blueprints from his corpse!
The X Rider's body must be in this vicinity!
It's right here, Centipede Yáng Guìfēi!!
Accursed X Rider! You survived!?
-Ok, we'll find King Dark.
-Right!
You're not getting away!
-King Dark, show yourself!
-Face us!
Hold it!!
Come, come, Crow Bomb!
Curse you, X Rider!
Where are you, X Rider!?
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
-There you are, King Dark!
-Let's go!
Blast that King Dark!
It's not yet time for us to fight.
But we'll settle this soon!
Thus did Jin Keisuke defy King Dark again,
thanks to Kazami Shirou and Ichimonji Hayato.
But this would prove just the
prelude to a new challenge.
To be continued
Next episode
Jin Keisuke falls into a GOD
trap and is strung up in the air.
Toubei and the others have no choice
but to give GOD their blueprint pieces.
Look forward to the next episode,
featuring Riders #2 and V3:
"A Terrible Weapon Targets the Three Riders!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider