Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Mortal Combat!!
X Rider Versus X Rider!!
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
But Nanbara escaped GOD and tore the blueprints
into nine pieces to entrust to his old colleagues.
GOD has stolen one of the pieces,
and the X Rider holds four.
Where are the four remaining blueprint pieces?
And will the X Rider or King Dark find them first?
Is that you, Chameleon
Fantômas? Show yourself!
I've received some interesting information...
This job will require the incarnation
of that master of disguise, Fantômas.
Certainly. Just await word of
my inevitable success, sir!
AB Communications Inc.
Why'd it stop?
A malfunction, maybe?
Hello? I think the elevator's malfunctioning...
Hello...? Hello!?
Good grief...
Andou...!
W-what's going on?
Wh-who in the world are you!?
Andou, chief of AB Communications'
Tokyo Division. In other words...
...You!
But we can't have two versions
of the same man running around.
You'll have to disappear.
S-stop! Someone help!!
From now on... I am you!
-Oh, it's Keisuke!
-Keisuke, welcome!
Come on, come on, come on!
-What have you been up to lately?
-Yeah, we've hardly heard from you!
Hey now, how about cutting the
gas and making some coffee?
-Right!
-We'll make it good!
That ballerina you've been looking for, Kikuchi
Akiko? Seems she's back from Germany.
It was on the news. Her
school's in Setagaya Ward, uh...
I remember... Maejima Block 3.
Kikuchi Ballet
One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
Three, two, three, four, four!
Two, three, four, five!
Two, three--
Mistress, someone's here to see you.
Really? I'll be back in a moment.
Hi, long time no see!
What a pleasure! Do come in!
You're looking well.
Thank you! ...That will be
all for today's lesson.
Thank you, mistress!
Won't you have a seat?
Is something the matter?
No, I just came to see someone else
who's been waiting for your return.
-Really? And who might that be?
-A young man named Jin Keisuke.
Jin Keisuke? ...I'm afraid I've
never heard that name before.
-It doesn't ring a bell?
-That's right...
-...Are you sure?
-Th-that's right...
Everything alright?
You're not--!
You've seen too much, woman!
Why is Jin Keisuke looking for you? Talk!
GOD are bound to have seen the news too!
Speak! Why would Jin Keisuke want to see you?
I don't know! I've told you I don't
know! S-somebody help me!!
-Don't feel like talking, eh?
Then I'll have to make you!
-Hold it!
So you're Jin Keisuke...
What an unsightly fellow!
Chief!
-C'mon, you can do it!
-Keep Akiko safe!
I am Chameleon Fantômas of GOD's
Villain Army! Interfere and die!
GOD's monsters don't get any mercy from me!
-Get going, chief!
-Right!
Don't let him escape!
Great Transformation!
Curse you, X Rider!
Fantômas, where are you?
Right here!
Imbecile!
Here I am!
X Rider!
I'll finish you another time!
Fool! You underestimated the X Rider!
Forgive my bluntness, but that was
not the full extent of my abilities.
Please give our next clash your full attention.
Just don't forget that the
X Rider was powered up recently.
Consider it inscribed on my heart!
Touto General Hospital
Surgery   Internal Medicine
Paediatrics   X-Ray
Keisuke!
What happened with that monster?
He took off.
How is she?
Nothing serious. She just
fainted from the shock.
-You're awake!
-And who are you...?
-I'm Jin Keisuke.
-I hear you've been looking for me!
That's right.
May I know why?
You met a researcher named
Labique in West Germany, didn't you?
-Labique...?
-Yeah.
I recall. He attended my
performance in Munich.
That's right. Did he give you anything?
No...
That can't be right...
He told me himself that--
Well... He did buy me a present.
A present?
That's right. He enjoyed my dancing
so much that he bought me this.
That's gotta be it! Could I
have a look at it, please?
...Chief?
You again!
Quite right! The incarnation of the
faceless Fantômas, master of disguise!
I'll take this pendant as a trophy of my victory!
Chief! Pull yourself together, chief!
That darn Fantômas...
Chief!
You truly live up to your famous namesake,
Chameleon Fantômas! A job well done!
...Is what I'd LIKE to say, idiot!
But there's not even a scrap of
a blueprint inside that pendant!
What!?
Not a bad idea, if I do say so myself!
He never guessed that I took
it from Akiko on our way here!
Looks like that's another
blueprint piece for us!
Dr. Nanbara tore the blueprints to his
matter-converting RS Device into nine pieces.
One of his colleagues in West Germany hid this piece
in a pendant to be transported to Jin Keisuke.
-Cheers!
-They did it!
-Yeah!
Way to go, chief! You've still got it!
Oh, it was no big deal... I couldn't
have pulled it off without Akiko!
No kidding!
That reminds me, the Kikuchi
Ballet's putting on a show tonight!
-I wanna go!
-Me too!
The Kikuchi Akiko Ballet
presents Sleeping Beauty
-Shall we go?
-I'll be right with you!
-C'mon!
-C'mon, c'mon!
Kikuchi Akiko!
Alright! Hand over the real blueprint!
Somebody help!!
Hey, over there!
If you want the ballerina back, bring
the blueprint piece to Hell Valley!
Drive!
Great Transformation!
Gone!
There you are, X Rider!
Cruiser Jump!
Here's the blueprint. Let her go.
Give it to me!
Not until she's free!
Alright then, an exchange.
Release her!
Hurry back. Your fans are waiting.
X Rider, don't tell me you really--!
Go, Cruiser!
And now you're gonna give it right
back, Chameleon Fantômas! Let's go!
Take him!
I've no further use for you now! Farewell!
You can't fool the X Rider the same way twice!
Curses!
You--!
-I'm the X Rider!
-Bring it on!
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
The Vacuum Hell Wheel reduces the enemy's offensive power by rolling them along at high speed, driving their head into the ground.
After that, they're thrown into the
air and finished with an X Kick.
X Kick!
The X Rider defeated Chameleon Fantômas in
mortal combat and reclaimed the blueprint piece.
-She looks so pretty!
-Doesn't she, boss?
Seeing Kikuchi Akiko's sprite-like dance
reaffirmed Keisuke's resolve to fight GOD.
But King Dark's already plotting his next move to acquire the RS Device!
Don't give up, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
A mysterious old woman appears, controlling
a horde of blood-sucking leeches.
The X Rider falls into an endless swamp as
the leeches close in! Hang in there, X Rider!
Look forward to the next episode:
"'I Want Bloood' The Leech Monster of Corpse Swamp!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider