Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Apollo Geist's Final All-Out Attack!!
This is GOD's secret base in
Japan: the Palace of Apollon.
Apollo Geist spends three hours
a day on its shooting range...
...Training for the sole purpose
of defeating the X Rider.
No! I missed!
Guard captain, show me my
results for the past week.
Sir.
It started three days ago...
I normally score
three bull's eyes, but--
One miss... Two misses...
And three misses today!
Is there something wrong
with my trigger finger?
Your coffee, chief.
I'll get you another sir,
it won't take a moment.
Never mind!
Forgive me sir, but
is something wrong?
You don't... look well.
Don't talk nonsense!
Aren't I the immortal Apollo
Geist, the pride of GOD!?
Please excuse me!
The Supreme Commander revived
me an immortal body, and yet...
It was Hayata and Dr. Miyamoto
who performed the operation.
Miyamoto
Apollo Geist!
What brings you here?
I have a question to ask you.
What is it?
You oversaw my resuscitation.
You must know what I want.
Is your body malfunctioning?
For three days now... my
fingers have been seizing up.
Paralysis of the fingers?
I see... It's started at last.
What? What has started!?
Explain yourself!
Y-you're hurting me! Let me go first!
You know what's wrong
with me, don't you?
Yes...
The operation was only able
to extend your life for a month.
It'll start with finger paralysis, and
then you'll lose control of your legs.
In the end... your brain
will cease to function.
What!?
How long do I have left?
If the finger paralysis
began three days ago, then...
Today at the earliest,
tomorrow at the latest.
You revived me once. You'll do it again!
Replace my defective organs with new ones!
I can't, it's impossible!
Why!?
Because you killed Hayata!
I can't do another operation
like that without Hayata's help.
Hayata... Forget about him!
You can at least replace
my mechanical parts alone!
That's not possible either, but...
But!?
The X Rider may be able to save you.
What? The X Rider?
Specifically... the X Rider's Perfecter.
The X Rider's Perfecter...
Attaching the Perfecter
to your heart might solve it.
Then I've more reason than
ever to kill the X Rider.
My thanks, Dr. Miyamoto...
Your role is over!
Today at the earliest,
tomorrow at the latest...
I'll kill the X Rider and
take the Perfecter first!
Don't sneak up on
a guy like that!
There something I
can do for you?
What're you doing!?
Dr. Miyamoto!?
Why are you--?
What's up? You know him?
We met in the Palace of Apollon...
He's with GOD?
Jin Keisuke-- No, X Rider!
Do you recognise my voice?
Apollo Geist!
This is Apollo Geist's
final challenge to you.
You will settle things at the
Palace of Apollon's fighting arena.
If you aren't there in twelve hours,
those two lovely ladies you know will die.
No! He's got Chiko and Mako!
X Rider, Apollo Geist is
looking forward to seeing you!
Move!!
GOD, those cowards!
Chief, maybe Chiko
and Mako are still--
You think they haven't got them yet?
It's all up to you, Keisuke!
Chiko! Mako!
Hey! Snap out of it! Hey!
You're just a little
too late, Jin Keisuke.
One of the GOD commander's dolls...
Apollo Geist is a man of his word.
Be at the Palace of
Apollon within twelve hours.
Wait, Apollo Geist! I don't know
where the Palace of Apollon is.
Naturally, I will provide a map.
But don't assume you'll
make it there alive...
So this is the way to
the Palace of Apollon.
But what Apollo Geist said...
'Don't assume you'll
make it there alive'...
What are you doing?
Surprised, Jin Keisuke?
You killed us once, but Apollo
Geist has relit our flames of life!
And this time we won't fail!
Jin Keisuke... You won't make it to
the Palace of Apollon alive...
...Because we're going
to kill you here and now!
Having fun, Jin Keisuke?
Grab him!
One more time!
Set Up!
Dr. Kawakami's name was changed to Dr. Hayata
in this ep, so we've implied Hayata's his first name.
Rider Electro Shock!
Ridol Stick!
Rider Crown Splitter!
Ridol Rope!
X Rider!
Apollo Geist wasn't bluffing,
chief. They've got them!
And what's this guy gonna
do about wrecking my shop!?
I don't blame you for being angry, but
be patient. He still has his uses.
What use could he possibly be?
He'll give us the edge on Apollo Geist.
Don't fool yourselves! You
think Achilles would talk?
Achilles! You should make the
most of this second chance at life.
Yeah, the X Rider's right. Even
a GOD monster wants to live!
Are you saying you'd spare me?
You have my word.
I thought you might've been getting
tired of taking Apollo Geist's orders.
No kidding! Alright, I'll help you!
Darn that GOD... I should send
them a compensation claim.
Since you asked, I think that
should cover the refurbishments.
Apollo Geist!
And this is for Jin Keisuke's funeral.
I don't want an enemy thinking ill of me.
Don't give me that! Let the girls go!
If that's how you want it...
Foolish man.
Just don't give the game away.
I've got it.
-Who's there?
-It's me, Achilles.
Tell Apollo Geist
I've got Jin Keisuke!
That's Achilles for you... The
elevator will be right down.
Make it snappy!
Good work, Achilles. Apollo
Geist will be pleased.
-This way, you--
-Wait!
I'll take him to Apollo Geist.
Sir. Allow us to escort you.
Let's go!
Apollo Geist, Achilles has
brought Jin Keisuke here.
Alright, enter.
What!? Why was Achilles
holding the Perfecter?
What do you want with the Perfecter?
Sir, it was Achilles who
caught Jin Keisuke--
Not a bad little trick, Jin.
But not good enough to fool me!
You always were a smart one, Apollo Geist.
Curse you, Jin Keisuke!
-Someone save us!
-Chiko! Mako!
-Help!
-Keisuke!
Where are you!?
Chiko? Mako?
-Keisuke!
-Save us!
-A tape...
-You'll have to settle for us instead.
Jin Keisuke!
I'm gonna enjoy this!
Set Up!
Ridol Stick!
X Kick!
Ridol Attack!
Rider Hammer Shoot!
What's wrong, Apollo Geist? Don't you
want to fight me? Where are you!?
X Rider! I'm right here!
Here I come!
Our final duel at last...
All of those useless fools are dead.
Will you fight with all you have!?
First, I have to know...
Where are your hostages?
Right there!
-X Rider!
-Please!
You've gotta win! Justice always wins!
Don't worry! I'll save you!
Wait! There's a third!
Chief!
Don't worry about me, just save them!
If you want to die, I'll oblige you!
Go, Cruiser! Save the chief!
Rider!
Save the girls, chief!
Let's go!
Bring it on!
-Boss!
Ridol Whip!
X Rider!
Geist Cutter!
Apollo Magnum!
What's wrong, Apollo Geist? You're
not the marksman you were!
...Listen, X Rider.
I will die soon. I can't
change my fate.
You're dying?
But I won't die alone. You're
coming to hell with me, X Rider!
Die, X Rider!
Farewell, GOD!!
X Kick!
Looks like this really is
the end of Apollo Geist...
And the Palace of Apollon will follow him!
Who's that? Who are you?
My name is King Dark! You
and I will fight someday...
I look forward to it, X Rider!
King Dark...
The X Rider has vanquished
Apollo Geist at last.
But just who is the mysterious King Dark?
The X Rider is dogged by a
strange feeling uneasiness...
To be continued
Next episode
The X Rider has destroyed Apollo
Geist and the Palace of Apollon.
But a terrifying new plan is
already brewing in the darkness.
Behind it is King Dark. Just
what kind of being is he?
Look forward to the next episode:
"Terrifying Giant! King Dark Emerges!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider