Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
X.X.X Rider is Born!!
GOD General Commander...
Neptune. Go!
The plan is already proceeding.
Starting today, you're going to become king of the sea!
It's been half a year since I've last been to Tokyo.
Who the hell are you guys?
You're Professor Jin's son, Jin Keisuki, aren't you?
You guys are...
What are you doing?!
You're an important hostage. Come with us.
You think you can take on us by yourself? How brave!
You're just a human!
You mean you guy's aren't human?!
Wait!
Foolish man!
Do you want to be Neptune's sacrifice and die?
Die, Jin Keisuke!
You've chosen the path of death.
When these bubbles catch you,
your body will turn into a skeleton and die!
Keisuke!
Yo!
You surprised me!
I thought you were in Okinawa.
The marine university closed...
...so I decided to look for a part-time job in Tokyo or something.
But, are you okay? Why are you wet?
Yeah. Swimming during winter, I guess.
Swimming during winter? With your clothes on?
It was a bit cold.
Where's my father?
He's in his hiding place.
His hiding place?
Over there?
Yes.
Professor! Professor.
Where did he go?
When did my father move into here?
Watch out!
You're just like before, father.
Keisuke. You've got a long way to go.
Scientists need to have better skills than that.
Cut it out.
I don't remember saying I want to become a scientist.
What?!
You jerk!
How could you, father?
Stupid son!
Professor!
Keisuke, you too.
Why does this happen every time you meet?
Father!
I thought you guys were really close!
Heh, with this damn father?
What?!
Please stop.
I'll let you off today.
I can't let you get bullied in front of your future wife.
No...
Wife?
Bad taste, father.
You're embarrased, huh?
Keisuke. Wear this from now on.
What's this?
Stop it. This looks girly.
Don't oppose me!
Do as I say.
You've got to be kidding me.
Keisuke.
You need to wear that.
What happened to you when you came back from Okinawa?
Think about that carefully.
F-Father...
You knew?
It suits you.
That stubborn father.
What the hell is he thinking?
Your father wants to work with you.
Absolutely not.
I don't want to be crammed in a small room and study about human engineering.
Ryouko, I...
...want to cross the seven oceans and become the world's best sailor.
You might be okay with that, Keisuke...
...but Professor feels really lonely sometimes.
Lonely?
He works by himself in his university...
...and the only person by his side is me, right?
Although he says stuff like that,
I really think he's actually heartbroken.
I saw him write letters to you many times.
But, now he really wants you to help with his job.
Because everyone around him thinks he's mad.
Keisuke, why don't you help him?
Mizuki Ryouko.
Yes?
There's a phone call for you.
Excuse me.
Jin Keisuke.
I am the GOD General Commander.
Tell your father...
...that GOD needs his, Professor Jin's knowledge.
If he refuses...
...he'll die.
What's wrong, Keisuke?
Hey! What's that?!
The ship's shining!
GOD Organization is a secret society in which opposing countries secretly joined hands...
...and uses modified humans to try to take over Japan.
A secret society run by fear.
I'm not helping you.
I just want revenge for my ship.
Keisuke!
Ryouko!
Don't move!
F-Father, what?
Huh?
Keisuke. Wake up.
Hurry!
How terrible.
Don't surprise me like that.
Do you know why I want you to wear this?
This jacket is a complete bulletproof vest.
As well as bullets, it's also
resistant against fire and explosions.
It's the Professor's creation.
So that's why...
Keisuke. Starting tomorrow, you'll have a busy day.
A full blown fight against GOD is finally going to begin.
Rest today.
Father...
Why is he making me do these things?
Because I didn't help?
GOD!
Die!
Who're you?!
Wait!
Ryouko. Why?
Jin Keisuke!
That's because you and your father are in the way!
My father's in danger!
Father!
Father! Father!
Stupid son...
Hang in there!
You...
Behind you...
You guys are GOD?!
We're called the GOD Warfare Agents.
You two shall die happily together!
What?!
Keisuke...
You'll die at this rate.
I don't want you to die!
This is the only way...
...the only hope.
I'm counting on you.
Now with the last of his remaining consciousness...
Professor Jin used his all to perform a cell operation on Keisuke's body.
That was the Professor's final love given to his son.
I'm still alive.
Why?
Go, Keisuke.
I knew this day would come.
Keisuke. Your body isn't human anymore.
This was the only way I could save your life.
Forgive me. You became a modified human, a Kaizorg.
Kaizorg?
Your body has the power to resist hydraulic pressure of up to 10,000 meters undersea.
Your name is "Kamen Rider X".
Kamen Rider X?
Look, Keisuke.
That island was made by me.
That island is me.
The island itself is a great computer.
My full character and knowledge is there.
Jin Keitaro, the scientist, lives there.
Keisuke. This is my Jin Station.
Keisuke.
I'll always be here.
The next time you need me...
...I'll be waiting here.
You can come visit me at this Jin Station at any time.
Father...
GOD stole my blueprints.
With them, GOD will be a bigger devil organization.
Keisuke.
You're going to ride on this Cruiser!
And this is your Ridol.
These two are used to Set Up into
X Rider, the Perfecter and Redizer.
Keisuke.
My last wish.
Push the "C" switch.
Father!
Don't cry, Keisuke.
I'll be here.
This Jin Station is me!
Go, X Rider!
Defeat the evil organization GOD!
Watch me, father.
Set Up!
Jin Keisuke, with his Redizer and Perfecter, Sets Up into Kamen Rider X!
Who's that?
Who the hell are you?!
X Rider!
Rider?!
Let's go!
Ridol Stick!
Damn you, X Rider!
X Kick!
I am the last bomb!
You're...
I'm not Ryouko.
I'm Kiriko.
Kiriko?
Use this neckerchief for your wound.
In half a day it should get better.
Similar...
In order to annihilate Japan, the great organization GOD has begun to take strange actions.
Jin Keisuke, betrayed by his lover and his father killed, hasn't yet healed his heart.
Why did Ryouko betray him?
And who is this mysterious woman, Kiriko?
Don't lose, Keisuke!
Run, X Rider!
The battle against GOD has just begun.
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"Run, Cruiser! X Rider!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider