Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Godradamus' Great Prophecy!
110, police? I need help!
Someone's chasing me!!
Listen well, girl. That's a testing chamber for GOD's Killer Smog.
Now you die!
Help!! Let me out!!
Ulysses...
Prepare for orders from the Supreme Commander.
The time has come to cover Tokyo with
Killer Smog in our Tokyo Annihilation Plan.
Ulysses, you will coordinate the operation and
stop GOD's enemy, the X Rider, from interfering.
Understood? You must contain the X Rider!
Sir!
A strategy to contain the X Rider, eh?
Alright, we'll start by drawing him out!
Ulysses!
Who are you?
Chief of GOD's Secret Police.
Apollo Geist?
Don't be like that. The Secret Police will
be cooperating fully in this operation.
I appreciate it!
I'll take care of luring the X Rider.
Thanks for waiting.
How is it?
So you're Keisuke's friend, but...
Any special reason you know each other?
Well, something like that.
Don't be vague or anything...
Morning, boss!
You're late! Your friend's been waiting.
Friend...?
Look-- Huh?
Where'd he go?
He was just--
What was he like?
A snobby guy, all dressed in white.
Apollo Geist!
Apol-- That was him!?
(Incantation)
Apollo Geist lost me in the crowd...
What's going on?
This prophet's spouting some real nonsense!
-Prophet?
-Yeah.
He said Tokyo's going to be wiped out!
I have seen a vision!
Trust in Godradamus' words!
Tokyo will be annihilated!
The day... Today!
The time... 3pm!
At that hour, every human in Tokyo will die!
Run! Run! Abandon Tokyo
and run while you yet live!
Stop talking nonsense!
How can you justify this claim?
Prophecy needs no justification!
The proof... is here!
Everyone, don't listen to this rubbish!
I'm Uematsu, a geophysicist
at Touwa University.
Academically and scientifically, there's no
way Tokyo can just be wiped out!
I see... I see a non-believer,
dying in a most cruel fashion!
It is... you!
Ridiculous!
Godradamus' prophecies are 99% accurate!
You fool!
Dad, I'm scared!
Don't worry, prophesies don't come true!
Strange... No sign of the prophet.
The phone's ringing...?
Good timing. Let's check it out.
Welcome, Jin Keisuke!
I knew GOD was behind this. What's the
meaning of these weird prophesies!?
GOD's great prophecy is no lie.
Tokyo will perish at Ulysses' hands.
No way! You think I'll
let you get away with that?
I wonder if you can stop us, Jin Keisuke.
That telephone booth is one
of GOD's gas execution chambers!
Gas execution chambers!?
Don't waste your time!
His flesh and bones will have melted
by now. Deactivate the Killer Smog.
Behold! Jin Keisuke - no, the X Rider,
has been reduced to nothing!
Did he run away!?
Ulysses!
I didn't run anywhere!
I-it's you!
Ridol Whip!
Get him!
Apollo Geist!
Why are you interfering!?
Calm yourself! This is not the
time to fight with the X Rider.
That strategy is over. Leave him to me,
and accelerate preparations!
X Rider! I'll spare you this time!
Wait!
Apollo Geist!
You're going to tell me
everything about GOD's plan!
I'm afraid you'll have to catch me first.
Darn it! No leads on GOD...
Wait! Maybe there's one lead left...
Uematsu Geophysics Research Lab
Death to the professor... Thus spake the
inflexible voice of God in Heaven.
Run! Run! Abandon Tokyo
and run while you yet live!
Your father will die!
I'm scared!!
-Hiroko?
-What's wrong?
The prophet! The prophet was here!
There's no one else here!
You must have been daydreaming!
It's the truth! He said you'd die, dad!
Darling...
Don't you give me that silly look too!
You know I don't believe that!
The phone...
Who could that be?
Don't answer the phone, dad!
The prophet said you'd die!
Hiroko, you're a scientist's daughter.
You shouldn't believe in prophecies!
Now get back to your homework, alright?
Hello, Uematsu here.
Godradamus has prophesied that you will die cruelly and fall into Hell!
Nonsense! Do you think...
Do you think I believe that!?
GOD's great prophecy is no lie!
You're that prophet...
How did you--?
Many heard me prophesy your death.
As such, I must ensure it comes true.
W-why are you doing this?
To create the World of GOD!
You rotten prophet!
Jin Keisuke!
Run for it!
Right!
Care to discuss GOD's plan?
As I prophesied...
Tokyo will be wiped out today.
That is GOD's plan!
And I am its coordinator!
Then your true identity is Ulysses!
Well deciphered, Jin Keisuke.
Whatever that nosy Apollo Geist
says, I'll kill you myself!
Set Up!
Ulysses Killer Smog!
I won't last long at this rate...
Ridol Rope!
I nearly had him, too!
The family have fled.
Curses! It's nearly time to
begin the plan... Back to base!
Just a few minutes until GOD's prophecy
of Tokyo's annihilation comes true.
Soon my Killer Smog will spray from
every telephone receiver in the city.
Not a trace of its population will be left.
All of you to your positions!
Wait, Ulysses.
Apollo Geist!
To ensure GOD's prophecy comes true...
You must first kill these three!
So you caught them, Apollo Geist?
Very well then, execute them!
-Darling!
-Dad! Mom!
Please, at least spare them! The prophet
only predicted my death! Right? Please!
Too late! Circumstances have changed.
Fire!
What are you doing!?
Shoot him if you can!
Apollo Geist, how can you say that!?
You underestimate GOD's Secret Police.
X Rider! I played along
just to be sure it was you!
X Rider!? When did he--?
Your plan to annihilate Tokyo
through its phone lines is over!
Listen! The countdown will start soon.
You can watch the end
of Tokyo from that pit!
They're... they're really
going to annihilate Tokyo!
Starting countdown. Minus twenty...
Nineteen...
Eighteen...
Seventeen...
Sixteen...
-Suction Magnets!
-Fifteen...
Fourteen...
Thirteen...
Twelve...
Eleven...
Ten...
Nine...
-Where's the Killer Smog?
-Eight...
-Sorry, but your Killer Smog's valve stays shut!
-Seven...
-Curse you, X Rider!
-Six...
GOD's great prophecy must be realised!
Too bad!
I already cut the connection between
the phone lines and gas cans!
Why, you...!
I'll kill you... X Rider!
X Rider!
Ridol Whip!
Ulysses Crown Binding!
It feels like my head's splitting...!
Electro Shock!
Darn it!
You'll join the great Ulysses in death...!
X Kick!!
Curse you!!
Is that the end of Ulysses?
X Rider!
The Chief of the Secret Police
has a prophecy of his own.
Apollo Geist!
I swear on the name of
Apollo Geist... that I will kill you!
Apollo Geist has personally
challenged the X Rider at last.
How will the X Rider fight one so
terrifyingly intelligent and strong?
To be continued
Next episode
GOD revives the 'Mad Bugs,' extinct
for 2,000 years, to drive Japan insane.
And a spectacular fight unfolds when
Kamen Rider X accepts Apollo Geist's challenge.
Is this the end of Apollo Geist at last?
Look forward to the next episode:
"Apollo Geist's Mad Bug Hell"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider