Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Jin Keisuke, who was killed by the
great organization GOD along with his father...
...revived as Kamen Rider X, thanks to his father.
Why did Keisuke's lover, Ryouko, side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
The one who fights against the mysterious GOD, Kamen Rider X!
The One-Eyed Monster's Kidnapping Operation!
His skills are pretty good.
We're leaving!
Be a good boy.
Have a safe trip!
We're leaving!
Be careful.
This is strange.
This is strange. We're going the wrong way.
Driver, where are we going?
Eh? This isn't the way to the kindergarten.
You're wrong.
Strange...
Was there a kindergarten in these mountains?
One-eyed monster, this is G.O.D General Commander.
The first plan was a success.
Take the children, and put all the parents in the city into panic mode.
Understood.
One-eyed Radar!
I'm a one-eyed monster, Cyclops!
This morning, a bus carrying
kindergartners suddenly disappeared.
We are going to continue the investigation of this incident.
This could be, possibly be...
Hello?
Ow!
Jin Keisuke, who is a Kaizorg, has many times more power than ordinary humans do.
I'm sorry.
I though I only lightly slapped you.
Lightly? Ouch...
Who are you?
I'm just a passerby.
I heard you talking to yourself, so I was a bit worried.
What?
You could hear my voice from outside?
Well...
...my ears are much better than ordinary people's.
What did you say?
What a suspicious guy.
Oh! Don't tell me you're a modified human from Destron!
Destron?
What's that?
Oh, right.
Destron was destroyed, I forgot.
We need to look out for Destron as well...
Ah, I had something to do.
Leave here already.
But...
Okay, okay.
Hurry, hurry on and leave.
The shop's closed today.
I remember passing by that microbus around here...
Hey!
Old man!
Hi!
I envy those children.
What was that voice just now?
Help us!
Please help us!
What's wrong?
This is very bad!
An accident occurred in the tunnel just now!
An accident?
Help us, please!
All right.
Damn...
Let's go!
Wait!
Oh, you're...
Wait, don't go. This is a trap!
What did you say?
You've come to interfere with me again.
Ryouko.
What are you doing?!
Are you really an ally of GOD?
Ryouko.
Watch out!
Stop it!
Hey.
Wait!
H-Hey, wait!
A monster!
Bastard... you're a cyborg of GOD aren't you?
Jin Keisuke, welcome.
I'm a member of the GOD radical group...
One-eyed monster, Cyclops!
Cyclops is a one-eyed monster who appears in Greek myths.
He is an invincible and frightening monster that catches and eats humans.
I knew it, you guys were behind this after all!
Get Jin Keisuke!
Hey, you're pretty good.
Run!
Damn...
Monster of GOD!
You two. I'll take your lives!
One-eyed Radar!
Run!
Set Up!
Ridol Whip!
Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider?
No way...
I'm dreaming, right?
Here I come!
Yo!
Damn it.
Ridol Stick!
You're awake.
You're okay now.
Y-You're that woman from before!
What is even happening?
Wrong.
She's similar looking to her...
...but she's a different person.
Huh?
I don't know.
Kiriko.
Please tell me today.
Who are you and Ryouko?
I...
I am, I assure...
...I'm not your enemy.
The allies of GOD...
Are using the underground of the tunnel as their base...
...and they're kidnapping little boys and girls,
they're plotting something scary.
It is your mission...
...to destroy that.
Hey. GOD?
Yes.
What's that?
Hey, wait a second!
Kiriko!
Hey. There's something I want to ask you.
Are you a Kamen Rider?
My name is Tachibana Toubei.
I used to be the President of the Rider Team.
Kamen Rider #1...
#2...
V3...
And Riderman, #4. I know them.
But you're not any one of them.
Who're you?!
My name is... Jin Keisuke.
I was killed along with my father, who was my only blood relative...
...by an organization called GOD.
And revived as a modified human.
And, my other name is...
Your other name?
Kamen Rider...
Kamen Rider.
Kamen Rider X.
Kamen Rider X!
This is the GOD General Commander.
Jin Keisuke and Tachibana Toubei. They will get in the way.
Proceed with the Alpha Plan before we get interference.
Roger.
Bring out the children.
Stop it!
Help us!
Please forgive us!
Stop!
Help us!
All of you are going to be preserved as frozen humans.
When this country is under
the command of GOD one day...
You'll be reborn as slaves of GOD.
Freeze them!
Stop it! Let go of us!
Help us!
Mother!
Let go!
Let go of us!
Begin the freezing process.
No!
They're frozen.
Process successful. Bring them out here!
All of you shall become slaves of GOD.
Alert!
A truck is heading towards the tunnel.
What? Why isn't it moving?
What? It's not going back either.
Damn it.
W-What?
No good.
H-Hey! Hey, the ground is moving!
H-Hey! What am I...
What's going on here?
Hey, get off.
Get off already!
Hey, hey!
What is this place?!
Bring him.
What the hell is this place?!
What are you telling me I did?
Go!
This is GOD's base, huh?
H-Hey, please stop!
We've captured the truck's driver.
Dirty guy.
Put him in prison.
Wait!
What's wrong?
Damn!
Bastard!
Do you remember this face?
Ah! That woman!
To come sneaking all the way into GOD's base...
...takes guts, doesn't it?
Freeze him!
What?!
Do it!
Emergency alert.
Jin Keisuke's entered our base, and he freed the children!
You're an ally of GOD, I knew it.
Do you still call yourself a human?!
Set Up!
Hurry!
You saved me!
I'm leaving the children to you.
Okay!
X Rider!
Get him!
Ridol Stick!
Ridol Rope!
X Rider's Ridol, by pressing the "right" switch,
can turn into the Ridol Rope.
Rider X, there you are!
One-eyed Radar!
X Kick!
X Rider!
X Rider.
The children who were frozen...
...turned back to normal!
Thank you.
You did well.
It wasn't me. She did it for us.
Kiriko!
X Rider! X Rider!
Thank you!
I'm glad.
You should all study hard.
Thank you!
You too.
The frightening cyborg of GOD, that one-eyed monster was defeated by X Rider.
And the children were able to go back to their families.
However, the wall between X Rider and GOD is thick.
Be strong! Move!
Our X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"The Japanese Islands Fragmentation Plan!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider