Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
Feeling the RS Device should benefit mankind, Nanbara tore
the blueprints up and sent eight pieces to old colleagues.
The ninth and final piece was hidden
in his daughter Rie's pendant.
Entrusting the blueprints' safety to the
X Rider, Dr. Nanbara left this world.
Vengeful Ogre Geronimo! Silent Assault!!
Behold my power!
Those blueprints are mine!
The names of those eight colleagues
are bound to be in here. Find them!
Who's there?
X Rider! What's so funny?
You're wasting your time looking
for a list of those names!
I already looked; Dr. Nanbara's too cautious
to leave something like that lying around.
Do you think I'd fall for that?
More likely you already stole the list yourself!
I'm telling the truth!
I killed many white men after their
lies turned me into a vengeful ogre!
The blood of the great Indian leader
Geronimo flows within me! Get him!!
I told you you're wasting your time!
After him!
Where did the X Rider go? Find him!
He already beat them...?
It's the X Rider!
Forget about finding those
blueprints, Scorpion Geronimo!
Curse you, X Rider!
This isn't over!
Blasted GOD monster...
Still nothing?
Right... No sign of anyone that was
working with the doctor before he died.
Not even one clue!
Just eight people in all of Japan...
It won't be easy to find them!
Here's your rice balls!
Thank you! Ok, did I forget anything?
-You just be careful!
-Climbing the Tanzawas is like hiking!
Besides, my friends are basically veterans!
Did you make a schedule?
Let's see, first up is...
Shou, what's this drawing for?
I found it in a letter for dad!
It looks important! What if you'd lost it?
That's why I'm keeping it with me!
What if I can't find the blueprints...?
-Morning!
-Morning.
-Where's Mako?
-Sick?
As if! She hasn't even had
a cold since she was born!
-So, she's playing hooky!
-No, she's visiting her grandpa's grave.
Visiting a grave...?
Here lies Nanbara Kouichi
Dr. Nanbara, I was shocked
to get your letter to father.
I'm... afraid he died in a
traffic accident last week.
But please don't worry. My brother
and I will protect that blueprint.
-I've brought you some water...
-Thank you so much!
You must be a kind young lady,
visiting a grave at your age.
That's how my father raised me.
I've heard this man was a great doctor...
Was your father a scientist also?
Maybe I'll get some clues here.
But I don't see any hint of GOD.
So that girl has one of the blueprints...
Excuse me, but did you know Dr. Nanbara?
Yes...
And your father was a scientist too?
Might I know why you're asking?
Dr. Nanbara gave me a job
to do. I can't fail him!
I'm... in a hurry. Excuse me.
Miss!
...Guess it's too soon for her to trust me.
I sense danger...
...Or did I imagine it?
Jin Keisuke... So you're keeping
an eye on his grave too?
Are you... the priest from the temple?
It seems you didn't make a donation.
I'm afraid I forgot! What can I give you?
The piece of paper you received from Dr. Nanbara.
I-I'm sorry, but that's--
Don't be coy. I know all about it!
Your father was Dr. Yazawa, Dr. Nanbara's
closest friend amongst his eight colleagues.
Then someone is after the blueprint he sent!
Yes; me. Scorpion Geronimo!
Help!!
Where is your piece of the blueprints?
Stay away!
Stubborn girl, don't you
want to live? Talk! Talk!
A scorpion...!
Are you willing to die for a piece of
paper that has nothing to do with you?
Dr. Nanbara entrusted it to us... We have to protect it, for mankind's sake!
I shan't give it to you!
You'd better talk! Unless you want
to be stung to death by my scorpion!
Come on, talk!
Scorpion Geronimo!
Clever move, disguising yourself as a priest.
Save me!
Hold it!
You can't run, Scorpion Geronimo!
Idiot! You're the one who should
be running, X Rider! Attack!
X Rider, do you want this girl to die?
Don't worry about me! Get them!
No one asked you!
Report this to King Dark: The second piece
of the blueprints belongs to the X Rider!
I won't give up so easily! I'll get it back!
Looks like watching the doctor's grave paid off!
Well, I'm the one you should be
thanking for giving you that hint!
Only because I brought it up!
More importantly, will you trust me now?
-Sure she will!
Would you two keep it down?
I trust you.
Then... where's the blueprint
Dr. Nanbara sent you?
My little brother Shouichi has it.
And where's Shouichi?
He went hiking in the Tanzawas this mor--
What the heck is that?
A spy scorpion!
Scorpion Geronimo heard
everything we just said!
And my brother? What about him?
I promise to bring him back safely!
We're counting on you!
Hang in there, Shouichi...
There's no time!
Set Up!
Alright, let's take a little
break. Have a seat, boys!
Sir, smoke!
Almost looks like Native
American smoke signals...
What's going on?
-Native Americans!
-Native Americans?
Which of you is Yazawa
Shouichi? Talk! Out with it!!
What do you want with Yazawa?
Who are you people!?
Sir!
Are you alright!?
I'm Yazawa Shouichi!
Why are you doing this!?
Don't, Yazawa!
Alright Shouichi, give me
that blueprint of yours!
Blueprint? I don't know
what you're talking about!
Your sister Keiko told me!
Don't try to hide it!
-My sister...?
-So give it to me!
No way!!
Open fire!
Stop!!
So, you'll hand it over? A second
volley will be the end of you!
Yazawa, you have to give it to
them, no matter how precious it is!
-Sir!
-Alright, I'll do it for you guys... I'll do it!
-Here!
-Wait!
Shouichi, you don't need to do that!
The X Rider! Fire,
fire! Slaughter them!
There's a mountain hut nearby,
sir. Can you take them there?
-Alright! Let's go!
-Yes sir!
C'mon, hurry!
-Everyone alright?
-Yeah!
-Sir, Sawai's not here!
-What!?
Alright, I'll have to find
him. You all wait here!
Yes sir!
I'd have died if I stayed
with Yazawa... No thanks!
Is that so? You don't want to die?
Help!
Sawai!
Sir!
Not a bad pair of hostages!
Let's go look for him too!
-C'mon!!
-Ok!
X Rider!
Are you kids alright?
Well... Sawai went missing,
so sir's looking for him, but--
What?
Listen, X Rider! I've got
the kid and his teacher!
That voice...!
Save us!!
That boy isn't Yazawa
Shouichi! Let him go!
X Rider, my only objective
is Dr. Nanbara's blueprint!
Give it to me, or I'll kill
the boy and his teacher!
Coward!
Alright, I'll count to five. Bring
out the blueprints or they die!
I don't want to die! Please!!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
And that's five!
Kill me instead if you have
to! I've got the blueprint!
X Rider, bring that blueprint to me!
He'll do anything to achieve his goal...
You're a brave boy, but we've
got no choice but to hand it over.
X Rider...
I promise to bring it back.
Scorpion Geronimo!
Here's the second piece of the blueprints!
Bring it to me!
Release Sawai and his teacher first!
Alright, here they come.
You've earned Scorpion
Geronimo's trust, X Rider. Go on!
-Go on, quickly.
-Right. Come on, inside!
Well, take it!
And now I'll have your piece too!
Take it if you can!
Look around you first!
Fire!!
This strategy again?
Justice-spouting wimps like you can't
stand to see innocents die, can they?
You hypocrite!
Did you just work that out?
Cruiser!
-Rider!
Run for it! That way!
Ridol Stick!
Die!
Ridol Rope!
X Kick!
-X!
-Rider!
What's that!?
X Rider, the second blueprint piece is mine!
Go, Rhino Beetle Lupin!
Find the third piece of the blueprints!
Understood!
Both the X Rider and King Dark have
one piece of the RS Device's blueprints.
But where are the remaining seven pieces?
To be continued
Next episode
A scientist uses a special light ray to tattoo
two boys' backs with the third blueprint.
Learning this, GOD's Rhino Beetle
Lupin pursues the boys to retrieve it.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Mysterious Phantom Thief Rhino Beetle Lupin!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider