Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Farewell, X Rider
So King Dark's made his move at last...
I hate to think what kind of
destruction that giant could cause.
But where could his base be?
I'd better destroy it soon, or...
Keisuke!
-On your left, your left!
-Ok!
Chief, I was just staking out the east side.
Right, keep it up. But where
are Ichimonji and Kazami?
Oh, I'm sure they're taking
care of things their way.
I shouldn't rely on them, anyway.
Yeah, he's got us after all! Right?
-That's right!
-Ok, ok!
Hey, don't make things any harder
for the chief! And be careful.
You can count on us!
-Good luck!
-Here we go!
Stop! Stop!
Watch it! Are you trying to make us crash?
Seriously!
Please, I beg you! My
grandson... he's sick!
Won't you take him... to the hospital?
Where's your grandson now?
Our house...
Alright, get in! We'll take him!
Thank you, thank you...
Um, I don't think we--
-Please!
-...Yeah, alright.
S-s-stop! That's it, there!
Sorry, where's your grandson exactly?
Huh? Where'd he go?
Sir!
Sir!!
-What's going on?
-Sir!
Hey, what's up?
S-s-scorpion!
GOD!?
That's right! The name is
Scorpion Geronimo Jr.!
-Why, you--! Run!
-Right!
You three...
...are my hostages!
There's no escape!
Closed today
They sure are taking their time...
Extending the search is one thing,
but they should've been back by now.
Speak of the devil.
Chief!
It's the chief's car alright...
-A scorpion?
-Listen carefully, Jin Keisuke!
-GOD?
-We have Tachibana Toubei and the girls!
We'll exchange their lives
for that last blueprint piece.
See you at Tama Hills!
The scum...!
Looks like there's
two on patrol. Right...
-Stay back, Keisuke!
-No, Keisuke!!
Jin Keisuke! That's far enough.
I brought the blueprint, like you wanted!
Come on out, Villain Army!
Scorpion Geronimo? But you're dead!
I'm his son, Geronimo Jr.!
Don't give him the blueprint, Keisuke!
Our lives aren't worth the world!
Shut him up.
How about if I have
those two girls scalped?
Stop!!
Wait!
I'll give you the blueprint. Here.
Throw it to me.
Catch.
Unlike GOD, I keep my
promises. We'll be going now.
Don't move, Jin Keisuke! The
main event's only just starting.
What?
You killed my father, and I will avenge him!
-Coward!
-Get him!
Keisuke!
Keisuke!!
Tear him apart!!
Great Transformation!
You did it, X Rider!
-Chief, get Chiko and Mako out of here.
-Right!
Cruiser Big Turn!
Let's settle this one-on-one!
Challenge accepted!
Geronimo Jr.'s skills are something else...
He handles that bike like it's a horse!
Of course... It must be his Indian blood!
X Rider...!
I've been powered up,
just like the X Rider was!
And now you'll see the end of
this world with your own eyes!
The end of the world!?
Right! King Dark has begun to
move, and we have the blueprint!
Watch closely!
The X Rider is dead...
There's no way we can stop GOD now...
-Boss!
-Hold it!
Keisuke, you're alright!
Sorry to worry you, chief.
I could only find King Dark's
base if he thought I was dead.
Curse you, Jin
Keisuke! Take him!
Hurry, Keisuke! King Dark
could run wild any minute!
-Ok, chief. Hang in there.
-Don't worry about us!
So this is King Dark's lair?
Did you think I'd let you find
me without setting a trap?
King Dark!! Where are
you? Show yourself!
That hole is your grave! Die!!
-The building's shaking!
-And Keisuke went in the tunnel under it!
King Dark!
Die... Jin... Keisuke!
Great Transformation!
X Rider!
-X Rider...
-This is the end for you!
Do you really think you can fight King
Dark with that tiny body of yours?
-What?
-Destruction Ray!
You fool!
Oh no!
Let's clean up the waste first.
Cruiser Jump!
Nothing... But he must have a weak spot!
King Dark is invulnerable! An immortal giant!
Die!
Pesky little insect!
Of course! If I can get in his mouth...
If you want to be eaten, be my guest!
-King Dark just...
-...ate the X Rider!
Contain the X Rider until King
Dark has levelled Tokyo!
It's moving again!
Where's the control room?
Poison gas!
Where's the control room!?
Could this be it?
Who...?
X Rider, my name is Dr. Noroi.
I was your father's best friend.
Best friend? He did mention a
Dr. Noroi... A devilish genius!
Furthermore... I am GOD itself!
King Dark is but a part of my body.
So that's it...
And now... the Earth is mine too!!
I don't think so!
Die!
I want to see the X Rider's
death with my own eyes!
What's going on?
What's happened to the X Rider in there?
Ridol Whip!
D-don't do it!
This is the end of GOD!
If you kill me, King Dark
will explode! You'll die too!
I've done it before.
Now it's your turn!
I don't believe it...!
Not... when I'm this close...!
But I won't die alone!!
He did it! The X Rider did it!
-X Rider...!
It exploded...
-And the X Rider...
-...with it.
Stop crying, you two.
...You'll set me off.
Mr. Tachibana Toubei
He's alive! He's alive!!
The X Rider's alive!?
Chief... Chiko... Mako.
I've gone on a journey in search of a new fight,
just like the other Kamen Riders before me.
I'm going to live up to my name as the
X Rider, so keep an eye out for me.
I'll be back someday, for sure.
Until then...
Until then, goodbye!
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Black gloves and a red chest
He leaves his mark in red and black
"Stop GOD's monstrous army!"
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Furiously kicking even stone to pieces
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
The white Cruiser ascends the clouds
Racing even light across sky and sea
"Stop GOD's evil traps!"
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Furiously jumping as high as the sky
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
I'll be back someday, for sure.
Until then...
Until then, goodbye!
The End
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider