Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Jin Keisuke, who was killed by the
great organization GOD along with his father...
...revived as Kamen Rider X, thanks to his father.
Why did Keisuke's lover, Ryouko, side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
The one who fights against the mysterious GOD, Kamen Rider X!
Assassination Dark Spider Operation!!
Ryouko!
Wait!
Hey! Where's Ryouko?!
That woman will soon become a part of GOD as well!
What?
Hey, where did she go?!
Jin Keisuke. GOD won't lose!
Damn it.
Call number 4. Call number 4.
Haneda Airport at 13 o'clock. Haneda Airport at 13 o'clock.
All right.
Now I know what GOD's plan is.
Haneda Airport at 13 o'clock, huh?
5 more minutes left!
This time, I'll get proof that he's a member of the GOD organization!
He disappeared.
This can't be!
Interpol investigator.
It seems you've followed me all the way from the country of Adabu.
Well done.
Bastard, you're a part of GOD!
For what reason have you come to Japan?
Let me tell you.
Envoy Kibara of Adabu...
...has come to Japan in order to sign an oil export agreement...
...and is currently staying at the New Japan Hotel.
That Envoy Kibara will be...
What did you say?!
Now that you know this secret...
You too...
Be quiet!
Modified human.
That's right. My name is Hercules!
Hercules?!
You shall die here!
Kill him...
Poisonous spiders.
Kill him, poisonous spiders.
Kill him, kill him...
You were looking?
Help me!
You were looking, weren't you, little girl?!
Now, come!
Stay silent!
So you're here...
You're Jin Keisuke!
Who the hell are you?!
Meeting you so early is such a pleasure.
This superhuman powered Hercules shall erase you!
Die!
That's just an appetizer.
The next time we meet, you'll be dead!
What does Hercules want?
I see. Maybe this girl knows something...
You.
No use.
Mama, I'm scared! I'm scared!
Sayoko, it's alright now.
There's no need for you to be scared.
What did that monster do? Could you please tell me?
Mama?
Sayoko. Tell me.
He said he'll kill a famous foreigner.
He's going to kill a famous foreigner?
What's his name?
Um... um...
I don't remember!
Calm down, Sayoko.
Remeber.
You're okay.
Sayoko.
Damn.
Mister!
I remember! Kibara! He said it's Kibara!
Kibara?
Thank you, Sayoko.
I'll be back very soon.
I did tell you, didn't I?
That the next time we meet will be your last!
Set Up!
Ridol Whip!
Rider X!
Ridol Stick!
Even with your power, trying to break that is impossible!
X Rider, look below that bridge!
Help me!
Sayoko!
Rider, look!
Don't move, Rider!
G.O.D has seen through everything already!
I'll cook you slowly.
Die, Rider!
That's it, Rider.
This is the end for you!
See that? The last of Kamen Rider X!
Contact from G.O.D General Commander.
Envoy Kibara is at the New Japan Hotel.
Hercules. Kidnap the envoy at once!
Roger.
Bring them.
I need to rescue the hostages...
Wait for me.
How will GOD contact me?
What would you like?
Ryouko!
I'm Kiriko.
Why are you here?
G.O.D has targeted your life.
I'm aware of that.
Always be prepared.
Why do you know about GOD?
Who are you?
I can't tell you anything now.
I want to meet Envoy Kibara.
Yes. Envoy Kibara is in the Hamari Shrine right now.
Hamari Shrine, eh?
Thank you.
Envoy Kibara.
What do you want from me?
I want that important body of yours.
Oh, me?
The GOD organization wishes to remove
every single drop of oil from Japan.
I need you for that.
If you do that, Japan will...
Don't be stupid.
You can't resist anymore.
How scary.
That was dangerous.
I was told to press this button...
...in an emergency situation.
What was that signal just now?
The real Envoy Kibara has been captured by GOD.
That was the signal.
You're Jin Keisuke!
Crap.
You knew all along?
Jin Keisuke. Don't underestimate the GOD organization.
This time, I'll stop your breathing!
You're Hercules!
How's this?
Become the seaweed of the sea! Disappear!
Jin Keisuke!
Die!
If I fall here...
...everything I've done up to now will be useless.
I need to go.
I need to follow them.
This wonderful place shall be your grave.
I...
...love Japan.
I can't destroy Japan.
Don't act so tough.
I'll make you gasp.
Get ready to execute him!
Execute me?!
Exactly.
All those who object to the GOD organization,
regardless of who they are, shall die.
If you don't want to die, then do as we command.
Understand?
We're ready for his execution!
Watch carefully, envoy.
Even the strongest of cars will be done in no time.
Here.
Become a small lump of iron!
See.
How about that?
What kind of sin do they possess?!
Sin?
You're the one who possesses sin!
Me?
That's right.
If you resist...
...then those two will need to die.
No!
Get ready to execute them!
Stop it!
Please!
I don't want to die!
Help us!
Sayoko!
I'm scared!
Mama, I'm scared!
Please stop!
I'll agree to your conditions!
Please stop! I promise!
Please!
Envoy Kibara!
Don't do as he says!
What's that voice?!
Where are you, X Rider?!
X, come here!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
You bastard!
Show yourself!
Come out, bastard!
Hercules, here I am!
Rider X!
Go!
Run away, the three of you!
I don't know who you are... but thank you!
Run!
Rider X!
Damn you...
Die...
How's this?!
How's this?
You can't move now!
X Kick!
H-How did you know where I was?!
You made it look as if you melted into the car.
But you hit your body on the car...
...and by using the recoil, you moved the other way.
You can't make optical illusions in front of me!
Hercules. Do you now understand my strength?!
I underestimated you. I lose.
However, GOD will definitely defeat you one day.
Take this! My power!
Here I come...
...X Rider!
Die!
Take a look at my death!
Kamen Rider X won this battle between him and Hercules.
However, the fearful powers of GOD will target Japan once again.
Go, Kamen Rider X!
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"GOD, the Shadow of Fear!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider