Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Jin Keisuke, who was killed by the
great organization GOD along with his father...
...revived as Kamen Rider X, thanks to his father.
Why did Keisuke's lover, Ryouko, side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
The one who fights against the mysterious GOD, Kamen Rider X!
GOD, the Shadow of Fear!!
Did you call for me?
Medusa.
The time has come to test your powers.
Do you understand?
Then I shall feast on life blood as a sacrifice.
Once human blood is absorbed into my body...
My body will be able to exert
many times more power than before!
You jerk, turn into stone!
Go, Medusa.
I'll tell you our command later.
Medusa, I'm telling you our command.
Your job is to find out how
Professor Kogure developed Alpha Gas.
Using the terrifying poison of Alpha Gas...
...every single human in Japan shall die in madness!
For that, first...
...kidnap the professor's only daughter, Saeko.
Yes, Commander.
There.
That's the daughter, Kogure Saeko.
That was fun.
Kogure Saeko. Kogure Saeko.
Your companion is waiting at the back gate.
Who's calling me?
Strange. No one other than us three came with us.
I'm going. Please wait here.
I wonder who called me?
You're Kogure Saeko, aren't you?
Yes.
Who are you people?
You're going to be held captive for Professor Kogure.
No!
Come with us!
Let go of me! Hepl me!
Let go of me!
Help me!
Come on.
Wait!
It's Jin Keisuke.
Shake him off!
Damn.
Stop the car!
I'll get you off the car!
Are you okay?
Thank you very much.
Why were you targeted by GOD?
They were going to hold me captive for my father.
Sorry to sound rude, but who's your father?
He's Kogure Seijiro.
That doctor of science?
I'll take you to your home.
Jin Keisuke. You interfered again!
Remember that!
You can't run away from me, Jin Keisuke!
Jin Keisuke, that jerk...
That was Ryouko...
Oh no, I don't know where Keisuke is.
This is my house.
You fell into my trap, Jin Keisuke!
Father!
This is terrible.
GOD must be behind this.
Kiyomi, hang in there!
The professor was... Some strange guys came in...
...and took the professor!
But, where did they take him?
I was punched...
...and then I went unconscious.
I knew it... I knew it, my father is...
First, the amusement park...
...and now, the laboratory.
What's GOD's target this time?
Okay, stop crying.
Your father should come back.
I'll be by your side.
Don't worry. Let's go.
These are orders from the GOD General Commander.
Rider X, Jin Keisuke, kill him.
Do so by any means possible.
Kill that detestable X Rider!
Miura. Untie me and get me out of here already!
What's the matter? Miura! Hurry!
Professor. If you tell me where the blueprints for the Alpha Gas are...
...then I'll untie you.
What?
Then you're a member of them as well?!
It seems you've finally realized.
Do you want to know my true identity?
My true identity is...
The assassin of GOD, Medusa!
Professor Kogure.
If you adore your daughter, then confess already.
Whether you want your daughter Saeko alive or dead...
...is up for you to decide.
Well, I'll let you think for a while.
There's something I need to do until then.
Like this.
Here.
Get out of my sight, obstacles!
It came from the laboratory.
Saeko, stay here.
I'll be right back.
Saeko... this is your father...
Father?
Jin Keisuke killed me.
Kill him!
Kill Jin Keisuke for me!
Yes.
Anything you say, father.
Die!
Saeko!
What are you doing?! It's me, Keisuke!
A snake! A snake is going to kill me!
I see. So you were hypnotized.
Wake up, Saeko!
Ah, Keisuke.
Finally, you're awake.
GOD?!
Set Up!
Ridol Whip!
X Rider!
Damn you, X!
Ridol Stick!
Die, Rider X!
Kiyomi!
My name is Medusa.
Too bad for you that I wasn't the professor's assistant.
Keisuke!
Damn it.
Pierce through fear!
Cruiser Jump!
The time bomb's switch has been set,
so that when X Rider comes to rescue you two...
...it will make a hot explosion!
Here it is.
Medusa. X Rider has attacked.
How useful.
I don't need this house if it's in exchange for X Rider's life.
Then we'll make it explode.
What about this child?
She's bait in order to lock up X Rider.
She's going to be locked up with X Rider?!
I'll set this onto the ceiling and we'll blow them up along with X Rider!
In order to achieve their method, they won't choose their targets.
That is the rule of GOD.
Saeko!
Keisuke!
He was lured by a fake voice!
Saeko, I'll help you.
I can't let you be sacrificed for X Rider's sake.
Ryouko, what are you doing?!
I've had commands from the
General Commander to kill X Rider.
But, he won't tell me to kill the child as well.
Leave! She's important bait!
No. I'll let the child go.
You're an ally of GOD!
Acting so selfishly is unforgiveable!
I understand.
We can get X Rider without the child!
Stop it!
The time bomb has been set and the underground corridor has been opened to let X Rider through!
He will soon come!
Saeko!
Stop it, Ryouko!
Saeko, don't worry.
I'll eliminate all traitors of GOD!
Cry!
Scream!
Keisuke!
I, X Rider, will save you guys!
A time bomb has been set!
What?!
Damn it!
X Rider! Quickly!
It's no use. It'll take much more than my power.
X Rider.
This wall is...
This mark is strange.
This is a hidden door.
Thank you, Saeko.
Okay. Saeko, Professor, hurry!
Fell into my trap, huh?
Medusa!
Rider X!
Ridol Stick!
Cruiser Great Rotation!
Cruiser Attack!
There you are!
See this, Medusa!
Come, Rider!
Crap!
Damn it!
Rider X, you...
X Kick!
You shall turn into stone!
You doged it! I don't have any more energy!
Kamen Rider X, who is sent to fight against GOD.
That desolate fight has just begun.
He doesn't have time to rest.
Go for it, Kamen Rider X!
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"The One-Eyed Monster's Kidnapping Operation!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider