Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
King Dark! Demonic Invention!!
How is research proceeding?
King Dark, the lab tells
us they'll need more time.
Much too slow! Tell
them to hurry up!
King Dark refers to the research of world famous
Nanbara Souichirou, director of GOD R&D.
His research aims to build a device capable of
transforming any matter on Earth into energy.
He calls it the RS Device.
With the RS Device installed inside him, King
Dark will have the energy to run rampant.
The day King Dark arises will
be the day this world falls...
Tamai, I'm exhausted...
How about a break?
No objections from me, doctor!
Here, doctor.
Thanks...
Sorry, I was miles away.
You can tell me if something's
worrying you, doctor.
Tamai--
Don't worry, I've removed all
of GOD's bugs from this room!
Doctor, please tell me! The RS Device's
blueprints are finished, aren't they?
Doctor, please tell me!
The idiots still haven't realised
there's microphones in their buttons...
You guessed it. The RS
Device's blueprints are complete.
But... I shudder when
I think about its power.
GOD will use it
as a demonic weapon...
But in the right hands, it could
be a gift from the heavens!
A demonic invention or
a gift from the heavens...
Doctor, you have to get out of here!
I can't. GOD has my daughter's...
my only daughter's life by a thread.
What? The RS Device is
finished? Report to King Dark!
Toad Goemon, show yourself!
Toad Goemon is here!
Nanbara hid the fact that he's already
completed the RS Device's blueprints...
Get them out of him, Toad Goemon!
I have a brain worthy of Japan's
greatest thief, Ishikawa Goemon!
I'll show you how a burglary
genius always gets his mark!
Save the boasting for after the fact...
Ishikawa Goemon was a master of Iga
style ninjutsu, and I have inherited his skills!
We've got Nanbara's daughter...
Start by using her.
The summer holidays at last!
I'm going to my house in Karuizawa
-I'm going to Hawaii!
-What about you, Nanbara?
Rie's dad's a big shot!
Probably Europe, right?
My dad's working!
What'd I say?
You didn't have to show
off about going to Hawai'i!
-Right!
-I meant Hawai, in Japan!
What's up? Having trouble
with your parents?
Not taking you on holiday until
you've done your homework, huh?
No! My dad'll take me anywhere I like!
Really? What a nice dad!
But then... Why do you look so sad?
Where's your dad now?
I don't know!
Something's up...
Didn't I tell you to come straight home?
B-but...
Say anything about the doctor's
work and your life is over.
Listen, we're watching
you around the clock.
Even in this room.
Let him go! Let my dad go!
No. Just live your life as usual.
We don't want anyone getting suspicious.
Someone's already suspicious!
The guy from the park!
Get out of here!
Now's my chance!
Don't even try it!
No one escapes me!
Help! Help me!
Rie!
Help!
-Help!
-Rie!
Hold it!
So you're from King Dark's
army... Put her down!
Jin Keisuke... You think you
can defeat Toad Goemon?
I'd be glad to prove it!
Take this! Flaming Toad Oil!
Set Up!
Ridol Rope!
Toad Goemon! You're
not going anywhere!
Curse you, X Rider!
Toad Oil!
My Toad Oil deflects
all your punches!
I don't even feel them!
Now it's my turn!
Goemon Throw!
Saving Rie comes first...
Toad Goemon! We'll
settle this next time!
Cruiser!
Darn it!
-You'll be safe here.
-You must've been so scared!
Poor thing...
You said it.
To think King Dark got his hands on a
world famous scientist like Dr. Nanbara...
What kind of research might he be doing?
I just hope my dad's alright...
The heck...?
"Hand over Rie or Nanbara's dead
--Toad Goemon."
-Keisuke!
-He's already gone!
-Dad's in trouble!
-Rie!
Don't worry, we've got
a really strong friend!
Stop it! Are you trying
to ruin our research!?
Rubbish! Don't try to pull
the wool over my eyes!
Where are the RS Device's blueprints?
-They're still not complete!
-Liar!
What are you going to do to us!?
Hand them over if you value
your assistant's life, Nanbara...
Don't do it, doctor! The RS
Device is a gift from the heavens!
Come now, there's no need for violence!
You won't hand it over? What if I...
Now for the other one!
-Wait!
-Don't worry! It's just one life!
No price, no research,
is worth a human life.
I'll give you the blueprints.
Good, just hand them over...
Don't move.
What's this!?
Are you trying to scare
me with that cheap toy!?
It does look like a
toy, doesn't it...?
The computers all vanished!
And that's just the power
of a prototype RS Device!
That's a mini RS Device...?
Open the door.
Look out, doctor! Quickly,
run! Hurry, doctor!!
Tamai!
I can't protect the blueprints alone...
What should I do?
At the very least, I
can't let GOD have it...
It seems I've only one choice.
Dr. Nanbara divided the blueprints
into nine pieces to hide them.
Doctor! Dr. Nanbara!!
Rie's safe!
Not here...
No Toad Goemon either. Did
something happen to the doctor?
Just where'd he go?
Meanwhile, Dr. Nanbara mailed eight of
the blueprint pieces to eight colleagues.
That should do it... I hope.
Rie! Rie...?
Did they take her away
while she was alone?
Tamai! You're alright!
Yes, and I know where
they're holding Rie!
You do? Show me, please!
Alright, but why don't
you let me look after that?
Certainly.
...But Tamai, that monster
burned your hand!
Who are you!?
Toad Goemon!
A prototype RS Device is even
better than the blueprints!
All we have to do is
build a bigger version!
I'll protect Dr. Nanbara!
There you are, X Rider!
Just in time to die!
What's that weird ball for?
You're too late! X Rider...
This is your death!
I removed the ignition. I was
wondering when you would notice.
Blast you! X Rider... I'll get
the blueprints after I defeat you!
This way, doctor!
What was that device, doctor?
The RS Device... It can process
the energy of any material.
A demonic weapon in GOD's hands...
Demonic...?
GOD forced me to develop it...
But I fled, hoping I could turn
it into a gift from the heavens.
Rie's at Tachibana's coffee shop!
Thank you, X Rider!
Take him!
Ishikawa Goemon was a prodigious shinobi!
Behold his Iga style wood technique!
Think you can find me, X Rider?
Got you!
Blast! You found me!
Toad Oil!
The oil again...
A Rider's punch is
nothing against my oil!
Flaming Toad Oil!
Ridol Windmill!
Flame Counter!
X Kick!
-Dad!
-Rie!
Thank goodness...
I'm so glad!
Dad! Dad!
I won't leave you alone again!
What a relief!
-Dad!
-Doctor!
Dad! Dad!!
W-what is this...?
Keisuke, the doctor!
Doctor...!
Hang on!
I... believe you're on the
side of justice, so please...
I split the blueprints into nine,
and... sent eight to my colleagues...
P-please... protect them...
What are their names?
-Doctor!
Dad!!
Dad! Dad!!
He split it into nine... but
sent it to eight colleagues.
What about the other piece?
-Keisuke...
-Rie...?
Dad must have put it in here...
-Rie...
-I knew dad better than anyone...
But why did he have to run away?
Rie, I promise you and your dad...
I'll keep his blueprints safe.
I won't let GOD lay a finger on them!
Go, Scorpion Geronimo!
Find all nine pieces, including
the one Jin Keisuke has!
You can rely on Scorpion Geronimo!
Earth's doom? Or mankind's salvation?
The terrible battle for the torn
blueprints is just beginning!
To be continued
Next episode
The RS Device's blueprints have been
split into nine pieces and hidden.
GOD's Scorpion Geronimo sets his sights
on a young hiker with one of the pieces.
Stop him, X Rider!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Vengeful Ogre Geronimo! Silent Assault!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider