Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Special Edition
The 5 Riders in Full Force!!
Closed for the day
What's with the sign, chief?
You're losing business!
Oh, Keisuke! Take a look, take a look!
Well, I'd better get ready. Busy busy busy!
"Summer Storytelling for Kids:
Are the Kamen Riders Friend or Foe"...?
Welcome, one and all!
We shall now commence our
discussion of the Kamen Riders!
What a lot of strapping young
children we have here today!
He's starting! What about this
storyteller? Cool moustache or what?
Now I'm sure we all agree that the
Kamen Riders are heroes, don't we? Well...
...That's nothing but a lie!
They've fooled you all just
to make themselves famous!
They're nothing but liars!
We all feel sorry for the
poor cyborgs, don't we?
These seem to be the villains of the piece,
don't they? But it's just the opposite!
On the contrary, the original Kamen Rider
is just a weakling with wads of cash!
With this in mind, it's natural to assume he
must have bribed those monsters to take dives!
And Rider #2 isn't much better!
He cuts a fine figure on
his motorcycle, doesn't he?
But that too is a lie!!
And what of Kamen Rider V3!?
His transformation pose makes
him look strong, doesn't it?
But Deathtron taught him how to
do it!! I shall demonstrate!
-What's with this storyteller!?
Now you've done it...!
What are you doing!?
I tried keeping quiet, but I've
had enough of your lies! Beat it!!
-Liar!
-The Kamen Riders are heroes!
-Yeah, get outta here!
-Hold it, you jerk!
Calm down, everyone!
...Stupid thing...
Please, settle down!
Welcome, one and all!
Without further ado, I present
the true tale of the Kamen Riders!
-This is gonna be the real thing!
-Yeah!
It all began with the evil
organisation known as Shocker.
They kidnapped the young scientist Hongou
Takeshi and transformed him into a cyborg...
...even trying to replace his love of
peace with their own wicked desires!
Shocker's group of scientists
have modified your body...
You are now a cyborg.
A cyborg...?
You expect me to believe that!?
E-even if I die... I won't obey you...!
But Hongou escaped and began his fight
against Shocker as the Kamen Rider!
Hongou Takeshi transforms when
the wind passes through his belt.
The Spider-Man, Sarracenian, the
Bee-Woman, and the Cobra-Man!
Rider Kick!
Tokageron led Shocker's monsters
into battle against Rider #1!
Rider Fight!
Time for the killing shot!
Thunderbolt Rider Kick!
I won... The Rider Kick did it!
Hongou Takeshi's allies included
Ruriko, Hiromi, Shirou, and others.
Our second chapter introduces one
I'm sure you know: Ichimonji Hayato.
When Rider #1 pursued Shocker to
Europe, Ichimonji came to fill the void.
Shocker's real target...
must be the Kamen Rider.
Just who are you?
Someone who'll protect Japan
in Hongou Takeshi's place...
The Kamen Rider!
You're a cyborg too!?
Let me introduce... the Kamen Rider.
Transform!
Rider Kick!
Mighty monsters like Pirasaurus
and Dokugander assailed Rider #2!
Rider Kick!
Rider #2 was assisted by Taki Kazuya, and Mari, Yuri,
Michi and Hiromi of the Tachibana Racing Club.
Rider... Transform!
And then Rider #1, Hongou
Takeshi, returned to Japan.
-Rider Kick!
Hayato...
Hongou!
Naturally, Shocker stood no chance against
Hongou Takeshi and Ichimonji Hayato.
They defeated every monster which challenged them.
You Kamen Riders might be able
to transform... But so can I!
Like me...?
Rider Punch!
Dr. Death!
Kamen Rider!
Rider Tailspin Shoot!
He's gone...
Rider Kick!
Aside from its monsters, Shocker also sent
its strongest officers after the Riders.
Colonel Zol, Dr. Death, and Ambassador
Hell appeared one after another.
But even they were unable to best the Riders!
And then Shocker's leader
created GelShocker to invade Japan.
GelShocker was mighty, and
backed Riders #1 and #2 into a corner!
I now declare GelShocker's
Japanese branch in operation.
Shocker has absorbed Geldam's
resources... and become GelShocker.
I am GelShocker's cyborg
EagleMantis! All humans are my prey!
Take them away, and don't miss any!
Unable to defeat the Riders, GelShocker
built six fakes to confound them.
-Ichimonji, now!
-Right!
G-GelShocker will have the last laugh...
All glory to...
...our great leader!!
Vanquishing the most terrifying officer of all,
our heroes finally confronted Shocker's leader.
Give up this plot for world conquest!
Let's see your real face!
So that's the leader...
I'll take you two to hell with me!
Even with Shocker's leader vanquished, more
monsters appeared before the two Riders.
Namely: Scissors Jaguar, a soldier of Deathtron.
But then, a certain man arrived...
Kazami Shirou, whose family
were executed by Deathtron.
Energy to maximum!
I'll kill #1 and #2!
Hold it!
Thanks to Riders #1 and #2, he
was reborn as Kamen Rider V3!
#2, we've found our successor. Let's do it!
But the first two Riders sacrificed themselves to
protect Tokyo from TurtleBazooka's atomic bomb.
Transform... V3!
As you know, Kamen Rider
V3 ran wild on his foes.
V3 Screw Kick!
V3 Kick!
But Deathtron's leader
wouldn't surrender so easily.
High-ranking officers like Doktor G
and Baron Fang made their move.
V3 Rolling Three-Stage Kick!
The Fang Clan... perishes at last...
But for all these enemies, V3 gained an ally too.
Now, do you know who that is?
You tell me!
Riderman!!
Quite right, Riderman!
Deathtron scientist Yuuki Jouji...
He modified himself for revenge
against Marshal Armour!
Rope Arm!
V3, now!
Right!
Awoken to justice, Riderman
swore to fight alongside V3.
But Riderman ultimately departed for
the heavens to protect peace on Earth.
Riderman... You did it.
You saved mankind!
You're a hero! From now on,
you're Kamen Rider #4!
Now, our tale climaxes with
the most exciting scene of all.
With Riders #1, #2 and V3, Riderman miraculously alive, and the arrival of Rider X...
...the Five Riders were in full force at last!
Riders, Riders
Oh, Kamen Riders
They're never far away
Our allies, the heroes of justice
Taking down the enemies of peace
Don't give up, #1, #2, or V3
Don't give up, Kaizorg X Rider
-Rider Double Kick!
Well then--
Hey, old man!
You expect me to sit and
listen to that fairy tale!?
That's not what happened and you know it!
Imagine thinking the Kamen Riders never lost!!
You're the liar here! I thought
you'd left already? Kick rocks!
Shut your mouth!!
Waiting room
Darn you!
Hold it!
I figured it was something like this.
Keisuke, how the--!?
-There's...
-...two of them!
Chief, this guy's with GOD.
What? GOD?
I get it, that's why you
were lying about the Riders!
Well, there's no
point me hiding now!
Neptune...!
The great King Dark has revived us!
Hold on, hold on...
Chief.
It's... Shirou!
Honestly, I try to pay the chief a visit
for once, and... Who are these guys?
Watch it, they're as bad as Deathtron!
Keisuke, this is Kazami Shirou!
It's been a while... since I ran wild.
-Get the kids out of here!
-Right!
I'm Jin Keisuke. The
chief told me about you!
The name's Kazami Shirou!
Excuse me if I get a little wild...
Retreat!
-Kazami, look!
-What? Let's go!
Set Up!
Transform... V3!
X Kick!
Now we've got V3's moves on
film as well as the X Rider's...
What a catch!
-Kazami, good work!
-You think so? Same to you.
X Rider!
We've fully analysed
your fighting style!
You're very much mistaken if you
think you're the equal of GOD!
GOD have identified X's weaknesses.
Hang in there, Kamen Rider X! Break
GOD's hold and bring peace to the world!
To be continued
Next episode
Spider Napoleon drains all of the X Rider's energy,
and only V3 - Kazami Shirou - can save him.
He equips the X Rider with Mercury Power!
X Rider gets even stronger!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Behold! X Rider's Great Transformation!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider