Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Corpses Call from the Haunted House!!
There's a house! See? Let's go!
Hello? Good evening?
Would you mind if we came in?
Hello in there!
This is silly, let's just go in.
-Anybody home?
-They must be away...
I don't like this place...
Let's go back, ok?
What about the storm?
I know, but...
Come on, please!
It won't open!
Welcome... I am the
keeper of this house...
The ghost monster... Occultos!
You fiend!
Ghost monster Occultos!
My lord!
The goal of GOD's Ghost Plan is to
foment chaos by terrifying the citizens.
Begin the operation at once.
Understood!
I heard the couple who went missing
in this forest were young, but...
-Fog...
-Keisuke!!
Keisuke!
Where'd he get to?
-He must've got lost in the fog!
-It's really heavy, huh?
Alright, stick with me.
-Ok!
There's a house here?
-Let's take a look.
-Right!
Who knew there was such a
big house in this forest?
Maybe they know something
about the missing couple.
Good point. Try knocking.
-Right.
Excuse us!
Good grief, what a dump!
You think it's abandoned?
It's creepy, either way.
Oh, excuse us for barging in like this!
You see, a young man and woman
disappeared in this forest yesterday.
We're looking for them, but...
Have you maybe seen them?
We... know them...
They... are dead...
What's that? They're dead!?
Th-these two-- The
missing couple-- Look!
It's them!
What happened to you two!?
We... told you...
We... are dead...
-They vanished!
-Vanished!?
Well, now...
-Who's there!?
-Why, you--!
Welcome! But I'm afraid you three
won't be leaving this haunted house.
-Somebody save us!!
-Keisuke!!
-Run for it!
-It won't open, it won't open!
Help, help!!
Stop right there!
-Keisuke!
Chief, this is one
of GOD's monsters!
Indeed, I am the
ghost monster Occultos!
Run!
Do you truly think you're
my equal, Jin Keisuke!?
Behold Occultos' psychic power!
-Keisuke!
How does that feel?
Do you realise now
that you're outmatched?
I refuse to waste my time on you!
Keisuke!
You alright?
Chief...
The house is disappearing!
This wall's disappearing too!
Gone...
Skeletons!!
So this really was them...
These bones are what's
left of the missing couple.
Then we just saw...
...Their ghosts!
I don't get it! It's like
someone put a spell on us!
Even Jin Keisuke can't see through
Occultos' three-dimensional illusions.
-Ok, you two call the police.
-Right...
Chief, help me gather up these bones.
Interesting... Maybe I'll
loosen Occultos' leash.
And then deliver the
coup de grâce myself!
Hey, will one of you come
to the bathroom with me?
Why?
Because it's haunted!
That's a lie, there's no
such thing as ghosts! Right?
Right!
Well I'm still scared!
-Ok, we'll come with you.
-Sure.
We'll wait here.
Hold my stuff?
Finally!
Talk about overdoing it.
Weird...
See ya!
-See ya.
-Bye-bye!
Someone's hanged herself!
Why in the world is someone
parked here at this hour?
Excuse me! Hello?
Th-th-they're dead!
Ghosts! Ghosts! Ghosts!!
-Save me!!
-Your life is mine!
Back again, Jin Keisuke?
I won't let you murder
innocent people!
Psychic power!
Interfere with me a
third time and you die!
Please forgive me...
I was too late to save you.
Open
Ghosts were popping
up all over last night!
GOD are trying to throw
Tokyo into a panic!
Give me a minute, chief!
I need to think of a way to
counter his psychic power!
And while you're thinking, ghosts
are scaring people to death!
Wait... Isn't it that security
guard's funeral tomorrow?
Funeral...?
The Wise Bodhisattva of Freedom and Compassion knows
that the body and the Five Aggregates are but Void...
...and thus helps those who suffer. O Sariputra,
Matter is but Void, and Void is but Matter.
Matter becomes Void, and Void becomes Matter. The Five
Aggregates are but Matter. O Sariputra, all is thus Void.
It is birthless, deathless, tainted, pure,
ever-decreasing and ever-increasing--
Just his wife and kid...
That's a shame, isn't it?
Yeah...
People are afraid to come
out in case they see a ghost.
I'm frightened!
I am the ghost monster Occultos!
Darned GOD monster!
This time, you die!
Set Up!
X Rider, this is the third and
final time you cross me!
Shut up! You won't get away with killing
so many innocent people, Occultos!
X Rider!
Don't make me laugh!
Ridol Stick!
Behold Occultos' psychic power!
Ridol Barrier!
The X Rider's Ridol Stick has reflected Occultos' psychic waves.
Now's my chance!
X Kick!
Curses, I was too late! X Rider... Now
I want to kill you more than ever!
The X Rider has vanquished the
horrible ghost monster Occultos.
But Apollo Geist's rage only
burns hotter! Don't lose, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD's monster Salamandra is turning
people into terrifying serpentine mutants.
Salamandra, master of poisonous vipers,
lures the X Rider into the reptile house.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Ghouls!? Mysterious Snake-People Appear!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider