Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Showdown!
King Dark Versus X Rider
Closed for the day, call 0499 487...
Her name is Noda Sachiko. She's
a student of the late Dr. Nanbara.
A student of Nanbara's? Then maybe
she has a piece of the blueprints...
If she does, you must beat the X Rider to it!
This sounds like a job for me.
Then begin at once, Ant Capone!
Sì, King Dark.
Here's your coffee, daddy.
Aren't you a good girl, Nanae?
I promised mommy I'd look
after you until she got back!
So you did.
I'm scared, daddy!
Who's there!?
I came to see Mrs. Noda, but--
Sachiko's away! What do you want with her?
The blueprint Dr. Nanbara gave her.
Well? Why don't you tell me where it is?
Blueprint...? I don't know! And
I don't know where Sachiko is!
Idiot... What husband doesn't
know where his wife's gone?
Out with it. Where is she?
Who are you, anyway!?
Ant Capone!
Now talk! Talk! Where's Sachiko gone!?
I-I don't know!
Daddy!
Where's your mommy gone?
Mommy's gone to Nasu View Hotel...
Good girl! And you can come with me!
Come here!
Go for it! Hurry, hurry!
A little faster, Chiko!
That's it!
One more length, Chiko?
Hey, Keisuke! Phone!
-The phone?
-It's a woman!
A woman?
Yes, this is Jin Keisuke...
A blueprint from Dr. Nanbara?
I'm from the Nanbara Group. We decided to
hand it over as soon as we heard about you.
I'll meet you right away, but...
How will I recognise you?
-I'll be wearing a red flower.
-Got it.
You're not going anywhere, Jin Keisuke!
You're Noda Sachiko?
I've come to collect you. Please get in.
-But...
-Sorry, I'm Tachibana Toubei.
Don't you run that coffee shop?
-That's right. Now--
-Thank you so much.
That's enough messing around...
You guys are the ones
who aren't going anywhere!
GOD must be chasing their tails right now...
-You underestimate GOD!
-A GOD monster!
Tachibana Toubei, be a good
slave and drive like I tell you!
Yes, master.
A red flower...
Then they must've--
No, the boss isn't back yet.
He's not in his room, either.
Right, listen. There's a homing device in the
chief's bag. Use that to contact him, ok?
Give me the blueprint and you're free to go!
I don't know what you're talking about...
Take a look around, lady.
Just one of my ants can hypnotise you.
But all of them together can drain the blood from your body in seconds!
Talk! Where's the blueprint?
-I-it's--
-Hold it!
Don't tell them!
Curse you, Jin Keisuke!
Blast!
Run for it!
Great Transformation!
And curse you too, X Rider!
Hurry now!
I haven't given up yet!
I can still get the blueprint!
Chief?
Chief!
H-hey, where'd she go?
Sachiko's safe. Probably back at the hotel.
It's been five hours...
Where can she be?
Maybe she got scared
and went back to Tokyo?
Anyone would do the same.
They wouldn't just quit if she did.
I don't think she's that naive.
She'll only be safe once they
have her piece of the blueprints.
You think she might hand it over?
It's possible.
Come in!
For Mr. Jin Keisuke?
Thanks.
What is it?
Invitations to the restaurant.
-Invitations?
-Invitations!?
-Awesome!
-Knock it off!
The history of the Japanese usage of the Swahili
term "jambo" is too complex to fit here, but rest
assured you're not about to see a spelling mistake!
Jambo African Show!
Welcome, everyone, to the Nasu View Hotel.
We hope you enjoy the Jambo African Show.
Well, without further ado, let's go! Action!
Jambo!
Is she ever serious?
I was hoping you'd join us.
I thought we'd be stand out less in a crowd.
Good thinking.
Even GOD wouldn't show up here.
So, where's the blueprint?
-I'll take this!
-Darn it!
This is what you get for ruining our show!
-You should run.
-Thank you!
If I don't get this blueprint to Mr. Jin...
...You could give it to me instead.
Who are you?
Give me the blueprint if you value Nanae's life.
Mommy!
Nanae!
Where is it!?
In my handbag...
Then you've got one chance:
Bring it to me yourself.
I'll trade you Nanae for it.
But look, come alone, alright?
-Nanae!
-If I see Jin Keisuke, Nanae's dead!
-Are you alright?
-We got your bag back!
So, can you give us the blueprint now?
Forgive me, but... I misplaced it.
Huh? But you were just gonna
give us something out of your bag!
I assumed I would be safe if
they thought I'd given it to you.
B-but...!
-Please forgive me.
-Keisuke!
GOD probably think you've
given us the blueprint, so...
There's nothing for you to worry about now.
Then... you forgive me?
If you don't know where it is,
then there's nothing to forgive.
Well, my daughter is waiting
at home. I should leave.
Shall we take you to the station?
I'll be alright by myself, thank you.
You're alone?
Yes. Where's my daughter?
Where's Nanae?
At the top. C'mon.
Nanae is safe, isn't she?
Quit babbling!
-Nanae!
-Mommy! Mommy!
The blueprint comes first!
Take her away!
What are you doing!? You promised!
You only get one chance at tricking GOD!
You can die together, mother and child!
Hold it!!
X Rider! How did you find us!?
I thought Sachiko changed her
mind too quickly, so I followed her!
But you're too late, X
Rider! I've got the blueprint!
Do you now? Are you sure
it's not a fake again?
No way!!
-Run!
-Alright!
Vacuum Hell Wheel!
X Rider! King Dark will triumph in the end!
All of those blueprints will be mine!
Behold my majestic form!
King Dark!
I swear to someday crush you
with these very hands!
The terrible giant, King Dark,
has challenged me himself...
King Dark has finally appeared before the X Rider.
Will even the X Rider be
able to defeat this colossus?
To be continued
Next episode
A girl appears in Keisuke's dreams.
When her angelic face becomes that of a GOD
monster, Toubei plunges into a deep valley.
Look forward to the next episode,
featuring Riders #2 and V3:
"Terror! King Dark's Vengeance!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider