Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
GOD Secret Police! Apollo Geist!!
One of GOD's monsters, the invincible Achilles,
teamed up with the mysterious Apollo Geist.
As a result, the X Rider fell
in battle for the first time.
Encouraged by Tachibana Toubei, the X Rider
began training to create a new finishing move.
Good luck, X Rider.
Kamen Riders #1, #2 and V3
all overcame this training.
If I can get out of this pinch,
I'll be a real Kamen Rider too.
X Rider, think carefully about your opponent's weakness!
You remember what his name is?
Achilles...!
Judging by that name...
Could Achilles' weakness be his heel?
Achilles is an invincible hero of Greek mythology.
He had but one weak spot: his heel.
According to the myth, Achilles died
when that heel was struck by arrows.
That's the origin of
the term "Achilles' heel."
His Achilles' heel! His weak spots
are the jets attached to his feet!
I can't compete with his speed on the land...
But if I can take the fight to the air...
Chief, lend me a hand!
Alright! Come at me like I'm Achilles!
Chief!
Don't forget... how you were breathing!
Yes, sir!
The enemy has guts.
You're a worthy foe, X Rider.
Achilles won't have it
easy next time they fight.
Any problems with the human robots?
None at all, sir.
Alright then, just keep an eye out.
Achilles, the situation is beyond
satisfactory. But you have further orders:
Monitor the X Rider. He must not
interfere with our operation.
The human robot project's as good as
finished, and the X Rider's all washed up.
So why would the Supreme Commander
give me an order like that?
Achilles!
The X Rider is unharmed.
What did you say, Apollo Geist!?
Not only is the X Rider standing,
he's training desperately to crush you!
What!?
Achilles, why don't
you follow his example?
Nonsense!! You think the
invincible Achilles might lose!?
Alright, I'm off.
I'll challenge him myself!
Apollo Geist, why didn't you stop him?
You're the Chief of GOD's
Secret Police, that's your prerogative!
I beg your pardon, Supreme Commander.
But from my perspective, Achilles
is unable to make calm decisions.
He's a poor fit for managing
the human robot operation.
Very well, I trust your analysis.
Resume preparations for the second phase!
Who's there?
Miki! You're safe?
Wonderful, wonderful!
What a relief.
Jin Keisuke, listen!
Miki...!
Come to Ooi Wharf if you want
the cure for Miki's condition.
Achilles will be waiting,
Jin Keisuke.
H-hey!
Miki!
She's unconscious.
Probably caused by one of those darts.
Ooi Wharf, eh? Achilles...
Keisuke, you're going?
Of course.
But your new finishing move will
take another two days to perfect!
That doesn't sound like you, chief.
Did you tell the Kamen Riders
before me to wait?
You've got me there.
Alright, go for it!
Take care of Miki.
This is GOD and Achilles I'm dealing with.
He won't just hand over the antidote.
What kind of trap has he set for me?
The X Rider won't lose this time.
A bee!
Miki, bring Tachibana Toubei to me.
It's Jin Keisuke! Come out, Achilles!!
I've been waiting for you, Jin Keisuke!
Chief! Miki!
These human robots can't hear you.
Human robots? That's what the virus does?
And only the antidote
can return them to normal.
You coward! Hand over the antidote!
I have one condition!
Say it!
Jin Keisuke's-- no, the X Rider's life.
My life?
Your answer?
The chief and Miki take priority...
Achilles, I surrender.
You're a brave one. But I'll have
a little sport killing you.
Go! Show him a rollerskate hell!
Start!!
Give him one lap!
If only Apollo Geist could see this.
Alright, he must be dead by now.
Where's Keisuke? Where's Jin Keisuke!?
What's your problem!?
Dead...?
He got me!
Achilles!
Looks like it's one-on-one now.
Curses!
I've beaten you before, and will again!!
My only chance of beating Achilles
is to take the fight to the air.
Die!
X Two-Step Kick!!
It's incomplete... But did it work?
Curse you... How did you know
my weakness? X Rider...!
That must be the antidote.
I haven't lost yet!
D-don't shoot, Apollo Geist!
Are you trying to kill an ally!?
Listen! I am Chief of
GOD
's Secret Police.
You're with those horrible Secret Police...!?
Unable to serve him as you are, I execute
you in the name of the Supreme Commander!
Stop! Spare me!!
Wait!
What a villain. I should cure the chief
and Miki while there's no one else here.
So that's the X Rider?
Prometheus, this is GOD's Supreme Commander.
Yes, Supreme Commander.
With Achilles' death, the human
robot operation is discontinued.
The second phase is to train
the human robots as saboteurs.
We'll then begin sabotage operations all over Japan.
Hold your fire!
Apollo Geist.
Show me to your hideout.
Alright.
What do you think, Apollo Geist?
I'm quite the teacher, aren't I?
You train GOD's Combat Agents.
This is the minimum I'd expect!
Minimum...? Listen, none of those
humans have even held a gun before.
I've only been working with them half a day!
This location is no longer secure.
Move all personnel out of the village at once!
Why?
The X Rider has the Dream Virus' antidote.
That girl Miki is bound to have
told him about this village.
There's no doubt he's coming here!
So the X Rider's on his way...
Listen, leave no evidence here.
Move out at once!
Acting so high and mighty...
The X Rider's coming, is he?
He doesn't know the villagers have been trained as Combat Agents...
It'd be a waste to move!
I'll kill the X Rider right here!
As Apollo Geist suspected, Jin Keisuke was on his
way from Joutou University's labs to cure the villagers.
No sign of GOD...
With Achilles dead, are the
villagers still human robots?
Let's see...
The villagers are gone.
Could they be hiding from me?
Don't worry, you can come out!
I'm here to help you!
Is Miki's mother here?
It's alright, I've brought the antidote!
Don't move, Jin Keisuke! I'm Prometheus,
this operation's new commander!
I see, so you're carrying on Achilles' work?
Have a taste of my talents.
You coward!
Come on, fight, Jin Keisuke!
The villagers are still...
I don't want to hurt them...
This is a dirty tactic, Prometheus!
The surprises are only
just starting! Now, begin!
Open fire!
Bamboo Spear Unit, charge!
Stop! You have to stop!
Don't waste your breath. These villagers
have already become GOD saboteurs!
Kill Jin Keisuke! Go!!
No, I can't fight you!
I'll have to escape!
Jin Keisuke's fallen right into my trap.
Ready the landmines!
That's what you get. I'm going to find Apollo Geist.
I want to see his face when he sees this.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Apollo Geist!
What's going on, Prometheus?
You should have moved out by now!
There's no need to leave that village now.
What?
Jin Keisuke snuck in, and I caught him!
Idiot!!
What!?
This is Jin Keisuke-- no,
the X Rider we're talking about.
Come to the village if you think I'm lying.
There would be no point. The X Rider's
probably cured the villagers already.
Darn you, Apollo Geist!
He can't be right.
Quick, back to the village!
There, I knew everything would be fine.
Trying to scare me like that...!
So you've come to.
I was never knocked out.
I hypnotised myself to sleep!
Why would you do that?
So you'd let your guard down long
enough for me to cure the villagers.
W-what!? Assemble the saboteurs!
Keisuke!
Nicely done, chief!
Ma'am, your daughter Miki's just fine.
Thank you!
C'mon, you need to get somewhere safe.
Saboteurs!!
Men!? Are you ignoring my orders!?
Well? Do you believe me now?
The villagers have regained
their senses and escaped!
Apollo Geist will laugh if he hears
about this... Let's go, Jin Keisuke!
Prometheus Napalm!
Set Up!
Darn it!
Multiple Napalm Attack!
That should finish off the X Rider-- Huh?
You're still alive, Rider!?
Cruiser Attack!
X Rider!
Ridol Stick!
Napalm Bomb!
There he is!
X Kick!!
GOD's human robot operation has been crushed.
But Apollo Geist is raring to take on the X Rider.
Fight, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
Money is vanishing from the city. Eerie lizards
are stealing money and killing people.
With their water snake monster Hydra attacking
the X Rider, GOD are causing societal upheaval.
Look out, Rider X!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Immortal Water Snake Monster, Hydra!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider