Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
And how is the new virus
culture coming along?
It's developing incredibly fast.
I've never seen anything like it.
Sir, I have to know. Just
what is this new virus?
All you have to do is keep your
head down and work on the vaccine.
But...
If the pathogen is as dreadful as it seems, we
can't test it on humans until the vaccine is ready.
Test it on humans...?
Yes. Anyway, Sawada, how many vaccine samples have you made?
...About twenty right now.
Oh? That's not many, and
the experiment starts soon...
So, you really intend
to test it on humans...
I'll need you to be on
hand when the time comes.
But... to be used like a guinea pig...
I... can't imagine anyone volunteering.
I've taken care of that.
Scary!
It's GOD's Cat Monster Plan!
What a dreary night!
What's a cat doing out here?
You little--!
Huh? Where'd it go?
Mom!
Dad!
Dad, come quick!
What's wrong, Kaori?
Keisuke!
Chief! Why the emergency call?
Something's up.
A cat killed your mother? Kaori,
did you have another bad dream?
It wasn't a dream!
It was real, honest!
Alright, alright. Why don't you show
me? Come on, let's take a look.
Mom!
What's wrong, Kaori?
Why are you still awake?
It sounds like she had a nightmare.
A nightmare?
She said you'd been killed by a cat!
Killed by a cat...? Oh, my.
Yoshie!
I'm scared, dad!
What's happened to you!?
W-what do you want!?
Sir? What are you doing here?
It seems the human test
was a success, Sawada.
What!?
Let me show you who I really am.
I am one of GOD's monsters, Cattius!
Once you become a cat-man, you'll be
a big help to GOD's Cat Monster Plan!
Dad! Dad!!
He's one of us now.
The experiment to turn humans
into cat monsters is a success.
Listen! You will help cultivate
the Cat Monster Virus!
-Now to make this girl one of us--
-Hold it!
Jin Keisuke!
GOD... Just what are
you plotting this time?
-Keisuke!
-Run for it, chief!
Rider!
Hurry!
We should be safe now.
This is the one.
Who is it?
It's me, Tachibana! Open up!
M'still sleepy... What's the rush?
I need a little favour. Can we come in?
You mind?
I guess not.
Come on in.
You first.
The thing is...
GOD's after this girl!
The coffee shop's too public, so...
Can we hide out here for a while?
Sure, but only 'cos she's cute.
-You don't mind, right, Chiko?
-Fine by me!
Help!
What's up?
Don't you think it's cute?
-Here's your tea.
-Thanks.
H-hey, where'd you get that cat?
I don't like it!
You see, a GOD monster turned
her folks into cat-people.
Cat-people...?
To cut a long story short... Monsters.
Cat monsters?
Man, I wonder what they look like!
Hey, what's so funny?
Cat-people!
They got to you guys too?
You'll pay for this!
Unfortunately for you, everyone in this
apartment block is a cat-person!
And now, you'll be joining them!
Run as soon as you see a chance.
Take this!
Help me!!
There you are, Cattius!
I'm scared!
Don't worry. Just keep
your eyes shut tight.
Once I sink my infectious claws into your
body, you'll become a cat-person too!
This isn't over, X Rider!
C'mon, you must be hungry.
Kaori. Your parents...
They haven't really
turned into monsters.
They're just... sick.
Sick?
That's right!
But I'll help them get better.
Really?
I promise.
So keep your spirits
up, and try to eat.
Ok!
Where did the cat-people
from that apartment block go?
And why are this girl's
parents being targeted?
The Cat Monster Plan isn't
progressing steadily enough!
Ten or twenty cat-people
won't accomplish anything!
The virus culture's been stalled.
Is Sawada resisting?
He won't cooperate
no matter what we do.
Even after you turned
him into a cat-person?
That just made his brain cat-like
too. He can't do his job now.
Then turn him back!
Take a good look, all of you.
This vaccine can
return your human forms.
If you want it, then
follow orders and work!
Understood?
Chief!
You fell right into
our trap, Jin Keisuke!
Set Up!
The X Rider!
Ridol Stick!
Cat Shoot!
X Kick!
Ridol Whip!
It's gone!
If this is what you want,
you'll have to face me!
Alright!
This way!
Make your move, X Rider!
Apollo Change!
Ridol Stick!
Apollo Cutter!
Everyone! This will turn
you back to normal!
Dad, mom!
-Kaori!
-Kaori, thank goodness!
I think I just
dreamt I was a cat...
Same here.
Me too.
The mysteries of life...
Hey, how about a coffee?
-Right!
Curses! I'll pay
him back for that!
GOD's horrific Cat Monster
Plan has been foiled.
But this has only deepened
Apollo Geist's hatred.
X Rider, don't let
your guard down!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD's monster Occultos plunges the citizens
of Tokyo into despair with his Ghost Plan.
Tachibana Toubeh and the gang infiltrate a
haunted house, where a dark trap awaits.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Corpses Call from the Haunted House!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider