Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Apollo Geist's Mad Bug Hell
What am I supposed to have
done!? Let me go! Spare me!
Apollo Geist! Thank goodness
you're here! Tell them to stop this!
I-I revived that legendary Ancient
Greek insect for GOD's sake!
Please spare me! Why don't you
say something, Apollo Geist?
Dr. Aota, GOD no longer needs you.
As such, you're to be disposed of.
How can you be so ruthless!?
What's that...?
The legendary insect of Ancient Greece
which you revived: the Mad Bug.
It's only fitting that the discoverer
experience its horrifying effect himself!
S-stop! Please stop!!
Bite!!
I'm an invincible warrior! An immortal warrior!
Kill! I must kill, kill, and kill again!!
That's right. All humans are your enemy!
To battle, warrior of Ancient Greece!
Apollo Geist.
Supreme Commander. The fossil of a Mad Bug has
been successfully revived in the twentieth century!
It's said that Ancient Greek soldiers allowed the insect
to bite them that they might overcome fear in war.
If they cause humans to hate and kill one
another, these insects will be a boon to GOD.
I agree. And its reproductive rate
is incredible; on par with a cockroach.
If they infest Japan, they'll
drive the people insane!
Then let us call it the Insane Japan Plan.
Apollo Geist, I probably don't need to tell you, but--
Understood. I won't allow the X Rider to interfere.
I'm praying for your success.
Incoming report for the Chief of Secret Police:
Dr. Aota strangled taxi driver to death, now
driving recklessly towards Kotsuyama Apartments.
Like clockwork.
Kill...
Alright, cross carefully!
Careful now...
Kill... All humans are my enemy!
Look out!
That taxi's out
of control! Hold it!
Quick!
Thank goodness you're alright!
Hey! Pull over!
Is he trying to kill me too!?
Darn it!
What are you doing!? Pull over!!
Get out!
You'd better explain yourself!
All humans are my enemy!
Is he really insane?
Don't overstep your position!
Shouldn't we silence Aota before
Jin Keisuke learns his secret?
Idiot! If you kill Aota now, Jin Keisuke
will know it was GOD's work.
Aota must die 'naturally.' Then Jin Keisuke won't
suspect a thing about the Insane Japan Plan!
Are you injured?
I'm fine.
We heard about the incident
from the crossing guard.
I see. He needs treatment, at any rate.
It seems something's wrong with his mind.
We'll call the police once we get him to hospital.
Thanks.
No wonder Apollo Geist is the
Chief of GOD's Secret Police.
He doesn't take any chances!
Our secret will be safe now.
Wait... I doubt he's that smart, but--
Jin Keisuke!
I thought your timing was too good to be true!
Now talk! What's GOD want with this man!?
Stop!!
Someone wanted to keep his cohort quiet.
If he regains consciousness, he
might tell me what GOD are up to.
You're quite something, Jin Keisuke!
Compliments don't seem
right coming from you.
But thanks to GOD, especially you,
I can't just trust other people anymore!
So, are you planning to
take that man with you?
Of course.
Then let me warn you he's
no longer of any use to GOD.
Will you still take him?
I'd still be myself, even without GOD!
How can I ignore a dying
man right in front of me?
And you'll fight for him?
If that's what you want.
Jin Keisuke! Apollo Geist isn't just
the Chief of GOD's Secret Police.
He's also known as GOD's Killing Machine!
Prepare to die!
Here I come!
Me too!
Apollo Change!
Set Up!
Try this! Apollo Shot!
You coward! Is this how you
fight a duel, Apollo Geist?
You've only just realised?
How naive you are, X Rider!
Ridol Stick!
X Kic--
The X Rider's finished.
Dolt! The X Rider went in
voluntarily. He's just buying time.
He'll show himself again
when he sees an opportunity.
What a dreadful foe...
Killing Aota right before my eyes...
That was my chance to defeat Apollo Geist...
Just what are GOD after, anyway?
One Mad Bug can breed
this much in half a day?
Its reproductive powers
are greater than I'd thought.
Take this one to the next target location.
Thank you--
Sir! Your change, your change!
Wait!
What a weird customer...
What the heck happened here!?
A monster cockroach!
What's going on?
Some people died in the coffee shop!
People died...?
Chief!
The police are holding the manager as a suspect!
The police?
Hey!
Hey! You can't just arrest me without
investigating! Is this police procedure!?
No Tokyo police station is
holding the chief. So where is he?
Is anyone there? I can prove
I'm innocent! Call Jin Keisuke!
Apollo Geist!
Officer, arrest this man!
He's a member of this secret organisation called
GOD! He's an evil thug with his eyes on Japan!
This is no time to laugh!!
How dense you are.
Haven't you realised it yet?
This is the Tokyo branch of GOD's
Secret Police! We police the police!
So it was a trick!
What do you want from me?
Tachibana... We will call
Jin Keisuke, as you requested.
But I have a couple of
questions for you first.
Does GOD's Secret Police honour
my right to remain silent?
We do, but... I wonder
how long you'll last?
Torturing me won't help!
I won't tell you anything!
Let's see how Tachibana likes pain!
Curses, where's the Mad Bug gone?
Apollo Geist will punish me if I don't find it!
...It might even mean execution!
Is that what you're looking for?
A paleobiology expert told me about Greece's
legendary Mad Bug, extinct for two thousand years.
That explains the runaway taxi,
and the murders that happened here.
Talk!! Where is GOD
breeding the Mad Bugs!?
I don't know!
Stop! Please, don't do it!!
I won't if you talk!
Alright! The Tokyo branch
of GOD's Secret Police...
Tachibana must be there too!
Awake, are we?
I won't talk!
We've plenty of time...
It's against my principles to rush things.
One of those bugs was in my shop!
And you've seen what they can do.
Their bite turns humans into killing machines.
How would you like to live as a killing machine?
There's no antidote for the Mad Bug's venom.
Or you could just answer my questions.
They're not difficult...
Will you listen?
What if you could never live as a normal
human again... Never see Jin Keisuke again...
But realise your dream of
becoming a grand prix racer?
It can stay a dream! I'd rather die!
Kill me! You won't make me talk!
You'll have your wish! Die in
madness, Tachibana Toubei!!
Keisuke, the rest is up to you...!
It won't be long now!
The Ridol Rope!
You got it!
X Rider, you're here!
X Rider!
How did you find this place!?
One of your own men told me all
about those horrible Mad Bugs!
That idiot...!
X Rider, I can't let you leave the Tokyo
branch of GOD's Secret Police alive!
Then the X Rider will destroy your Tokyo branch!
Apollo Change!
Chief!
You can't escape!
I'll wipe out the Mad Bugs!
Look out!!
The Mad Bugs...!
It's on fire!
X Rider...!
Your Tokyo branch
is burning! C'mon, quick!
Darn it! That X Rider...!
Curse you, X Rider!
Here I come!
Apollo Geist Cutter!
X Fatal Kick!!
Is this the end of Apollo Geist?
X Rider... I lost.
You were... a good rival,
and a worthy opponent.
One last handshake...?
Apollo Geist, it's a shame
we had to be enemies.
...Here.
Take my Arm Bomb and die with me!!
Darn! It won't come off!
Rider! X Rider...!
X Rider...
You're alright!?
X Rider!
Apollo Geist's timing was just a
little off because of his injuries.
He might have been my enemy,
but I have to respect how he died.
Apollo Geist of GOD's Secret Police is dead.
But no sooner has the X Rider overcome one crisis
than GOD's demonic hands reach for him again!
To be continued
Next episode
Two students are chased by a strange man, but
Jin Keisuke saves them from the Death God Kronos.
Keisuke infiltrates GOD's fortress, the Palace of Apollon. But what is this Palace of Apollon?
Look forward to the next episode:
"GOD's Secret Base! X Rider Sneaks in!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider