Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
GOD's Secret Base!
X Rider Sneaks in!!
Thank you so much.
Take care. Next?
Is that it for today?
No, one more.
Huh? How weird. I'm sure
there was still one left...
Wonder what this is?
What's wrong?
H-he was just here--
There's no one here now.
He left that behind.
I'll look after it. You can go home now.
Alright...
Dr. Kawakami, prepare to receive your orders.
Yes sir, GOD Supreme Commander.
The time has come for GOD to use
your outstanding surgical skills.
A representative of mine will escort you to
GOD
's base in Japan, the Palace of Apollon.
Be at Mukougaoka's underground
car park, space C-5, 1400 hours.
It would behoove you to be punctual.
GOD's base in Japan, the Palace of Apollon...
Calling Palace of Apollon. Supreme Commander's
orders have been relayed to Dr. Kawakami.
Destruction of tape confirmed.
Palace of Apollon communications room. Deliver
remaining doll to electronics engineer Dr. Miyamoto.
Roger. To Jouhoku College!
Jouhoku College
Sorry!
Watch where you're going!
You bumped into me too, y'know!
This place should do...
What's this!?
What kept you so long? I'm starving!
Chill out, chill out! I got cake, anpan, and even fruit! Just gimme a sec...
Hurry up...
-Here we go!
-My stomach's rumbling!
Huh?
What's this supposed to be!?
Don't tell me I can eat it!
You're such a dope!
The anpan turned into a doll...?
...I've got it! The guy who
bumped me in the corridor!
I'm so hungry I might die!
-The doll...!
-Creepy!
Orders from GOD's Supreme Commander. Escort
Dr. Miyamoto to the Palace of Apollon.
Be at Mukougaoka's underground car park,
space C-5, 1400 hours. Don't be late.
-It disappeared!
-What's going on!?
So you saw it? Now you must die!
-Run!
-Wait!!
-No way!
-Help!!
Hurry!
Somebody!
-Help!!
-Murderer!!
What's wrong?
-He wants to kill us!
-Help us!
Who wants to kill you?
-He was so creepy!
-His face was all grey!
Huh?
All quiet now, not even a dog.
But it's the truth!
-This weird doll was talking!
-He said we'd die for hearing it!
A talking doll? What did it say?
Something about orders from
GOD
's Supreme Commander!
Where was this doll?
On a park bench. There should
still be some pieces there!
Can you take me to it?
-But...
-Don't worry, I'll be with you. C'mon.
-Should we?
This is the place.
No trace of anything like a doll.
-It really was here!
-But it... exploded.
Looks like I'll have to shut those two up...
Thanks for waiting!
Wow, that looks good!
Some food at last!
I dunno how you can eat
after a scare like that, Chiko.
It's called having priorities.
Lunchtime!
Enjoy.
Look at that!
What's up?
It's him!!
You must die...
I am the Death God, Kronos.
Perish at my hands!!
Let's go!
I knew GOD were in on this!
Jin Keisuke... I'll kill you first!
Set Up!
X Rider!
Accursed X Rider! I, Kronos, shall take
your head back to the Palace of Apollon!!
Just what is this Palace of Apollon!?
Take this! Kronos Hell Scythe!!
Your life is mine!!
Cruiser!
Kronos! I'll see you at the Palace of Apollon!
Curses! He was at the threshold of death!
Here, some coffee should calm you two down.
Thank you!
Why do you think he wants us dead?
Don't worry, Keisuke will sort it out!
But... if he can't, then...
Then... No, he won't fail!
We'll cross that bridge when we come
to it. Don't let it get you down, Mako.
Half past one already...
Keisuke should be there soon.
Those two heard a secret order from GOD.
The place: Mukougaoka's
underground car park, space C-5.
The time: 1400 hours.
They're not coming.
It's possible they've changed plans...
Dr. Miyamoto?
Please get in.
This is Dr. Kawakami.
Introduce yourself.
Miyamoto, from Jouhoku College.
Good to know you.
Now then, I'll be escorting you
to the Palace of Apollon, but...
Its location must remain a
secret even to GOD's allies.
Put these on.
But we--
This is one of GOD's rules.
It'd be safer to do as he says.
It's been two hours... Just where
is this Palace of Apollon?
This is the Palace of Apollon's entrance.
You may remove your blindfolds.
It sure is foggy outside.
Where's the Palace...?
It produces a manmade fog to
prevent its being seen from above.
How thorough...
That's GOD for you!
The surprises are only just beginning...
The Palace of Apollon!
Follow me.
At ease.
After you, gentlemen.
This elevator descends ten metres every second.
In other words, we're a
hundred metres underground?
Even a nuclear blast wouldn't reach us.
Behold the Palace of Apollon!
Welcome, Drs. Kawakami and Miyamoto.
I am GOD's Supreme Commander.
The pleasure's ours, Supreme Commander.
Give them the tour of our Japanese
base, the Palace of Apollon.
Sir. Since the Supreme Commander wills
it, follow me and I'll show you around.
This first room is GOD's
Security Division's gymnasium.
The Security Division is comprised of champion-class
martial artists and athletes from around the world.
Second is GOD's Communication Department.
GOD's satellites orbiting Earth let us
transmit to and receive from any location.
Next...
This third room is Technology, the fourth
is Personnel, and fifth is Vehicles.
Sixth is GD, seventh is
Strategy, and eighth is Medical.
And this?
The Supreme Commander's office.
You mean... GOD's Supreme
Commander is in there?
Even I don't know who's within. Only the Chief of GOD's
Secret Police, Apollo Geist, has entered this door.
Apollo Geist!?
What do you think, doctors? Now that the tour is
over, will you work at the Palace of Apollon?
I never expected this. It's
like an underground fortress!
I couldn't have said it better.
You'll see something even more interesting
if you look through the window behind you.
Dr. Miyamoto should find it especially so.
I should...?
Who is that?
Please tell Dr. Miyamoto who you are.
Professor of electronics at Jouhoku College, and
GOD agent, Miyamoto Daigo. Code number 606.
He's lying! You've created a
duplicate of me! I am Miyamoto!
You can stop acting, Jin Keisuke.
So, you've seen through it?
Hold it!
GOD Supreme Commander! If you saw through my
disguise, why bring me to the Palace of Apollon?
GOD has bases of this class all over the world.
Jin Keisuke, what do you think
you can accomplish by yourself?
I can crush you! Even ants
bring down concrete walls.
Well said. GOD needs
courageous people like yourself.
I will give you the highest
position in GOD! Join us!
I expected more from GOD's Supreme Commander.
Can't you even understand one human's heart?
Do I really seem like that kind of person!?
Very well. Then sacrifice yourself
to GOD in the Palace of Apollon!
The wall's down. Bring it up!
The X Rider!
GOD made a mistake letting me go free!
Now to check out the Supreme Commander's office.
This is--!
The warriors of Ancient Greece
fought to the death in the colosseum!
X Rider, face the pride of GOD's fighters!
Ridol Stick!
Doctors, this is the individual
on whom I'd like you to operate.
What sort of operation is GOD's Supreme
Commander overseeing in the Palace of Apollon?
Beware, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
The X Rider has infiltrated the Palace of Apollon,
where the supposedly dead Apollo Geist awaits.
Meanwhile, GOD's monster Kerberos targets
Tachibana Toubei with his Fire Plan.
A showdown between Apollo Geist and the
X Rider, and the imminent Fire Plan.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Apollo Geist Strikes Back! X Rider, Beware!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider