Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
Why did Keisuke's beloved Ryouko side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
Kamen Rider X fights against the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Bizarre!? Little Earth,
Medium Earth, Big Earth
What kind of rhino beetle is that?
-A globe?
-Unbelievable!
Weird...
What the--!?
GOD calls me iron-armed Atlas!
It's a monster!
Die!
You get the same!
Heave-ho!
Seven energy surveyors were
killed on Mt. Kuromine?
If the Mt. Kuromine incident is GOD's
doing, things will only get worse.
We have to make contact with
Keisuke as soon as possible.
Y-you're right there, but...
Where could that fool
be at a time like this?
The survey investigation's
still scheduled for tomorrow.
No choice, I'll have to go.
You, Mr. Tachibana...?
What? You don't think
I can handle it?
Not at all! But perhaps
I'll accompany you.
Alright then, it's settled!
What's that noise?
Sounds like some kind of insect.
Look at that huge rhino beetle!
Rhino beetles at this time of year?
Kengo, leave it be.
-Dad!
-Kengo!
Run for it!
Why you little--!
Damn you!
Run!
Keisuke!
Hey, what kind of timing is this?
My apologies, chief!
You're Jin Keisuke, aren't you?
Yup.
You really are strong!
I'm Nakajou Kengo.
I'm Nakajou.
This is my son.
The name's Jin Keisuke,
nice to meet you!
Atlas!
This is GOD's Chief Commander.
Prepare for orders.
The survey team has finally reached this
mountain, and Jin Keisuke is with them.
Kill all of them except the president!
I pray for your success, Atlas.
Understood.
You saw me! You saw
the iron-armed Atlas!
-Run!
-Stop it!
Atlas Little Earth!
Get down!
-Hold it!
-Keisuke!
Alright, this way.
My sister has her reasons.
What kind of reasons?
I can't tell you.
But she and I are still in contact.
It was my sister who
asked me to protect you.
I can't just take your word for that.
Didn't Ryouko try to kill us just now?
Try to believe in my sister.
She's still your fiancee, Keisuke.
Hey, keep up!
Is this a rhinoceros beetle?
Keisuke, another huge rhino beetle!
Look out!!
Not again...
Don't let your guard down!
-Chief, get back! Get--
-Watch out!
Oh no!!
Kiriko!
Kiriko!!
Murdered...
Kiriko's been murdered by Ryouko...
Chief, I'm counting on you.
Set Up!
X Rider!
It's that accursed X Rider!
Atlas Big Earth!
Atlas Earth Throw!
Die, X Rider!
Awake, are we?
You're a lazy tyke.
W-what happened...?
You were out cold.
And the survey team...?
Mr. Nakajou postponed things.
What with Kiriko's death and all...
They'll set off again in
two or three days.
You've got to win this time.
Right.
Hi, glad to see you're better.
Thanks.
Where's Kengo?
Since we're setting off again tomorrow,
Kurata took him to buy provisions.
That's risky...
What if he attacks again?
Earthquake!
W-w-w-what are you!?
The iron-armed Atlas!
What's it to you?
W-what!?
You...!
It's the Rider!
Stop right there! If you don't,
I'll electrify this rope!
Earth Throw!
To me!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
This isn't over!
Odd...
Atlas was barely hurt.
Kengo, are you alright?
I'm good, it just surprised me!
Are you coming on the
survey tomorrow too?
Hold on a sec.
Strange... Is this
right right path?
Let's ask that old fellow.
Mister!
Look out!
Damn!
Kengo, are you alright?
Not a scratch!
President!
What's wrong, Keisuke?
The culprit's right there!
But the arrows were coming
from a different direction...
She tried to kill Kengo! Ex-girlfriend or not,
how can you cover for a murderer?
Ryouko, wait!
Wait, Ryouko!
Ryouko...?
Keisuke, don't ask me
about this right now.
Believe me... that there will be a day
when we look back on this and laugh.
Run. Hurry.
Did Jin Keisuke get away?
It was my fault, my apologies.
Are those tears, Ryouko?
No, I don't cry.
But you hid your sister Kiriko
from us... Could it be, you...?
I won't acknowledge such disrespect.
My loyalty to GOD is unquestionable.
Weird, this whole thing
smells fishy to me.
President, it doesn't look
like we're getting anywhere.
Yeah...
There's the old man who
was making charcoal!
That's strange, he shouldn't have
been able to get here ahead of us.
I'll ask him the way.
Kengo, wait!
Quit it!
Oh no!
These arrows...
Was it you who killed Kiriko?
Finally figured it out, Jin Keisuke?
Atlas, I'm the one you want.
Keisuke!
Kengo!
Mr. Nakajou, stay back!
Set Up!
Damn you!
Drop dead!
Ridol Whip!
Oh no! Mr. Nakajou, Kengo's--!
Kengo!!
How'd you like it if I took
this brat's life right here?
Kengo!
This won't be your everyday sneeze.
Help me!
Ryouko!
Kengo...
Ryouko, hang in there!
Keisuke...
Is that... an Interpol ID badge?
So that's it!
Ryouko, are you--?
I'm... an investigator
fighting against GOD...
I became your father's assistant...
to infiltrate their organisation...
You're in no shape to talk now!
I was going to explain to
Kiriko once it was settled...
Kiriko must have... hated me...
That's not true!
I'm sure Kiriko understood!
Keisuke, Atlas' weakness is...
his left... shoulder...
Ryouko!
Get away!
R-Ryouko?
I'm a cyborg!
A cyborg...?
Everyone who swears loyalty to GOD...
is implanted with a self-destruct device...
You mean you're--?
Get away... Traitors can't
escape GOD's Chief Commander...
Ryouko!!!
Ryouko...
You won't have died in vain.
Atlas' weakness is his left shoulder...
I swear I'll defeat him!
Cruiser Jump!
Cruiser Big Turn!
Damn you!
Ridol Stick!
Feeble!
Atlas Great Earthquake!
Atlas' weakness is...
his left... shoulder...
X Kick!!
Curses!
Overcoming the death of his father, of
Kiriko, and now of his beloved Ryouko.
But Jin Keisuke will never write the word
"sadness" in his diary. Keisuke must fight on.
What conspiracy is the huge GOD Agency plotting?
Who is the unseen GOD Chief Commander?
And where does this suspicious
new creature's allegiance lie?
To be continued
Next episode
Hundreds of villagers suddenly disappear,
and Keisuke meets an amnesiac girl named Miki.
Machinegun bullets fly over Keisuke's head!
Just then, the young
hero Apollo Geist appears.
Look forward to the next episode:
"X Rider's Finisher Training"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider