Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Ghouls!? Mysterious Snake-People Appear!!
You'll feed my snakes well!
Where'd that come from?
You trying to get yourself killed!?
Hey, pal...
What's wrong?
Hey!
I think someone's following us...
There's no one there!
Don't scare me like that! Did we come
here to photograph the ghost, or not?
Well?
A snake!!
Leave if you want, but
Takashi's counting on me!
I promised I'd get
him a photo of the ghost!
Man, I'm glad I don't
have a little brother...
Closed
Chief!
Find anything?
Yeah. Turns out the victim
was quite the athlete.
An obvious target for GOD.
That blasted ghost...
This settles it, at least.
The weird disappearances over the
past three months must be GOD's work.
And look at this, chief.
What's this?
The Tokyo suburbs are panicking
over this ghost business.
The locals are too scared to
even set one foot in this spot.
Doesn't that smell fishy to you,
chief? In this day and age?
You think GOD's got
a secret base there?
Yeah.
Just be careful. You're up
against a GOD monster.
Right.
Keisuke, don't you want a coffee?
-No thanks, I'm good.
-But we just made some!
Here you g--
Just like a ghost!
Who's there? Come on out!
Do you think you can
trespass here and live?
Honda! Hey!
Excuse me! Please
open this gate!
Whatever's the matter?
A monster's after me!
What a peculiar day... I just let
someone in who said the same thing.
Really? Who?
He's inside. Come on in...
There he is.
H-Honda!
You're alive!
Someone save me!
Salamandra...
How goes your experiment to create snake-
people with transfusions of your blood?
Sir, it's almost complete.
Excellent. Your snake-people's fangs will transform more humans...
...and soon all of Japan's
citizens will be snake-people!
Here you go, my precious
babies! Feeding time...
Come on, eat up! Eat up!
You big boys too, eat your fill!
What a cutie...
Yes, you're cute too...
Mangrove snake! How
are you feeling today?
What's wrong with them...?
You...!
These marvellous snake-people
were born from my own blood!
I brought you here that
you might join them!
And now for the injection...
A demon...! There's a demon
here! So scared... Help me...!
Mad... He's been driven
totally mad by fear.
I knew there was something
about this cemetery.
Katsumura, where's my
brother? What happened!?
Scared... Help me! So scared...
Big brother...
Hey, you can't go in there!
But my brother's--
No! There's something in this
graveyard science can't explain...
You're not going!
-But my brother--
-I said no!
Leave this place, foolish
humans! Leave at once!
Disobey and my curse will
only take more lives!
-Run!!
-Run for it!
Hold it!
Who're you?
I'm Jin Keisuke, a
friend of the X Rider.
X Rider's friend...?
The X Rider will save your brother.
You should go home where it's safe.
Trust me. Alright?
C'mon, run!
So you're GOD's new monster!
My name is Salamandra!
Die, Jin Keisuke!
Turn to stone!
Set Up!
X Rider!
The X Rider...
Here I come--
A mirror!
Now's my chance!
The X Rider's dead!
Apollo Geist! Are you
trying to kill me too!?
All that matters is that he dies!
What!?
Come now, don't lose your
head. My goal is simple:
To defeat the X Rider.
Now, retrieve his corpse!
I'm going to tear it to shreds!
The X Rider died...
trying to save my brother!
Honda's actor also fell victim to a snake monster
in Kamen Rider Amazon. Talk about typecasting!
That Salamandra's really something...
But what was it that hurt her back there?
A mirror!
That's it! She can't
stand her own reflection!
Now I know her weakness,
the rest is simple.
I just need one of
my bike's mirrors...
Didn't the X Rider fall right here?
I don't see a trace of him...
Great...
The X Rider's dead... But don't
worry big brother, I'll save you!
There's a wall...
Someone in there must
know where he is.
Excuse me!
Is anyone here?
Who might you be?
I'm looking for my big
brother. Have you seen him?
To think some food would
just bring itself to me...
Come, come...
Let me out! Let me out!
Where'd Jin Keisuke go?
Talk! Where's Salamandra's base?
Talk!
A python!
A scorpion!
Oh, just a tortoise...
You've gotta help me!
Big brother!
What are you--!? Let go!
Do it! Turn this child
into a snake-person!
No way! Help me!
Let go! What are you doing!?
After him!
X Rider, I'll let you
test my snake-people!
Don't panic...
-Takashi, jump in!
-Right!
A mirror of water!
The pain...! Help me!!
Don't come out until
it's over, alright?
Ridol Stick!
This is the end, X Rider!
Join my snake-people!
Komodo dragon, eat the X Rider!
The pain...!
Big brother!
Let's see how you handle
Salamandra's attack!
A mirror!
Not a mirror!!
Now!
X Kick!
-I'm back to normal!
-Me too!
Big brother!
-Takashi!
-Big brother!
The X Rider foiled Salamandra's plot and
restored the snake-people to normal.
But his fight never ends. Go
for it, Kamen Rider X!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD revives its past monsters and sends them after the
X Rider, led by their Chief of Secret Police Apollo Geist.
Faced with such overwhelming odds,
the X Rider finds himself in a crisis.
Look forward to the next episode:
"Apollo Geist's Final All-Out Attack!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider