Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
But Nanbara escaped GOD and tore the blueprints
into nine pieces to entrust to his old colleagues.
GOD has stolen one of the pieces,
and the X Rider holds two.
Thus does a deadly race for the
remaining six pieces begin!
Hellish Dictator
Starfish Hitler!!
Tokyo International Airport
International Departures
At last, the fourth blueprint
piece is here from America...
They say this Dr. Egawa's the
biggest physicist in the world.
Ok chief, let's put the plan into action.
Got it.
They're coming out!
Right! Time to do our thing!
Doctor!
-Welcome!
Excuse me, are you Dr. Egawa from
the United College of Technology?
That's right.
We'll take you to the
hotel for the interview.
The car's ready, so...
Alright, lead the way.
They totally blanked us!
Here you go.
Thank you.
How rude can you get?
Right? And after we were so nice!
You gotta be Chiko and Mako!
Who is this guy?
Water...?
...Is that what I think it is?
Who are you!?
Starfish Hitler!
A pleasure to meet you, Dr. Egawa.
I am Starfish Hitler,
of GOD's Villain Army!
Starfish Hitler...?
My secret police identified you, a student of Dr.
Nanbara, as having received a blueprint in the USA.
And now we're going to take you
somewhere more comfortable. Hurry!
Starfish Hitler!
Keisuke, we were right. Those
journalists are with GOD!
Roger! I'm on their tail now!
Führer! There's a motorbike after us!
What? Jin Keisuke, is it?
Never mind, keep going!
Where'd they go?
The mic's gone!
The doctor must've...
Chief, try to track our scientist
couple by their mic's wavelength!
Ok!
Starfish Hitler!
King Dark, may I introduce the United College
of Technology's Dr. Egawa and his wife.
I'd expect no less from the
evil dictator Starfish Hitler...
...is what I'd like to be saying, you fool!!
That is not Dr. Egawa or his wife!
They obviously changed places
with these impostors in America!
Can it be...?
Hurry up and find the genuine article!
Bring me that blueprint!
Unless you'd rather be...
O-of course, sir! I shan't fail!
Keisuke's substitution plan
worked great, didn't it, boss?
Yeah, it sure did. But the doctor
and his wife must be exhausted!
Not at all! It was almost fun!
But will our two impostors be alright?
-Yeah, Keisuke's gone after them.
-They'll be fine!
Stop!
Begin the torture!
Stop! Please stop!!
More voltage!
Stop!!
Release her. We don't want her dead.
Well? Do you feel like talking yet?
I am the reincarnation of Hitler, whose
cruelty caused the world to tremble!
I have ways of making you talk...
We're just hippies!
All I know is that I was asked
to stand in for Dr. Egawa!
How bold you are, daring to challenge GOD!
He said we should run if you
found out! That's what he said!
Don't... betray them! How could
you... live with yourself!?
Enough! Do you want to die!?
Just answer one question:
Where is the real Dr. Egawa?
I don't know all the details, but he's
hiding somewhere at the Manazuru coast...
The Manazuru coast, eh?
Cursed Jin Keisuke! He's found us!
A starfish in a tree...?
Starfish Hitler!
There you are, GOD monster!
Indeed, I am the hellish dictator of
GOD
's Villain Army: Starfish Hitler!
Fire!
Set Up!
Ridol Rope!
Take him!
Starfish Rocket!
Ridol Stick!
Not bad, X Rider. But I haven't
the time to waste with you!
Hold it! Where's the couple you
kidnapped from the airport?
That's for you to figure out yourself.
Darn it!
Won't budge...
But it's definitely hiding something.
...That's it!
Ridol Whip!
Electric Power!
Looks like an entrance to me.
I'm too late!
Dummies...?
Darn it...
"X Rider, your trick was a daring one. I will certainly repay you in kind."
--Starfish Hitler
A time bomb!
Darling, it's been so long
since we relaxed like this.
Maybe taking the odd sunbathing
break from research isn't too bad...
-It's enough to make you forget about GOD!
-But... should we be doing this?
Well, we're not just lazing
around! We're hiding from GOD!
Speaking of... The blueprint's safe, isn't it?
I get it! It's in there, huh?
Alright then!
We've found them... and this time
they won't fool us! Begin offensive!
Starfish Hitler!
Who's there?
Room service!
I have your food.
Bring it in.
Where are the Egawas?
-They went to their room for dinner.
-Oh, ok.
Did you see something?
No sign of GOD yet.
But... Keisuke's kind of late...
-Keisuke!
What in the world happened!?
I screwed up. There was a time bomb...
More importantly, are the Egawas safe?
Yeah, they're fine. Just
went back to their room.
Really? That's a relief...
What about our two impostors?
They're in hospital, critical condition.
-At least they're alive...
-Right.
What a day... Let's make the most of this!
Well said!
Here you go...
-To our health!
-Cheers!
Alright... Shall we eat?
Th-the starfish--!
Starfish Hitler!
You're one of GOD's monsters!
Quite right! I am the hellish dictator of
GOD
's Villain Army: Starfish Hitler!
Your knowledge of us makes things
simpler. Give me the blueprint!
Fools!
That's...!
Darling!
Oh no!
You're a persistent one, Jin Keisuke!
Shut up!
Hand over that bracelet!
Take it if you can.
-You alright?
-The blueprint is ours. Retreat!
-Hold it!!
-Keisuke, you can't fight in your condition!
Chief... chief, please let me go! Who
knows what might happen if they get away?
...Alright. But I'm coming too.
Attack!
Set Up!
You want more, X Rider?
Go, Starfish Rocket!
Take him!
Ridol Whip!
Blitz Starfish!
How does that feel, Rider?
Hitler's finishing move!
Whirling Hell!!
X Rider!! Don't lose! You can't lose!
Here I come!
X Kick!
X Rider... I won't let you
get this blueprint piece...
It will... explode with me!
Starfish... Hitler...!
I don't think so!
The bracelet with the blueprint...
Chief!
-Chief...
-Keisuke!
You did it!
Now we've got three... But
we have to find the other six!
The X Rider narrowly brought down
the hellish dictator Starfish Hitler.
But King Dark won't stop
there. What's coming next?
Hang in there, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
Well, next week is a Kamen Rider Special Edition
featuring Kamen Riders #1, #2, V3, Riderman, and X...
...in mortal combat with the monsters of
Shocker, GelShocker and Deathtron!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Special Edition - The 5 Riders in Full Force!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider