Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
But Nanbara escaped GOD and tore the blueprints
into nine pieces to entrust to his old colleagues.
GOD has one stolen one of the pieces,
and the X Rider holds another.
Thus does a deadly race for the
remaining seven pieces begin!
Mysterious Phantom Thief
Rhino Beetle Lupin!!
Doumoto Theoretical Physics Laboratory
Ok, now for a slider!
Uh-oh!
We're sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Actually, why don't you come
in? I'll give you something!
Really?
Go on, make yourselves at home.
What are your names?
-I'm Norio!
-Takashi!
Norio and Takashi, is it? Well, eat up!
-Ok, thanks!
-Thank you!
Looks like they're out...
This is a piece of the blueprints for Dr. Nanbara's
energy-generating invention, the RS Device.
Nanbara... To think you'd trust
me enough to send me this...
But my cancer hasn't given me long left.
I'm just a lonely old nobody
with no wife or children...
I've no choice but to
do something drastic.
Rhino Beetle Lupin, how goes the search for the
other seven pieces of Dr. Nanbara's blueprints?
Sir, one of my beetles is gathering
information as we speak.
I feel for these boys, but...
mankind must know peace.
If I can use my Alpha Ray to transfer
this blueprint onto their backs...
...I don't mind being remembered
as a worthess person.
Images burnt in by the Alpha Ray can
only be seen with a special filter.
Chief, I found a clue at last!
-Really?
-Yeah, take a look.
That's Dr. Nanbara at a science convention.
This is one old picture...
It was taken twenty years ago.
This is the guy who caught my eye.
See how close he is to Dr. Nanbara?
This is Dr. Nanbara's mentor, Dr. Doumoto.
He respected him more than anyone.
-The experimental physicist?
-Right.
There's definitely a chance this
Doumoto might know something...
You don't think--?
What have you learned,
Rhino Beetle Lupin?
Sir, my intelligence has identified an individual
who likely has one of the blueprint pieces.
My, my! You truly are the incarnation of
France's famed phantom thief, Arsène Lupin!
And what is this person's name?
Dr. Doumoto!
Now nobody knows where this blueprint is...
Alright boys, time to get up.
Come on, rise and shine.
Huh? Guess I fell asleep...
Me too...
That's what you get for
eating right after you play!
Go on, take all the
sweets you can carry.
-Thank you!
Take care of yourselves, won't you?
-Ok!
-Bye!
A rhinoceros beetle?
It must have followed those boys in...
W-what the--? Who are you!?
Rhino Beetle Lupin,
of GOD's Villain Army!
A thief?
If you know what I want, then you must
have received a blueprint from Nanbara!
I don't know what you
mean. What blueprint?
Don't play the fool!
Search the place!
This task is simplicity itself for one
named after the infamous Lupin.
Only a fool underestimates Lupin...
There!
You see? A letter from Nanbara.
The blueprint isn't here!
Out with it! Where is the blueprint?
You won't talk...?
Hold it!!
I thought I'd find you
here, GOD! Let him go!
There you are, Jin Keisuke!
Set Up!
Ridol Whip!
Adieu, X Rider!
Running away, are you!? ...No,
I need to check on Dr. Doumoto!
My life is over... Please... don't
let them get that blueprint...
I won't. But where is it?
The blueprint... the blueprint is...
Please hold on! Where is the blueprint?
I... put it...
Doctor! Doctor!!
I took too long...
When did you sneak in!?
Now Doumoto can tell neither
of us where the blueprint is.
All that remains is a battle
of wits to find it first...
Darn it!
Where in the world could it be?
A kid's glove...
But I thought Dr. Doumoto
didn't have any family?
Norio
Maybe this Norio knows something!
-Here it comes!
-Ok!
Go for it!
Hey! Does this belong to any of
you? I got it from Mr. Doumoto!
What is it?
Oh, that's my glove!
-It's yours?
-It says 'Norio'! That's me!
Really? Great, here you go.
Thanks!
You visited Mr. Doumoto, then?
Ahuh. He gave me and Takashi
tea and sweets this morning.
Hey, did Dr. Doumoto give
you two anything else?
No...
Ok... So, where's Takashi?
He should be at the pool over there.
That so? Thanks.
Hey, there's a rhino beetle
on Norio's shoulder!
A monster!
Begin!
It hurts! It hurts...!
Think carefully, boy! Did anything
strange happen at Doumoto's home?
No...! I told you...!
Don't lie to me...
-It hurts...
-Then think harder.
Wait, maybe...!
You remembered? Out with it!
We fell asleep... right
after he gave us sweets...
Maybe... something happened then!
Fool! Why didn't
you say so sooner!?
-Keisuke!
-We're closed for the day, so--
Did you come for a swim, Keisuke?
No, I'm looking for a kid...
A kid?
Did something happen?
Yeah... No time to explain now.
-Jeez, he thinks we're so dumb!
-Let's go!
You're Takashi, right?
-That's right...
-I've got something to ask you.
You had sweets at Mr.
Doumoto's house, right?
Yeah... and then we fell asleep.
You fell asleep? Anything strange happen?
No, nothing...
...Looks like I've hit a dead end.
Huh?
Hey, hey, it looks like there's
something drawn on his back!
A blueprint!
I get it... Dr. Doumoto used some
sort of ray to tattoo it there!
The sun's UV rays must
have uncovered it!
Quick, get in the water. We
can't let anyone else see it.
Weird... He still hasn't come up.
Something's wrong.
I've taken the boy. Nothing personal.
--Rhino Beetle Lupin
No!
Jin Keisuke! The child is mine!
Rhino Beetle Lupin!
You won't get away!
Try this on for size, Jin Keisuke!
Set Up!
Cruiser Jump!
Hand him over, Rhino Beetle Lupin!
X Rider!
What a stubborn fellow! But
I've no time for you right now...
Rhino Beetle Smokescreen!
They're gone!
Blast!
-It burns!
Take it off!!
Almost there... Keep the heat on them!
Quick, take a picture.
Fool...! Give me the film!
-I'll take this!
-How dare you!?
-Just cut them down!
-I've had enough of this! Get him!!
Rider!
-Chief! The kids!
-Gotcha!
Go on, run for it!
Rhino Beetle Lupin!
Come on...
Ridol Whip!
You fool, X Rider!
X Rider, try my Guillotine
Hat on for size!
X Kick!
Now you try it on!
This blueprint's mine,
Rhino Beetle Lupin!
So, he was all talk...
Who will make up for Rhino
Beetle Lupin's failure?
Starfish Hitler!
Boss, are the kids stuck
with those blueprints now?
No, don't worry about that!
Keisuke told me something called a 'Sigma
Ray' can rub out Dr. Doumoto's Alpha Ray.
Hey! Your backs are blueprint-free!
He's right, it's gone!
The blueprints that were on these boys'
backs are now in Keisuke's hands...
But King Dark's Villain Army is
already making its next move.
Don't give up, Keisuke - Kamen Rider X!
To be continued
Next episode
GOD's Starfish Hitler finds a scientist couple with
a blueprint piece, but learns they're impostors.
Starfish Hitler's demonic hands reach for the coastal
hotel where Toubei is guarding the real couple!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Hellish Dictator Starfish Hitler!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider