Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Jin Keisuke, who was killed by the
great organization GOD along with his father...
...revived as Kamen Rider X, thanks to his father.
Why did Keisuke's lover, Ryouko, side with GOD?
And who is Kiriko?
The one who fights against the mysterious GOD, Kamen Rider X!
The Japanese Islands Fragmentation Plan!
Idiot! Be careful! There's ammunition inside!
It's gonna explode! Run!
Bus incident in Onigamizaki.
All the passengers including the driver were killed.
Police are investigating, huh?
Put the ammunition in the underground room!
It's GOD General Commander.
Bullman Minotaur.
It seems you've successfully carried the ammunition.
We'll cause a civil war in Japan with these weapons!
Roger.
Father!
Mother!
Father! Mother!
Watch out!
Hey. Won't you tell me why you were there all alone?
I don't have a father and mother.
They both died in the bus accident that happened the day before yesterday.
Mother! Father!
Young man!
Okay, here it is.
Tachibana!
Sit here.
This girl...
She lost her parents in that accident, and now she's alone.
A pity.
Alright, fine.
I'll be responsible for her.
I'm glad.
Sachiko, this man is a great person.
He'll take good care of you.
Sachiko, huh?
Here.
I...
Have a lot of friends who are just about your age.
You'll be able to get along with them.
And you won't be lonely.
This man right here...
He lost his father too, and yet he's still bright and happy!
You're not lonely now, are you?
Nope!
By the way, that incident seems really strange.
They say the bus fell, right?
Maybe G.O.D is behind it.
I think so too.
I'm trying to find some evidence, but...
What's wrong?
Please look after the girl!
Set Up!
Ridol Whip!
Kamen Rider X!
Cruiser!
Who the hell are you?!
I am one of G.O.D's cyborgs...
Oxman Minotaur!
Damn it...
Damn!
I knew it was Ryouko...
Ridol Stick!
X Rider, remember this!
I'll be back!
Alright, you look great.
Take care.
Yes!
I'm off!
Okay. Come back as soon as possible!
Right!
The child is heading for the graves.
Father, Mother.
I'm being taken care of by an old man, and a kind young man.
I'm still lonely, but I'll do my best to live life fully.
Please go to heaven without worrying about me.
She's so late...
What happened?
Tachibana.
I was just attacked by G.O.D, near where that accident happened.
It was them after all.
Really?
Yes.
But he ran away, so I don't know where their base is.
I knew it...
So, is the girl okay?
Well, about that...
She said she was putting flowers on her parents' grave, but she hasn't returned yet.
I'm worried.
Eh?
I'm certain she did come here.
Where did she go?
Hey! Sachiko!
Tachibana!
I think I heard a girl's scream coming from over there.
I couldn't hear anything.
Well, my ears are special. Let's go.
Oh, hey!
This is a ribbon that I bought for her!
Oh?
You're...!
Seems you've fallen into my trap.
Just look.
Sachiko!
Don't move.
Move, and the girl will die!
You cowards!
You would even threaten children?
Surrender!
Hey, tie them up.
This is it, Jin Keisuke
Now, you can't turn into Rider X anymore.
What?!
I'm exacting my revenge, as promised.
Hey, put them on the truck!
Load these weapons onto the truck.
I need these weapons for my grand plan.
Wars will be started throughout Japan.
I wanted to show you...
But your lives will end before then.
G.O.D, why you...
Alright, we'll set this place to explode soon.
Set up the bomb's timer.
It'll explode in three minutes.
May you happily move on to the next world together.
Wait! I don't care what you do to me, just let the other two live!
Afraid not.
Hey! At least let the little girl live, please!
To expect sympathy from G.O.D, you really are naive.
Damn you!
Excuse us.
The next world will be much happier.
Ah, it fell off!
But am I really going to die?
What are you saying? Don't give up!
Hey! Can't we do something?!
I want to save the girl, at least!
I understand!
But we can't do anything with our hands bound like this!
Pops! Pops!
Pray. Pray to the God of Justice.
What are you doing?!
Kiriko!
Thank you.
Set Up!
Thank goodness!
Thank you, Kiriko.
For rescuing us.
X Rider, hurry and pursue them.
That is your duty.
Cruiser!
Cruiser Jump!
Cruiser Great Spin!
X Rider!
Rider X!
Damn you, you're still alive?!
As long as GOD exists, I won't die!
Damn you, Rider X!
This time, I'll defeat you!
X Kick!
The plan to bring weapons into Japan, and turn it into a battlefield, were thwarted by X Rider.
However, what's the next target?
Go, fight! Kamen Rider X of justice!
To be continued
Next episode
Look forward to the next episode:
"The Terrifying Human Genius Plan!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider