Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
X Rider's Finisher Training
Run!!
Hurry, hurry!!
Quick!!
Run for it!!
This way!
What was that?!
No hunting
Idiots! Did you think
you could outrun me?
You're nothing but GOD's test subjects.
Dream Virus, away!
Starting now, you'll work
for GOD as human robots.
Alright, now go back to your daily
lives until further orders.
Did I miss one?
After them! Hunt them down!
I'm scared, mom!
Miki, you have to go on alone!
No!
Come on!
Please let her be alright...
Woman, are you the only one who escaped?
If you don't want to speak,
I'll just have to make you!
Daughter Miki... Bottom of cliff...
Find her!
Who's there? Come out!
Over there!
You're wasting your time searching!
Curses!
Who the heck are you?
A friend of the X Rider?
Time to take out the trash!
Achilles, they should call
you the Instant Kettle.
Instant Kettle?
What do you mean?
You heat up in no time.
That's what I mean.
That's your weakness, Achilles!
Curse you!
Hold it!
Who is that guy!? After him!
Achilles, how is the Dream Virus taking?
The experiment's a total
success, Supreme Commander.
The Dream Virus will be ready
for mass-production in three days.
You must keep it hidden until then.
In particular, don't take your
eyes off the X Rider. That is all.
That's right...
There's still one loose end left.
We have to find that missing
girl and shut her up.
How's my time, chief?
Not bad at all.
Let's give it one more lap!
Alright.
Get going!
It's my dream to train
a Grand Prix racer.
Hongou Takeshi, Ichimonji Hayato,
Kazami Shirou...
Any of those three could
have been champion for sure.
But they've scattered across the
world to protect justice and peace.
As for Jin Keisuke...
He has the potential to be even better.
But he has his own evils to fight...
Look out!!
Are you alright?
Hang in there!
What's up, Keisuke?
Something happen?
This girl suddenly walked
out in front of me!
She did!?
Hey, little lady!
Little lady?
Looks like she's had a terrible shock.
Might even have lost her memory.
We should get her to a hospital quick.
Right.
Emergency transmission: Missing girl
found. Jin Keisuke's got her.
Chief, I'll draw them off!
Gotcha!
Jin Keisuke, you die today...
with that girl you saved!
What? You're not just after me?
This is bad!
Commence strategy!
Chief!!
Tachibana Toubei, hand over
the girl if you want to live.
Who's there!?
A GOD monster!
This car's going sixty!
What are you doing at the window!?
My feet can keep up with a jet.
The name's Achilles!
That so?
Achilles my foot!
You can't escape!
Try chasing this!
You again!
Darn...
Set Up!
X Rider!
Ridol Rope!
Tachibana Toubei, it's no
use running. Join GOD!
What!?
Ridol Stick!
You saved me, X Rider!
So you're here, X Rider?
One of GOD's monsters!
And they named me Achilles!
Ran off, did he?
Chief, GOD's after this girl.
She must know some secret of theirs.
We've got to help her
regain her memory, and soon.
How dare you interfere!?
I know you're hiding up there!
Who are you? You with GOD?
Apollo Geist.
Apollo Geist...?
Don't forget your mission, Achilles.
What is your primary objective?
Isn't it to turn all Japan's people
into robots with the Dream Virus?
If you'd lost to the
X Rider just now, then what?
You think I'd lose to him!?
Idiot!
Your blood goes to your head
too fast. That's your weakness.
Now where have I heard that before...?
Calm yourself. Then dispose
of that girl called Miki.
We ask this girl's parents, relatives, or
anyone who knows her to come forward.
Contact Coffee Shop COL
in Ikuta, Tama Ward.
Once again, that's Ikuta, Tama Ward--
There's broadcasts like
that on the TV and radio.
Someone's bound to come asking about you.
Then you'll remember everything you forgot.
Anything?
This dart that nearly hit you
is coated with a weird liquid.
I'm having it analysed now.
Weird liquid...?
Hey, now...
What's wrong?
So this dart's the cause.
A dart like that gave her the shock?
Keisuke, give her a closer look!
She might remember something!
No... We should play it safe
until she calms down.
C'mon, stop crying. It's alright.
Um, excuse me...
Miki! Miki, what a relief!
Wh-who might you be!?
Are you her father?
Excuse me.
Thank you for saving her.
I was driving Miki, turned away
for a second, and she was gone!
Thank you so much.
Thank you for looking after her.
Drive safely.
You fool, Jin Keisuke...
I was right in front of you.
Now... Let's give this girl the
same treatment as her mother.
I'm scared! Help, mom!
Now, now, settle down.
I'm your dad.
No! You're not my dad!
You're the monster who hurt the villagers!
So you've regained your memory?
You'll join your mother and the rest!
Achilles!
I see you've given
up the daddy act.
Why, you!
It was a bit of a risk...
But Miki's regained her
memory thanks to you!
Cruiser!!
C'mon Miki, Quick!
Don't lose them!
Good girl, Miki.
Hide somewhere safe.
Ok!
Cruiser Big Turn!
Who are you?
Don't interfere, Apollo Geist!
I'm not interfering!
Fight, Achilles!
This is bad! Miki might--
Ridol Stick!
You'll fall to Achilles!
Help!
Curse you...
Why are you dawdling?
Hurry up and kill him!
X Kick!!
Alright... Withdraw.
Three days until
Operation: Dream Virus.
Cursed X Rider...
Let's see you recover by then!
Hey!
What happened, Keisuke?
Hang in there!
I failed...
GOD took Miki away
right in front of me...
I couldn't lift a finger...
So, you lost?
What's the point of
being the X Rider!?
I'm ashamed of myself...
I see...
You've tasted failure for
the first time in your life.
What should I do?
Chief... Will you tell me?
The three Kamen Riders
who came before me...
What did they do
at times like this!?
Those men are outstanding
heroes of justice.
They'd fail, and fail again,
and stand up again every time.
Stand up...?
Keisuke!
Standing up after every loss
is what makes a Kamen Rider!
And I'm... I'm still
Kamen Rider X...
But I can't use their
title if I just complain...
I'll do it...
I can do it, Chief!
That's the spirit!
I helped Riders #1, #2, and V3
out of a few pinches too.
The Double Punch,
the Midair Kick...
They mastered new finishing moves
by risking their lives in training!
Keisuke, it's time for the X Rider
to start his Finisher Training!
Chief... I'll do it!
You can count on me!
That's what makes you the X Rider!
Training starts now!
This fires blanks, but they'll
still leave a mark! Got it?
Ready!
Begin!
Too slow! You're a sitting
duck in midair!
What's all this then?
Let me try again!
This is the fate of a Kamen Rider.
Good luck, X Rider.
The X Rider had been overwhelmed by
Apollo Geist and Achilles' attack.
Would this training yield
a new finishing move?
GOD's plan to turn the Japanese
into robots will soon unfold.
To be continued
Next episode
X has started training to
develop a new finishing move.
The training is harsh and strict.
But he'll complete it with
Tachibana Toubei's advice.
Next week, you'll see
the X Rider's new finisher.
Look forward to the next episode:
"GOD Secret Police! Apollo Geist!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider