Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Kidnap the Psychic Girl!
Today we've invited the famous psychic girl
Kawamura Keiko and her mother to the studio.
Shocking Hour
Wondrous ESP
Keiko is the daughter of
parapsychologist Dr. Kawamura.
She'll show us her mystical powers, from seeing inside
this box to bending hard spoons with telekinesis.
This looks interesting!
Now, our audience already know the answer, but...
Keiko, can you tell us what's inside this box?
A panda teddy.
She got it!
I'm sure the studio audience and folks
watching at home must be surprised!
Next, she'll bend this spoon with her telekinesis.
Is something the matter?
She says she can't do it...
Why not?
You see... Someone in this studio is
generating negative thought waves.
Someone's generating negative thought waves?
I can do it now.
She really bent it!
Alrighty...
Let's give it a try!
That's not how you do it! I'll show you.
Twist!
Forward and back!
Who are you?
I'm Sekiguchi Jun!
Beastman Chimera, prepare for orders.
Yes, GOD Supreme Commander.
Kawamura Keiko's father, Dr. Kawamura,
is the world's leading ESP researcher.
Hold Keiko hostage, and force Dr. Kawamura
into assisting our own ESP development.
Sir!
The chimera is a creature from Greek mythology.
This terrible monster had the heads of a lion and
goat, the tail of a dragon, and could breathe fire.
My gosh, look at them!
Experimenting with telekinesis, are we?
Hey, Kawamura Keiko and Sekiguchi Jun's
telekinesis is something special!
Take a look!
Well now, you're as good as they say!
Right? It's amazing, a human having such an ability!
...Yeah...
But if it ever fell into the wrong hands...
Be careful that GOD don't set their sights on you.
Of course, of course! Right?
Keiko, is something wrong?
Mama, I'm scared.
Whatever of?
Him.
That's the chauffeur from the television
station. You mustn't be so rude.
Are you scared, little lady?
I'm so sorry. She's just tired from appearing
on television. Please don't mind her.
Now that's a psychic for you...
Stop the car, please.
Mama!
You have my wife and child?
What's the meaning of this?
It's just as I said.
In short, we're holding them hostage.
What!?
-Darling!
-Papa!
Akiko! Keiko!
-Papa, help us!
-Darling! Darling!
Do you see? Our organisation is so
powerful it has its own TV channel.
Are you sure you won't cooperate with us?
Well, think it over all you need. Just have
an answer ready by noon tomorrow.
Gone...
Jin Keisuke!
Apollo Geist! I knew you were behind this.
What do you want with Dr. Kawamura?
What indeed? Maybe you
should ask the guy behind you!
What?
One of GOD's wretched monsters!
Jin Keisuke! Prepare to be
executed by the beastman Chimera!
Hold it!!
Alright, let me finish him off.
Set Up!
Ridol Stick!
Try my 10,000 degree flame!
Darn...!
Mama, let me try.
Open... Open, open...
Got it!
Really...?
You did!
Come on.
Going somewhere?
Mama, I'm scared!
Chimera!!
What is it!?
See for yourself.
When did they--?
You're dealing with a psychic!
How could you leave them unguarded!?
Take them back to their cell and post a guard!
Keiko!
As Chief of GOD's Secret Police,
I can't forgive this failure!
I'll execute you here and now!
Wait! I killed GOD's archenemy, the X Rider!
You can't execute me for something like this!
Killed the X Rider...?
I'll believe it when I see it.
What's that Keisuke up to at training time?
The youth of today...!
Is that him?
Has Jin Keisuke shown up yet?
No, I'm still waiting for--
Maybe Chimera wasn't lying...
Who are you, by the way?
An acquaintance of Keisuke's?
I suppose you could say we're acquainted...
Well, until next time.
What the--? How rude...
Chief! Chief...!
What are you doing up--?
Hey! What happened to you?
I wanted them to think I was dead,
but I might've overdone it a little.
Are you alright?
Yeah, it's just a few scratches.
More importantly, I need you
to do something for me, chief.
Sure, sure!
I can sense some bad guys
right outside the door...
Keiko...
I can't pick the lock with them there
like I did before! Now we'll never get out!
Well, think it over all you need. Just have
an answer ready by noon tomorrow.
What are you!?
Captain Chimera of GOD! The time
has come, give me your answer.
Are Akiko and Keiko safe?
For now...
Please let them go!
...If you do, I'll do whatever you want.
There it is! We've got him!
Great! I see he got your lighter.
Hey, looks like they're headed for his lab.
His lab...?
Kawamura Parapsychology Labs
Get out!
What are we doing at my lab?
They say it's darkest at the foot of the lighthouse.
Your wife and daughter were under here all along!
Chief, I'll head in first.
Right behind you.
-Darling!
-You're alright!
-Papa!
The emotional reunion can wait.
First, you must prove your loyalty!
Our rules demand that you
undergo cyborg surgery!
What? Cyborg surgery?
Right!
Bring all three of them!
-Spare us!
-Papa, I'm scared!
-Wait!
Please wait...
At least spare my wife and daughter!
Shut up! Settle down!
-Darling!
-Please!
-Papa, Mama...
Begin.
Please, Lord...
He's coming!
He's coming. He'll be here soon.
Keiko? Who's coming?
I don't know, but I can feel someone
really strong getting nearer.
Am I too late?
Set Up!
Cruiser Jump!
Come quickly!
I'm on my way, Keiko!
Hurry, hurry!
Hang in there, Keiko!
He'll be dropping in any minute!
Rider!
You...!
Now, run for it!
Alright!
Ridol Whip!
X Slash!
Ridol Stick!
C'mon, get in already!
Hit it!
Long Pole!
Here goes!
How's that? Come at me if
you want to get burned!
I won't survive that heat
unless I cool my body...!
X Kick!!
Hey! Rider!
Hey!
Rider!
I'm too late! Accursed X Rider...
You're one tough guy!
The psychic girl and her
parents have been saved.
No matter what GOD tries next,
don't give up, Kamen Rider X, X, X!
To be continued
Next episode
The mysterious prophet Godradamus
foretells Tokyo's destruction.
Just as he predicts, GOD's killer
smog throws the city into chaos.
But has Rider X uncovered
Godradamus' true identity?
Look forward to the next episode:
"Godradamus' Great Prophecy!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider