Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Terrifying Giant! King Dark Emerges!!
What lovely flowers...
Ok, I'll get you one! Hold this.
Be careful!
Are you alright!?
Yeah, I'm fine...
Can you come down too, Sanae?
Did you find something?
Yeah, a weird cave...
Here, watch your step...
What's so weird about it?
Be quiet and listen...
You think there's a monster in there?
Don't be silly...
It must come out somewhere else.
We're just hearing the wind.
Come to think of it, I heard there's
caves connected to Mt. Fuji around here.
They probably spread all over the country.
Connected to Mt. Fuji...?
What a find!
C'mon, let's go inside!
Sure, why not?
Hup!
Big brother...!
Calm down, it's just a statue.
Are you sure?
But what's it doing here?
C'mon, let's check it out!
Just looking at it gives me the creeps!
Its eyes opened!
Come to me...!
Run for it, Sanae! Quickly!
It's sucking me in!!
Big brother!!
So, you're all here...
Genghis Khan Condor!
Toad Goemon!
Scorpion Geronimo!
Beetle Lupin!
Genghis Khan Condor, the real Genghis
Khan killed countless people...
Combine that devilish spirit
with the ferocity of the condor!
Genghis Condor can do no less!
Use that power you possess to
throw all Japan into disarray!
My Vampire Plan all begins
with one sacrifice...
Wipe the X Rider off the face of the Earth...
Just you wait, X Rider...
Up with her!
Well, well!
Yo! Is your shift over?
...Are those flowers?
Have you got a date?
You don't take flowers to a date!
That's not exactly Keisuke's area...
I... just don't know
many young ladies.
Excuse me? And what are we?
No kidding, how rude can you get?
Sorry, sorry... Ok, off you go.
Geez, this guy just can't take a hint!
Come on, Chiko!
Hey, lay off those two a little.
I'll be in real trouble if they quit.
They're having a tough time right now.
Who are they going to see?
A friend, I think.
Seems her big brother went missing.
Yamagami Hospital
Internal medicine, surgery, pediatrics
Director: Yamagami Hajime
How's that?
They're gorgeous... Thanks.
You're looking better than we thought!
You'll be over this in no time.
No! My brother died protecting me!
Sorry, I didn't mean to upset you...
Same here, I...
Does it still hurt?
Shall I take a look?
Don't touch me!
Come in!
You two should leave. We don't
want her to fall back into shock.
-Alright.
We'll be back, ok?
-See you!
-Let's go.
Sanae, my loyal blood slave...
Yes, master...
Tell me about your two friends.
Mako and Chiko...
...work at Tachibana's coffee shop...
Tachibana's coffee shop? So,
they're the X Rider's two allies...
Sanae's not doing so well, is she?
I know... She did just
lose her brother, after all.
But I get the feeling
that's not the reason.
Now that you mention it,
something does feel a little off...
...Is it me, or are we being watched?
I guess this park is kinda creepy!
-Chiko!!
-What should we do!?
-Run for it!
-Right!
And who might you be?
You don't look like
one of GOD's monsters...
I am Genghis Khan Condor!
Genghis Khan Condor?
Your life is mine, Jin Keisuke!
Genghis Khan Fire!
Mini condors, attack!
You too will become my slaves!
X Rider!
I was so close...!
X Rider! Next time you die!
You're safe now. Go
to Tachibana's place.
-Right.
You're still so gloomy...
C'mon, drink up.
Yeah...
Just what is he after...?
Chief, can you get these
two to a safe place by 1pm?
A safe place...?
A downtown hotel should be fine.
Until we know what Genghis
Khan Condor wants...
...we've got to keep these two safe.
Alright, I'll find them a hotel.
Ok, you two?
-Ok.
And don't let anyone
but me or the chief in.
We should be safe on
the thirty-second floor, right?
I never want to see
that monster's face again.
Well, you won't if you're careful.
Don't be a stranger!
What a bed! We never
get breaks like this!
Nothing gets you down, does it?
Go, blood slave!
Who's there?
It's Sanae!
Sanae?
Sanae!
Are you feeling better?
How did you find us?
Mr. Tachibana told me. It's so
awful what happened to you!
Well, I guess so, but...
What a nice breeze!
Don't open it!
But... I was ordered to...
Ordered to!? By who?
By my master...
Your master!?
Sanae!!
Now, you will join me...
-Genghis Khan...
-...Condor!
Yes, become vampires!
Become my blood slaves!
Then infest the city and bring
more humans to our side!
-Chiko!
-Mako!
We're getting reports that a
strange virus is spreading citywide.
Young women are assuming the appearance and
mannerisms of what can only be called vampires.
The cause has yet to be identified, but the
police ask that you not go out alone at night.
In other news--
Keisuke?
It's him. It has to be
Genghis Khan Condor.
Looks like his plan is to turn
everyone in Japan into vampires.
Things will only get
worse if we don't find him.
But where's he hiding?
Someone help me! Please, help!
Let her go!
A vampire?
Hang in there! You're safe now!
I was so scared...
She bit my wrist!
...You were lucky.
A little longer and
you'd be a vampire too.
Genghis Khan Condor...
How are you turning these
people into vampires?
What's with those two? Disappearing
when you try to do them a favour...
Where did you come from?
Don't scare me like that!
How about some coffee?
Not coffee...
What?
There's something we want more...
Cut to the chase, then!
What do you want?
Your blood!
You guys... That's not funny!
I'm even thirstier after
being interrupted once today...
D-don't tell me you're really--!
So, he got you after all!
Let go!
Middle-aged blood is lousy! No flavour!
I was so close to catching
one of those vampires...
-Well, how about a coffee?
-Sure.
Chief...
You too!?
Let's take him to the master.
Good work, my slaves.
Now Jin Keisuke, too, will
become a loyal vampire.
The X Rider!
Did you think your vampire
virus would affect me?
Curse you!
Take him, my slaves!
Don't leave a drop of his blood!
I have to fight... Please forgive me!
Foolish X Rider, I haven't lost yet!
To me, Cruiser!
X Rider, just try and foll--
Hold it, Genghis Khan Condor!
You're not getting away!
You think so?
Cruiser Big Turn!
Blast him!
Keep going, Cruiser!
Go!
Ridol Stick!
Genghis Khan Fire!
Fire!
Curses! I can't breathe fire!
Now!
X Kick!
His vampire virus will
disappear with his body...
...and the others will return to normal.
Chiko!
Wake up!
-Your fangs...
-...are gone!
Mine too!
The X Rider beat him!
GOD's King Dark has appeared in Japan.
But the X Rider rises to oppose him.
We're with you, X Rider!
To be continued
Next episode
A scientist hides the blueprints
for GOD's latest terrible weapon.
King Dark dispatches Gama Goemon,
a monster with a great thief's mind.
Fight on, X Rider!
Look forward to the next episode:
"King Dark! Demonic Invention!!"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider