Kamen Rider X!
Kamen Rider
Set Up! Set Up! Set Up!
Gin no kamen ni kuro mafuraa
A mask of silver and a black muffler
Hitai ni kagayaku Bui to Bui
V and V shining on his forehead
「Sutoppu! Goddo no waru-dakumi」
"Stop GOD's conspiracy!"
Chichi no sakebi wa nami no oto
His father's scream is the sound of the waves
Ikari no Raidoru hikinuite
Furiously drawing the Ridol
Ekkusu Raidaa kyou mo yuku
X Rider comes again today
Kamen Rider X! X! X!
Killed with his father by the evil organisation GOD,
Jin Keisuke is revived as Kamen Rider X.
His mission: to preserve peace and justice by
fighting the mysterious agency known as GOD.
Dr. Nanbara had completed blueprints for GOD's
RS Device, which can convert any matter into energy.
But Nanbara escaped GOD and tore the blueprints
into nine pieces to entrust to his old colleagues.
GOD has stolen one of the pieces,
and the X Rider holds five.
Thus does a deadly race for the
remaining three pieces begin!
Arise! King Dark!!
Nasu Rindou Lake Family Ranch
Where's that music coming from?
It's a doll!
-Get it for me!
-Sure.
Yuki!
Yuki, your mommy's calling you.
Come on, it's looking stormy...
-Bye-bye!
Nasu Family Ranch Management Office
-The doll's moving!
-Where are you going? Bad baby!
Who are you!?
I am Lizard Viking, of GOD's Villain Army!
My, what a cute little girl! Will
you let Uncle Lizard see that doll?
No! She's my baby!
How precious! You know, Uncle
Lizard just loves little girls.
Come here, let me give you a hug!
What do you think you're doing!?
Darling!
Mommy!
Now, come here...
Blast!
That brat's fast on her feet!
-Huh?
-Mako!
-Chiko!
-Hey, are you alright?
-Hey!
We'd better take her back with us!
-Can you get our stuff?
-Yeah.
Let's go!
-Boss!
-Boss, come quick!
What's that?
A lizard did it?
Sounds like GOD to me, chief.
But... what would GOD
want with that doll?
There's probably some secret to it!
Will you let me see your doll?
Don't worry, I'll give her right back!
Please listen, I'm a friend of Dr. Nanbara!
I've hidden a very important
blueprint inside this doll.
Whoever's listening to this,
please protect the bluepri--
So that's it!
My doll!
I've got to find her
before it's too late...
Daddy! Mommy!
A lizard!
It's no use running, dear!
Come and get your hug!
I'm scared!
Don't let her get away!
Cry and bawl all you want, darling!
Now, will you give me that doll?
Stop!!
So you've come, Jin Keisuke!
You monster...
How dare you treat an
innocent child like this!?
Curse you... Take him!
Trample him!
Great Transformation!
Help me, Rider! Help me!!
Historic Site - The Killing Stone
-Let her go!
-One move and she dies!
Get away, quickly!
-Help!
You coward!
And that's one of my good points! Now, hand over
the doll and change back if you want them to live!
What?
Well, X Rider? What will it be?
Give it to me!
Good work, Lizard Viking! I am impressed.
You honour me, King Dark.
Now all that remains is to finish Jin Keisuke!
Yes, milord! I'll enjoy every second of it!
But show me the blueprint first.
Milord.
It isn't there, is it?
Impossible!
...It's not there!
You imbecile!!
That girl... I'm going to kill her!
Yuki!
Good timing! Have you seen
those two girls who helped you?
GOD caught them!
-GOD!?
-The man too!
They got Keisuke?
And this was inside my doll!
What's this?
A piece of Dr. Nanbara's
blueprints! Come on, Yuki!
Why the heck are we stopping?
What's wrong?
Lizards!
So you did this?
...Alright. Take me to Keisuke!
I'll take you to him... once
you give me the blueprint.
What are you talking about?
I don't have any blueprints!
-I'm scared!
-You're not getting away again... Take him!
Yuki...!
Chiko, do you really think Keisuke'll come!?
He'll come! I know it!
Mashiko Pottery Direct Sales Office
Don't bother struggling, Jin Keisuke. There's
someone I'd like you to meet. Over here!
-Chief!
-Keisuke...
That's enough of that!
Take Jin Keisuke to the kiln!
Keisuke!
Block the entrance!
Keisuke!!
Chiko!! Mako!!
-Boss!!
Don't worry! Keisuke's coming! I promise!
I'm scared!
Keisuke, please hurry!
Wait, maybe I can melt it!
Hold fire a moment.
Jin Keisuke is dead! Nobody can
save you now! Say your prayers!
It's melting!
That did it!
Great Transformation!
Alright, take aim...
Is this really the end...?
Hold it!!
You survived!?
It's the X Rider!
X Rider!
X Rider!!
You enjoy torturing people,
don't you, Lizard Viking?
Let's see how you like it!
Get him!
Catch!
Chief!
-Rider!
-I'll get you for this!
He won't get away! Chief,
take care of the others.
Right!
Faster! He's gaining on us!
Aerial Hell Wheel!
Daddy, mommy!
-Daddy, mommy!
-Yuki!
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad you're ok, Yuki!
Curses! Another one lost to the X Rider...
I'm surrounded by failures!
It seems that if I want the job done...
...I will have to do it myself!
King Dark...!
Peace has returned to the peaks of Nasu.
But a new plot is already forming
around the last blueprint pieces.
To be continued
Next episode
A woman comes to Nasu with blueprints for
Jin Keisuke, but Ant Capone is after her.
The X Rider's Vacuum Hell Wheel
explodes in the Nasu Highlands!
Look forward to the next episode:
"Showdown! King Dark Versus X Rider"
Ore wa Ekkusu Ekkusu Raidaa
I am X, X Rider
Chichi no tsukutta Kaizoogu
A Kaizorg created by my father
Tetsu yori tsuyoi
Stronger than iron
Oto yori hayai
Faster than sound
Ekkusu masuku paafekutaa
X's mask, Perfecter
Chichi no negai ga ore no chi ni
My father's wishes are in my blood
「Warui yatsura ni makeru na to」
"Don't lose to those villains!"
Sakende iru ze
He screams
Itsu made mo
Eternally
Ore wa Ekkusu
I am X
Ekkusu Raidaa
X Rider