KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Shocker Graveyard:
Monsters Revived
Didn't catch anything today, huh?
I guess we should stick to the usual spots.
Yeah. Let's head home for the day, huh?
Upsy-daisy...
What's that sound?
It's coming closer...
Wh-Who are you?
Say something!
M-M-Monster!
Welcome.
We need humans who
survive our aptitude test.
Run, Kato!
It's your turn now.
We're going to take you
to the Shocker Graveyard alive,
and use you as a sacrifice
in our devil festival!
This is Shocker's Graveyard in Japan.
The crosses mark
the bodies of the cyborgs
who died at the hands
of the Kamen Rider.
Here in the Shocker Graveyard,
the devil festival is about to commence.
Great Leader of Shocker,
Use the limitless power of the devil
to bestow revival energy
upon this cyborg.
For each sacrifice of the devil festival,
we can revive five cyborgs.
Ambassador Hell.
Bring Kamen Rider and
his friends to the devil festival.
That will let us revive
all of the buried cyborgs.
Behold! Shocker revival energy!
Harinezuras.
Jaguar Man.
Saigang.
Beaded Lizard Man.
Zanjioh.
You have been restored to life
with Shocker's revival energy.
Go with Kamikirikid and bring the Kamen
Rider and his allies to the graveyard.
Kamikirikid.
Before you fight the Kamen Rider,
you should undergo
training with the others,
who have experienced loss
at the Kamen Rider's hands.
Now, try the Rider Kick!
Go on! Do it!
What, is that all you have?
The real Rider Kick is ten
times stronger than that!
Next!
You're raring to go.
That's what I like to see.
Ambassador Hell! We've found Taki Kazuya.
Good. Make contact at once!
Where the heck did Hongo get off to?
He could have at least dropped
a line to let me know...
The wire's been cut...
I guess someone snuck into the room, eh?
Sneaking into someone's room...
Are you with Shocker?
A-Are you Mr. Taki?
How do you know my name?
Mr. Hongo sent me...
Hongo sent you?
I've escaped from Shocker.
What did you say?
I was in danger,
and Mr. Hongo saved me.
And he told you to come to me?
Y-Yes.
Understood.
Don't you worry.
I'll keep you safe, I promise.
Okay...
Th-They're after me, I know it!
I've found you.
Those who learn Shocker's
secrets must not escape!
Mr. Taki!
Hold it!
It's the Kamen Rider!
You came back to life to
continue to spread evil, did you?
It's a rematch between
Kamen Rider and the cyborgs!
Taki, leave this to me.
- Got it!
- Get to the club!
This isn't over!
That must've been awful.
Here.
Thank you.
I see...
You ran away from Shocker, did you?
Damned Shocker...
They've brought back cyborgs
that Rider beat in the past.
What? He has to fight
all those monsters?
That'd be too much for me...
Could that be Takeshi?
I'll get it.
Hello? Tachibana Racing...
Yuri?
Hey...
It's Shocker.
They said we're surrounded...
We should come out with our hands up!
Yeah.
This isn't good...
There's no way to escape.
We need to at least get Mr. Kato to safety.
I'll go.
I can't cause any more trouble for you.
We can't let you do that.
- Everyone, barricade the door.
- Right.
- Emi, hurry!
- Okay!
- Block the window.
- Right!
Heave-ho!
Everyone, grab weapons!
Right!
Okay, don't let your guard down!
They're here!
Give that man to us!
Not a chance!
Everyone... run, quickly!
Wait!
You're back, Rider...
You never learn, do you?
Now, fight me!
Rider, Shocker's after this man.
Understood.
Mr. Kato, go with Rider, hurry.
Right.
Taki, I'm going to take
this man somewhere safe.
Mr. Taki! You okay?
Mr. Taki!
- Mr. Taki!
- Hey, you okay?
- Grab on tight!
- Right!
Hold on tight. Don't let go!
I'd never let go...
This is my big chance, after all.
What?
Kamen Rider...
You made a major miscalculation this time.
Shocker's real target
was you, Taki, and the others!
You're...
Who are you?
I'm Kamikirikid, and I was
born to defeat you!
Taki, Tachibana and the others
are under attack as we speak!
No!
KAMEN RIDER
Here we go.
Hey! Get out of here!
Kamen Rider already took
the man you were after!
That's right!
Fool!
We were really getting
Kamen Rider out of our way!
What?
Now, come with us to
the Shocker Graveyard,
and take part in the devil festival!
Shocker Graveyard?
So it's us you're after?
No! I won't be part of some devil festival!
I won't go!
It's not up to you!
You're all going to be sacrifices
to bring our cyborgs back to life!
Damn you!
Kamen Rider.
You'll be sacrificed at the devil
festival in the Shocker Graveyard, too.
Shocker Graveyard?
I see... you're going to sacrifice
Taki and the others, too?
That's right.
Any who oppose Shocker must die!
We'll finish this later!
Damn...
Taki!
Pops!
Kamen Rider.
We've taken your allies to serve
as sacrifices for the devil festival!
Damn! I can't believe it!
It's Rider! Hurry!
Wait up!
Now...
Take me to this Shocker Graveyard!
C-Can't breathe...
Talk!
H-Hell Valley...
Now, talk!
Where is Shocker's Graveyard?
B-Behind those rocks...
Is that the way in?
Great Leader of Shocker...
Use the limitless power of evil
and the blood of these sacrifices
to restore our cyborgs to life!
Transfer the evil spirits of
the altar to the sacrifices.
Chairman!
Don't give up hope, no matter what!
Hang in there!
We're done for, though!
Mama!
Suffer. Suffer more!
The greater your suffering,
the more powerful the devil
festival becomes!
Suffer! Keep suffering!
- Rider!
Taki, run away!
Right!
Run away!
Let's go, everyone!
Hurry!
Pops! Get everyone to safety!
Right!
- Taki!
- Rider!
Hurry! Outside!
Taki!
Rider Punch!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider Throw!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Rider Throw!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider, I've finished off the combatants.
Taki, I'll handle things here.
You look after Pops!
Right.
Let's go, Rider!
Swimming through the
oceans with a Rider Swim,
a great dive flitting through the sea!
Calling up whirlpools with a Rider Screw!
Dragging enemies down with a Rider Lung!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
He finally did it!
We're saved!
Yeah... I was so scared!
Pops, are you all right?
Yeah. Where's Rider?
He's over there...
There's our guardian angel!
Rider!
Rider! Rider!
The Kamen Rider brought
an end to the Shocker Graveyard.
But what new scheme was
Shocker plotting against him?
Ride on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Girizames.
Shocker commanders arrive from
countries all over the world.
Rider and Girizames face off with the
fate of their top secret plan on the line.
And what is the Shocker
leader's true identity?
Join us next week for "The Shocker
Leader Appears!! Rider in Peril."
The Shocker Leader Appears!! Rider in Peril
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!