KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Showdown!! Snowy
Mountain Monster Bearkonger
Where are Pops and the others?
Are you okay?
Hey, they're over there!
Hey!
Just pathetic.
This mountain's gonna end
up with a bunch of holes.
Well, let's have another run.
Yeah, I appreciate Pops
making time for it.
This is one time we
can be grateful to him.
- Right!
- Well, let's go.
Hayato and Taki...
Take a nice rest, both of you.
I'm sure nothing will
happen to interrupt it.
Hey,
what's wrong with you girls?
We're done.
Get a load of these lazy
girls, Mr. Chairman!
Come on, Goro.
You think you can
ski any better?
Yeah!
Fine.
Just watch me!
I'm going, okay? Just watch!
Ow!
Hey, ski! Ski!
Stop laughing and go after him!
What did you expect?
He is a beginner, after all.
- Was it around here?
- Where could it have gone?
I think it was more this way...
It should be
somewhere around here.
Hey, excuse me!
Have you seen a child-sized ski?
It slid into the
underbrush there.
Thank you very much!
Mr. Chairman, I'll go find it!
It's dangerous!
Don't go in there!
Don't go in where?
There's ravine under that snow.
Just this year, more than ten
people have fallen and gone missing.
What?
I'll help you find it.
I know the area.
Be careful!
I hope he'll be okay.
I found it!
That's great!
Hey, I got it!
Thank you, son!
Here, Goro. Say thank you.
Thanks a lot!
Just be my friend in return.
Friend? Sounds good to me!
That's great!
I'm Tadashi Mikawa.
I'm Ishikura Goro.
And this is Mika and
Emi, Tobei, and Yuri.
Tadashi!
That's my dad.
I'll teach you how to ski
tomorrow, Goro.
Nine o'clock tomorrow, okay?
Nine o'clock? Sure.
See you!
That blasted,
interfering Mikawa child...
Hotel Village
There.
"We're here at the Hotel Village
at the Kusatsu Highlands.
It's a very nice place."
What's the matter?
That awful card again...
It makes me feel so uneasy.
It's turned into a blizzard.
Doctor Mikawa.
Come to me!
Mikawa
Doctor Shinigami.
How is Operation:
Snow proceeding?
It will soon be complete.
Operation: Snow is Shocker's plan to
melt the snow in the Kusatsu Highlands
and cause massive flooding.
To accomplish this, Shocker has
threatened physicist Doctor Saburo Mikawa
into creating energy bombs that
can generate 2000 degrees of heat
for an extended period of time.
Gentlemen,
we must speed up the plan.
Bearkonger.
Your job is to keep
obstacles out of our way.
Follow Mikawa's son.
Why did you call me
out at this hour?
Doctor Mikawa.
Your son has made friends with
some truly dire characters.
Ichimonji Hayato,
of all people...
Wait! Wait!
I made your energy bombs so
that you'd spare my son's life.
I've done enough, haven't I?
Please, don't harm Tadashi!
Please!
P-Please!
Doctor.
If your son learns our secret,
we will kill him.
I will provide a demonstration.
Let me go!
Doctor, watch carefully.
If you don't wish to see
your son die like this,
keep him away from
Ichimonji and the others.
If you understand,
then you may go.
Can it be? Was Tadashi...
Tadashi.
Tadashi!
Papa!
What did you say?
You can't see us anymore?
Sorry...
after I said we could be friends.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, everyone.
Tadashi,
could you please tell us why?
They'll kill me if I tell
you, Mr. Ichimonji.
Goodbye!
Taki...
Something's going on here.
Doctor Shinigami.
The fool...
Go, Bearkonger!
Wait! Wait!
Don't touch Tadashi!
Throw him in a cell!
Papa! Papa!
Help!
- Take him away!
- Help! Help!
Taki, you go for Tadashi.
Right!
Hold it!
I'm scared!
Wait, Shocker!
Transform...
Get him!
Let's go!
You're finished now, Rider!
This isn't over, Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
You great fool.
You couldn't even
kill one child?
This is ridiculous!
Bearkonger.
You must do what it takes to lure
out Ichimonji and his allies.
Now, go!
I swear upon my life
that I will succeed.
Arm the energy bombs!
Now armed.
Thirty minutes to detonation.
I see.
So your father was forced
to work with Shocker...
But to melt the snow in the Kusatsu
Highlands to cause major flooding...
It sounds like
something they'd do.
Mr. Ichimonji,
please save my father.
The incinerator at our house...
He has a terrible fever.
Hayato...
Are you sure about this?
I'm fine.
My body can take worse than this.
Hayato, they'll probably
try to strike elsewhere.
Be careful.
I will.
Taki.
Emi and Mika have been
gone a long time...
Hotel Village
Hey, where are you going?
Never mind that.
Go help cool him down.
Right.
That will do you no good!
Emi...
What's going on?
Let's go, Mika.
Wait.
Someone's coming...
Mika!
Let's go!
In here.
That was scary!
Who are you?
Who are we?
This is room 412, isn't it?
It is not.
You should check a room's
number before you enter.
That's right.
Something's wrong here, Emi.
412... this is our room!
That sounded like Mika and Emi!
Taki, over there!
Shocker...
Taki, let's go!
Ichimonji Hayato!
Death!
Where are you? Show yourself!
Look up on that hill.
They never give up...
Hayato, hurry!
Transform!
Bearkonger!
Where are you?
Pops! Speak to me!
Rider!
Mr. Mikawa!
The energy bombs will
go off in five minutes!
Hurry... go!
Mr. Mikawa!
Damn you, Shocker.
Rider.
You'd better hurry.
We only have five minutes.
Taki, you handle things here.
Rider! Hurry!
Damn... no time!
That way!
Taki!
Rider!
Take care of this!
Right!
What now, Rider?
Rider Kick!
Mr. Mikawa!
Tadashi!
Are you feeling better now?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I can't thank you all
enough for what you've done.
Go on, sit down.
You don't need to thank us.
Well, Mr. Chairman?
Now that we're
friends with Tadashi,
why don't we spend
another couple days here?
We're in Kusatsu, after all.
A bath in the hot springs will
heal our wounds in a second.
That's right...
Let's do it, then!
Yeah!
Okay, I'm gonna go for a swim.
Let's go put our
bathing suits on!
I'm gonna swim, too.
Say, Hayato?
I heard Kusatsu's water
was good for injuries,
but does that go for
the heated pool, too?
It's a psychological thing.
My wounds are all healed.
How about we hit
the slopes again?
Kamen Rider had put a stop
to Shocker's evil plan.
But as long as evil exists in this
world, the Kamen Rider will fight.
For the sake of
peace and justice!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the ice devil Todogiller.
The evil Shocker uses the devil Todogiller
in their plan to freeze all of Japan.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Deadly Ice
Devil Todogiller."
The Deadly Ice Devil
Todogiller
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!