KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Shinigami Chameleon!
Showdown at the Old World's Fair!
Takeshi infiltrated Shocker's secret
base in search of a mysterious steel box,
but he was quickly exposed
and thrown into a trap.
Kamen Rider...
This is the Rider-killer
trap I arranged just for you.
Die, Rider!
A Rider-killer trap?
Damn...
It's hopeless.
The walls are all
one meter thick.
Rider... I arranged them to be
too thick for you to break through
based on an analysis
of your power.
He'll run out of
power soon enough.
How long can I hold out?
Kamen Rider's superpowers
cannot last forever.
There are limits to the turbine-generated
power that he can store at one time,
and he needs to get his turbine to
spin again in order to generate more.
But in this tiny locked room
with no wind and no way to drive,
he can't get the
turbine to spin.
We can see Rider's energy
fading before our very eyes.
Watch the death of a
fool who opposed Shocker.
Listen to me, Shocker!
If you kill me now,
you'll never find the Nazi
box you've been searching for!
Your desperation is pathetic.
You think you can
fool me that easily?
If you think it's a lie, check the
box in Doctor Heinrich's possession.
It's a fake!
A fake?
I wouldn't put it past
him, Doctor.
Doctor...
Strange...
What is it?
This box is a fake!
It can't be...
Look! The gun shot through it!
The Nazi box was designed to
survive even a nuclear blast!
And the wavelength
meter isn't responding.
It's a fake!
Damn him!
I can see I made my point.
Hongo. Where's the real one?
Release me, and I'll tell you.
Don't be absurd!
Release him. But...
Now, speak.
Where is the Nazi box?
The real box...
Assistant Professor Abe Naoki of
Jonan University sent it to Doctor Oyama
in the engineering department
of Osaka Hanshin University.
The engineering department
of Osaka Hanshin University?
Well, now...
Can you escape
us, Hongo Takeshi?
What?
Now, combatants of Shocker...
Use your talent and training
to kill Hongo Takeshi.
Not good. I don't have
enough energy to fight...
He's gone.
He can't have gotten far, though.
All right. Find him!
Who's there?
You're Yumi's
father, aren't you?
Yes. Who are you?
Search this room!
They're coming.
There must be a
drainpipe up there...
It's our only chance.
Hang in there. You're safe now.
Am... Am I safe?
Where's Yumi?
Where's my daughter, Yumi?
There's no need to fear.
Yumi is safe.
Is she?
Yes.
And what happened
to the Nazi box?
Please, Mr. Sunada.
Tell me.
What is the secret
of the Nazi box?
Just before the fall of Berlin,
the dictator of Nazi Germany, Hitler,
hid his treasure on
the I-155 submarine
and took it to their
ally at the time, Japan.
Only I, the submarine's
captain, knew about it.
Hitler's plan was
to escape to Japan,
and use the trillions stored on
board to rebuild the Third Reich.
But Hitler ended
up killing himself,
and the treasure has
remained in Japan, unused.
The location of the
treasure is inside that box.
A treasure worth trillions...
Shocker would surely want
to use it for evil.
Ruriko!
Takeshi! You're all right?
What are you doing
here in Lake Biwa?
I couldn't just sit
around, doing nothing.
So I followed you
on a motorbike.
You're absolutely incorrigible.
But I appreciate it.
Really?
I'm glad that I could help you.
Really.
Who's this man?
Yumi's father.
The one you've
been worried about.
Sunada, miss.
I'm so glad. I really am.
Wait, I know.
It's from Yumi.
She asked me to give it
to you if I found you.
Yumi...
Ruriko.
I'm going to take
Mr. Sunada somewhere safe.
What should I do?
Head to Osaka ahead of
me and meet with Boss.
Tell him what happened to me.
Mr. Sunada.
Let's get you to Yumi's hospital
in Tokyo as soon as possible
and show her that
you're all right.
Ruriko! See you in Osaka!
Hanshin Institute of Technology
Hongo was telling the truth.
Doctor Oyama has the box.
I got dressed up as Doctor Oyama,
like he asked...
but Shocker still
hasn't shown themselves.
No one saw that, did they?
Of course not.
But I wonder what's
taking Takeshi so long...
Where is Takeshi?
I'll get it.
Hello? Oyama here.
Is that you, Hongo?
Yes... nothing out
of the ordinary here.
See you later.
What happened?
Boss...
H-Hands...
What?
Don't act so surprised...
You've been waiting for
Shocker, and here we are.
I wasn't waiting for Shocker...
I was just...
You're Tachibana Tobei, Hongo Takeshi's
helper and Shocker's hated enemy.
And Midorikawa Ruriko.
Damn.
So you knew it was me...
That will speed things up.
I'm going to keep you
here until Hongo arrives!
Hey, show yourself!
Where did you go?
Boss!
Takeshi!
KAMEN RIDER
Boss!
Ruriko!
Shocker took them both...
It's open!
I got it open...
There's nothing here!
Maybe there was a time when only Nazi
science could make a box like that,
but that was 26 years ago!
Science is advancing every day.
And Doctor Oyama is Hongo's mentor,
and a genius in electrophysics!
He opened that box ages ago.
Silence!
Don't say another word.
Go on, hit me!
Hongo already has the map
that was inside that box.
Wait, Chameleon Man.
This foolish human will
make a valuable hostage.
What? You're going
to hold us hostage?
Yes, hostages.
To trade for Hongo's map.
Don't be stupid!
I'd rather bite my tongue and die
than go along with your schemes!
Boss!
Once they learn there's
nothing in that box,
Shocker will make its next move.
Hello?
Hongo, Tachibana Tobei and Midorikawa
Ruriko are in my possession.
I'll trade them for the
map in your possession.
I'll be in Senri—Expoland,
the old site of the world's fair.
Come at noon.
I'll be there, Shocker.
A motorbike!
There's no one on it!
He's not here. Where's Hongo?
I'm right here!
Hongo!
Boss!
You tricked me!
So this is the map
to the treasure?
Look, Hongo!
I will kill both of them!
This fight isn't over yet!
After him!
Hongo, be careful!
That monster can change
color, like a chameleon!
It's not safe! Keep away!
I can't beat him unless I
transform into Kamen Rider.
But if I transform now,
Ruriko will know everything...
She'll know I'm a cyborg.
But I can't do that...
What's wrong, Hongo?
Fight me already!
Die!
Hongo!
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
What are you doing with us?
You can't possibly have
any more use for us!
But of course I do.
The Kamen Rider will
surely show himself again.
I need you to keep
him from interfering.
That's the forest
shown in the map.
It's time to see it... the treasure of
Hitler that's gone unused for 26 years.
This is it!
It's here! Buried here!
We've finally found it.
Now the trillions buried
here will belong to Shocker.
Shocker will become
stronger than ever before!
It's here!
Hitler's treasure...
This has to be it!
The Kamen Rider!
Tell me... was there really
a Nazi treasure there?
The treasure was there.
But I dug it up in advance
and threw it into the Pacific.
It was a tainted treasure,
generated by the evils of the human heart.
I... I see...
Rider Kick!
Rider Chop!
Closed Today
Congratulations!
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you so much!
Aren't you glad to
have your papa home?
Mr. Hongo made this
happen, right?
Mr. Hongo!
Takeshi...
Hongo Takeshi had foiled
Shocker's evil scheme.
While enduring the pain
of his cyborg existence,
he continues his
fight against evil.
To be continued
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
Next Episode Preview
is Bee Woman.
People who buy glasses from a certain
store are disappearing one after another.
What is it about these glasses?
What is Shocker
plotting this time?
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Creepy Bee Woman!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!