KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Kamestone's
Killer Aurora Plan
That's strange...
- What's going on?
- I'm scared...
It's so creepy...
Let's go home.
What are you talking about?
We came here to enjoy
ourselves, didn't we?
But...
Scary...
Look! An aurora!
But it's too strange.
An aurora in Tokyo?
Okay, I'll take a picture!
My eyes... my eyes!
What's wrong?
My eyes!
My eyes hurt!
What's wrong, you two?
My eyes... my eyes hurt...
They hurt! My eyes hurt!
- My eyes hurt!
The appearance of
the terrifying aurora
brought the wail of police and
ambulance sirens all over Tokyo.
The blinded townspeople were taken
to hospitals one after another.
Quickly! The third building.
Mr. Shimizu.
Ichimonji...
Their eyes...
Their vision will
recover, won't it?
We're doing everything
we can to help them.
That's all I can say for now.
They won't be blinded for
life, will they?
Ichimonji.
That aurora destroyed
the patients' retinas.
I believe that an IV of a drug I've
been researching will cure them,
but I can't be sure just yet.
Thank you.
I'm going to find out
what caused that aurora.
It's a man-made
beam of some kind.
Someone must be controlling it.
Go on.
I'm counting on you.
Hayato.
I've heard Goro, Emi,
and the others were taken in.
Is that Hayato and Mr. Taki?
I'm impressed that you
recognized us, Goro.
Hayato!
Mr. Taki!
Mr. Chairman!
Hey, everyone.
Do your eyes hurt?
We're okay.
The pain's all gone now.
Everyone got the
proper treatment
so no one is going to go blind.
But...
But who would do this?
It's too awful!
Your attempts at treatment
are all too late.
The cyborg I created
personally...
All who witness the aurora
created by that cyborg
will rot from their eyes out
until their entire
body dissolves.
Then the city of Tokyo
will belong to Shocker!
Hayato, there you are.
Accursed Shocker.
Just what are they
planning this time?
Taki!
Put on the special eyeglasses!
Shocker cyborg!
Are you the one
behind the auroras?
That's right.
Quite an enchanting
aurora, isn't it?
Taki.
Don't lose your eyeglasses!
You Shocker fiends...
You've really gotten
me mad this time!
Take this!
Uh-oh, I'm gonna fall...
Hayato!
Transform!
Blasted Kamen Rider!
Taki!
Close off the emergency exits,
and stand by inside the hospital!
Right!
Well? Can't see now, can you?
Filthy Kamen Rider...
Now, die in agony!
My eyes...
My eyes!
What?
You requested aid
from FBI headquarters?
Yes.
The resources of the
Tokyo Police and JSDF
are all focused on the
blinded townspeople.
And Hayato's lost his
sight, too.
I reckon that you and I are the
only ones who can fight Shocker now.
I thought stalling their momentum
would be our best shot right now.
Fair point...
So, who are they sending?
Tanaka Robert.
An FBI veteran,
the son of Japanese immigrants.
He's the only person I can think of who
can fight on even footing with Shocker.
Great to hear it.
When's he reaching Japan?
He arrives tomorrow
morning at eight o'clock.
The FBI says he's on
the plane already.
Meanwhile,
the passenger plane carrying
Tanaka Robert was entering
Japanese airspace.
Doctor Shinigami.
The Kamen Rider is Shocker's
most urgent concern.
Unless we destroy
the Kamen Rider,
Operation: Blindness will
surely end in failure.
Work with Kamestone to
see the Kamen Rider dead!
All is proceeding
as I planned it.
Hey.
I thought you'd be
arriving in Haneda.
I wanted to give
Shocker the slip.
How's Ichimonji doing?
He's completely blind.
Looks like it's you
and me against Shocker.
The chief was worried,
so he gave me some special eye medicine.
Johoku Hospital
It's time for lights out.
We ask that all our
patients now go to sleep.
Wretched Shocker...
Even if I can't see,
I'll still beat you.
Even blind,
I'm still a cyborg...
I can drive using my
enhanced hearing alone!
I drove.
I drove!
I was able to drive!
Wretched Shocker...
You've failed in your plan.
I can still fight you.
And I will foil your plans!
That is my mission!
I guess there's a motorbike
garage near the hospital.
They say you can hear engine
noises outside at night.
Oh, really?
Goro and Yuri heard them, too.
Really? I must have
been out like a light.
I didn't hear a thing.
Well, best to rest up while
you're in the hospital.
Hayato!
Goro, eh? You sound excited.
Hayato, I can see again!
- Yeah!
- What?
It's because of the medicine
that Robert brought!
You're using it too, right?
Hey.
Well, we're going to be going.
Let's go, Goro.
See you around!
Hayato...
It didn't work on you?
You haven't even used it...
KAMEN RIDER
Johoku Hospital
That Hayato...
he's been driving around blind.
Is that water?
It's gasoline...
Who would dump gasoline here?
That's not gasoline...
It's nitro!
Someone's trying to kill Hayato!
This is Robert's...
Johoku Hospital
I ran an analysis
of the eye medicine.
It's far more effective than
the one I was researching.
Has this medicine restored
sight to all the other patients?
Yes.
Ichimonji, what in the world...
Robert!
Where's that Shocker
base you mentioned?
It's right here.
Taki, it's time for you to die!
Damn!
Hayato!
Where's Taki?
He said he'd found
a Shocker base.
He went with Robert
just a little while ago.
Damn...
I knew it.
Robert's behind this.
Pops, there's a transmitter
on my motorbike.
See which way it went.
North-northwest, 20 kilometers.
Which means...
Mukogaoka Amusement Park!
Mukogaoka?
Robert!
Just who are you?
Taki, it took you long
enough to catch on...
Who are you?
Since you're dying anyway,
I might as well tell you.
This is my true form!
Kamestone!
Where is Robert?
Having a rest at the
bottom of the sea...
An eternal one!
Take him away!
Taki!
Where are you, Taki?
Taki! Taki!
Taki, run!
I knew you'd come
here, Ichimonji Hayato!
Die!
Transform!
Kamestone...
Oh no!
My eyes... my eyes hurt!
Exposure to Kamestone's aurora
had rendered Kamen
Rider completely blind.
And the pain in Rider's eyes
was continuing to grow worse.
Well? Such is my power!
No... he's going to beat me!
Die!
Where is Kamestone?
Kamen Rider!
Your end is finally here!
Well? You can't follow my
movements, can you?
I can't hear Kamestone
move with all this noise...
Die!
Rider can't see.
That's why he's doing this!
Damn!
I can hear his footsteps.
He won't escape!
Now!
Rider Kick!
Rider, have your eyes recovered?
They recovered the
moment he fell.
Thank you, Taki!
No more auroras, right?
Yes, we're all safe now.
Kamen Rider got
rid of Kamestone!
But I wish I could've seen
him beat the monster...
You saw, right, Hayato?
I'm afraid I was still
blind at the time.
Aw.
But I'll be sure to win the upcoming
Silver Race instead, all right?
I dunno if I can trust
you, Hayato.
Right?
Kamestone, creator of the
deadly auroras, was gone.
But Shocker would return again,
their desire for world conquest unquenched.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Unicornos.
This one-horned monster spits a white
fluid that turns humans to stone.
His deathmatch against the two
Riders, Ichimonji Hayato
and Hongo Takeshi,
takes place in a limestone cavern.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
Rock Monster Unicornos
Versus the Double Rider Kick
in "Rock Monster Unicornos
Versus the Double Rider Kick."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!