KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Terrifying Operation: Pet
Rider S.O.S!
Taki!
Look out!
Thanks, Rider!
Rider... you'll pay for your interference!
Leave this monster to me!
Rider... let's go!
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Rider!
This isn't over!
That was close...
Just what was that monster?
General Black.
Let's begin the next
phase of Operation: Pet.
My leader.
Things are proceeding apace.
Nezcondor will spread his
bacteria throughout Tokyo,
and throw the citizens of
Tokyo into fear and unrest.
Within twenty-four hours—in other
words, at this time tomorrow...
Tokyo will be a wasteland.
I see.
At last, Tokyo will belong
to Gel Shocker, then?
Yes. It will be so.
Nezcondor.
Spread your plague germs across Tokyo.
Turn the city into a wasteland!
Leave it to me!
I'm home!
I want a snack!
Peel it, okay?
That hurts!
I'm home!
What happened?
Hey!
What could this disease be?
What's the matter?
Hey!
Hey, what's wrong?
It's a report from the hospital.
There's been an outbreak
of plague in the city!
What? The plague?
Even the people carrying the infected
to the hospital have come down with it.
At this right, the plague will
spread to all of Tokyo...
No, maybe even all of Japan!
Yes? Rider Corps HQ.
Hongo...
Someone's been attacked
by a Gel Shocker monster!
Where?
Where's the Gel Shocker monster?
It was already gone when we arrived.
Hongo!
This is getting serious.
Our hated enemy, Hongo
Takeshi is flailing helplessly.
General Black!
It's time to wipe them out
with a concentrated strike.
Initiate phase two of Operation: Pet!
Sir.
I will send a cyborg
directly to Rider Corps HQ.
I'll finish off Hongo and his friends
by infecting them with the plague!
Well? Cute, eh?
Fancy mice are genuinely charming and cute.
It really is cute!
A mouse wouldn't make a bad pet at all.
Then you can have it.
Really?
Yeah, it's yours.
Thanks!
We'll take good care of it!
Let me see!
Hurry!
Can I see it?
Let me see it!
Well, isn't he cute?
The more I watch it, the cuter he looks!
Hey...
Does this mouse remind you of someone?
Yeah, actually!
Who is it?
Let's see...
It's just not coming to me...
What?
That expression!
A perfect match!
What are you talking about?
We're back!
Seems like you're having fun.
What's up?
Hey, who do you think
this mouse looks like?
A fancy mouse, eh?
Very cute...
What's the matter?
Hey.
That monster we fought before, Nezcondor...
It looked a bit like a mouse, didn't it?
Yeah? So what?
Rats spread the black plague.
Do you think that pet mouse might...
Well, I've never heard of pet
mice spreading the plague.
But, what if Gel Shocker
is controlling the mouse?
Let's head back!
Damn you!
You... darn monster!
The mouse is gone!
You won't get me!
I'll be back!
He runs fast. I'll give him that...
Pops, did he hurt you?
No, I'm fine.
But this is a tough monster
we're dealing with.
Don't underestimate him!
I can't believe they tricked us like this!
General Black, that was
a pathetic performance.
Are you simply helpless
before the Kamen Rider?
My leader.
I've reviewed the reasons
for Nezcondor's loss,
and equipped it with a more
powerful secret weapon.
It's only a matter of time before
the Kamen Rider falls to Gel Shocker.
If they create an effective vaccine,
they could overcome Nezcondor's
plague, too, couldn't they?
You should wait, sir, and watch
the enhanced Nezcondor in action.
He'll spread even more powerful bacteria
and turn Tokyo into a living hell.
Nezcondor, show our leader your power!
M-Monster!
H-Help me!
Hey! Come here and help me out!
Hey!
Hey, what's wrong?
That hurts...
KAMEN RIDER
H-Help me!
A m-monster...
Someone! Someone!
Darling... hang in there!
Hang in there, darling!
Daddy! Daddy!
Doctor.
Isn't there any way to relieve
his terror, at least?
I gave him a tranquilizer,
but it doesn't seem to help.
And we found non-plague germs
on the patient's fangs.
Non-plague germs?
Yes.
Is there a vaccine?
No...
What about his eyes?
The moment he was brought in,
we got some corneas from the eye
bank and gave him a transplant,
but he's acting so wild...
What he needs is rest.
Doctor. Another urgent patient.
What?
Taki.
Help me!
Hey. Are you all right?
H-Hey. What are you doing?
Stop it!
Let me go!
That was close.
We can't even transport
our patients like this!
How terrible.
We need...
We need to beat Nezcondor
as soon as possible.
A new antibiotic!
Pops!
I think I can make a vaccine
to resist the new bacteria.
Look!
We need to finish it as soon as possible!
Yes.
Hongo.
The trains have stopped.
What?
They think mice chewed through the cables.
Where?
Where is Nezcondor?
Hongo.
I'll gouge out your eyes so
that you can never fight again!
Then I'll infect you with my bacteria,
and let you die an agonizing death!
Hongo!
Let's get out of here!
Hang in there!
Will Mr. Takeshi be blind now?
No, it's a scratch on the
surface of my eyes, that's all.
It's okay.
But you need rest and
relaxation until you heal.
I can't rest until I defeat Nezcondor.
Don't push yourself too hard.
The vaccine will be finished soon.
Hang in there until then.
Leave Nezcondor to Taki.
It's a fancy mouse!
There's something on its tail!
Darn it... it bit me!
What is this?
"Taki is in our custody.
Hongo Takeshi, if you wish to save Taki,
come alone to the third sluice gate.
Nezcondor."
Damn him...
Mr. Takeshi, you need to rest!
You fool!
Where are you going in your condition?
It doesn't matter if my
vision is compromised.
As long as I can see a little, I can fight.
Stop it!
Mr. Hongo!
I can't abandon Taki!
Hey, wait!
Hey, Hongo!
Taki!
Where is Taki?
Hongo... you're practically blind!
You can't even see where Taki is!
Why did you come, you fool?!
Taki!
You really think you can
fight in your condition?
Nezcondor... you've underestimated me.
I'm no ordinary human.
Your poison won't affect me!
Rider Transformation!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider!
Hold it!
Rider, Rider!
Let's go!
Shocker is coming
It's payback time!
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
I can't see!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Let's go, Nezcondor!
Rider Jump!
Rider Lunar Kick!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo!
Hongo! Nezcondor is dead!
I see...
Hongo... can you see me?
I can't... I can't see anything!
Hang in there, Hongo!
Hongo!
Hey, Hongo!
It's a vaccine! The vaccine is complete!
Pops...
Here...
It'll fix your eyes!
Pops...
Gel Shocker's terrifying
Operation: Pet was foiled,
and Hongo Takeshi's eyes were healed.
But Gel Shocker would have more terrifying
monsters waiting in the wings.
Fight on, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Centipede Tiger.
Gel Shocker will form a Gel Shocker Kid Corps
to oppose the Kamen Rider Kid Corps,
to be positioned all over the country.
If anyone resists us, burn them to death!
Then we'll really make the Kamen Rider suffer!
Enroll in the
Gel Shocker Terror School!!
Go, Centipede Tiger!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!