KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Sea Snake Man of
the Ghost Village
That's a strange sound...
- Yeah, weird...
- Look out!
Hey!
You idiot!
Are you trying to get killed?
Sorry. Let me on!
The hell I will, jackass!
Please... I'm begging you!
Won't you take me somewhere
I can get a phone?
You're not a criminal on the
run, are you?
No, no!
I'm... a resident employee
of Okuyama Village.
A policeman, huh?
I've been through the most awful things...
you'd never believe it!
Okay, come on in.
Go on.
So, just what happened to you?
You guys wouldn't believe
me if I told you...
Our village just...
No, no, I need a phone, first.
There's a rest stop
just beyond that tunnel.
You can use the phone there.
That's weird...
there should be a rest stop here.
We just passed this way!
He's right... no way!
What are you doing?
Turn around!
You have to turn us around!
You're safe to back up!
Sea Snake Man's beams give him the
power to change the scenery around him.
I think we made it
through, this time.
Damn it!
What's wrong?
We're done for...
- He melted!
- He's melting!
A monster!
You will now die!
Drive... keep driving!
Tokyo <—> Osaka
There's nobody driving it!
- What's going on?
- That's weird!
There's no driver!
It's empty!
There's no one inside...
no driver!
That's quite enough!
It's much too early
for all this fuss!
I can't even read my newspaper.
It's all Goro's fault.
Goro's a lazybones anyway.
You should wake up earlier and help
me, or make breakfast some time!
I'm sorry.
But there's a reason I
slept in this time...
See, I...
It's been a while since I last
saw Pops in such a temper.
Goro...
are you making mischief again?
No!
I was doing my homework last night,
and I heard this late night news report...
You idiot!
You can't listen to the
radio while doing homework!
Just listen, okay?
There was this weird sound
that came over the broadcast,
and it turned into
these nonsense words...
Goro, what were the words?
Um...
I think... "Ka-tsu-yo-shi."
It kept repeating,
so I got curious.
Katsuyoshi?
Yeah.
That doesn't seem very strange.
Pops, don't you realize?
Realize what?
Katsuyoshi... Shocker.
Ka-tsu-yo-shi...
Shi-yo-tsu-ka...
Shocker!
Then Goro was hearing...
a Shocker message?
Some kind of
directive, no doubt.
That reminds me.
I saw the strangest article...
Shocker could be behind it, too.
This might be it.
"The Story of the Ghost Truck.
It raced down Route 246 at
full speed with no driver."
246?
Taki went out in that
direction this morning.
Taki did?
I was asked to help with the
plans for a new motocross course.
Taki took a helicopter to scope out
the proposed site for courses...
Hey! Hey, Takeshi!
Mountains, valleys, flatlands...
This will make a great course.
Villagers, in a place like that?
The sight of a helicopter shouldn't
be that surprising to them...
Strange.
Sea Snake Man has been equipped with
this Shocker invention, the prism eye.
It lets the beams he emits
deceive the human eye,
making them think the
scenery has changed.
Shocker intends to use this device to
spread mass panic all over the world.
Ambassador Hell,
Taki has arrived.
I see.
Taki, the perpetual thorn
in Shocker's side...
You're a moth flying
right into a flame!
Sea Snake Man.
Show that young man
what you can do.
Yes, sir.
Hey! Help!
Die!
A Shocker monster...
Of course.
Shocker's taken
over the village.
All right, here I come!
Shocker... where have you gone?
Show yourselves, Shocker!
Welcome, Taki.
This is a Shocker
cyborg training camp!
Training camp?
There you are, Shocker cyborg...
Get him!
Now, behold my power!
You will never
escape this place!
What happened to the helicopter
that flew towards Okuyama?
It would have to be
out of fuel by now...
You think it crashed?
Did you get any
reports about a crash?
No... nothing like that, yet.
The sound of an engine...
It's uninhabited!
There's no pilot!
There's no one on board!
There's no one there...
No pilot!
- It can't be!
- It's flying itself!
Hurry!
Be careful!
Get around behind it!
Check it out carefully!
I don't believe it...
No fuel, no pilot,
but it still landed!
Hey... that's strange.
You're sure of the flight plan?
He was set to take aerial
photos around Okuyama Village.
Shocker!
Damn...
Get him!
Where is Taki? Talk, now!
Hongo Takeshi.
Behold the power I've mastered
in the Shocker training camp!
Shocker training camp?
Rider Transformation!
You've come, Rider!
Sea Snake Man... tell me the
location of Shocker's training camp!
It would do you no good...
Because you will die here!
That is the power of
the training camp!
KAMEN RIDER
If I follow him back,
I can find the Shocker training camp.
It must be that village...
There's nobody here.
This is Taki's...
Taki must have landed here.
Help me...
Taki!
Taki... You're safe?
- Taki...
- I made it through, more or less...
You're okay?
I'm okay.
Takeshi, Shocker has
taken over the village.
They're using it as
a training ground.
Innocent people are being killed
every day by Sea Snake Man.
Taki, why haven't you escaped?
Shocker sees everything here.
But how did you get
here, Takeshi?
Sea Snake Man attacked me.
I played possum and
then followed him here.
Takeshi...
help these people, please...
Taki...
Hey, everyone,
we're getting out of here!
Come on,
Can we really escape?
Yes, of course we can!
Can we?
Yes, we can!
Okay! Let's get out of
here, everyone!
- Hurry!
Taki, are you all right?
Hurry!
Hold tight, okay?
Thanks...
- Hurry!
- Hurry up!
Are you all right?
Everyone hold hands
and stay close!
Hang in there!
It's no use...
we just can't do it.
It's the same thing
that always happens...
Wh-What's going on?
What's going on?
Taki,
can you handle things here?
Yes.
There must be a device
causing hallucinations...
I'll see if I can
find a way through.
Something's wrong, here...
What is that light?
Damn it...
They have power over
this area somehow...
Damn you, Sea Snake Man...
I see...
When his eyes reflect sunlight,
he generates illusions.
Hongo Takeshi,
you cannot escape!
Ambassador Hell,
what are you after?
What is the true purpose
of the training camp?
Fool.
You think I'd reveal
our secrets to you?
Sea Snake Man... finish him off.
Sea Snake Man...
Did you use that device
to create those illusions?
Brilliant as ever,
Hongo Takeshi.
You deduced the secret
of the prism eye.
Now, die!
Rider Transformation!
Damn you, Rider!
Get back here!
Hold it, Sea Snake Man!
Seems it's time for
the final battle...
Let's fight!
Indeed, Rider!
Come here!
We'll settle things now!
Try me!
Rider Back Jump!
Rider Kick!
I've finally defeated
Sea Snake Man!
Thank you so much.
Thank you for everything.
No, thank you.
We owe you so much...
No. It was your strength to
keep going through your fear
that drove the villain away.
Now, show us those smiles!
- Hey, you okay?
- Not really...
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
The power of the Kamen Rider
in defeating Sea Snake Man
restored peace to
the "ghost village."
But Shocker would continue to concoct
their dreadful plans in secret.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
Fight for justice and peace!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Cockroach Man!
His terrible white powder
causes humans to age to death.
Shocker's insatiable desire
for world domination continues.
Go, Kamen Rider!
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Cockroach Man!!
The Dreadful Germ-Stuffed Ad Balloon!"
Cockroach Man!! The Dreadful
Germ-Stuffed Ad Balloon!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!