KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monster Imoriges
Showdown at Hell Ranch!
Toru!
Hey, Hitomi! What's up?
What's up? You're so mean.
Huh? How?
Ever since you joined
the Rider Kid Corps,
you haven't played with me at all!
It's not like that...
Then what's it like?
You know a bunch of people have
gone missing in this town lately, right?
Yeah. My papa said the same thing.
Everyone who works at the ranch goes
missing and he doesn't know what to do.
I want to find out what's behind it.
It's gotta be Shocker!
What's wrong?
Monster!
Hey!
You monster!
We have no use for women and children.
Shocker kills those it has no use for!
Damn... Michiko!
Well?
Do you see what I can do?
Take him away!
You murderer!
I knew it was a Shocker
monster behind this...
I'd better contact HQ!
You'd better make it back
to the Kamen Rider Kid Corps HQ.
Got it?
Kamen Rider Kid Corps
Headquarters
Hey, a pigeon's arrived!
- I'll handle it.
- Right!
Contact number 512.
"Shocker monster sighted.
Come at once. Toru."
Hey, where was 512?
512 is Ikaho.
I'll get going now.
You tell Hongo.
Okay, good luck.
Mr. Taki, where are you going?
Just out, to a hot spring.
Hey, take us with you!
No fair!
No kids.
Please.
We're members of the
Kamen Rider Kid Corps, too!
Hey, where's Mr. Taki really going?
Ikaho.
It's normally an unremarkable ranch.
But beneath it, we're
building an airport facility.
Yet Kamen Rider has no idea!
This is the airport.
Once it's finished,
we can house hundreds
of supersonic fighters,
which will rain bombs down
on cities all over Japan.
At last, Japan will belong to Shocker!
Imoriges.
Use your ability to travel
wherever there's water,
and bring me the men I need.
We must complete the
airport as quickly as possible!
What's going on?
Things are awfully loud in that barn...
I'm gonna go look!
Here we go...
What's all this?
M-Monster!
- Monster!
- You're coming with Shocker!
Let me go!
Papa!
Hitomi! Get away, quickly!
You little brat...
Now that you've seen me, you must die!
Get her!
Help! Someone help!
Someone help!
Ow!
Someone help! Stop it!
Hold it!
Help! No! Stop it!
It hurts! Stop it!
Come on.
All right...
Now, hold on tight! Let's go!
Okay!
Hitomi! Hitomi!
Where could she have gone?
Hello? Where are you going?
The hotel.
You'd better turn back.
This town is finished.
A monster's been abducting people.
Damn you, Shocker...
Yes. It's true.
We've already had a few dozen victims.
I've remained here to do my duty,
but I'll probably leave tomorrow.
I see.
But why did they choose this area?
Okay, I'll stop by Toru's house.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Halt, intruder!
There you are, boss!
Oh, it's you two...
Why are you dressed that way?
Remember? This is Kunisada
Chuji's birthplace.
Come on out, Toru!
So you're Toru, then?
Yes.
We got your message.
What kind of monster did you see?
What's that sound?
I welcome you, Taki!
But you're all going to die here!
That's a Shocker monster...
Where could it be?
Call me Imoriges!
Show yourself!
Over there!
Don't move, or the child dies!
Naoki!
Get them!
Let go! Let go!
He came here with the light...
Hold it, Imoriges!
Who is he? Who is he?
Rider! Come to meddle again, have you?
Who is this man of light,
who sends the darkness scattering?
Taki, take them to safety!
Got it!
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for anger!
Jump! Dive!
Slam into them!
Give it all you've got! Rider Kick!
Hit them with the force of a storm!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!
He came here in a roar...
Rider... it's time you see what I can do!
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of lamentation,
who brings evil plots to light?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for strength!
Fly! Run!
Get the dynamo humming!
Full charge! Full charge!
Your body is going to melt away!
Hit them with an engine's roar!
It won't be that easy...
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider!
Taki!
Take this, you jerk!
Rider... this isn't over!
We did it!
Yeah!
Toru!
Hey, Hitomi! Where have you been?
Mr. Hongo saved me!
Mr. Takeshi is here, too?
Say, you're bleeding!
I'm okay.
It doesn't even hurt!
Taki, get treatment for Hitomi's wound.
Got it.
We'll be waiting at Hotel Tenbo.
Right.
Here we go!
Okay!
KAMEN RIDER
At last, I will put an end to Rider!
Just watch me!
Where is their home base?
And why are they
kidnapping all those people?
I don't even know what they're after...
Well, Hitomi's injury wasn't serious.
Should we get her back to the ranch?
Yes, poor thing.
Getting wrapped up in something so awful...
She must be exhausted,
mentally and physically.
Hitomi. Where are you going?
I'm going back home by myself.
Why?
Because I left home
without telling my big sister!
She's gotta be really worried about me!
Good point.
I'll walk you home, then!
Thanks!
Pursue them. Go!
Emergency! Emergency!
Mr. Taki! Mr. Hongo! Emergency!
Hitomi's missing!
Hitomi?
We can't find Toru, either.
You're members of the Rider Kid Corps,
yet you let them escape your notice?
We're sorry...
They don't have anywhere
to go but back to the ranch.
I'm worried. Let's follow them.
Listen.
You two stay here, in the hotel.
Okay.
We'd better take back our lost honor!
Yeah!
Hiroko!
- Hitomi!
- Big sis!
Where have you been? I was so worried...
Sis, save me!
Let me go!
Let go!
They'll make valuable hostages!
Take them away!
Stop it!
Rider!
This time, I will end you!
There's something off here.
Yeah. Let's check it out.
Let's look back there.
No one's here.
Hongo Takeshi.
If you wish to save the
woman and the children,
come alone to Hell Valley
at sunrise tomorrow.
Damn you, Shocker...
Hell Valley, then?
You came, Hongo.
Shocker.
Where are Hitomi and the others?
I came alone.
All right.
I'll let you have them.
Look over there!
Shocker... where are the others?
I have them working as slaves,
to build an airport under this ranch!
An underground airport...
So that's your game.
All right.
Return them to me, now!
Do it!
- It's hot!
- Hitomi!
- Hold it!
Who is that?
Who are you?
Show your face!
Taki!
Leave this to me!
Damn...
Imoriges...
I'll show no mercy this time!
Hurry!
Rider Transformation!
No... I will not let Rider beat me!
Damn...
Rider Kick!
Not again... I must not be
defeated by the likes of Rider!
Rider Screw Kick!
Rider!
Taki, look out!
Damn you, Rider...
Soon, you'll see my true power!
Thank you for everything.
Naoki, Mitsuru. Take care.
Take care!
Bye-bye!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
The danger has passed.
But Shocker would create a new monster
and attempt world domination once again.
Ride on, our Kamen Rider... Hongo Takeshi!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
I cause human bodies to melt into mud...
The sea urchin monster,
Unidogma has arrived!
The mystery of the wooden
box resting in the eerie grave...
Stay tuned to this channel next week for "The
Terrifying Unidogma + Ghost Monsters."
The Terrifying Unidogma
+ Ghost Monsters"
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!