KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Tsuchigumo Man
Dokumond
What an eerie night...
A liquid explosive that will
melt and burn all metal?
But Sawada...
completing this will lead to disaster!
No, I think it'll be useful
for industrial purposes.
Just wait and see.
Is that you, Minoru?
Sorry, Big Brother's
staying out late again.
That stinks.
I wanted you to help
me with my homework.
But if it's for your
research, I guess you gotta...
Good night, then.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I know.
Once this invention is complete,
I'll take him to the
mountains or something.
Well, I'm off for the night.
It's just not working...
It worked!
I've done it!
Who's there?
Monster!
You saw me, did you?
Help me! Someone help!
I was sure I saw that
spider monster...
It's so strange...
Help me!
This terrifying monster is
Shocker's Tsuchigumo Man, Dokumond.
His invention is complete.
Then we should go.
Wait.
He's writing down his
research data now.
We'll take that in the morning.
Yes!
I've sorted out all the data
about the liquid explosive.
Morning already?
Give me that bag!
Damn it!
After him!
Don't let him escape! Get him!
Damn! You won't catch me!
Catch him! Catch him, quickly!
After him! Go after him!
What was that sound?
Hongo Takeshi...
Be on your guard!
Shocker!
What have you done?
Get him!
Die, Hongo!
Damn...
Rider Transformation!
Municipal Hospital
It'll be all right, Minoru.
He'll get better right away.
Director, can he be saved?
He's in very bad shape.
We've done one surgery,
but we need to leave him be overnight,
then do another surgery
in the afternoon to know.
I see...
Cheer up! It'll be okay!
Monster!
The monster... help me!
Sawada, speak to me!
- Big Brother!
- Help me!
Bring the instruments.
Yes, sir.
It's chasing me.
I'll never...
give you my research!
Sawada!
Go to it.
Damn you, Shocker...
So it's Sawada's
research they were after?
Fool!
You've failed completely!
Our plan to dissolve everything
in Japan made of metal...
everything from
ships to airplanes...
has gone up in smoke!
You failed to steal the research
data, and by killing Doctor Sawada,
you've ensured there's no one left who
can make more of the liquid explosive!
I'm very sorry.
You great fool!
You'll be put to death at once!
Wait. Doctor Sawada is still alive.
You must follow up
on your plan at once.
He's alive?
Does that mean Hongo saved him?
I have the perfect plan in mind.
We'll extract his brain before he
dies and turn him into a cyborg.
Then he'll have to make
the explosive for us!
Dokumond!
Abduct him from the
hospital at once!
Go!
How were things at the hospital?
They won't know until they do
the follow-up surgery tomorrow.
It's awful that Minoru's brother
has to go through this...
Could it be Shocker again?
Yeah.
They were after Sawada's data.
But the data burned
up in the car!
But Shocker won't give up that
easily, I'll bet.
Yes...
Only Sawada knows the
secrets of his research.
Shocker will surely
come after him again.
But Mr. Sawada is in a coma
in the hospital, isn't he?
Poor guy...
Knowing them,
they'll still try it.
Anyway...
will you look after Minoru?
We don't want him abducted.
Just leave it to us!
Right?
Cheer up, Minoru.
Okay!
Just you watch me...
They tricked us!
I've been waiting, Shocker.
I knew I'd find you behind this!
You wretch, Hongo Takeshi!
Behold the skills of the Tsuchigumo
Man, Dokumond!
Damn...
Rider Transformation!
Hey, Shocker!
I need a plan...
This isn't over!
Taki, you okay?
I'm fine.
They're awfully
persistent, aren't they?
Shocker never gives up easily.
KAMEN RIDER
What are they up to?
Stop!
What do you people want?
Get out of there.
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
You won't escape now!
Good morning.
- Excuse me, nurse.
- Yes?
Prepare the patient Sawada
for surgery at once.
Wasn't that scheduled
for this afternoon?
Just do it.
Right...
The director is acting strange.
Not at all like
his usual self...
Hey. Hey!
Sawada's getting surgery.
Wasn't it going to
be this afternoon?
Has he regained consciousness?
No, not yet.
Let's check it out.
Good morning.
There's been a change of plans.
I'm doing the surgery now.
I'll be the witness, then.
No, we don't need a witness.
But the regulations...
I'll call you in later, then.
I'll do the checkup
and anesthetic first.
Now,
get him to the operating room.
Yes, sir.
I don't like that director guy.
Yes... but he wasn't
acting like that yesterday.
Maybe that's just how
great doctors are.
2nd Operating Room
Surgery in Progress
Take the man at once.
That checkup is taking a long
time, isn't it?
Well, maybe that's just
how these things are.
Surgery in Progress
Damn... it's started already.
What's wrong?
Something's off about all this.
Hey. Are you sure about this?
We just have to try it!
Nurse! Nurse!
Speak to me!
Damn, they were disguised
as the director!
Damn you, Shocker!
Where did they take Mr. Sawada?
Listen to me.
Discard all other parts of his body.
Remove only the
brain for transfer.
Understood?
Where is the prisoner
set to receive it?
Help me!
Here he is.
Very good.
Prepare them for
surgery at once.
This is the Sawada household.
This is the hospital.
This is the director's house.
What do the three
have in common?
It's no use.
I think I'm barking
up the wrong tree...
It's already 11 o'clock.
We need to get him back
by noon for surgery,
or it'll be too late.
Big Brother... don't die!
Please, don't think like that.
I'm back!
Shouldn't you be
at the hospital?
Goro!
What's wrong with you?
Show a little respect!
At least for Minoru's sake.
What are you guys so mad about?
I went out to catch
spiders outside
to do research on that
Tsuchigumo spider monster.
You could at least
show some appreciation.
See?
Of course,
this isn't a Tsuchigumo spider, but...
That's it.
Goro, you did it!
How can spiders walk around on their
own webs without getting trapped?
It's because their feet
generate a special oil.
In other words, if I track
Dokumond's footsteps from the window,
I can find their base.
Can you really track
a spider's footsteps?
Rider Transformation!
As a cyborg, Hongo Takeshi possesses
eyes twenty times sharper than a human's.
All right, got it.
Begin the surgery.
Is this the place?
There you are, Shocker!
Fight me!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Taki, you handle things here!
Rider, Rider!
What's wrong?
The Kamen Rider is here!
Shocker is coming,
Get rid of him!
with its armies made of demons
Dokumond,
this is all on your head!
Kill him!
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Kamen Rider, step outside!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Kick!
You all right, Rider?
Look! Dokumond is finished!
The surgery saved
Doctor Sawada's life,
and his research on the liquid
explosive was protected.
But there was no telling how
long Shocker would continue
to challenge Hongo
Takeshi, the Kamen Rider.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Beaded Lizard Man.
Beaded Lizard Man spits a red venom
and our Kamen Rider uses his new
technique, the Head Crusher, to fight him.
Join us next week for
"The Monstrous Beaded Lizard Man.
Deathmatch in Fear Valley!!"
The Monstrous Beaded Lizard Man
Deathmatch in Fear Valley!!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!