KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
The secret organization Shocker
is plotting world domination.
This is Shocker's secret base.
Shocker employs transplants and
other techniques out of Nazi Germany
to create humans amplified with the
properties of insects and animals.
This is their latest creation:
a human scorpion.
The Monstrous Scorpion Man
Countless innocents made to do
hard labor in this base for
the Scorpion Man experiment
are to be executed,
simply for collapsing from exhaustion.
Mr. Fujisawa...
Are you all right?
For a failure to qualify
to become one of
our chosen cyborgs,
or even combatants
or technicians,
you will all be put to death.
But the great ruler of
all, Shocker,
will give you one last chance.
We will now release
you from your cell.
If, within the next ten minutes,
you can pass across the desert
and arrive in the safe zone,
we will ensure your freedom,
and no further harm will come to you.
Your ten minutes begins now.
Now... run through the desert.
Your lives are on the line!
Run...
Five minutes have now passed.
Please... take me with you!
Please!
Nine minutes have passed.
We will now begin the countdown.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Their sentence will be carried
out by man-eating scorpions.
Let man-eating scorpions
carry out the death sentence!
What did we do wrong?
Tell us!
I don't want to die!
Please, I don't want to die!
Spare us!
Please, spare us!
What an awful thing...
How can they be so merciless?
Did you see that?
The man-eating scorpions, a proud
invention by our Shocker scientists,
have passed the
human trial stage.
Their completion will deliver
the Earth into Shocker's hands.
Scorpion Man.
Execute Operation M1 at once.
Then destroy Hongo Takeshi!
Hongo Takeshi...
Killing that man is my
lone purpose in life.
First,
I will set some bait for Hongo.
That old man, there.
At that same time, Hongo Takeshi
was working with Tachibana Tobei,
his supporter, assistant, and
trainer, to test his cyborg prowess.
15.30 meters!
48.70 meters!
Rider Kick!
Wow! Look at that
destructive power!
Hongo's superpowers definitely come
from that wind turbine in his belt.
This is the source of
your superhuman abilities.
It appears so.
The wind spins the dynamo,
which builds up energy,
which is transferred to
my enhanced musculature.
It's utterly incredible.
You've always had exceptional
reflexes and stamina.
Those traits have been artificially
enhanced, giving you unfathomable power.
With training,
you could likely grow even stronger.
Boss!
Strange news came in.
Strange news?
To repeat that last story,
ten bodies found adrift off
the coast of the Boso Peninsula
disappeared immediately
after discovery.
The local Nagahama Police believe
that a fishing boat capsized,
and the disappearance was the result
of long-term weathering at sea,
but the Coast Guard
has received no report
of any such vessels capsizing
over the last few months...
Could Shocker be behind this?
Yes.
I'm going to go to Nagahama.
Mr. Hongo, take me with you.
I thought you killed my
father, and I hated you for it.
But now that I know it was really
that awful organization, Shocker...
I want to help you, to make up for the
trouble I've caused you in the past.
That's not a wise idea.
If anything were to happen to
you, your late father...
No, I believe he'd allow me.
I won't let you.
Mr. Hongo...
Mr. Tachibana, I'm leaving now.
Chiba Prefecture Nagahama Police Station
Let me go! They'll kill me!
They'll kill me!
Someone save me! Save me!
He was babbling about "Shocker"
being behind the recent incident.
Shocker?
Who was that old man?
He apparently escaped
from a mental institution.
Some men from their
staff came to fetch him.
He seems pretty convinced they'll
kill or experiment on him...
Please... let me go!
I won't say anything.
I won't talk to anyone!
Spare me!
Please, let me go!
Let me go!
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
It's the Kamen Rider!
Attention, Shocker!
I'll be taking that
valuable witness with me!
KAMEN RIDER
It will be dawn soon.
Shocker wants to destroy this
peaceful town and its people,
and bend all of
society to their whims.
Nobody knows about the evil
they get up to in secret.
They wouldn't believe
me if I told them!
That is why I must fight.
This poor old man is just
one of those I must save.
I don't know.
I don't know anything...
Mr. Ito.
You need to hang in there.
The lights! Turn on the lights!
Right! Right!
Please!
Hongo...
Hayase?
Let me go already, would you?
Hayase!
Hey... What brings you here?
I'm so sorry.
But it's been a
while, hasn't it?
I brought him here.
Boss told me to.
Ruriko...
Mr. Tachibana told you to?
Who are these people?
Don't you worry.
This is Hayase Goro.
He's my best friend.
And this is Midorikawa Ruriko.
Ruriko's father was
also killed by Shocker.
I'll help you out from now on.
No matter what you need, Hongo.
I feel a lot better
having you here.
Let me introduce you, Ruriko.
This man is my racing rival,
and also my best friend.
He calls me his rival, but on race
days, he always beats me by a nose.
I got so frustrated, I went away for
a while to learn some new techniques.
Mr. Ito.
There are all these
people here for you.
Please, take heart.
You're safe, Mr. Ito.
We won't let these Shocker
guys lay one finger on you.
I see that now!
Look out!
Scorpions!
Stay in this room.
Wait.
I'll go this way.
Okay.
I hope those two are all right.
The enemy they're
fighting is merciless.
I'm sure they'll be
fine, Mr. Ito.
A scorpion!
The terrible
man-eating scorpions!
Man-eating scorpions?
My dear!
Mr. Ito!
No!
Ruriko!
Hongo!
They took Ruriko in a car!
I'll go after them!
Good!
Hayase, should we take them?
Hold off.
If we just tail them,
we might learn where Shocker's base is.
Good idea!
Tell us where Hongo is!
Where is Hongo?
How should I know?
Talk or you die!
Hayase... go save Ruriko!
Hurry!
All right... Shocker combatants
never act without a commander.
Where is your Shocker commander?
Hayase...
Listen, Hongo.
Hayase Goro is no
longer my name.
I am now Scorpion Man,
a Shocker commander!
You...
I joined Shocker of
my own free will.
I allowed them to alter me
so that I could
finally beat you!
And now at last, I have won!
Look there, Hongo!
Hayase...
I'll do whatever
it takes to win.
Soon, Hongo...
You'll learn the might of
the man-eating scorpions!
Damn it!
Hurry!
Get them!
Hide. Hurry!
Hayase, stop this!
Snap out of it!
I don't want to
fight my best friend!
Get him!
Hayase!
I'll say this just once...
Return to the man you once were!
Rider Scissors!
The terrifying man-eating scorpions
vanished when Scorpion Man did.
But Shocker was honing its
claws for another strike.
What fate awaits Takeshi and Ruriko,
his friend and new assistant?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin Shocker
HQ sends for our Kamen Rider
is the man-eating Sarracenian.
What horrors will this man transformed
into a carnivorous plant bring to bear?
Shocker lashes out with a
new, eerie plan.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
See you next week
for more Kamen Rider,
in "The Man-Eating Sarracenian."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!