KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Gel Shocker's
Deliveryman of Death!
Hosoya
No one's there.
What's this?
When did it get here?
This is...
We of Gel Shocker mourn the
death of Hosoya Tsutomu,
head of the Japanese Industrial Society.
November 25th at midnight...
The 25th is tonight.
What's going on here?
Who would play such a prank?
Who's there?
You will die... that is why I am here!
It disappeared!
Hosoya Tsutomu.
Death itself is here for you!
Who are you?
Why do I have to die?
Don't bother resisting.
When you're on Gel Shocker's
death list, you die.
And I, Spiderlion, am your executioner!
Help me!
What's the matter?
A monster... it's trying to kill me!
What?
Wh-What are you doing?
Gel Shocker always gets what it wants.
Y-You mean, you're...
H-Help me!
The first page of the
assassination list is complete.
General Black.
Your Operation: T3...
In other words, your plan to assassinate
the leaders in various fields across Japan
has been analyzed
carefully by our computers,
and approved.
My leader.
The tests have already been run.
Now that my plan is approved,
I'll move it into action in force.
See that it is done.
And deploy Gel Shocker's robots.
Page two of the assassination list
begins with the chair of the Japanese
Science Academy Cooperative,
Doctor Aono Kiyoshi.
Ridiculous.
Come in.
Excuse me, sir.
- Oh, all right.
- Your car is ready.
You take care of this.
Of course, sir.
Er...
Has someone passed away?
Someone's just playing a prank.
It says I'm going to die in an hour.
Modern science isn't advanced enough to
predict the hour of a person's death.
It's certainly funny.
Doctor...
Damned Gel Shocker...
now they're after Doctor Aono?
I remembered that my little brother was
a member of the Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
Right.
So, where's Doctor Aono now?
The academy meeting
should be over now, so...
He should be heading home around now.
Twenty minutes until his predicted death.
Yuri.
It's hard to believe, of course.
Well, it's Gel Shocker we're dealing with...
We have to assume they'll
go through with it.
Chairman, we should contact Captain
Taki and Mr. Hongo at once.
I've already taken care of it.
Hey. This isn't the right way.
This is the right way, Doctor Aono.
You're not Yamada.
Did you know, Doctor?
The time of your death
is five minutes from now.
You... are you planning to kill me?
You should stop talking now, Doctor.
General Black...
I'm leading him to the designated location for
the second entry on the assassination list.
Good. Everything is in place.
General Black.
Yes?
General, someone's tailing the car.
What?
Get the combatants in position!
Those two blips will be Taki and Hongo.
Taki.
It's one minute to the time
Gel Shocker predicted for his death.
Right. Hey, it's turning.
Doctor, hurry!
Right!
Doctor Aono, we're here to save you.
Thank you!
Get to safety, quickly!
Not so fast!
Doctor Aono!
There you are...
I've been waiting!
Doctor Aono,
your death will come right on time!
You...
You can't escape me!
Doctor!
Doctor Aono!
A Gel Shocker cyborg, eh?
Indeed!
Combining the physical strength of
a lion and the abilities
of a spider... Spiderlion!
You're not on the assassination list,
but I will deal with you, regardless!
Are you the one behind the
predicted assassinations?
There's nothing Gel Shocker cannot do!
Rider Transformation!
KAMEN RIDER
Listen to me, Kamen Rider...
You can try to interfere,
but our assassinations
will continue unabated!
Rider, where's Doctor Aono?
I'm afraid I was too late.
Damn...
But we'll stop their next
predicted assassination!
I dozed off there...
We're back.
Hey, you two.
For Pops?
The third person on Gel Shocker's
assassination list is Pops?
What?
Tonight at midnight...
Should I make reservations
at the temple, then?
Pops, this is no time for jokes!
Come on, don't sound so scared.
You're here with me, right?
I don't have anything to fear.
But...
We can't underestimate that Spiderlion.
Spiderlion?
Yeah...
Taki...
This is our best chance to take
out Spiderlion once and for all.
We should move Pops to a safe place first.
No, it's going to play out the
same no matter where we are.
It won't be that easy to fool them.
It's best if we stay here and wait.
I trust my life to your hands.
Taki. I'm going to check
on things out front.
Hey, look! I'm still alive!
See? Nobody came at all!
They got us all riled up for nothing.
But Gel Shocker wouldn't make
that prediction for nothing.
That message was about tonight, right?
Yes, it was...
What is it?
Your name's gone!
What does it mean?
It's just a cruel prank.
Hongo Takeshi
"Hongo Takeshi"!
Oh no...
Gel Shocker's real target is Hongo!
No, Kamen Rider!
Wait!
Where is he?
Where is Spiderlion?!
I see... he's here, is he?
Why don't you take me to him?
Go on...
Welcome, Kamen Rider.
Spiderlion... show yourself!
Listen closely, Rider.
The third entry on the assassination
list is not Tachibana Tobei.
What?
The name on the third page,
Kamen Rider... is yours!
I see.
Is that why you lured me out?
I will now take you to Gel Shocker's
13th execution cell.
Kamen Rider.
Your death will come
at 6:00 in the morning.
What?
Have a nice rest with that
sleeping gas in the meantime.
- Damn.
- Wait...
Wait...
Help me! You can't mean to kill me!
You fool.
You think we'd hesitate to kill you
if it meant killing the Kamen Rider?
Good morning, Kamen Rider.
It's time for your execution.
Enjoy a nice, leisurely death, won't you?
H-Help me!
Stop this!
Stop it!
Stop...
The Kamen Rider is dead!
Raise the ceiling and check!
Not even the Kamen Rider could escape
Gel Shocker's predicted assassinations.
Your predicted assassination
has failed, Spiderlion!
Y-You...!
How did you survive being
skewered by the spikes?!
I can easily break spikes
as brittle as these!
Damn you, Rider!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Die!
That trick won't work a second time!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Swimming through the
oceans with a Rider Swim,
Rider... this time, I will end you!
a great dive flitting
through the sea!
Rider Flying Chop!
Calling up whirlpools
with a Rider Screw!
Dragging enemies down
with a Rider Lung!
The Kamen Rider could not afford to die.
Oh, oh Rider!
He foiled Gel Shocker's assassination plan,
Kamen Rider!
and kept his promise to keep us safe.
Ride on!
Maintain your forward momentum
to protect justice and peace!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Good evening, everyone. Hongo Takeshi here.
Let's hear about next week's
story from Director Tsukada.
Next week's story is about Catgecko, a
monster that can jump out of paintings.
Do any of you have paintings
of cats in your house?
The monstrous Catgecko might
just jump out of them.
Eerie
The Bloodthirsty Black Cat Paintings!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!