KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Defeat It
Double Riders!! Siomaneking
Did you get a bite, Professor?
It's pulling! It's pulling hard!
This is a big one!
What in the world?
Is that a big one, Professor?
Professor. Give it your best, would you?
Japan's great oceanographer,
Professor Sakai,
isn't much of a fisherman, I see.
Oh, please...
You'd better catch something
to impress your wife and son!
What's that?
What was that?
Monster!
Get it, Tanaka!
Damn you, monster!
Professor Sakai...
I have business with you!
Monster!
Professor, you will come with me.
The Katsuura region is also
known as Kii no Matsushima.
Tsurushima, Kameshima...
There are all kinds of islands around here.
And the valleys are all
bubbling up with hot springs.
Nachi Falls is very popular.
To your right, you can see the open sea.
The sea is vast and large...
It's a beautiful area, isn't it?
Yes, the famous Pacific
Ocean. It's quite large, isn't it?
Isn't this a great view?
It feels great to be freed
from the world of asphalt.
It's nice to take things easy.
What? What's that boat?
What?
Look. That boat there!
Looks like a fishing boat...
No one's on board...
It's acting strange.
You think it was set adrift?
But to have nobody on board...
Captain.
What is it?
I see a strange boat there.
Could we stop a minute?
I see a strange boat.
A strange boat?
Why not cooperate already, Professor?
Never!
But I thought you'd long had a dream
to build cities on the ocean floor,
ranching fish and farming seaweed.
The real issue is who was
on that fishing boat.
Who was it?
The oceanographer Professor
Sakai and his assistants.
His wife and child are
staying in the hotel.
I know Professor Sakai.
He's Masao's dad!
Masao?
Yeah, I met him in the hotel.
We're friends now.
Do you think they heard
about what happened?
They're not in the hotel now.
They went to see the whale museum in Taiji.
Taki's searching for them now.
Whale Museum
Mama, aren't they big?
They certainly are.
Mama, let's go to the aquarium!
Hurry!
Mama, there's fish swimming everywhere!
Aren't they beautiful?
It's like we're at the bottom of the ocean.
I wonder what that one's called.
There's sharks, too! Wow!
A monster!
What's wrong, Masao?
I... I just saw a scary monster!
I don't see anything...
That's weird...
Dolphins are smart, huh?
That's right. Your father said that.
He wants to train dolphins
to guard the fish ranches.
If that happens, I'm going to get
an aqualung and become a sea cowboy!
Masao, hurry! Hurry!
Hurry!
Come on!
Come on, hurry!
Come on, Masao!
Keep going!
Hang in there, Masao!
I'm taking you to meet Professor Sakai.
Come with me!
Mama! I'm scared!
Take them along.
Wait!
Damn you, Shocker... where
have you taken the Professor?
Get him!
Wait, you!
Taki! I'll fight you!
Hold it!
Hongo!
Hongo Takeshi!
I am Siomaneking...
Fight me!
Gladly, Siomaneking!
Taki, take them to safety!
Right!
A formidable opponent...
Well? Impressed by my power, are you?
Rider Transformation!
Let's go, Rider!
Die, Rider!
Damn you... this isn't over!
Wait, you!
KAMEN RIDER
Ma'am.
Do you have any idea why Shocker
might be after Professor Sakai?
I'm afraid not.
What was he studying?
My husband's passion project
was the creation of underwater cities.
Underwater cities?
This is just what he told me,
but it was an underwater
ranch for cultivating fish,
and an underwater farm
for raising seaweed...
And what was the other thing?
Underwater oil fields and mines!
That's right! It was an underwater
city built around those things!
Very impressive! Absolutely brilliant!
Isn't that wonderful?
Hongo, that's what Shocker's after, I bet!
I see...
So they're planning to
build an underwater city.
We need to foil their plan
and rescue the professor ASAP...
But where could their base possibly be?
Yeah, that's the big question.
I've got no idea!
I wonder where Papa is...
I hope he's all right...
What was that sound?
Mama!
Masao! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
I'm scared, Mama!
There's nowhere left for you to run!
This way! Hurry!
Masao!
- Masao!
- Mama!
Let's go, Taki!
Taki! Taki!
Masao!
Taki!
Where could Masao and his mother have gone?
No sign of Taki, either...
Hongo! Look! Over there!
Damn... this is serious.
What now?
I'll pursue. You call Hayato.
Right.
Rider Transformation!
That damned Rider is on his way...
You won't escape me, Shocker!
I knew you'd come, Kamen Rider...
Excellent.
Go!
Dear!
Papa!
Keiko! Masao!
Well, Professor Sakai?
Feel like working with us yet?
You cowards...
Shocker will do anything
to achieve its goals.
Well? Will you help us?
You stubborn fool!
Proceed, Siomaneking!
Masao! Masao!
Help us, dear!
Well, Professor Sakai?
Masao! Masao!
Damn you...
Kill that man!
I'll kill you first. Die!
Rider!
You've shown yourself, Kamen Rider...
But your coming was predicted.
Behold!
Damn...
Don't struggle, or I'll throw you off!
You cowards!
They won't survive a fall
into the ocean from there.
Surrender at once!
Hayato!
Transform!
Taki! Get the doctor to safety!
Right!
That's perfect.
We can finish off both Riders at once!
Kill them! Kill them!
Hongo!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Where have you gone, Rider?
Rider Kick!
Show yourself!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Hayato!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Rider Throw!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
- Now!
- Right!
Rider Double Kick!
We did it!
Curse you, Riders!
It's not safe here. Hurry!
Come on! Hurry!
We did it!
The duel between the two Riders
and Shocker in the southern Kii Peninsula
ended with the Riders triumphant.
Summer tranquility returns
to the Kumano-nada Sea,
but Shocker will surely attack Japan again.
We'll be counting on you then, our Riders!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
As blood banks are attacked,
the sound of someone licking
their lips can be heard.
Blood-sucking monster Shiraculas
gets its hands around Rider's neck.
Next time: "The Deadly Blood-Sucker!!
Give It Your All, Rider Kid Corps."
Let us watch!
The Deadly Blood-Sucker!!
Give It Your All, Rider Kid Corps
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!