KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Man-Eating Flower
Dokudalian
Put that one in, too!
My sister really loves those...
Oh, you're giving them to your sister?
Yeah, it's her last birthday
before she gets married!
Oh, a much older big sister? I see.
That will be 500 yen.
Here.
And I'll give you this as a bonus.
Oh, thank you so much!
It's a present from me to your sister.
Thank you so much.
This makes thirteen.
This woman is the Shocker
monster Dokudalian.
A 200 year old woman—no,
a 200-year-old carnivorous flower
from the jungles of New Guinea,
converted into a monster by Shocker.
Here, Big Sis.
Thank you.
I'll never forget this beautiful bouquet.
Oh, Sis, you're all sentimental...
Of course I am.
Just because you're getting married
doesn't mean we're not sisters anymore.
Akko...
Big Sis!
What is that?
I'm scared!
Sleep... sleep...
Now, collapse, and sleep...
Akko! Akko!
The sleep waves worked, I see...
Take her.
Hello, hello, turtle man!
Turtle man, my friend!
Somewhere in the world...
Hey, taxi!
Gimme a ride!
Huh?
That's a weird uniform for a taxi driver...
But you can't refuse service to me...
Ow!
Say... that's assault,
you know! It's not nice!
Monster!
The terrible man-eating flowers
of New Guinea earn their name
from the way they draw in
and absorb any humans who get near.
In other words, they break down
animal proteins to sustain themselves.
You now work for Shocker!
Shocker's reason for kidnapping all
women was to have them create poisons.
Delicate fingers were required
to create crystallized poison
from the poison flower extract.
Poison flower extract is pouring in
from our New Guinea Branch.
Kidnap more women, and proceed
quickly with creating the poison.
We're almost finished, Colonel Zol.
One drop of a suspension of this
poison can kill one hundred people.
If we convert that suspension into a mist
and disperse it secretly
in the air late at night,
then no one will wake up in the morning.
We can kill an entire city overnight!
I call it Operation: Poison Smog.
And on that day, Shocker
will conquer the world!
Shall we test the death smog
on one of the prisoners, then?
Let me go!
Magnificent!
Shocker does not look kindly on failures.
Dokudalian, realize that death awaits
you if your operation does not succeed.
Sis! Big Sis!
The plant is gone, too...
Big Sis!
- Big Sis!
- Look out!
It's not safe to run out into the street.
I'm sorry...
What's got you all worked up?
I think something bad
happened to my sister...
Hey...
What's this?
Leaves from my plant...
But this is a man's clothing.
It was my sister who went missing,
but my plant went missing, too!
Its leaves looked like this!
Jonan University Biochemistry Laboratory
I don't understand it.
This leaf contains a tremendous
amount of animal proteins.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's less like a plant and more
like a carnivorous beast.
But there are carnivorous
plants out there, aren't there?
Not very many. That's the point.
And it's toxic on top of that...
it's a dangerous plant.
I see.
So the man wearing this clothing
might have been eaten by this plant.
What did you say?
That flower ate a human?
The florist is across that street.
Okay, go for it.
I'll wait here. Go buy
yourselves some flowers, okay?
Leave it to us!
I'm worried about those two.
They'll probably slip up
and give away the plan.
They'll stand out less than you would.
Anyway, take Akko home
and hurry back, would you?
I'm worried.
Okay!
Excuse us!
We'd like some flowers...
Yuri! I bet that's it!
It's just how the little
girl described it...
You want that one?
Dear ladies of the
Tachibana Racing Club...
You've come right to me...
Shocker!
Taki!
Wait!
Hayato!
I'll dine on you!
Just as Koike said...
KAMEN RIDER
Transform!
Rider!
Mari and Yuri are in danger.
All right. Let's go!
"Store for rent"...
Oh no!
Damn you, Shocker!
What are they kidnapping
those young women for?
You're working too slow!
Can't you go any faster?
Another one succumbed to the poison...
Dispose of her at once!
Help me!
So that's the way in...
Hold on. Leave it to me.
I see. They're making poison...
That must be Akko's sister.
Hey! Get going, everyone!
Get to safety!
Mari! Yuri!
Look at this!
You want me to feed
them to Dokudalian?
Wait!
What do you want from me?
You've got a few brain cells
in your head, at least...
Don't let them get away!
Run!
Damn you...
Do it!
Hayato!
I doubt he's been captured, but...
He's been in there a long time, though.
Think we should bust in there?
Let's give him a little while longer.
Mr. Tobei. Mr. Taki.
Those aren't our names.
Who are you, exactly?
Ichimonji Hayato and the girls
are waiting for you in a certain location.
Monster!
I guess they came in disguise, too...
Hang on, Pops.
It might be more fun
to go along with them.
But Taki...
We can die after we see the others.
How very brave of you!
Now, show them!
Light it!
Taki!
Nice work, Pops! Taki!
All right...
Almost there...
Transform!
Is it just you?
Big Sis...
So pretty!
All happiness to you.
Thank you so much.
Write to me a lot, okay, Sis?
Her husband's a lucky man!
Yeah, I agree...
Kamen Rider defeated
the man-eating flower monster
and foiled her poison smog plan.
But what terrible thing
would Shocker try next?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the steel monster Armadillong.
The destructive steel beast's
plan to conquer Japan
involves blowing up gasholders.
Ichimonji Hayato and his
allies must put a stop to it.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Steel Monster Armadillong"!
Steel Monster
Armadillong
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!