KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Kurage Wolf
The Rush Hour of Terror
Awaken.
It's time to open your eyes.
Fusion of man, jellyfish and
wolf, Kurage Wolf...
Awaken!
You are the product of
perfect data assembled
by Gel Shocker's incomparable
biologists and computers.
You will demonstrate your
power for our leader at once!
Hayasaka Power Station
Hey, what's that sound?
I'm not sure.
It's the signal for a drop in voltage...
Hey!
Look! The voltage... the
high-voltage current is dropping!
There must be a breakdown somewhere.
Let's run some tests.
Right!
- This must be the place.
- Yeah.
M-Monster!
You think you can escape me?
Face my incredible power!
Go!
Magnificent.
He can isolate the current he absorbs
into positive and negative
charges inside his body,
letting him unleash a
powerful electrical discharge.
My leader!
His power would let him drop
a lightning bolt on Tokyo effortlessly!
Excellent.
Do you have a target in
mind, General Black?
Yes.
I have chosen Shinjuku Station.
Behold...
Shinjuku Station
Two million people pass through here during
the morning and evening rush hours.
A properly timed strike
would inspire mass panic!
My leader, it is as you see.
General Black, we've
spotted a boy at the site.
What?
That's not good. He might have seen it.
Investigation team!
Look into that boy at once!
Choco, it's bad for your
health to eat so much.
Yeah, it's bad for your skin, too.
Fall is the season for food!
And they say a person's appetite
is the barometer of good health.
This means I'm the picture of health.
Good morning, Chairman.
Good morning.
Where are Hongo and Taki?
They haven't arrived yet.
I knew it!
That means that I don't
have time to goof off!
Chairman, what are you
in such a hurry about?
Read a newspaper for once!
Fine...
What is it?
Here it is!
"Autumn Night Mystery!
Unexplained Power Outage."
"Two employees of Hayasaka
Power Station have gone missing."
Hayasaka Power Station
Hongo! Where are you?
Pops!
Hey.
Where's Taki?
He went to the police to learn more.
I see.
What's that?
A scrap of tattered clothing.
It probably belonged
to one of the employees.
You think the employees were incinerated?
Or electrocuted.
But look at how tattered it is...
It's hard to believe.
But if they were both struck with a
high-voltage current, like a lightning bolt,
it's possible.
Gel Shocker, you think?
It very well could be.
Hey, what are you doing?
Come with us.
No way!
Just come along!
What are you doing?
A bunch of monsters!
Damn you...
Mr. Policeman!
Mr. Policeman, help!
What's wrong, kid?
A bunch of monsters are after me!
A bunch of monsters?
C'mon, kid...
It's true! Up there!
So, where are the monsters?
They're probably hiding!
Hiding?
Come on... there are no
monsters in this city.
Forget you!
Hey, kid!
Darn it...
Hey, wait!
What's wrong with you?
A bunch of monsters are after me!
What are you doing, Mitsuru?
I'll take your place.
While I do that, you let HQ know.
Got it, Naoki?
Mitsuru!
Okay!
What? Mitsuru took his place?
All right. Understood.
Let's go, Taki!
I think I lost 'em.
Well, better get going!
Hey, it's the wrong kid!
Damn... where did the other one go?
Dang it! Let me go!
Talk! Talk, or we'll kill you!
Wait! Don't kill him!
He's a member of the Rider Kid Corps!
He'll prove useful. Take him away!
Now search for the missing whelp!
Let me go!
Not so fast!
Taki! Take Mitsuru to safety!
Right!
Hongo!
Get away, quickly!
Taki! Take Mitsuru and go!
Hongo... how do you like
the feel of a 100,000 volt shock?
Have you lost your mind, Hongo?
Damn you, Hongo...
Have you forgotten?
I'm no ordinary man... I'm a cyborg!
What?
Rider Transformation!
I knew it... it does work!
Now's my chance to kill you! Die!
Rider Knee Block!
Kurage Wolf...
we'll finish this another time!
Damn... he got away!
KAMEN RIDER
- Mr. Hongo!
- What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Where are Taki and Mitsuru?
They're not back yet.
Where's Pops?
He went to Shinjuku Station.
Shinjuku?
He went to meet a friend.
Mr. Nakamura, he said.
An old friend from his racing
days, he said.
Shinjuku Station
You sure have changed.
Mr. Nakamura arriving on Alps Flight 3.
Mr. Nakamura. You have a phone call.
Mr. Nakamura. Mr. Nakamura.
I have a call. Could
you wait here a minute?
Sure. I'll bring the car around.
Hey, over here! Over here!
Tachibana!
Sorry about that!
What was the call about?
Nothing. Mistaken identity.
Really? Get in, then.
What was that strange shock?
That's odd...
I haven't turned the key,
but the engine's already on.
I might have to take
it in for a check up...
Well, let's head out.
We couldn't find Mr. Taki or Mitsuru.
Hey, you're all here.
Come on in.
Where's Taki?
He and Mitsuru are still out.
Where did they go?
Well...
Nowhere serious.
Really?
Allow me to make an introduction:
This is my best friend, Nakamura.
This is the Rider Corps.
Nakamura.
A pleasure.
Go on, sit down.
I'll make some tea.
What's wrong?
Where'd that electric charge come from?
I can hear an electric current...
As a cyborg, Hongo Takeshi's ears
are many times more powerful
than those of a normal human being.
It's coming from Nakamura.
That's strange...
What's wrong, Hongo?
Oh, nothing.
Look into this, would you?
Nakamura, let's go on in.
Let's swap some stories from the old days.
Here, I'll take your bag.
Look out!
- What are you doing?!
- Pops, he's a Gel Shocker monster!
Get back, everyone!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's true!
His touch is deadly.
You'll be electrocuted!
That's enough!
It's not safe, Pops.
Look carefully...
What's going on here?
Your end has come at last, Hongo.
Everyone... run away, quickly!
Hongo!
He's not breathing.
That's one obstacle out of the way.
Mr. Taki! Mr. Taki!
You fool!
Taki and the child are
already in our custody!
Get them!
Since you've interfered with us so often,
we'll execute Operation: Detonate Shinjuku
Station right in front of your eyes!
Be sure to watch closely.
Don't be stupid.
You can't make lightning that easily!
I see you don't know the
principle behind lightning strikes.
What are you talking about?
Any child knows that positive
and negative currents collide in the air
to make them happen!
Precisely.
My body can isolate positive
and negative electric currents.
In other words, my right arm is positive.
The left arm is negative.
Watch carefully!
Ready?
You expect it to be that easy, Kurage Wolf?
Rider!
That voice... the Kamen Rider!
Show yourself!
I see... so you can only use your power
if your arms can come together!
Impossible! I saw you die!
Where are you, Rider?!
Damned Rider...
You underestimated me, Kurage Wolf.
It's easy for me to feign death.
Damn. Get him!
Damn you... this isn't over!
Taki. See to the others.
Right.
Damned Rider...
I may have spotted his weak point,
but I still have a hard fight ahead...
Persistent fool.
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Damn you, Rider!
With my shining machine...
Shake him off!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Now, feel the extent of my power!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Swing!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Rider...
Don't you move!
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
Move, and he dies!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
I still have enough
power to kill one person!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Mr. Nakamura! Run!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
All right... Now!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Damn you, Rider...
Nakamura!
Hey, Nakamura!
Tachibana!
Thank you!
I'm so glad!
Where are the others?
I took them to HQ.
And the boy...
- Toru?
- Yeah.
He said he was going to join
the Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
I see.
Kamen Rider fought desperately
to see Kurage Wolf's hideous plan foiled.
But Gel Shocker was already
preparing their next move.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Servant of my beloved Geldam...
Let us celebrate the birth
of a new power, Inokabuton.
Now, awaken!
Throw Kamen Rider to the pits of hell!
Hongo Takeshi...
we'll meet again next week.
Monstrous Inokabuton,
Defeat Kamen Rider With Insanity Gas
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!