KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Hongo Takeshi
Becomes a Cactus Monster!?
Dear?
This arrived today.
The sender isn't marked, though.
What's this?
A package with no return address...
It's a bit unsettling, isn't it?
I've never seen a cactus like this before.
Never?
But you study them for a living... how
can there be a cactus you haven't seen?
Stand, Doctor Matsuda.
Stand, and come to me!
Doctor Matsuda.
Thank you for coming.
I'm going to turn you into Cactusbat,
a cyborg fusion of cactus and bat!
It seems a fitting role for
a man who dedicated his life
to the study of cacti.
Your body is already infused
with cactus extract, after all.
Begin the alterations!
Go, Cactusbat!
Kill Suzuki and Yasuoka of the Council
of Scientists For World Peace!
What's wrong?
You're looking awfully pale...
Are you coming down with a fever?
Matsuda!
Who are you?!
What's wrong, Mr. Chai...
What happened, Dad?
Dad?
Matsuda... I didn't realize you were here.
Matsuda... W-What are you...
Not so fast, Yasuoka!
Vice chairman of the Council of Scientists
For World Peace, Doctor Motoichiro Yasuoka,
has gone missing after an attack
by an unidentified assailant.
Strict security precautions
have been taken.
Now for our next story...
So it wasn't
just my father, but Doctor Yasuoka too?
Suzuki.
You really believe the cactus you
found on the scene was your father?
Yes.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
Taking out two major figures
from that peace council...
It's going to have serious consequences.
Hongo.
You think...
Yes.
Gel Shocker.
General Black.
It seems the plan was a success.
Yes. I've taken out those fools
with their talk of "world peace."
Taking out those two will
hobble their organization.
There's no further need to worry.
Now, turn all the people
of Japan into cacti.
Initiate Operation: World
Cactus Transformation.
Sir.
Go, Cactusbat.
Bury Japan in cacti and
turn it into a desert!
Someone!
Hold it!
Are you the one who killed Doctor Suzuki?
That's right!
It was me... the Gel Shocker
monster, Cactusbat!
So it was Gel Shocker...
And my hand will turn you
into a cactus as well!
Hongo!
Taki, help that man. Hurry!
Right.
Rider Transformation!
Wait, you!
Kamen Rider... I don't have
time to fight with you!
I must execute Operation:
World Cactus Transformation!
KAMEN RIDER
What's that, Naoki?
A guy out there gave it to me.
Really. Giving cacti as presents...
Hey, hey. That's dangerous.
Give it to me.
Chairman?
The thorn won't come out!
What's wrong?
Mr. Taki!
Yuri.
Call Mr. Suzuki and have
him come by right away.
Right!
Hang in there!
The chairman's hand turned into a cactus!
You'll be fine.
We got to him early, so the poison
won't spread to his entire body.
Chairman... I'm sorry!
I wish I'd never taken that cactus...
Silly. Don't cry.
Mr. Suzuki... please!
Create a vaccine as fast as you can!
Help!
Kid...
My mom and dad got turned into cactuses!
Are you all right?
- Get to safety!
- Yeah.
Yeah!
Rider Transformation!
Rider... we'll finish this another time!
How dare you come back so soon?!
Dispose of that weakling monster at once!
No, no. Please wait a moment, my leader.
I analyzed the broken claw to
calculate Rider's strength,
then modified its hand
to endure those values.
Do it.
As you can see!
Next time, even if Rider interferes,
he'll destroy him without fail.
Cut the hand off?
That's right.
Cut my hand off.
You can use it to make a vaccine!
But...
First your father, and Doctor Yasuoka, too...
When I think of all the
people turned into cacti,
one hand seems like a minor sacrifice.
Please. Use it!
Mr. Tachibana...
Pops...
Takeshi...
What's going on?
If you need something for your research,
use my hand!
What are you talking about?
Mr. Hongo!
He got me.
We need the vaccine quickly.
If you don't hurry, we'll
only see more victims!
Mr. Hongo...
Do it!
I'll take this one.
This one?
That'll be 2,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
This one's lovely, too.
It puts out red flowers.
Cactusbat!
Continue with your efforts
to turn people into cacti!
Pops!
Speak to me!
You have to wake up!
It's no use...
Everyone's done for!
Suzuki, keep going!
Pops...
I'll take care of him.
Keep working on the vaccine!
Hongo... can you really fight
with your hand in that condition?
No! Don't destroy it!
Damn it!
Look out!
Suzuki, get out of the way!
Well? Can't make your vaccine now, can you?
Soon, I'll turn you all into cacti!
Wait here and suffer until then!
Are you all right?
Wait!
Hongo, it's no use!
It's all over now...
Damn!
Takeshi!
My hand has recovered!
Pops!
This is it!
Suzuki, you did it! This is it!
This is it! This is it!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Help me!
Captain!
Hongo.
Leave this to me.
You take care of them.
Hurry, this way!
- Hurry
- Run!
You're not a cactus yet?
Watch...
You won't get me again!
Rider Transformation!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hurry, everyone!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Kick!
Doctor!
Doctor Matsuda!
What am I doing here?
Takeshi!
Taki!
Everyone's back to normal!
Including Mr. Suzuki's father!
Doctor Yasuoka, and Kiyoshi's parents, too!
Doctor Suzuki's vaccine turned
them all back to normal!
I see...
Congratulations!
Pops, we beat Cactusbat, too.
- Cactusbat?
- I see.
I've never heard of that cactus!
You sure are in the dark, Doc!
The terrifying Operation: World
Cactus Transformation was halted.
But when would Rider's hard fight
to achieve world peace end?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Geldam's insatiable ambitions lead
to Geldam's leader finally appearing.
Geldam's science division works hard to
create a transformation stoppage system.
Hongo Takeshi is frozen in his
transformation pose at absolute zero.
Join us next week for "Hongo
Takeshi Cannot Transform!!"
Hongo Takeshi Cannot Transform!!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!