KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Terrifying Truth
of Doctor Shinigami?
Meteors fly to Earth from space,
where they enter Earth's atmosphere
and release heat and light.
This is the origin of shooting stars.
Isn't it pretty?
Yeah.
Whoa, that's hot.
Be careful!
A shooting star!
It is!
Romantic, isn't it?
It's coming this way!
Over there!
Let's check it out!
But...
It's shining...
It's a little bit creepy...
It's dangerous.
I'll be fine.
Be careful, Katsuo!
Katsuo!
S-Someone help!
Please... Katsuo was...
Please, help m...
The experiment was a roaring success.
Shocker's incredible science allows
us to control meteors in space.
Soon, we'll sow panic by dropping
meteorites all over Tokyo...
No, all over Japan!
A toast to the completion
of the new machine model.
Cheers!
Takeshi, shall we test it?
Okay, get to it.
Let's go!
Start!
Race, race, machine!
Soar like a shooting star!
Let the jets of your engine roar!
Rider Transformation!
Crush those evil monsters!
Charge, Cyclone!
Race into the flames!
Hurricane Jump!
Fight, Cyclone!
Cyclone Jump!
Cyclone!
Race, race, machine!
Run like lightning!
And carry all our hopes with you!
300 kilometers per hour...
Now let's test the brakes.
Good. It performs well.
We did it!
Get him!
I don't see Rider's body!
Maybe we blew him to pieces!
It's Rider!
Rider is invincible!
Now, confess!
Why are you bringing meteorites to Earth?
I...
Talk!
A new Shocker monster...
I'm Squidevil, the devil-trainer!
How many times must
we fight before you learn?
Cyborgs who serve evil will never triumph!
Fight me!
Rider Kick!
Kick Counter!
The Rider Kick won't work on me!
Squidevil...
What is its weak point?
What's Takeshi doing?
What's the point of having a
new machine at all?
No need to worry.
You know Hongo.
I'm sure he's taking his time trying
to get the most out of the new machine.
Here he is.
He's acting strangely...
Hey!
Hey! Hongo!
Takeshi! What's wrong?
Speak to me, Hongo! Hongo!
Terrifying...
Did you see that?
I've had even more training
in ways to kill you...
This time, I will be victorious!
Damn you, Squidevil!
Damn...
Hey, Hongo. Speak to me, Hongo.
A dream?
You're covered in sweat.
So it was a dream...
This isn't like you.
Just who was it they sent at you?
A terrifying cyborg, enhanced
through Shocker training...
The Rider Kick won't work on him.
What did you say?
Shocker has something that powerful?
I think he'll beat me if
I don't do something.
Taki, will you train with me?
Training? You're in no condition for that.
If you won't do it, I'll ask Tachibana.
Well?
The area's changed a lot, eh?
Yes, it has, in every way possible.
But what never changes is human dreams.
I still dream of winning
the World Grand Prix.
And I'm the same way, Tachibana.
Oh, really?
Well, we've both been in
that business for a long time.
That reminds me. I want
to show you something.
A brand new machine I just completed.
There's a place I want to stop by first.
Sounds great. Name the place.
Tokyo Observatory.
An ex-racer and an observatory...
There's an odd combination.
- I'll be right back.
- Sure.
Help!
Tachibana! Help!
Tokyo Observatory
Kumaki! Where are you?
What happened?
Welcome, Tachibana Tobei.
This is Shocker's Japanese
cyborg training center.
Who's there? Show yourself!
Doctor Shinigami!
From this day forth,
you will act as a trainer
for Shocker's cyborgs.
I refuse!
Tachibana Tobei will never serve Shocker!
Show him to the training center.
Kumaki! Run!
Give in!
Agree to be a Shocker trainer!
Hold it!
Leave him to me.
It's in your hands, Trainer Kumaki.
Kumaki... I'm disappointed in you.
You sold your soul to the devil,
and became a Shocker trainer...
It's no wonder you
betrayed your old friend!
Try to understand, Tachibana.
They would have killed me
if I hadn't agreed.
I want to live, even
if it's in a party of devils.
I still have a chance to
make my dream come true.
You fool.
You think you can keep racing
in a world fallen to Shocker?
Say yes, Tachibana.
It's the only way to save yourself.
I'll never agree.
Hongo Takeshi will...
The Kamen Rider will come to save me!
But until you agree to be a trainer,
Shocker won't challenge Kamen Rider.
You'll remain locked up in here forever.
What?
The only way to get Rider's help
is to become a Shocker trainer?
Tachibana.
Will you do this, or not?!
KAMEN RIDER
Rider Kick!
Hey, watch it!
Hey!
Mitsuru, Naoki! Are you all right?
Stop this!
It's cool, though!
We're being just like Kamen Rider!
I know you love Kamen Rider,
but don't you realize how
dangerous the Rider Kick is?
Only Kamen Rider can
perform the Rider Kick.
It's beyond the abilities
of children like you.
You'll just get hurt. Understand?
You think he's right?
Well, if you don't believe me,
I'll show you the danger Kamen
Rider's training exposes him to.
Taki! I'm all ready!
It's Kamen Rider!
Okay, let's start training.
Watch closely, you two!
Come on!
I wonder what training
Squidevil is going through...
Put your back into it!
Now, jump higher!
Use your entire body! All of it!
Jump higher!
What are you doing?
If you think you'll beat Kamen
Rider that way, you're wrong!
Use all your power! All of it!
What's wrong with you?
Now, come this way.
Ram into this.
Harder!
One more time! Go!
What are you doing?
Don't touch me. There's
a remote control in my head!
Don't be ridiculous.
Come this way.
A remote control?
So his weak point is his head!
Well?
Rider's really something, isn't he?
But I wonder where Rider went...
Yeah!
Well? You both saw it, didn't you?
It's pretty amazing.
I won't try to be Rider anymore.
Me either.
You've shown us how dangerous it is.
I'm glad you understand.
Right, Taki?
That's right.
I'm glad you got the point.
Emergency!
Emergency, Mr. Hongo!
It's a real emergency!
What's wrong, you two?
Another cockroach in the kitchen?
Of course not.
The boss's car just came back.
But he wasn't inside it!
What did you say?
Pops wasn't inside it?
Taki, let's go!
Be careful!
There could be a time bomb inside.
Right.
No fear of that, Hongo Takeshi.
There it is.
Tachibana Tobei is in the hands of Shocker.
I knew it...
Why would you do this?
One reason alone: to make
the Kamen Rider fight Squidevil.
What?
Hongo Takeshi.
If you wish to save Tobei
Tachibana, get into this car.
We'll tell you where to go.
I've done everything I can.
It's all up to you now, Rider.
Kumaki!
Tachibana, get to safety.
Japan is my home.
I can't watch Shocker's
shooting stars tear it to pieces.
- Then you are...
- Yes.
Go with me. Let's escape together!
Right.
Kumaki!
Hey! Kumaki! Speak to me!
Tachibana...
I'm glad we got to spend
a little more time together.
Squidevil is in the Fujimi Highlands.
He's going to fight the Kamen Rider there.
Hey!
Their shooting star plan...
can be prevented if you defeat Squidevil.
Now, go!
Go!
Hey, Kumaki!
So you've come, Hongo Takeshi.
Where is Tachibana?
You fool.
You expect Shocker to keep its promise?
Tachibana Tobei will be
Shocker's slave until his death.
Get him!
The brat, Taki...
Where is Hongo Takeshi?
Where is the Kamen Rider?!
Hongo...
Doctor Shinigami.
Where is Squidevil?
He's right in front of you...
What?
You mean, you...
Kamen Rider...
Squidevil will face you now!
Rider Transformation!
Rider... see how you deal with this!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Damn...
Rider!
Rider... he can't handle it after all?
Rider, get up!
Right...
His weak point is his head!
Understood.
Try me!
You won't win this...
The shooting stars
are nearing the Earth now.
Soon, Japan will be in ruins!
What did you say?
Rider Chop!
He broke my remote controller!
Now!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Rider!
Well done, Rider.
Brilliant as ever!
I couldn't have beaten him all on my own.
Shocker's commander-in-chief,
Doctor Shinigami,
was secretly the monstrous Squidevil.
And Kamen Rider fought hard and
foiled their terrible shooting star plan.
Ride on, Kamen Rider!
Shocker will never stop trying
to ruin our peaceful world!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Girakorogi.
Sharp red nails stand in Rider's way.
What horror is Shocker planning
with those nails of death?
Join us next week for "The Monstrous
Girakorogi's Nails of Death."
The Monstrous Girakorogi's
Nails of Death
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!