KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Shocker Leader Appears!!
Rider in Peril
These are the Alps, a mountain range
sometimes called the Roof of the World.
These mountains are home
to a Shocker secret base.
This is FBI Shocker investigator,
Alps division, Pierre Andre.
Investigator Taki, Japan division.
Investigator Taki, Japan division. Over.
Do you read me, Taki?
Andre here.
Taki here.
I read you loud and clear. Over.
I have acquired important
information on Shocker.
What?
Andre, what's the information?
Radio transmission detected,
fifteen degrees right.
It's coming from that mountain hut.
Shocker is sending their top secret
plans to Manazuru Beach in Japan.
Confirming. Manazuru Beach,
at 10:00 tomorrow Japan time...
Do you read me, Andre? Andre!
Taki, Andre here.
Taki! Do you read me?
Taki!
You...
FBI scum...
you've outlived your usefulness!
A Shocker monster...
Die!
Taki!
Andre's been killed.
Andre...
We went through training together.
He was a good man.
Andre...
I won't let your information go to waste.
I will strike down
Shocker and avenge you!
Pops.
We're getting to the time Andre told us.
This stinks. I usually get huge
hauls at the worst times.
See? I got another one!
I wonder how Shocker plans
on bringing in the secret plans here.
Submarine? Transport plane?
It's from the sky!
Right down to the second...
They're punctual, at least.
Stop complimenting them!
I got your plans!
Damn you, Taki!
Retrieve the message capsule! Go!
Catch me if you can!
Pops!
I got it!
That way! Get him!
Not so fast!
Pops, hurry!
Got a haul of fish and Shocker's
message capsule.
That's a pretty good day!
Don't be so sure, Tachibana Tobei!
A Shocker cyborg!
I'm a cyborg based on the killer
of the sea, the saw shark... Girizames!
Give me that message capsule!
We worked hard to get this!
I won't let you have it!
Taki!
Leave it to me!
Then go to hell!
He's in danger!
Pops! Wake up!
Pops!
Pops, wake up!
Rider...
Taki has the Shocker message capsule!
Taki does?
All right...
Wait! Be careful.
They have a powerful
monster named Girizames...
Got it.
I almost became fish bait myself...
This is perfect.
Shocker... this should slow you down.
Good day to you.
Did something happen here?
What are you doing?
It's a checkpoint, to be sure...
But it's a Shocker checkpoint!
You're all members of Shocker?
Well, that's no good...
Get him!
Hold it, Shocker!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
All right... time to break through!
We did it! We did it!
Find the body!
You survived that, Rider?
The likes of you won't
kill the Kamen Rider!
Now, talk!
What is Shocker planning?
W-Well...
Talk!
You... You're Shocker's latest cyborg.
That's right.
A cyborg based on the bandit
of the Pacific, the saw shark!
My name is Girizames!
Girizames?
Let us begin!
Rider Kick!
Kick Counter!
Is this the end of the Kamen Rider?
Girizames...
I'll be taking this now!
Damn you, Kamen Rider!
I haven't given up!
KAMEN RIDER
Ambassador Hell.
How is Operation: V proceeding?
No need to worry.
The plan is proceeding smoothly.
At last... at last, we'll bring
an end to that Kamen Rider.
Meanwhile, Taki and the others,
having acquired the message capsule,
had asked FBI headquarters in
New York for help deciphering its code.
That's the reply from New York.
The FBI's computers
certainly are impressive...
They deciphered that complicated
code in just ten minutes!
Read it already!
Okay...
"The Shocker code deciphers as follows:
'The Shocker World Conference will
be held on an island in Tokyo Bay
located at 35 degrees
16 minutes north latitude.
Participating members will
include Shocker's leader
and commanders from across the world.'"
Shocker's leader?
Their leader's never
shown himself before...
He's really putting in an appearance?
Let's see. 35 degrees, 16 minutes...
It's here.
I wonder who their leader is.
My intuition tells me he's not human.
A cyborg, then?
No... he could well be an ordinary man.
The site of Shocker's world
conference is a former fortress island.
Morocco Branch leader, Mohammed.
Gibraltar Branch leader, Humphrey.
Singapore Branch leader, Yang.
Hong Kong Branch leader, Chang Fou Ti.
Intruder in block C. Intruder in block C.
What's this?
Excellent...
All men, go to yellow alert.
Rider!
Taki!
We're after one thing
here: Shocker's leader!
Right. I'll lure out the
combatants guarding the door.
Go avenge Andre for me!
Right!
Taki, I'm going in!
Got it!
The Shocker World
Conference will now begin.
Today's theme is Operation: V.
Is that the Shocker leader?
It's time to unmask him at last.
Right...
Shocker leader!
Welcome, Kamen Rider.
But I'm not about to reveal my face to you.
What did you say?
What in the world...
What's going on here?
The radio message from the Alps,
the message capsule,
and the coded message inside...
It was all arranged to lure
you here, Kamen Rider!
I see... so everything that
happened was part of your trap!
That's right.
Shocker's great plan to
rid the world of Kamen Rider...
This is the true nature of Operation: V.
Then these men, too...
That's right.
I think you've taken
Shocker a bit too lightly.
Do you really think we'd
bring our commanders here?
What's that?
They're all mannequins!
Not just any mannequins.
Mannequins designed to destroy Rider.
Farewell, Kamen Rider!
Damn!
Andro gas... made to destroy
the body of a cyborg!
Kamen Rider!
Girizames!
Now I'll finish you off!
Five minutes...
Keep Rider on the island
for just five minutes!
The island is sinking into the ocean.
The island is sinking? Taki's in danger...
Wait!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Kill him!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
Taki!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Rider, did you find Shocker's leader?
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
It was a trap...
A trap set to kill us!
Rider, Rider!
A trap?
The island is set to explode.
Jump in!
Understood.
Shocker is coming
I'm going on ahead!
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Rider!
No... Kamen Rider is invincible!
The Kamen Rider had escaped
Shocker's terrible trap,
but the identity of Shocker's
leader remains a mystery.
Ride on, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Squidevil.
In a plot to kill Kamen
Rider once and for all,
Doctor Shinigami unleashes
the mighty monster Squidevil.
But who is it, really?
Join us next week for "The
Terrifying Truth of Doctor Shinigami?"
The Terrifying Truth of
Doctor Shinigami?
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!