KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Killer Queen Ant
Arichimedes
Shocker's scientists have succeeded
in creating a cyborg from an ant egg.
Behold the birth of the cyborg
queen ant, Arichimedes.
Colonel Zol, use her to bring
Japan under Shocker's control!
I will, Boss.
I shall promptly put
Arichimedes's power to the test!
Tonan Bank, Jonan Branch
Emergency in the underground vault!
Let's go!
The vault has been breached!
A monster!
Behold the power of the queen ant!
This deadly laser network will kill
anyone who approaches this building.
As long as we have this network in place,
the Kamen Rider won't be able to get close.
Just don't forget the
Kamen Rider's strength.
The research we're doing here will
all go to waste if we're exposed.
Don't let your guard down for a minute!
Understand?
Once this research pays off,
all of Japan will belong to Shocker!
Yes, sir!
Colonel!
Someone's nearby.
Listen to me... remain on high alert!
All right, let's patrol.
Sheesh... they almost saw me back there.
But I'd better get going.
Going somewhere without me?
Ichimonji...
What are you doing here?
You've got some nerve,
heading off without telling me.
So I tailed you in secret.
The truth is, this thing picked up
a mystery signal coming from the area.
Talk!
How do we get past the
killer laser network?
Talk!
That branch... over there.
What's the password?
Kamen Rider.
The signal is coming from this direction.
That was a close call!
But Shocker must be hiding
something important,
if they have defenses like these in place.
Strange... Let's look in here.
That was close, huh?
Yeah.
The signal's coming from there.
All right.
I'm opening it now.
Just what is this room?
What is that thing?
A huge egg...
I've never seen anything like it.
It's the source of the signal
you were picking up.
But what's Shocker's game here?
Are they digging up monster
eggs and trying to hatch them?
Damn you, Shocker!
It's like it's made out of iron!
But it's clear Shocker's
using them for something.
All right, let's carry them out.
What good would that do?
We can run a more thorough analysis.
An alarm system!
Taki! Run!
Good luck, Hayato!
Look out!
Hey... are you okay?
My leg... my leg!
I'll get you to a hospital.
Are you all right?
You!
Return my egg!
Taki!
You show yourself, Ichimonji Hayato...
Shocker cyborg... fight me!
Taki... take the egg and flee!
Right!
Come at me!
It's an ant colony!
Killer ants!
Ichimonji Hayato...
The minute I give the order,
those ants will devour you whole!
Are you the queen ant?
That's right.
The killer ants that I lead
will tear Japan to pieces!
I won't let it happen!
Now, devour Ichimonji Hayato!
Damn...
KAMEN RIDER
Die!
Transform!
You won't escape me, Kamen Rider!
What's taking you so long?
Kill him already!
Die, Rider!
Can't breathe...
Like my body's on fire... the pain!
Well?
What do you think of my power?
Fool!
While you were wasting time fighting
Rider, they took the egg away!
Forgive me, sir.
Hokkaido, Tohoku, Chugoku, Shikoku, Kyushu!
We'd prepared to send more
ant queens to every region of Japan.
But your foolish mistake
has thrown a wrench in our plan!
I swear, I will retrieve the stolen egg.
Even if it costs me my life...
All right... I will trust you
and give you another chance.
But only one chance!
If I find Taki Kazuya, I'll find the egg.
All together, are we?
Hey, what's that thing?
An egg, obviously.
Even though it is on the large side...
Amazing!
How many could you feed
with an omelet like this?
Let's find out!
Try again!
What's wrong with this thing?
You didn't make a dent!
Of course not.
I took that egg from a Shocker lab.
Shocker?
A-And you're bringing it here?
That's dangerous!
Take it easy.
I just want to store it in
the warehouse for a while.
Hang onto it, will you?
H-Hey, wait a minute!
It'll be fine. Goro, help me out.
Okay.
It's not going to hatch into
a monster in the meantime, is it?
Mari, you're such a baby!
You watch too much TV!
So do you!
If that was a real egg,
we'd have such a big omelet!
All righty...
Hey, where did Hayato go?
He's putting the responsibility on
us, as usual!
Stop complaining and watch it.
No fair.
Putting us on egg duty...
like we're just a bunch of hens.
That Ichimonji...
Oh, right! You have a phone call!
Taki. I finished the analysis
on the fluid that hit me.
It's formic acid.
Formic acid?
That dissolving acid produced by ants?
But producing enough formic
acid to coat a human body
would require hundreds
of thousands of ants.
And Shocker is breeding ants at that scale.
And that egg is a queen ant egg.
If it shows any signs of
changing, evacuate at once.
It stinks!
Who dealt it?
How rude!
I wouldn't do anything so disgusting!
But it stinks!
Yuri, did you do it?
Don't be ridiculous!
Well, it wasn't me!
So this is the culprit...
Hey, are you kidding me?
What's this smell?
Mr. Chairman, the egg is
putting out that smell!
It's kind of creepy...
That hurts!
The egg is changing colors.
Like Pandora's Box about to open...
Now's not the time for poetry!
This is seriously bad!
But Ichimonji... if Shocker is
making a queen ant-human cyborg,
what's their endgame?
Ant swarms follow the orders of their
queen, devouring grass and trees.
There's no way to stop them.
Terrifying... What a terrifying plan...
Mr. Taki!
Come quickly! The egg is changing color!
W-What did you say?
Is that true, Mari?
Taki, run!
You need to run!
I was dreading this might happen...
But I want to see what comes out!
Not if you value your life!
Hurry!
What's that?
Ants...
Mr. Chairman...
Stay calm.
Just stay calm!
They're coming in through the windows!
Fight them to the end!
What's that?
It's an ant monster!
I bet fire will hurt it!
Let's try it.
Okay!
We did it!
Look! The ants are retreating!
Thank goodness!
Ichimonji Hayato here. Open the door.
Mr. Ichimonji... thank goodness!
Wait! That isn't Hayato's voice!
Damn!
It melted!
- Run!
- Hurry!
I'm scared... We're done for!
The egg.
The monster must be after that egg!
Pops!
Pour gasoline on it and burn it!
Go on, hold the door!
Look... it can even survive the fire!
It's no use, then?
Hang in there, everyone!
Transform!
It's here!
I'll feed all five of you to my ants!
Now, my ants! Devour them!
Rider!
Wait, Arichimedes!
Now that I'm here...
Your plans are through!
Rider... you survived, did you?
Now, I will send you to hell!
I won't allow Shocker to conquer Japan!
Fight me!
Hang in there, Kamen Rider!
Get him!
I'll melt you into sludge!
Wait! Wait!
Return my egg!
Never!
No!
How dare you?!
That won't work a second time!
Rider Kick!
A chain reaction is causing
the eggs to disappear...
Kamen Rider has foiled us again!
Mr. Chairman! The ants are gone!
Had a nice workout, did you, Pops?
You meanie!
Seriously...
I'd better split!
The Kamen Rider had stopped Shocker's
plot to conquer Japan once more.
But Colonel Zol would continue
to forward his evil plans.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the mummy monster Egyptas.
The monster Egyptas, awakened
from a 4000-year slumber,
will battle with Rider over
the fate of billion-yen gemstones.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "The Revived Mummy Monster, Egyptas!"
The Revived Mummy Monster
Egyptas!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!