KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Deathmatch! The Ant-Eating
Devil Arigabari
Mount Tengu,
in a corner of the Southern Alps.
Anyone who climbs this
mountain is never seen again.
Those who live near it have begun
to give it another name: Mount Vanishing.
Southern Alps
Entrance to Mount Tengu
Danger - Do Not Climb
- Feels great, huh?
- Yeah.
- It's past here.
- Right.
But, for those with an adventurous spirit,
Mount Tengu has another appeal.
And here comes another pair of them,
unaware that this mountain
is such an ominous place.
The peak is just past this waterfall.
Yeah!
The fog's really rolling in, huh?
- Yeah.
- Let's hurry!
Okay!
Hey, Yamada!
Yamada!
Yamada! Answer me!
Where are you?
That sounded like Yamada...
Hey! Hey!
Look carefully, right in front of you!
Yamada!
Monster! What are you doing?
Monster! What are you
doing with Yamada?
I'm going to run a little test
on your friend here.
Yamada...
Now it's your turn.
We'll see if you can endure the bacteria
known as "the Curse of the Amazon"
which I, the great Arigabari, spread!
Damn you...
An anteater monster.
It is a cyborg smuggled by Shocker
to Japan from the remote Amazon.
The anteater monster carries a bacteria
known as "the Curse of the Amazon"
which it injects into the human body.
Now, I'll inject you with
more of my bacteria!
Wait, Arigabari.
The man has endured
the bacteria admirably.
Assign him to spread the infection, now.
This will allow the computer
to gather data on how useful it is.
Return him to good health,
and then use him.
Then I will show my
power through him, then?
That's right, Arigabari.
Even if the Kamen Rider learns
of our plans and attempts to interfere,
I believe you can defeat him.
Go, Arigabari!
Descend from Mount Tengu to
the village, and show your power!
I shall! This is the day
I've been waiting for!
Southern Alps
Entrance to Mount Tengu
Danger - Do Not Climb
I'm gonna look for my big brother.
Don't be absurd.
Even grown adults have climbed
up there, never to return! Right?
Even without that, a kid like you
climbing a mountain alone is suicide!
- Right?
- That's right!
My brother is a
veteran mountain-climber.
Even if he's gotten trapped, I know he's
still alive, waiting for help to come!
But we've all been
searching for three days,
and we still haven't found him!
It's time to give up!
No!
Wait!
Big Bro!
Takeo...
It's true! He's alive!
Where's your friend?
Yamada wandered into the mist,
and died falling from a cliff.
I had to wait for the fog to clear...
No...
That's not my brother, somehow...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Nothing.
I'm sorry to worry you all.
We're just glad you're safe...
Takeo.
I'm Izaki from the third floor.
Could I ask you a favor?
Okay, coming...
What is it?
Mr. Izaki, it's awfully late...
You're going to serve Shocker, as I do.
Mr. Izaki!
A monster!
Soon, you will serve me!
I'd say you're worrying too much.
You think?
I just can't help feeling like
it's not really my brother.
Adults say it all the time...
A life-or-death experience
can really change someone.
I bet getting stranded changed him.
You think he wouldn't even
like the same foods, even?
Foods?
Yeah, I've been watching since
he came down from the mountain
and he hasn't eaten a bite.
Then what's he eating?
He sneaks out in
the middle of the night.
I guess he's eating something then.
It's like a ghost story!
There's just one thing
that's bothering me.
What is it?
Since my brother came back,
all the ants around the
apartment have gone missing.
Ants?
He says the ants are all gone!
Really?
The ants?
Hey, Goro!
Where are you taking that?
Um, well...
What are you using it for?
Mr. Chairman...
You can't have it. I'm using it.
I'm sorry!
My savior! I owe you!
What's going on, Goro?
Take me to my apartment complex!
I need to help my friend!
I can't say no to you. All right.
Thanks!
Hey!
Goro and Hayato... they're peas in a pod!
Hey, are you sure about this?
I'll be with you. Let's go!
Big Bro...
He's heading for that
new apartment complex.
Let's go!
What's he doing?
Big Bro...
He's eating the ants!
Big Bro, why are you eating ants?
I must continuously eat ants to cultivate
"the Curse of the Amazon" bacteria
growing in my body.
Big Bro...
"Curse of the Amazon"?
I'm gonna call Hayato!
You're a Shocker cyborg!
What did you do to my brother?
Your brother has become
a Shocker guinea pig.
I'm using him to spread a
bacteria developed by Shocker
among the people of
this apartment complex
to spread destruction and havoc!
So that's the story, eh?
Who are you?
Exploiting an innocent man
to spread destruction...
It's certainly clever!
But I won't let it go on!
Hayato!
Get him!
Goro, run!
Right!
Transform!
Let me go!
Come closer, Kamen Rider!
Beat him with the Rider Kick!
Rider Kick!
Rider!
Goro!
Rider...
Rider is no match for me!
Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
We'll know one way or another
by the end of the day.
No... don't die, Goro!
Doctor... please, take my blood!
He lost...
Goro...
This boy has suffered a
deep psychological trauma.
I hope the mental strain doesn't
affect his physical injuries, but...
- Mental strain?
- Yes.
You're not ready to be out of bed yet.
Hayato...
We'll look after Goro. Don't worry.
You're injured, too, remember?
Rider... he lost!
Goro... hang in there.
Kamen Rider will not lose.
He will beat that Shocker monster!
Goro!
This is all... this is all my fault!
The Kamen Rider is an idol...
a hero to Goro.
But he saw him defeated at the same
time he himself was badly injured.
Psychological and
physical injuries at once.
Hayato, I'm telling you...
they're both sapping his strength.
Pops...
But right now, I just don't
think I can beat Arigabari!
You fool!
If you can't grant the
wish of a single child,
never talk to me again about justice,
or protecting humanity, again!
"Can't" isn't allowed in this world!
Are you such a gutless coward
that one or two losses
has you throwing in the towel?
Pops!
That nickname is only for my friends!
No... let me say it, Pops!
Right now, your words are the only thing...
Mr. Chairman!
Goro is...
What?
Doctor...
I've done everything I can.
Whether he pulls through or not will
come down to his own strength of will.
Goro. Stay with us!
Kamen Rider...
After all this...
Why won't Kamen Rider come and see him?
God...
Rider...
Damn you, Arigabari...
Don't let him beat you!
Don't you give up, Goro!
That's right! Don't let it beat you!
It's no use...
I'll need more than this
to get past Arigabari's claws!
If it will save Goro, I'll gladly help you!
Taki!
Let's go, Hayato!
Thank you, Taki!
Hayato!
I did it, Taki!
I worked out a new move!
Shocker!
Ichimonji Hayato is here!
Come out!
Taki, go around that way.
Right!
They're all affected...
Arigabari had already been and gone,
spreading "the Curse
of the Amazon" bacteria
to the people of the apartment complex.
Mr. Izaki!
Mr. Izaki, speak to me!
Damn you, Shocker...
Hayato, he got to everyone.
Takeo's brother originally
went missing on Mount Tengu.
If this all started on Mount Tengu,
then that must be where Shocker's base is.
Taki, you keep watch here.
I'll head to Mount Tengu.
All right.
Transform!
Rider! Keep fighting!
You don't give up, do you, Kamen Rider?
Arigabari...
Seize him!
Rider!
I will stop you today.
For Goro, and for everyone!
Let's begin, Rider!
Kamen Rider...
You no longer stand a chance against me.
You'll meet your end here on Mount Tengu!
Kamen Rider... you're helpless before me!
Rider Manji Kick!
I won... I finally won!
They left these antidote capsules
in their base on Mount Tengu.
They should work.
He'll get better now.
Ichimonji... go see Goro. Hurry.
The antidote worked, saving
the people of the apartment complex
from Shocker's evil scheme.
Goro.
Kamen Rider!
I won.
I defeated Arigabari.
You need to get better too, Goro.
I know I will!
Takeo's brother has recovered as well.
Kamen Rider!
Really, you need to rest!
She's right!
Kamen Rider really came!
You mean in a dream, right?
Not in a dream!
Kamen Rider really came
to tell me he beat the monster!
It's true, Yuri!
Mr. Chairman... Goro's acting strange!
It's not strange at all.
The Kamen Rider fought
for Goro... and he won!
Goro, you gave Kamen Rider strength.
I did?
You did.
So... get better soon, all right?
Okay!
Mount Tengu, a place once feared,
would never be called
the devil's mountain again.
But evil organization Shocker
hasn't given up on Japan.
Keep up the fight, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the man-eating flower, Dokudalian.
It's a monster that creates
extracts from poisonous flowers.
When Mari and Yuri are captured,
Ichimonji Hayato must infiltrate
a Shocker base to save them,
but he falls into Colonel Zol's trap.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "The Man-Eating Flower, Dokudalian."
The Man-Eating Flower
Dokudalian
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!