KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Saigang's
Deadly Auto Race
How was our time, Pops?
Looking better and better...
But you need a little
more to win it.
How much more do we
have to get it down?
At least two minutes.
Please, Chairman.
He's easily won with times
like that in the past.
Hey!
That's right, Mr. Hongo!
That's what he's been saying!
Hey! Don't tell him that!
Anyway,
you need to drive your heart out,
so you won't have any
regrets, even if you lose.
Katsumaru is doing
everything he can, too.
Katsumaru, eh?
He's desperate to win and go to
America, isn't he?
Because if he gets to America,
he can fix Tadashi's legs.
Taki, you stand a
chance at the win, too.
Now, give it a lap, you two.
Right.
In preparation for tomorrow's
All-Japan Auto Race qualifiers,
Hongo Takeshi and Taki Kazuya are up early
to get their last training session in.
Meanwhile, in Shocker's base,
Doctor Shinigami,
who had arrived in advance,
was awaiting the arrival of the monstrous
Saigang from Shocker's Africa Branch.
Doctor Shinigami.
Saigang hasn't appeared yet.
Have patience.
Saigang will come.
Gate three here.
This is a prefectural
police patrol.
There's a motorbike rushing your
way at 200 kilometers per hour.
200 kilometers?
Stop it at any cost!
Right!
Okay... that must be it!
Stop! Stop!
M-Monster!
There you are, Saigang.
Doctor Shinigami.
Why did you call me to Japan?
Doctor, who is this man?
Isao Katsumaru.
He's taking part in
the race beside Hongo.
Saigang,
you must bring him here to me.
The bike's running great, Sanae.
You might just win and get
Tadashi to America, right?
Yeah.
He threw a fit about wanting
to come to Izu with me,
so I want to restore
his legs to normal.
But I want to run a good
race, even if I lose.
Mr. Katsumaru!
Mr. Katsumaru.
How are you?
I'm from Motor Communications.
Could I have an interview?
Yes, certainly.
I'll go to see Tadashi
in the hospital, then.
Okay, I'll catch up with you.
This way, please.
Right.
Go on.
Tadashi.
Emi and Tokko
brought this for you.
Mr. Hongo says he hopes
you get better soon.
Cheer up, okay?
Thanks!
Is that my brother?
Hey, Sanae...
Where's my brother?
He's getting interviewed
by a newspaper man.
Interviewed?
But he'll be back
soon, I'm sure.
Now, lie down and rest.
Isao Katsumaru.
You will henceforth
be loyal to Shocker.
And what is your role?
Work with Saigang and destroy
Shocker's enemy, Hongo Takeshi.
Very good.
Now, move the plan into action.
Hongo Takeshi...
There we are.
I think that should do it.
Hey, Katsumaru.
Finished tuning up your bike?
Yeah, I suddenly wanted
a race with Hongo.
Can I borrow him a
minute, Mr. Tachibana?
I don't mind, Pops.
Let's go then, Hongo.
Right.
You're raring to go, I see.
Go on.
Hongo.
What's wrong, Katsumaru?
My machine's acting up...
Who's there?
I can't see!
Are you a Shocker monster?
That's right!
I am Saigang!
What? Saigang?
Get him!
Where is he?
I don't know...
I can't see...
Where is he?
Where is he?!
He's going to beat me.
I have to do something!
Prepare to die, Hongo!
You're pathetic.
Doctor Shinigami... why?!
Why didn't you finish Hongo?
Wait. Are you telling me...
Hongo isn't dead.
He held onto a tree
growing out of the cliff.
Damn...
I'm such a failure!
Saigang.
There is no room for
error when fighting Hongo.
You must defeat Hongo
tomorrow, even if it kills you.
Well? How is it?
Does it sting?
No, it's all right.
I can see again.
That's great.
I was worried for
a minute there.
I'm so glad.
Katsumaru!
Where have you been?
We've been worried.
Sorry to worry you.
Some strange gas knocked me
out, but I'm better now.
Let's have a fair fight
tomorrow, Hongo.
You said it!
KAMEN RIDER
East Japan Road Race Qualifiers
East Izu One Lap Rally
Sponsored by JAO
Additional Support: Suzuki Automotive
How's the bike running?
Just great.
Leave the maintenance to me.
Move, Mitsuru.
But Hongo, better be careful.
If Shocker's still after you...
Yes, they'll probably
try something.
Katsumaru.
Let's have a good race.
Likewise.
Take your places!
It's time.
Now, let's get to the pit!
Yeah!
Hey!
Katsumaru!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
That's dangerous!
Katsumaru! Stop it!
Hey!
Katsumaru!
Katsumaru,
that's not the right way!
Katsumaru!
What are you doing, Katsumaru?
What's going on here?
Explain it to me!
Shocker!
I don't have any time to lose...
All right...
Rider Transformation!
A formidable foe...
Hongo!
What happened?
Taki, be careful!
Shocker's here!
- What?
- They've gotten to Katsumaru.
- Katsumaru?
Let's just get back
to the race for now.
Right.
He's so late!
What's he off doing?
Hongo
It's Katsumaru!
Katsumaru's coming!
Hurry!
Katsumaru,
you're three minutes behind!
Fill me up, hurry!
Here!
That's Mr. Hongo's gasoline!
You're right!
It's fine.
A little gasoline won't
decide the victory.
True.
But he sure is running behind...
He's here! It's Hongo!
- Emi, the gasoline!
- Hurry, everyone!
Everyone, hurry!
You're both running behind.
It's Shocker.
Katsumaru is working with them.
- What did you say?
- Where's Katsumaru, Pops?
He came through
thirty minutes ago.
Damn, I'll get that guy!
Pops, what's happened
to the gasoline?
Hongo
That's yours!
Miki accidentally put it
into Katsumaru's bike.
What did you say?
Katsumaru is in danger!
Hongo, it's Katsumaru!
Hurry!
We need to get
him off that bike!
Katsumaru! You okay?
Speak to me!
Hongo...
What am I doing here?
It's okay. Hang in there.
Are you all right?
I'm glad.
His wounds don't seem too bad...
Shocker must have
brainwashed him.
Hongo!
Saigang...
I'll get you this time!
Rider Transformation!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Saigang, show yourself!
Rider, Rider!
I see...
his weak point is his horn!
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider Punch!
Rider, Rider!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Taki, we're just five
minutes out of first.
We can still win this thing!
Right!
I see them!
It's Mr. Hongo and Mr. Taki!
Eto Hospital
Tadashi
Tadashi...
I'm sorry I couldn't win.
Hey, I don't mind.
For Tadashi
"Tadashi...
this is a ticket to America.
Go fix your legs,
and show everyone how much you can walk.
Promise, okay?
From a friend of
your brother's."
The deadly race was over.
But Shocker hadn't given up on
their plans for world domination.
Keep fighting, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Semiminga.
Semiminga emits killer sound waves
which throw the city into chaos,
and his battle with the Kamen Rider
takes them to the top of Shocker Tower.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
In "The Monstrous Semiminga's
Song of Slaughter!"
The Monstrous Semiminga's
Song of Slaughter!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!