KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Deadly Ice Devil
Todogiller
Here it comes!
Okay, here I go!
C'mon!
Send it my way!
I can't watch this!
Oh, Goro,
stop being such a brat.
- That's it!
- What's wrong with you?
I quit!
Wait up, Goro!
What's wrong with you?
Children should play!
- It's decided!
- That's right.
Come on, let's go!
Stop it! Let me go!
Okay, let's go!
Over here!
Here it comes!
You idiots. Keep it in bounds!
Hey! Who gave you
permission to play here?
- Sorry! Our ball went over there!
- We'll be more careful in the future.
Leave my land at once.
You're not allowed to play here.
How many times must I say it?
Get out this instant!
And as for this...
Our ball!
Now, get out of here!
Oh, what a mean man!
What do we do?
It's snowing!
It's cold!
So cold...
Hayato!
A Shocker cyborg appeared!
Damned Shocker...
Look at Ichimonji
Hayato's panic.
The cyborg I designed personally
is beginning to use
its terrifying power.
Soon, I'll make you an icicle,
just like that old man!
A fate worth looking
forward to...
Doctor Shinigami.
See that Operation: Ice is performed
at once, and just as planned.
We must bring the humans
turned to ice back to our base,
and then modify them
into Shocker cyborgs.
You will move on to this
stage of the plan at once!
The preparations
are all in place.
I will destroy Shocker's greatest
opposition, the Kamen Rider...
And then all that will remain
is to bring the humans
here for modification.
Evil organization Shocker was
plotting to execute Operation: Ice,
using their new
cyborg, Todogiller.
But what exactly
is Operation: Ice?
What is that?
Snow?
Thirty degrees to port!
The rudder's stuck!
What's wrong?
A monster!
Another fishing boat was
sunk on its way back to port.
What? But that makes
seven since yesterday!
What caused it?
An iceberg, right?
Yes.
Each boat was in the middle of a
telegraph about seeing a strange monster,
-A monster?
but they were cut off.
Hayato.
It could be that
monster from yesterday!
If it is,
that means Shocker's behind it.
What happened to
the boats' crews?
Not one man has been found.
Not one?
Then... if Shocker's the
one sinking the boats,
Shocker might be taking the
crews, too!
It's entirely possible.
Their families must
be so worried...
Those poor people...
Todogiller.
You must bring far
more people than this.
We must perform surgery
to bring them back to life
and turn them into
Shocker cyborgs.
Then, we will turn Tokyo
into a city of ice!
Mom! I brought your medicine.
Oh, thank you...
You have homework, don't you?
You can finish it next to me.
Dad's boat got sunk.
I don't have time for studying!
Yasuo...
your father will come back alive.
You have to believe that!
Everyone at the harbor is saying
there's no way to survive
hitting an iceberg.
I'm sure they're just mistaken.
So please...
please, don't worry so much about it.
If believing those rumors
forces you to stop studying...
It would just kill me!
Don't say stuff like that, Mom!
Okay?
Yasuo, your father isn't dead.
He would never die and leave
such a nice boy behind!
He will come home.
You understand?
Just believe that,
and wait for him.
All right?
You understand?
Yeah!
Shocker's brought turmoil
to this quiet sea,
and sorrow to its
people's peaceful lives...
Hey, son.
What are you looking at?
You like the ocean?
I hate the ocean!
You hate the ocean?
I hate the ocean that
took my dad away!
Your father was
taken by the sea?
When did that happen?
Yesterday!
I was really waiting for
him to come back, too...
Darn it! Darn it!
Daddy! Daddy!
Listen, son. Stay close to me!
That Hayato...
he's trying to get ahead of me again.
Fortunately, I stuck a
transmitter on his motorbike.
You can't escape the
eyes of Taki Kazuya!
Hayato!
Taki!
How did you know I was here?
I'll explain later.
I'll get them to tell us
where Shocker's hideout is!
Mister! A monster!
Let's get to safety!
So you've shown yourself at
last, Shocker cyborg!
You can freeze all together!
Run!
You wretched monster...
I'll make this place your grave!
Time to freeze!
Do you see now why Todogiller is
feared, Ichimonji Hayato?!
Well done, Todogiller.
Once that perpetual thorn in our
side, the Kamen Rider is finished,
there will be no one
left to stand against us.
Doctor Shinigami.
This is what I'll do
to the Kamen Rider!
My negative 300
degree freezing shot
will do the same thing
to the Kamen Rider!
Todogiller.
The Kamen Rider is
trapped in the cave.
Bring him to me.
KAMEN RIDER
I don't think this
fire is hot enough...
Taki and Yasuo will
die at this rate.
I know...
I have only one choice left.
Transform!
Kamen Rider's idea was to heat
his own body with the fire
and use that heat
to melt the ice.
Rider!
You're awake?
I'm cold, Rider!
We're almost out. Hang in there.
Taki, let's go.
I'll do it.
It's not working!
It's no use...
Could there be another way out?
Here it is!
Perfect!
All right, let's escape!
Yasuo!
Mom! You need your rest!
Where in the world
have you been?
I was just about to send
the police looking for you!
Ma'am. Please don't
be so hard on Yasuo.
He's been waiting by the ocean,
worried about his father.
Who are you, sir?
I'm a friend of Yasuo's.
Yasuo. Don't worry your
mother, all right?
Okay!
Thanks, mister!
Thanks a lot!
Todogiller,
it seems your plan has failed!
Damn... find him!
I'm right here!
Let's go!
Watch. I won't let him escape!
I'll show you all
how Kamen Rider dies!
Now his motorbike
will slip on the ice!
Die!
Take him to our base!
So that's the way
in to their base?
Even the great Kamen Rider is a helpless
ice cube when frozen like this...
Doctor Shinigami,
let me crush him while he's frozen!
I have a far more
interesting idea.
Defrost him, restart his heart,
return him to his
Ichimonji Hayato form,
and then send him to hell.
This is how Shocker
puts a man to death!
Kamen Rider...
You've caused Shocker
much grief in the past.
But now,
it's your turn to suffer!
We'll see about that!
You underestimated the power
of Kamen Rider, Todogiller!
I intentionally let myself get
captured to find a way into your base!
Where are you holding the
crew of the sunken boats?
I asked you where they were!
Tell me at once!
Now, hit Doctor Shinigami
with your freezing shot!
Do it!
I'll release them.
Don't...
I promise.
Please, don't do it!
Revive them all,
and return them to the surface.
Did you hear me?
You think it will be that easy?
Rider!
Taki!
Release Todogiller.
Then I'll return Taki to you.
Damn...
Taki!
Go after Doctor Shinigami!
Leave Todogiller to me!
Wait, Todogiller!
You won't escape!
Get him!
Wait!
You won't escape
us, Doctor Shinigami!
Men like you sell your
souls to the devil...
I can't allow you to go free!
Wait!
Destroy Kamen Rider at once!
Face me, Kamen Rider!
Rider Kick!
The ice melted!
- Thank goodness!
- We're saved!
Where's Doctor Shinigami?
I'm sorry... he got away.
And the frozen people?
I found them in the cave there.
They're all safe.
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad we
didn't lose anyone...
Right, Taki?
Daddy! Daddy!
Yasuo!
Isn't that nice?
Listen, Yasuo.
It was Kamen Rider who saved me.
Isn't that nice, Yasuo?
I'm so happy for you!
Hayato!
Goro, the Kamen Rider
saved me back there.
Jeez, Hayato,
you're so unreliable!
Sorry about that.
The Kamen Rider had put an end
to the ice devil Todogiller.
But Shocker had not given
up on world domination.
What kind of cyborg would they
create to send at Kamen Rider next?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Hiruguerrilla.
Hiruguerrilla drinks the blood of
humans and turns them into slaves.
It's the most terrifying cyborg that
dastardly Shocker has created yet!
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
Hiruguerrilla of
the Vampire Swamp
in "Hiruguerrilla of
the Vampire Swamp!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!