KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Harinezuras'
Killer Skull Plan
I heard something.
Just your imagination.
I didn't hear anything.
Look, over there!
Look, it's moving!
There's something in there!
What could it be?
It's such a creepy sound...
I saw something there!
I'm scared!
Wh-What is this thing?
Damn... you monster!
Feel my poison needles!
Come quickly, someone!
H-Help me!
You can't escape me!
That way!
I definitely heard
a woman scream...
Look!
What in the world...
Monster!
It was I,
the great Harinezuras,
who melted those people
down to their bones!
M-M-Monster!
You're under arrest!
Fools.
Catch me if you can.
Stop or I'll shoot!
You think that will stop me?
Hey!
How do you like
my killer needles?
This new cyborg is Harinezuras,
created from a hedgehog.
The sharp needles
growing out of its body
contain a terrifying virus
that melts the human body down.
I dunno why, but anyone who comes to
this club always meets the Kamen Rider.
You think we'll meet him
too, Mitsuru?
We'll just have to trust
Goro, huh, Naoki?
That's right.
Who's this guy?
He's the Chairman of this club.
His name is Tobei.
He's really snoring, huh?
Go, Takeshi!
One more lap to the goal...
Just talking in his sleep.
He did it!
He fell!
I didn't realize
you kids were here.
Knock next time, would you?
But you were sleeping
so peacefully... Right?
Who are those kids?
My friends!
I'm Naoki!
Mitsuru!
You look pretty cute
when you're asleep, sir.
Right?
Hey! Show some respect
to your elders.
Sorry.
Awful news!
Great. More noise...
But it's an emergency!
They found four skeletons
behind a warehouse near here!
Everyone's talking about it!
We saw that police car
earlier, too!
What is it?
I hear a strange sound...
It just got dark!
A power outage?
Maybe...
Goro, the flashlight!
Right!
Chairman,
there's something behind the door!
There's needles in the wall!
What's all this?
The floor, too!
Chairman, close the door! Hurry!
There are so many needles!
I'm scared!
This is insane...
It's like they're alive!
The floor, too!
Everyone, watch out!
What do we do, Chairman?
I'm scared!
Okay...
I'll crush them one by one!
The ceiling, too!
Why, you...
Look out!
The needles are going away!
Takeshi...
how did you know we were in danger?
The needles attacked me
in my apartment, too.
I just had a feeling...
How can needles
move on their own?
You think someone
was controlling them?
If they were...
Hey, you don't think it's
Shocker, do you?
It's entirely possible.
Hey, those needles are causing
chaos all over the city!
We've already had
a few casualties.
Really?
This is going to be trouble...
How do you fight needles?
There has to be a way.
Knowing Shocker, they've probably
created a cyborg to control needles.
We need to catch their trail,
before disaster strikes!
Right.
The mysterious needle swarm
in Tokyo last night has caused
significant damages
all over the city.
It's believed the incident
could repeat itself.
Residents are advised to exercise
caution when going outside at night.
My leader.
The experiment was
a roaring success.
Please send us large amounts
of the killer virus at once.
A transport carrying the killer virus
left the Amazon heading for Japan today.
It should arrive momentarily.
Ambassador Hell,
flying object detected to the southwest.
It's the transport
carrying the virus.
Guide their way here.
Shocker transport here!
Transport here!
We've taken engine damage!
We're going down!
Going down?
Hey...
find out where they've crashed!
The crash location
is Miura Beach.
Miura Beach?
Harinezuras...
Take a rescue party to
retrieve the killer virus.
Ten minutes until we reach the crash
site, Miura Beach.
We can't let the humans get
their hands on that virus.
Hurry!
There are motorbikes
in pursuit.
Hongo Takeshi and Taki...
They must have intercepted
the S.O.S from the crash.
I'll show them!
We lost sight of the truck.
But we learned all we need to.
They're after a Shocker transport
that crashed on Miura Beach.
Okay, let's go.
Huh?
What's that box?
Let's see...
I bet it's got a
treasure inside it.
I'll open it later when
I've got some more time.
Hey, run!
Hurry! Hurry!
- Who are you people?
- What do you want with us?
A plane crashed in this area.
The cargo that was on
it has disappeared.
One of you must have hidden it!
We don't know what
you're talking about!
Yes!
We never saw any plane!
We didn't, I swear!
We didn't do it!
You greedy cretins!
Don't play dumb with me!
Tell me where you hid it!
I don't know!
I really don't know!
Help me!
Dear!
Talk, or you'll end up like him!
Hongo and Taki are
approaching the village.
We must conceal
our plan from them.
Go stand watch!
Kid!
Hey, kid. Sorry to scare you.
Do you live in this area?
Yeah.
I see.
Did you see an airplane go
down, then?
I see... did you see any parts that
looked like they were from a plane?
No way!
Hongo.
Any luck?
No witnesses.
And no idea where the Shocker
goons we were chasing went.
You think they cleaned up
the crash site and left?
Looking for something?
We think a plane crashed in the area.
We're searching for it.
So that was a plane, was it?
You saw it?
Oh, yeah.
There was a light in the sky,
and a ball of fire came down!
Then a parachute opened up in
the sky and dropped a box down!
Where's the box, sir?
It creeped me out,
so I hid it in that boathouse.
Where is the boathouse?
Can you take us there?
Sure.
This way.
We'll beat Shocker to it!
Here it is.
I put it in here.
Thank you for your help, sir.
I don't see anything...
It's a Shocker trap!
Hongo Takeshi, Taki Kazuya!
You'll never escape that hut!
Damn.
This rickety hut can't hold us!
Damn these needles...
Taki, look out!
The needles are explosive!
Grab on to my shoulders!
Thanks!
KAMEN RIDER
I've done it!
Hongo and Taki have
been reduced to ash!
What? Kamen Rider!
Are you Shocker's new cyborg?
The invincible Harinezuras!
Get them!
Rider, go fight!
Leave the combatants to me!
Get him!
Go!
Taki, hurry!
Harinezuras!
Where are you? Show yourself!
Feast your eyes on this!
That's cheating, Shocker!
It's the Kamen Rider!
He came to save us!
Help!
Beat Shocker up!
Shut up! Be quiet!
Damn them...
hiding behind children!
Rider!
Surrender, or the children die!
Help!
What is that needle?
This needle contains
a killer virus
that can melt a human
body in an instant.
I think you know that by now.
Do you want to see
the children die?
Help!
No... We can't let
him kill the children!
Don't do it, Harinezuras!
What are you after? Tell me!
I'll explain it
all to you later.
Grab the both of them!
What are you going
to do with us?
Execute Kamen Rider and Taki!
Get ready!
Taki... hold on tight.
Do it!
We did it!
They're both finished!
Not even Kamen Rider could
survive a fall like that!
Now... torture the
people of the village
until they tell you the
location of the virus!
Go!
Look at that!
Do you see what's about to
happen to your children?
When the tide comes
in, they'll all drown!
It's almost high tide!
You're monsters! You're beasts!
Dad, help! Help!
Help! Help!
It's time to stop
being stubborn!
Talk!
Where did you hide
that plane's cargo?
We really don't know anything!
It's the truth!
I know where it is!
Yukio!
Please, let them all go!
Child!
Yukio! Where have you been?
Why didn't you run away?
I couldn't run and leave
you, Mom!
I know, because I hid it!
Tell me where you hid it, boy!
Inside a boat on the beach!
Now... let everyone go!
I will,
if you're telling the truth.
Now, show me!
Hey, kid. Where is it?
Over there.
Find it.
This is it.
Okay? Will you free
Mom and everyone now?
Of course not.
We'll work them to death
as Shocker laborers!
But you promised!
Shut up!
The child is useless to us now!
The children are safe!
Hey!
The FBI fool, Taki...
He managed to survive, did he?
And it wasn't just Taki!
Hongo Takeshi... come out!
Get him!
Hold on tight.
I'm taking the child.
Damn you...
It's Rider!
Hold it!
You won't escape, Harinezuras!
Give me that box!
Take it from me, if you can!
Hold it!
You've done it now, Rider...
Now!
Rider Kick!
The Rider Kick
doesn't work on him?
Okay, now...
Rider Lightning Kick!
Hey! Everyone's safe!
Rider!
They're all safe, then...
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Shocker's killer
skull plan had failed,
and peace had returned to
the small fishing village.
Peace... and justice!
These are the things the
Kamen Rider fights for.
Go, Hongo Takeshi!
Go, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Saigang.
Doctor Shinigami and Shocker
arrange a deadly road race
to challenge Rider
in the Izu Highlands.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Saigang's
Deadly Auto Race."
The Monstrous Saigang's
Deadly Auto Race
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!