KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Hey! Get back here!
Get back here!
Rider Fight!
Forgive us!
We'll be good from now on!
I surrender!
Rider's just so cool!
Time for me to be Rider now!
Nuh-uh! It's me!
It's me!
No. You said I could
be Rider all day today.
It's no fun being Shocker all the time.
Yeah, I wanna switch.
Let's switch!
Come on, let's switch!
No way! Nyah!
That's not fair! Wait up!
Wait up!
Hold up, there.
Sorry.
Looks like you're fans
of the Kamen Rider, eh?
You bet we are!
That's great!
Why don't I
take you to meet the real Kamen Rider?
Can you do that?
Do you know the Kamen Rider?
I don't just know him.
We're very good friends!
Let us meet him!
All right.
Then I'll take you to meet him.
But if we stay out too long,
Mom is gonna be worried...
I won't force you to come.
I'm going!
Me, too!
Fine, I'll go, too...
Now, go on in.
Monster School
Mukadelas'
Nao!
Toshihiko!
Kiyo!
Nao!
That bike!
You don't think they
were kidnapped, do you?
What an awful thought...
Nao!
We get to meet the real Kamen Rider!
I'm gonna get his autograph.
I hope we get there soon!
Is it very far away?
Worried, are you?
I can show you the Kamen
Rider now, if you like.
What? Is he in this car?
Look behind you.
Your cries won't save you.
Just do as I say, and you'll
all meet the Kamen Rider!
My darling students. Remain calm.
My powerful hypnosis was gifted to me
by the brilliant scientists of Shocker!
Mukadelas, I have your second directive.
What is the second directive, Colonel Zol?
The computer has chosen the next child
for the Mukadelas Monster School.
Her name is Namie Ikusawa.
She's a brilliant student,
just like those four.
I wonder if Goro's still studying...
I've gotta work just as hard as he does!
Nami?
What in the...
"Don't let Goro beat you"?
Look alive!
What are you doing?!
Whoa, calm down!
What's with you, Goro?
Did you forget your homework and
get a lecture from your teacher?
No!
Ow!
G-Goro!
What's wrong with that kid?
Better to let sleeping dogs lie.
Apparently his little girlfriend
didn't come to school today.
Didn't come to school?
Apparently she's a bit of a rival, too...
They're always competing for
the best grade in class.
That's a bit concerning...
Why so, Ichimonji?
Look at this newspaper.
Let's see...
"Young Students Disappearing Across Japan"?
"All of the missing students
had excellent grades."
"Grieving parents left behind"...
I can't imagine what Shocker
would want with young children...
But we can't rule it out.
Hey, are you serious?
The new Shocker commander, Colonel Zol...
He does have a history of using children
for his Near and Middle East campaign.
Oh, dear...
Attention, boys and girls.
You've all been chosen for
your incredible intelligence.
Soon, the world will belong to Shocker.
When that time comes, you will be the
leaders for boys and girls your age.
You require a special education
to give you what you need
to be Junior Shocker leaders.
Those classes will begin today.
First, swear your loyalty to Shocker!
For the glory of the great Shocker!
Let class begin!
Your first subject will be
the proper handling of bombs.
What's wrong with you?
Colonel, I wish to recommend
a member for Junior Shocker.
Who is it?
Ishikura Goro, my friend.
Ishikura Goro?
I wonder where Namie went off to...
Her Mom and Dad are so worried, darn it...
Goro!
Hey, it's Namie!
Namie!
Goro!
Taxi!
I'll pay later!
Just follow that car, please!
Namie!
Namie! Namie!
Huh?
That's weird... she was
there just a minute ago...
Goro, get away!
I can't believe they came after me...
Hey, what's that sound?
You'll never find me!
You can't escape me, brat!
You will join Junior Shocker!
Help!
Ishikura Goro.
We'll have special uses for you
as a member of Junior Shocker.
For instance...!
Shocker cyborg...
The name is Mukadelas.
Ichimonji Hayato!
You fell right into our trap.
What?
What trap?
We know that wherever this boy goes, Kamen
Rider and his allies aren't far behind.
We used him as bait in our plan
to destroy Shocker's enemies!
Impossible.
What are you going to do
to those innocent children?
They're undergoing special training
as members of Junior Shocker!
Special training?
In Colonel Zol's Monster School.
Ichimonji Hayato...
Behold the power of Mukadelas!
Don't make me laugh...
You won't escape!
Have a shot of my
brain-melting radio waves,
and die in agony!
Goro...
Not good... it's tearing
my brain cells apart!
Transform!
KAMEN RIDER
Goro!
Wait!
Taki! Get on, hurry!
Okay!
Kamen Rider... I've prepared a
more suitable opponent for you.
Rider! That's Gebacondor!
Damnable Shocker... They brought
Gebacondor back to life?
Sarracenian...
Rider, I lost sight of the car Goro was in!
Colonel Zol.
When will Junior Shocker begin
its campaign of destruction?
I believe they have reached a
suitable place in their training.
The Shocker 190-type automatic
rifle allows for 24-round bursts
and is effective at a range of 1500 meters.
This Shocker 205-type automatic
rifle comes with an infrared scope,
allows for 32-round bursts, and is
effective at a range of 2000 meters.
These are Shocker's most powerful rifles.
Next!
Explosives, sniper rifles, toxins...
Having mastered all of
these things, tomorrow,
Junior Shocker will begin spreading
destruction all over Japan.
No one will ever believe
that children are behind this.
You think nobody will notice?
But we both know someone
who will, Colonel Zol!
The Kamen Rider?
If I may, sir...
We will soon launch an attack on Kamen Rider
to prove the skills of Junior Shocker.
There haven't been any
disappearances since then.
We won't be able to locate Goro
until Shocker makes a move.
Dammit!
Goro!
Where have you gone?
Calm down.
Getting frustrated won't help us.
Hayato.
Listen, I...
I...
I'm all alone in life.
No parents, no siblings...
So...
I'd begun to think of Goro
as my real little brother.
I feel the same way, Taki.
I see.
I suppose you would...
I'm sorry.
Footsteps!
Goro!
Look out, Taki!
Oh no! Goro's been hypnotized!
His eyes... Look at his eyes!
Goro's joined Shocker?!
Damn... there's nothing we can do!
There must be a Shocker
commander controlling them.
I know... Mukadelas!
Junior Shocker... Go forth! Fight!
Let's make a break for it, Taki!
Right!
Taki. You keep them locked in here.
What about you?
I'm going to find Mukadelas!
You idiots! Blow up the door!
Stop it! What are you doing?
I hear it...
With my hearing ten times
stronger than a normal person,
I hear it clearly!
It's coming from...
that mountain!
Transform!
It's time to finish what we started!
Rider Power!
What now, Rider?!
Rider Kick!
Rider Throw!
Get back! I'm lighting it!
Stop it! Don't do this!
Rider Kick!
Mukadelas is dead...
Has the Junior Shocker
plan fallen through?
Kamen Rider!
Rider!
Rider?
What's going on here?
Everything's all right now, Taki.
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Shocker's plan to exploit
the children failed,
and these cheerful kids
were safe once more.
But Shocker would already be
formulating their next move!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Mogurang!
Shocker is plotting to use mole people
to cause pandemonium at Tokyo Bay.
Kamen Rider's fight with Mogurang unfolds
at the All-Japan Motocross Championships.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Underground Monster Mogurang!"
Underground Monster Mogurang!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!