KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Semiminga's
Song of Slaughter!
Hey, I got another one!
You got another one?
Cool!
Another one?
Naoki,
you're a master cicada-catcher.
It's all in the timing.
Okay, I'll get one, too!
There's one!
No problem!
What are you doing?
Who gave you permission
to take these cicadas?
This forest belongs to me!
That's not nice!
What's wrong, Mitsuru?
Give me your cicadas, too.
No way!
Just do it.
Come on.
Now, go home.
Man, this sucks.
Cicadas these days can
fetch a pretty penny.
Those stupid children...
What's going on?
My head's splitting in two...
I forgot my net.
I'm gonna go get it.
- We'll wait here.
- Hurry up, okay?
Stupid cicadas!
Monster!
Foolish human...
You'll become a guinea
pig for Semiminga!
H-Help me!
Help me!
That sounded like...
H-Help me!
Naoki!
The experiment was
a roaring success.
I have high hopes for
your deadly sound waves.
No one can escape my
killer sound waves.
I'll murder everyone in Tokyo!
See that it's done.
What is it?
We've sighted children in the forest
where Semiminga did his tests.
What's that?
All right...
Not even children can be spared.
Semiminga, go finish them off!
I'm so creeped out.
Let's go home already.
But we can't leave Naoki here.
Why don't we all
carry him together?
Guess it's our only choice.
Upsy-daisy!
Hey, kids!
Hey, Mr. Hongo!
You left your net on
the path back there.
What's wrong with Naoki?
No idea.
Naoki, what's wrong?
Naoki!
Cicada monster...
It was a cicada monster!
Let's get him home for now.
Come on, get his hat.
Hongo Takeshi has the child...
All right... just you watch!
Approaching attack target.
What in the world did Naoki see?
He insists it was
a cicada monster.
A cicada monster...
A cicada, huh?
It's not a Shocker
cyborg, is it?
No, it might just be.
Then, Hongo...
Bringing him to your
apartment means...
If it's Shocker,
they'll strike soon.
And when that happens...
Got it.
Change direction.
All right, initiate attack!
Taki...
It's a cicada's cry.
Taki,
get Naoki out of here at once.
Right.
What's going on here?
He's gone.
That can't be!
The killer sound waves
must have killed him!
Search carefully!
Am I the one you're looking for?
Hongo!
Killer sound waves, eh?
That might kill
a normal human...
But they won't be
enough to hurt me!
Die!
Talk!
Where are the killer sound
waves transmitted from?
Oh no!
Emergency order.
Pursuer detected.
Hongo!
The transmitter for the sound
waves must be under that canopy.
Hurry!
Right...
Hongo is up on the roof.
Shake him off!
Now, fight back!
Hongo! Hang in there!
Taki? Where's Naoki?
I got him out safely.
Okay,
try to get the driver for me!
Got it!
- Hongo!
- Taki!
The killer sound waves came
from inside this truck.
Okay, let's see what's inside.
Wait!
So you're the one producing
the killer sound waves?
Took you this long
to realize it?
Shocker's killer sound waves come from
me, Semiminga!
I won't let you
get away with this!
Try me!
Get them!
Rider Transformation!
Fight me, Kamen Rider!
Gladly, Semiminga!
The world around me...
going dark...
Kamen Rider,
I'll finish you now...
by sucking out all your energy!
Rider, this way!
KAMEN RIDER
Ishiyama General Hospital
Hongo Takeshi has likely been
hospitalized with serious injuries.
Good. Keep an eye on him.
My leader.
Our mortal enemy, Hongo Takeshi,
has been paralyzed from the waist down
by Semiminga's killer sound waves.
Now nobody will be
able to stop us.
We can turn Tokyo into
a land of the dead.
Well done.
The unexplained deaths
in Tokyo caused by the
killer sound waves
will inspire a panic.
Now we just need to secure
a broadcast tower for them.
Of course, that's easily done.
You'll see what
Ambassador Hell can do.
Excellent.
See that you succeed.
Semiminga, go!
Occupy the broadcast tower!
I thought so.
They're watching us like hawks.
For Heaven's sake.
Don't scare me like that, Takeshi.
When Taki called,
I thought they'd gotten you for good.
Well,
it wasn't entirely a lie...
If he'd come any later, that cicada
would have fried my brain for real.
But if you're all right, why not walk out
instead of checking into the hospital?
If Shocker thinks I'm paralyzed,
they're more likely to let something slip.
Right.
So? What can we do?
Say anything!
We'll make sure it's done!
To make best use of
Semiminga's killer sound waves,
they'll want to secure a
high, unimpeded location.
They'll probably want a
broadcast tower, then.
You mean... a Shocker Tower?
Right.
Then we need to find
the Shocker Tower.
That's right.
I prepared a sound
wave detector.
Then we'd better call Emi
too, right?
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Well? What's the word?
It's not here.
Good grief...
Never said finding Shocker
Tower would be easy, did we?
Don't start complaining yet.
We've got a long way to
go, right?
Yeah, yeah...
Chairman, something's off...
Yeah, this is it!
But... in a place like this?
Okay, let's get searching.
You okay, Chairman?
Just leave it to me!
That's strange.
Let's look in that direction.
There it is!
This really is it!
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Chairman!
Look!
Okay, come along.
Got it?
Right!
- C'mon.
- Right.
Here.
No visitors allowed.
Oh, hello there.
We were out hiking, so...
Let us have lunch, won't you?
We promise we won't
get in your way.
It's out of the question!
We'll eat fast and
be out of your hair.
We won't be long, okay?
I said no.
Now, get going.
If you insist. Let's go.
What a jerk.
See you around.
That went perfect!
That broadcast tower must be the
Shocker Tower that Takeshi mentioned.
Let's contact him at once!
Tachibana here.
Hongo, respond.
Tachibana here!
Taki? Hongo? Respond!
What are they doing?
You... you'll come with me, too!
Not a chance!
I won't let you contact Hongo!
Emergency call from
Ambassador Hell.
What?
Hongo and Taki have
vanished from the hospital.
He wants you to broadcast
the killer sound waves ASAP.
Damn... Hongo and Taki must
have followed them here!
Watch me now...
I'll smoke you out!
Listen up, Hongo Takeshi!
I know you're hiding nearby!
You'd better show yourself
before I count to five!
If you don't,
I'll kill all your comrades!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Come out, Hongo Takeshi!
You coward!
Going to let your comrades die
for fear of my killer sound waves?
Then I'll have to kill them all!
And not just them....
I'll bathe Tokyo in my killer sound
waves from here in Shocker Tower!
Kamen Rider!
Semiminga...
sorry to tell you,
but we have an electric
current blocking your
killer sound waves running
all around this tower.
What did you say?
You were so busy
searching for me and Taki,
you didn't even notice what
was going on around you!
Then that brat Taki set
up the jamming current?!
This will protect the tower
from the killer sound waves.
All right!
Taki!
Mr. Taki!
Rider!
Taki, take care of
Pops and the girls!
Right!
Mr. Taki!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
Listen up, Kamen Rider!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Even if I can't
reach all of Tokyo,
Go! Go! Let's go!
my power can still kill you!
What did you say?
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider!
I won't rest until I defeat you!
Rider Kick!
I don't think so!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
Rider,
leave the small fry to me!
Right! Good luck!
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
I've been waiting, Semiminga!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Come on!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Rider Throw!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Damn you...
All right. Now!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
He beat the monster!
That's great to hear.
Rider, Rider!
If we hadn't made it in time,
Japan would've been in serious trouble!
Yeah!
Shocker's killer sound
waves plan was foiled.
But Shocker was already
preparing its next cyborg foe.
Go, Hongo Takeshi!
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Kabutrong.
Kabutrong is ordered
to turn the children
of the world into
Shocker combatants.
Join us next week for "The Monstrous
Doctor Insect and the Shocker School."
The Monstrous Doctor Insect
and the Shocker School
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!