KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
The Terrifying Bat Man
Good night.
We have an early day tomorrow.
Don't sleep in too late, Miho.
I hear you. Don't worry.
Take care!
Bye-bye!
What was that sound?
Who's there? Is someone there?
Miho Yamano.
You have been chosen.
You have the honor of
being part of Shocker!
Shocker is a terrifying
secret society
with a network of organizations
spread across the world.
They plan to turn all humans into
cyborgs serving at their command
and in doing so,
conquer the world.
I'm sure I was just
hearing things.
I'm sure it wasn't real...
Nobody's followed me.
I was sure I'd
closed that window...
My mind's really playing
tricks on me tonight.
But I have to get
up early tomorrow...
How right you are!
We have many things
for you to do tomorrow!
Start
All-Japan Tryouts
Tokyo Region Qualifiers
One more lap, Takeshi!
Hongo Takeshi is a young
man of peerless intelligence
who works in Jonan University's
biochemistry laboratory.
He's been transformed
into a cyborg by Shocker,
but he escaped just before
they altered his mind.
As the one man in the world who
knows the extent of Shocker's evils,
he has chosen to risk
his life to fight them.
Hey! Look at that time!
One step closer to the
big race in Europe.
You big lug!
Still aiming high, huh?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Look out!
A Shocker cyborg?
I'd hoped to kill two
birds with one stone...
But at least I proved
the experiment a success.
The strange way
that model died...
If she really was a
member of Shocker,
there must be a clue
to find somewhere.
I don't understand...
Chie. You're sick.
Let's go to a hospital. Okay?
Don't come near me...
I don't want you to suffer
the same fate I have.
My love...
Do it! Bring your husband
into our collective!
Run, my love...
Who's there?
Stop it!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Chie!
Run!
Leave this building at once!
Hurry!
I'll look after your wife.
Is that... really my Chie?
She's completely
out of her mind...
What did Shocker do to her?
Damn!
Wait, you!
Shocker...
I'm a human bat!
Welcome, Hongo Takeshi, to the testing
grounds for Shocker's human experiments.
Human experiments?
This apartment complex?
Our scientists have
bred a new virus.
We must test its
effectiveness against humans.
That's why we're
gathering data here.
Infecting humans with a virus?
Of course.
That woman was one
of your victims!
You can see the results of
our experiments first-hand!
Wait!
Get out of my way.
I see...
They've all been
infected already.
That man is our enemy.
The hated enemy of Shocker!
Now, attack him!
Attack him and kill him!
I can't hurt them.
They're victims in all of this.
If I fight them,
they'll turn out like that model.
They're not doing this
of their own free will.
Well?
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Sound waves for the current human
bat experiments have ceased.
No need to worry.
The human bat has the ability
to induce autohypnosis.
If they find themselves in danger,
they can use it to protect our secret.
But what about the
current experiments?
When the human bat sleeps, the humans used
for our experiments will sleep as well.
I'm telling you, I don't know.
I don't believe you.
I think you know just
where Hongo Takeshi is.
If you didn't, how would you have
helped me find my father back then?
I was just asked to
pass the message along.
I'll get it.
Yes? Tachibana here.
Sorry, wrong number.
All right. I believe you.
Hello? It's me.
Yeah.
Where will you be
in the afternoon?
Right. Jonan University?
I'll bet that's Hongo
Takeshi he's talking to.
So he'll be at Jonan University!
Midorikawa Ruriko's father,
Doctor Midorikawa, was killed by Shocker.
Ruriko thinks it was Hongo
Takeshi who killed her father,
and so, in her hatred,
she's gone searching for him.
I don't believe it...
How is it possible?
What have you
learned, Kishimori?
Look for yourself, Hongo.
Hongo...
The blood you brought in
contains an intelligent virus.
An intelligent virus?
It reacts to external stimuli.
Move the slide and you'll see.
And so...
This intelligent virus...
If it were to reach brain cells,
they would move in accordance
with certain sound waves?
And if we're talking
about the human brain,
a person infected with that blood could
be controlled entirely with sound waves.
Kishimori.
Can you create a
serum for this virus?
With a serum,
they might just recover.
It's hard enough to believe
this virus even exists.
A serum would be
an impossible task.
Then you're saying...
those people will never...
KAMEN RIDER
That's the man who
killed my father.
What?
We need to take him to the
police, then.
We can't.
I'm an eyewitness,
but I still don't have any proof.
Let's follow him.
I'm sure we'll find some proof.
That's the café where we work!
What are you doing?
Boss,
where did that customer go?
Customer?
Oh, a young man burst in saying he
was being chased by shady characters.
He went out the window.
Out the window?
Would the "shady characters"
be you two, then?
Boss... that man...
He's the one who
killed Ruriko's father!
Really?
I guess I shouldn't
have let him get away...
Boss knows something.
Boss told me where my
father was that day.
Hongo Takeshi was there.
He must know where
Hongo Takeshi is hiding.
Hongo Takeshi must live
in that apartment complex.
So that monster is
controlling these people?
I believe these human bats have undergone
some kind of animalistic state of hypnosis.
We need to create some kind of serum,
or they won't be the only ones.
More and more people will
fall prey to this virus!
We can't let them steal
away people's freedom.
So? What do we do?
Mr. Tachibana...
I will fight!
Let me be
the last victim of Shocker.
Takeshi!
I hate that Ruriko
doesn't believe me...
But some day...
I'm going to get the car.
I want to bring them to the university
lab before he comes out of hibernation.
All right. I'll stand watch.
Hongo Takeshi is alone
in this apartment.
Boss!
Bat Man has begun emitting
sound waves again.
His instincts may have informed
him that the danger is past,
and so the hypnotism
is beginning to wane.
Who are these people?
Why did Hongo
Takeshi do this to you?
Hongo Takeshi?
Why do you know that name?
He killed my father.
Killed your father?
Who was your father?
Hiroshi Midorikawa.
I'm his daughter, Ruriko.
Doctor Midorikawa?
You knew my father?
Yes, I did.
And not just that...
I have proof that
Hongo Takeshi killed him!
Do you mean that?
I am on your side.
Quickly. Untie me.
Of course!
You...
Mr. Tachibana!
Hongo. Look at her neck!
He gave Ruriko the virus...
What?
Behold... the virus is
gradually taking her over.
My body is going numb...
Suffer! You must suffer!
Your father, Doctor Midorikawa,
was executed for betraying Shocker.
My father... a traitor?
Traitors must die.
Such is the law of Shocker.
Then Hongo Takeshi didn't do it?
You decide whether
she lives or dies.
Don't trust him, Hongo!
Even if you make a deal, we can't
guarantee he won't kill her anyway.
Human Bat.
How do I save Ruriko?
There is a serum
that will free her.
A serum?
No...
I was wrong about everything.
You mustn't put yourself
in danger for me...
What's it going to be, Hongo?
If you can prove that it will save
her, I'll do whatever you ask.
Hongo!
Don't do it!
Show him, Bat Man!
My slave, asleep in the
depths of consciousness.
Awake, and strike yourself with the
spine of awakening from my wing!
I see...
the serum is in your body.
Then the battle is won!
Stop!
Hongo... sooner or later,
that girl will die...
Following your example!
I knew from the start that
I couldn't trust Shocker.
You can't save her without me.
Now, watch her die in agony!
Ruriko! Ruriko!
Speak to me!
Takeshi!
Ruriko!
Rider Throw!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Here.
Chie.
Chie. Are you all right?
Now, that's nice to see.
I'm so glad it worked!
Hongo.
Ruriko understands
everything now.
You don't have to run anymore.
Mr. Tachibana.
Ruriko might have
softened towards me...
But my body...
My body remains how it was.
Hongo!
Hongo Takeshi has been cleared
of the murder of Doctor Midorikawa.
Yet he raced off alone,
enduring the sorrow of his cyborg state.
He had only one goal: To foil
the evil plots of Shocker.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Scorpion Man.
The person behind this terrifying devil
turns out to be a complete surprise.
How will Kamen Rider fare
against this man-eating scorpion?
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Scorpion Man."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!