KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
My Name is
Monster Bird Gillgaras!
Is the deadman gas
experiment ready to proceed?
It is.
Begin the experiment.
The deadman gas takes effect
in five seconds, then.
All right... siphon out the gas.
Suffer.
Any human exposed
to the deadman gas
begins to thirst
insatiably for human blood.
I'll use the deadman gas to force
not just the people of Tokyo,
but all the people of Japan
to hate and kill each other.
Doctor Shinigami.
Assign the newly-created
cyborg Gillgaras to the task
and initiate the
slaughter of humanity.
Kamen Rider! Kamen Rider!
Rider! Rider!
I want this one!
That crow is so smart.
It even talks!
It's cool how it knows
how to say "Kamen Rider."
Mom, I want this one.
I want this crow.
What a creepy crow...
But you promised
to buy me anything!
You'll have to take care of
it, you know.
I will!
Excuse me!
Welcome.
How much is the crow?
You want to buy it?
Yes.
Kamen Rider! Kamen Rider!
Oh, please! Crows can't talk.
This one can.
What do you want me to say?
- Hey, there.
- Hey.
You're not going
to see the crow?
The crow's gone.
Really?
Yoshiko in the Agatsuki
Apartments bought it.
- Wow, weird taste, huh?
- Yeah.
But that crow could even sing about
Kamen Rider and Shocker and stuff.
Hey, Mr. Chairman.
What?
Do you think crows
can talk like people?
- Crows?
- Yeah.
Don't be ridiculous.
Crows caw and cats meow,
and that's how it's always been.
I can't stop wondering...
Okay, I'm gonna check!
Hey, where are you going?
What about your homework?
Crows caw and cats meow!
Bye-bye!
What's his problem?
Don't scare me like that!
And here I thought
you were fearless.
I guess you're as human
as the rest of us, Pops.
Give me a break!
If you're hanging out together,
there must not be much going on...
Shocker's been keeping
a low profile lately.
It means we can do
a lot of training.
Hey, that's perfect
timing, then.
Goro's been acting strangely.
Goro?
He asked me a question
about talking crows,
and then he wandered
off, mumbling.
Talking crows?
Okay. Since you're such
a good friend, Goro,
I'll lend you my
crow for one night.
Thanks a lot!
- Come by my room, okay?
- Sure.
She just insisted, so...
Take it back this instant!
Crows have always
meant bad fortune.
Can't we at least wait
until she gets home?
Just looking at
it creeps me out!
And all this talk of crows talking
like people... it's too much!
Look, I'm taking it back...
Shocker! Shocker!
What's going on?
It's very unsettling...
Eiko... look!
A crow monster!
Foolish humans!
Hate each other!
Fight each other!
Send each other to hell!
Looks like the deadman
gas has taken effect.
Now, kill each other!
- Just wait here, okay?
- Sure!
Yoshiko!
What's wrong, Yoshiko?
My Mom and Dad...
Emergency! Someone come help!
Emergency!
They're... They're dead!
Monster!
Goro.
What's all the hubbub?
They're dead!
What?
Who's dead?
Mr. Taki...
It's like they killed each
other out of pure hatred.
Taki.
Everyone in the complex is dead.
I think they all tore
each other apart.
Then, you think...
There's only one entity in the world
that could do something so awful.
Shocker!
What an awful thing to do...
Come on, Goro.
We can't stay here.
Poor girl.
She's fainted from the shock.
Enemies of Shocker,
Ichimonji Hayato and Taki Kazuya!
This will make the
perfect prison for you!
Now, receive my
baptism of deadman gas!
Damn...
Shocker knew we would come!
Ichimonji, the gas!
I don't want to die!
Goro, get down!
Taki, boost me!
Ichimonji! You okay?
I'm more than human.
I'll be fine!
Damn you, Shocker!
Transform!
Shocker cyborg...
Are you the one behind this?
I am!
All humans exposed to the deadman
gas will tear each other apart!
I call it Operation:
Human Annihilation!
That certainly sounds like the
work of an evil Shocker assassin...
But sorry to say,
I'm putting an end to your plot!
Try it, if you can, Kamen Rider!
I can and I will!
Get him!
Die, Kamen Rider!
Strange...
I feel numb! What's going on?
The gas is taking effect.
It seems like it's
working, Kamen Rider.
The deadman gas turns
humans into killers.
But it does one more thing...
One more thing?
The deadman gas has a
special side effect...
When used against a
cyborg, it paralyzes them!
Damn...
- Hayato!
Ichimonji!
Ichimonji Hayato,
the Kamen Rider,
has been hospitalized
for full-body paralysis.
Kill him.
This is our chance to be rid
of Shocker's greatest enemy,
the Kamen Rider!
Our scientists report that injecting
the Kamen Rider with Gamma G,
the core material
of the deadman gas,
will completely destroy him.
Then let us administer
Gamma G to the Kamen Rider.
Go, Gillgaras!
KAMEN RIDER
Which should I pick?
It's so hard to choose...
This way, if you would.
How about this one?
This one?
Oh, it's creepy!
A crow, really?
But it's a unique crow.
Now, go and sing!
Kamen Rider! Kamen Rider!
Sold!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider! Kamen Rider!
He seems fast asleep.
Should we wake him up?
No way. We'll get a
scolding from the Chairman.
But we carried this heavy
thing all this way to see him!
If he's asleep,
maybe we should just leave it?
Kamen Rider!
Hush. Save it for later.
Listen to me.
Wait until Hayato's
awake to say that.
Do as you're told,
or we'll fry you up and eat you.
Do people really eat fried crow?
Of course.
Shinshu Ueda is famous
for crow dengaku!
So creepy!
All three of you together?
Hey, how's Mr. Ichimonji doing?
He hasn't regained
consciousness since then.
I see...
A crow? There's an
unusual bedside present.
It's not just any crow!
That's right.
It can talk like humans do!
Right?
What did you say?
Is this the crow that
Goro was talking about?
Hey, don't act so scary...
Where did you find it?
There was a man selling birds...
Selling birds? Okay...
Welcome.
What can I get for you?
A crow.
And one that talks, please.
Oh, please.
Everyone knows that
crows can't talk.
You're claiming ignorance?
Don't tease me, please, sir.
Stop playing dumb.
I know what's going on here.
You're a liar!
You just sold it to us!
Get back here!
Now, talk!
Why did you sell that crow
as a present for Ichimonji?
To purge this world
of Kamen Rider!
Why, you...
Taki!
It's too late to stop this.
By now, Gillgaras will have
put an end to the Kamen Rider!
Even the great Kamen Rider
is left paralyzed and bedridden
by the power of the deadman gas!
Perhaps I'll put him
out of his misery.
The Gamma G will destroy him!
You!
Ichimonji Hayato is not
the only Kamen Rider.
I am Hongo Takeshi...
the first Kamen Rider!
You!
Are you Hongo Takeshi, the one who's
been undermining Shocker's Europe Branch?
Ichimonji Hayato sent me a message
just before he lost consciousness.
You'll still make
a worthy opponent.
Now, breathe my deadman gas!
He was all talk after all.
Take him away!
Stick Hongo Takeshi
into the gas chamber.
Do it.
We've produced
enough deadman gas
to turn everyone in Tokyo
into a mindless murderer.
Now initiate the plan,
focusing on the Keihin Industrial Belt.
What is it?
Emergency in progress.
There is a deadman
gas leak in Z-Block.
What's going on here?
Death!
You... but you breathed
in the deadman gas!
There was an antidote in one
of the European Shocker bases.
I used it to save both
Ichimonji Hayato and myself.
Damn...
Death... surrender already!
Silence, fool.
Get him!
Go!
Gillgaras!
Wait, Gillgaras!
Hongo Takeshi.
We may have lost this base,
but the poison gas
we've stored up
still has the power to drive all of the
people of Tokyo to madness and death.
How do you know that?
Gillgaras has a
tanker of the gas.
He'll disperse the
poison from the skies.
I won't let it happen, Death!
Mr. Chairman, Tokyo's in danger.
I'm going to try
to stop Gillgaras.
Good luck, Hayato!
Let's show the people of Tokyo
the power of this poison gas!
Wait, Gillgaras!
Ichimonji again?
Get him!
Transform!
You'll pay!
Not so fast, Death!
Open the tanker and
release the gas!
Now!
Rider Double Kick!
Tokyo International Airport
I have a new
mission ahead of me.
Hongo...
I won't let you outshine me.
You can expect to see
amazing things from me.
Shocker's South America
Branch is formidable.
I'll be just fine.
You worry about Japan.
I'll take care of it.
It's the only one I have,
but to remember me by...
Give it to the others.
I will.
Ichimonji Hayato would leave Japan
to fight Shocker in South America.
And the first Kamen
Rider, Hongo Takeshi,
would be back in
action in Japan!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Jaguar Man.
With razor-sharp claws
and incredible speed,
he stops Kamen
Rider in his tracks.
The Jaguar's roar sends a
peaceful zoo into chaos.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Jaguar Man's
Deadly Motorbike Battle."
The Monstrous Jaguar Man's
Deadly Motorbike Battle
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!