KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Cockroach Man!!
The Dreadful
Germ-Stuffed Ad Balloon
I was sure I heard something...
Who's there?
Show yourself!
Stop it!
Please, no!
We can't leave it here.
Clean it up.
That was pretty crummy.
Now, watch me work!
Hey, Goro!
Kids aren't allowed.
Aw, that's no fun.
Now, watch me!
Amazing!
Isn't he great?
He's handsome,
and he's also really talented!
What's the matter? Hey!
Hey!
What's the matter?
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
Speak to me!
How awful...
You think Shocker's behind it?
Th-This is why I didn't
want to go bowling!
Oh, Goro!
We need to tell Takeshi at once!
If Shocker is behind this...
But why weren't the
rest of you affected?
I'd heard you'd gotten
obsessed with bowling,
but you even bought a ball?
These are expensive,
aren't they?
Yuri.
Were the people who collapsed in the
bowling alley using their own balls?
It didn't look like it, did it?
I think they used the
bowling alley's balls.
Taki!
The test was a grand success.
Infecting the ball
holes with the bacteria
will let us rapidly
age the humans
without them ever
suspecting a Shocker plot.
Well done.
Now, use the strain with
greater contagiousness,
so that it will spread to those who
touch the collapsed people as well.
Sir.
If we cover cockroaches with
the bacteria and disperse them,
the disease will spread like
wildfire and cause mass panic!
You think there's
bacteria in the holes?
Most likely.
They lined them with a bacteria that
rapidly increases cellular aging,
causing anyone who puts their
fingers inside to be infected.
Is that why they
chose a bowling alley?
Yes, Shocker wants to get as many
victims as possible, and quickly.
Let's return to the
laboratory and investigate.
Attention, apartment folks!
Cockroaches are a
plague upon humanity!
Let's all work together to purge
them from our kitchens and houses
and create a beautiful,
cockroach-free apartment complex!
This one-shot cockroach killer
is guaranteed effective!
One spray and the
cockroaches are dead!
And it's only 500 yen!
Come and try it!
Just 500 yen for all your
cockroach-killing needs!
You can't beat that
price, just 500 yen!
Well, any takers? Any takers?
Thank you very much.
That'll be 500 yen.
Thank you. Thank you.
Would you like one, ma'am?
Let's buy some, Mom.
- Good idea.
- We'll take one!
Thank you.
That will be 500 yen.
Thank you very much.
What about you, ma'am?
Would you like our
cockroach killer?
They must be trying to interfere
with Shocker's Operation: Cockroach.
We made a bundle off that worthless goop.
You're something!
A real rotten guy!
Keep your voice down.
You dare to interfere
with Shocker's plans?
Get lost, Shocker!
Wait, what's Shocker?
Who are you people?
Hey!
Hey, knock it off!
Help!
What are you doing?
H-Help us!
W-Wait a minute! Hey!
I'll pay you! Just spare me!
I'll pay you!
Help!
You've interfered with
Shocker's Operation: Cockroach.
As punishment,
I'll turn you into cockroach men,
and put you in charge of
Shocker's germ warfare.
Stop this! The spray was a scam!
It doesn't even work!
Please, spare me!
Begin the surgery.
I am Cockroach Man!
What's wrong, fatty?
You're next.
S-Spare me!
I'll serve Shocker
any way you ask!
Just don't make me a cockroach!
What a pathetic display.
We'll use him as he is, then.
Attention,
children of the apartment complex!
We're giving out free
balloons, just for you!
Let's go!
Come on, first-come,
first-served!
Come on around!
They're pretty balloons!
Here you go!
You came at a great time, Goro.
I'm always lucky.
I'll have a blue one!
I'll take white!
- Hurry!
- White, okay?
White, right?
Yes, here's a white one.
Thanks!
This guy was working with
the quack bug spray seller.
Quack?
What are you talking about?
We sprayed that stuff on the
cockroaches, but it didn't do anything!
Okay, let's get him!
W-Wait a minute!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You've got the wrong
guy, I'm sure.
Don't let him escape!
Hold it!
You big jerk! You liar!
Be silent, children!
They'll make fine guinea pigs.
Take them away!
Stop!
Go!
Wait, Shocker!
Darn it...
Masako, a phone!
Where's a phone?
That way.
Hello? Tachibana...
Oh, that you, Goro?
Hey, slow down a minute!
What?
Shocker kidnapped children?
Where'd they go?
Driving north from
Hiraodai Apartment Complex?
Understood. I'm on my way.
Pops, tell Taki to join me ASAP.
Right.
He's on our tail.
Damn... the brat called someone!
Forget him. Keep driving!
Hey, stop! Stop now!
You think I'm gonna stop
just because you tell me to?
It's a dead end!
Bro... I mean, Mr. Cockroach,
what do I do?
Useless trash.
You took the wrong road!
Look... I'm quitting
this rotten line of work!
Hold it!
Please... spare me!
Please? Spare me!
Traitors must pay!
Damn it...
I see... so you're the ones
spreading the bacteria, eh?
Rider Transformation!
You all right, Rider?
Run, while you can!
KAMEN RIDER
I'm getting it now.
Just hang on a minute.
The mysterious illness
spreads to anyone who touches
the rapidly aged people as well,
and an effective method of
fighting it has not yet been found.
Announcer Yamamoto
We'll have more about this incident
during the three o'clock news hour.
Let the bacteria-filled
ad balloon rise
and detonate it in midair
to complete the operation.
The bacteria will be carried
on the wind and spread quickly,
causing humans all over
to rapidly age and die.
Operation: Ad Balloon will
commence at three o'clock.
See that Hongo and Taki
are dealt with before then!
They say the victims
won't last a week.
You mean...
They're going to die like this?
Yes, after continued aging.
How awful...
Isn't there some
medicine to cure them?
Nothing we can
make up in a week.
But if we restore this
man's consciousness,
he might tell us
something useful.
All right.
I'll try this.
Hey. Wake up!
C... Ca...
What is it? Speak up!
Capsules...
Capsules?
In my jacket... jacket...
They gave him medicine,
to cure him if he was infected!
Damn!
The jacket's due to be
incinerated to prevent infection!
Here it is!
Throw this man out the window!
Someone's coming. Let's go!
Taki!
Are you all right?
Of course...
Cockroach Man must have done this.
Of course... I'll try these.
- I see...
- Damn!
That cockroach
bastard ambushed me!
So this is what does it, eh?
Hongo!
Hey, wake up!
Are you all right?
Come on,
I'll give you the medicine.
Go on, take it.
Thank you.
You're safe now.
What do you know about Shocker?
At three o'clock... from the roof
of the Sun Building... ad balloon...
Ad balloon?
Release... bacteria...
from the skies.
What did you say?
Look after him.
There's only one capsule left,
but see if they can analyze
and replicate it at once.
Where are you going?
Apparently they're going
to release an ad balloon
filled with bacteria from
the roof of the Sun Building.
Okay, I'll join you later.
I'll leave this to you.
I see you've had
a change of heart.
I'm sorry for what I've done.
I'm an honest man now.
Just five minutes left.
Okay...
Rider Transformation!
Cyclone Jump!
Preparations complete.
We've attached the
auto-detonator.
Good.
Now, foolish humans...
look up to the sky!
Now,
I will kill all of humanity!
Hold it!
You can't stop me!
Shocker is coming,
Get him!
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Damn!
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Rider!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Taki, take it!
Right!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Prepare to die!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Now!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Reverse Kick!
Right.
Let's get to the hospital.
Taki!
We've finished them off.
What a dastardly bunch...
Is the medicine finished yet?
Hongo was just heading
for the laboratory.
It's finished!
They'll be all right now.
You're all safe now.
Let's go, Taki.
Everyone's waiting.
And so,
the people's youth returned.
But there was no way to restore
the body of cyborg Hongo Takeshi.
The Kamen Rider's future holds
only endless battles with Shocker.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Gireela.
Gireela spits venomous darts.
What is Shocker's
Operation: Poison Water,
based around poison capsules
created from these darts?
Our Kamen Rider stands
against their evil plan.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Poison Butterfly of the
Amazon, Gireela!"
Poison Butterfly of the
Amazon, Gireela
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!