KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Terrifying Operation: Pet
Send Rider to Hell!
Isn't this great?
I never knew air could taste so fresh!
It's the best thing in the world.
Hey, I hear a canary singing somewhere!
Are there canaries in this area?
Over there!
Okay! Leave this to me!
He got it!
He's quite a little cutie, eh?
He's not afraid of you, Mr. Yamanaka?
Of course not.
Despite appearances,
I'm a kind and gentle man.
Cute, isn't he?
Let's take it back and keep it as a pet!
But its singing seems so strange...
What is it? What's wrong?
Yoko, what's wrong?
Hey... what's wrong with you guys?
You cannot escape!
You know what happens when
a snake hunts a frog?
Well, you're the frogs!
Wait just a minute.
If I may.
Ah, go ahead.
What an awful way to die...
What's the cause of death?
Poisoning.
It's like they were bitten
by a venomous snake.
A venomous snake?
What?
Four people were killed at the Tama River?
The police say they were
bitten by a venomous snake.
But you wouldn't see snakes around now.
That's true...
Hey, look! A canary!
Isn't it cute?
It'll get away!
I got it!
What do you think?
It's strangely tame...
You think it's someone's pet?
No way.
Small animals like me, that's all.
See?
Wow, it really is tame!
The way it sings seems strange, though.
Hey!
I found something we can use.
That's nice.
It's still usable.
Here you are, your own castle.
What should we feed it?
Let's see. Canaries eat...
Normal bird food is fine, it says.
We'll go buy it!
Can we have money?
Here.
It's so cute!
Hey, what should we call it?
Good question!
Hey, guys, you've got work to do.
Fine.
Venomous snakes out of
season, and a lost canary...
Thank you for coming.
That looked like...
Gel Shocker!
Over there!
No one's here!
Let me go! Let me go!
Darn it! Let me go!
We're going to use you to
lure out Hongo Takeshi!
Come along!
It's a police car!
Help, Mr. Policeman!
Mr. Policeman! Arrest Gel Shocker!
Gel Shocker... Do they look like this?
They're Gel Shocker, too!
Let me go!
Hold it!
I thought I might find
something like this...
Naoki, Mitsuru!
Takeshi! Please, help!
He bit me!
Now's your chance! Run!
As long as I'm around,
you won't have your way!
We need to tell Captain Taki!
It hurts...
What's going on here?
My head is pounding...
It... It hurts...
Can't stand it...
Ambulance... call an ambulance!
Captain Taki!
Mr. Hongo is fighting Gel Shocker!
What's wrong, you guys?
What's wrong?
Hey, what's wrong?
My head... it hurts...
I don't know what's going on.
Just call an ambulance!
Okay!
What's wrong, Mitsuru?
Get a grip!
It hurts...
Naoki!
Hey... it's a monster!
Yuri!
You see the power of Canarycobra?
And that's not even my strongest weapon!
Have a bite from my cobra
hand's venomous fangs!
You...
Are you a Gel Shocker cyborg?
I was hoping you'd show, Hongo Takeshi.
Witness the terrible
weapons of Canarycobra!
So you're a canary monster?
Run, everyone!
Get him!
Rider Transformation!
I'll see to it that you
never fight again, Rider!
I'll get you for this!
KAMEN RIDER
Are you all right, Mr. Hongo?
Does it hurt bad?
No, I'm fine.
He caught me off guard,
but I'll be better soon.
No, you'd better take care of yourself.
Take a nice, long rest.
Seeing you permanently disabled
would be worse in the long run.
Right.
Hey, don't you worry.
I'll finish off that monster my...
Oh, right.
If for just one more minute more...
No, thirty seconds.
If those headaches had kept up,
they would have driven us mad or killed us.
My head still doesn't feel right.
Our mistake was assuming it
was a cute little canary.
Who'd have thought it was actually
the Gel Shocker cyborg Canarycobra?
Yes.
But it's important not to
lose our love for our pets,
and affection for small animals.
Yeah.
But still...
If they send those awful
canaries all over in Tokyo...
Everyone will go mad or die.
The monster swore revenge on you, right?
That's right.
Gel Shocker is still obsessed
with world domination.
They'll surely mount a counterattack.
And they'll use any manner of dirty tricks.
I know.
Let's use TV and radio to tell
people about those weird canaries.
We've just received an urgent bulletin.
Attention, residents of Tokyo
and the surrounding prefectures.
If a canary arrives at your house,
please contact the police at once.
The canaries are dangerous.
Although their colors are
just like a standard canary,
they have a strange song that
almost sounds artificial.
It's the canary they were
talking about on the radio!
Shoo! Shoo!
My leader.
Operation: Pet is a roaring success.
Canarycobra is swiftly
racking up accomplishments.
Soon, everyone in Tokyo will be driven mad,
throwing the city into a panic.
Tokyo will soon be a Gel Shocker outpost.
And the next time they meet,
Canarycobra will destroy Rider.
Hey, a canary!
Mama, I see a canary!
Come grab it!
That's the canary they were
talking about on TV...
Mama, what's wrong?
Mama! Why won't you catch it for me?
Hello?
Is this the police?
This is the Omura household
in Fujimachi 1-7-18.
One of the canaries they
mentioned on TV is...
Oh, it's Taro's pigeon.
The Gel Shocker monster
was seen at Taro's house.
You can't take it off yet!
- It's better already?
- What?
To deceive your enemies, you
must first deceive your allies.
Hongo Takeshi!
I'm too late?
Hongo. But your leg...
I got your guard down.
Canarycobra...
I won't let you have your way!
Taki, get them to safety.
Right!
Behold my power!
Think you can get away, Hongo?
Once I defeat you, all of Tokyo
will belong to Gel Shocker!
Time to die, Hongo Takeshi!
Rider Transformation!
Rider, face me!
You want another broken arm?
What?
You can't break it now...
I've enhanced it with steel!
Die!
It's so powerful...
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Who are you?
Kamen Rider...
Their black shadows
threaten us all
I'm Nezcondor, and I'm
here to send you to hell!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Let's go!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Canarycobra.
Rider Jump!
Let's work together to kill him!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Wait!
I can finish Rider off myself!
Leave this to me!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
This time, it's your arm that will break!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Do it, Canarycobra!
With my scarf of red...
I'll be right here, watching Rider die!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
You okay, Rider?
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
I'll handle the other one!
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
Rider Lunar Kick!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
I did it!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Taki!
Rider, Rider!
Look out!
The Kamen Rider defeated
the terrifying Canarycobra,
but a new monster, Nezcondor,
has appeared in his place.
He's used his terrifying power to
send Taki Kazuya flying to his doom!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
A small fancy rat was fused with a condor
to be reborn as Nezcondor.
Use your plague germs and razor-like
wings to destroy the Kamen Rider!
Gentlemen...
Let us meet again for phase
two of Operation: Pet, "Rider S.O.S!"
The Terrifying Operation: Pet
Rider S.O.S!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!