KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The 8 Kamen Riders
Rider Kick!
The terrifying Gel Shocker
has created the Shocker Rider,
identical in appearance
to the Kamen Rider.
The Shocker Rider's goal is to frame
the ally of justice, Kamen
Rider, for his own evil deeds,
and to destroy the Anti-Shocker Alliance,
which possesses a tape containing
the secret of Shocker's leader.
In addition, the Kamen Rider
has been plunged into terrible peril
at the hands of the Shocker
Rider and Flytrap Bee.
Die, Kamen Rider!
Now I will truly take your place!
Wait...
Let me be the one to finish him!
He's dead!
The Kamen Rider is gone,
along with Flytrap Bee!
Now, I am the Kamen Rider!
I have no further need for this...
Shocker Rider!
Don't throw it away just yet.
Why not, Raydokuga?
Change of orders.
You'll be taking a fake Gel Shocker
tape to the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
What will you do with this?
Apparently, it's to be run
through Gel Shocker's computers.
And what's in that case?
A tape recording of killer sound waves.
Killer sound waves?
The Anti-Shocker Alliance will
foolishly put this in their computer,
and then, they'll all die!
Rider!
Rider! I'll help!
Let's give them an act. Ready?
Taki! Take this!
All right. This is all we need!
Pops. Taki.
I finished off the fake Rider
and the monster.
What? Fake Rider?
Damn Gel Shocker...
They even created a fake Rider?
Look out!
Rider!
Take that to the Anti-Shocker
Alliance at once!
Right! Leave it to us!
Enough!
That's enough.
That was a close call, Shocker Rider...
They almost found you out.
Indeed.
But that should keep them
in the dark a while longer.
That fake tape will soon put an end
to all members of that
impudent organization,
the Anti-Shocker Alliance!
And I will complete a litany
of evils in Kamen Rider's name!
My leader.
This is the Anti-Shocker Alliance's tape.
Put it into the computer, General Black.
Sir.
Knowing how much
they've learned about me
will give us an idea of the scale
of the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
It should be an interesting test.
Let's put it into the computer at once.
Here.
We gave the tape to a certain someone
in order to outwit Gel Shocker.
On January 6th, at noon,
that person will arrive in
Anti-Shocker's computer room.
My leader.
It's only one hour until then.
General Black.
Call off the plan to destroy
the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
We must steal the real
tape from them first.
Preparations are complete.
This will give us the identity
of Gel Shocker's leader, right?
That's right.
To think that we'll soon achieve
what we've dreamed of for so long...
I almost feel frightened.
I'm turning it on now.
Right.
Don't do it, Taki!
Kamen Rider?
What is it?
This tape is a fake.
What did you say?
Turning it on would make it explode.
That's impossible!
If you don't believe me, I'll test it.
Everyone, go outside.
We should probably leave this
in Rider's hands.
Go on, everyone.
Ready? Cover your ears and get down!
Rider!
I'm fine.
That's great!
If you'd turned it on,
you would have all been killed.
Rider, where in the world
is the real computer tape?
The real one is here.
Who are you?
South America's Anti-Shocker
Alliance chose me.
Ichimonji!
Hayato!
I wanted to spend New Year's
at home, at least.
Don't scare us like that!
Mr. Kogure, this is for you.
Thank you.
I'll hold on to this.
Rider... when did your scarf change?
Now that you mention it...
Are you...
Wait!
Too bad it's too late now.
Ichimonji, congratulations
on completing your long errand.
But this case belongs
to the Shocker Rider!
I won't let some Shocker Rider have it!
Hayato! Go after the Shocker Rider!
Got it!
Right!
Transform!
You can't escape me, Shocker Rider!
A fake is a fake from start to finish!
What was that?!
If you kill me,
your allies will die as well!
What was that?
The second Shocker Rider has already
infiltrated the Rider Kid Corps headquarters!
There's a second Shocker Rider, too?
Stop!
Rider... are you all right?
Headquarters is in danger! Hurry!
- Taki!
- The Rider Corps headquarters?
KAMEN RIDER
This is my New Year's gift to you all.
Isn't that great?
A New Year's gift from Rider!
What's inside?
Hey, tell us!
Open it and see.
Getting a New Year's gift
from Kamen Rider is the best!
I can't wait to see what's inside!
Let me open it!
Rider... what is all this?
A monster!
Gel Shocker monster Raydokuga!
This isn't a New Year's gift at all!
Beat him, Kamen Rider!
You don't like my gift, do you?
I suppose not... since it's
a gift from the Shocker Rider!
Shocker Rider?
A fake?
A fake Rider!
You've realized it too late.
None of you will escape alive!
Let's make a break for it!
Breathing in my poison powder will
put you to sleep for three days!
They'll be hostages. Take them away!
Hongo!
I knew you'd survived.
Gel Shocker's computer predicted
a 90% chance that you were alive!
That's why we needed hostages!
But your plan to get hostages has failed.
Hongo... you can sleep, too!
Rider Transformation!
Wait!
Hurry up!
Not so fast!
Naoki! Mitsuru!
What's wrong, Kamen Rider?
You're not your usual lively self...
Of course... were you injured
when you fell with Flytrap Bee?
Nonsense.
The Kamen Rider is invincible!
Kamen Rider... you can't beat us!
The Kamen Rider is nothing to fear!
Naoki!
Yumi! Mitsuru!
Hongo!
Ichimonji...
- Hongo!
- Takeshi!
I'm sorry.
They took the others hostage,
right under my nose...
Hongo! Stay with us, Hongo!
It might be from a member of the team.
Headquarters here.
Would this be Captain Taki?
That voice... General Black!
I have five hostages from your team.
Hey! Return the women and children!
This is a coward's move!
I'll happily return the hostages
if you give us what we want.
Fine. What do you want?
I'll trade them for the computer tape
in the Anti-Shocker Alliance's possession.
The location is...
Mr. Tachibana, I understand how you feel.
But...
But...?
We can't let them have this.
This tape represents the rage
that thousands feel for Shocker.
But... the lives of our allies in the fight
against Gel Shocker are also on the line.
I beg of you... please.
I'm sorry, but our members voted,
and this was the decision.
You're the ones who
asked us for help in the...
Pops.
It's no use.
We'll retrieve the hostages ourselves.
Anti-Shocker Alliance, my eye!
I can't believe how
self-centered they are...
What's this?
Please avenge my mother
who was killed by Shocker.
Won't this make trouble for you later?
Hurry, now.
Thank you.
Hayato.
Let's get going to the meeting place.
It's Hongo!
Hongo, you're in no condition for this yet.
Don't be a fool.
They have two Shocker
Riders on their side.
You think I can just
sit back, doing nothing?
But we still can't let you come...
You really think you can stop Hongo?
Let's go.
This is the place they said to meet.
I wonder where they're hiding...
Welcome!
Did you bring the tape?
We brought the tape, as promised!
Where are the hostages?
Bring them here at once!
We need to make sure
the tape is real first.
Show us the hostages first!
Very well.
As you will see, they're safe and sound!
- Mr. Takeshi!
Now, we'll confirm the tape's authenticity.
Captain Taki. Walk forward, alone.
Give us the case!
It's all complete!
Shocker Riders...
destroy the three of them!
Shocker Riders?
You tricked us!
Taki!
Shocker Rider No. 1!
Shocker Rider No. 2!
Shocker Rider No. 3!
Shocker Rider No. 4!
Shocker Rider No. 5!
Shocker Rider No. 6!
Let's show them what true strength is!
Right...
Rider Transformation!
Transform!
The Shocker Riders have
shown their full hand
before the first and
second Kamen Riders.
There are six of them all!
Can the double Riders
beat the Shocker Riders?
Fight, Kamen Riders!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The battle to retrieve
the mystery tape continues.
Taki remains clinging
to the ascending helicopter.
The six Shocker Riders use stunning
cooperative tactics to attack our Riders.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "The True Identity of
Gel Shocker's Leader!!"
The True Identity of
Gel Shocker's Leader!!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!