KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Creepy Bee Woman!
Sachiko! Dinnertime!
Okay!
Well, that's no good...
Are you all right?
What will you do, Papa?
Well...
I'll just have to buy new ones.
I'm really sorry...
Hey, it's okay.
Kagemura Glasses
Try these.
How do you like them?
I believe they'll
meet your standards.
What do you think, Sachiko?
Do they suit me?
Yeah! They look great!
We've only just opened, but we're
already getting wonderful reviews.
Eat it! It's good!
Throw some that way, too.
Shocker requires your aid!
Now, come to Shocker!
Papa? What's wrong, Papa?
Papa!
Papa! Papa!
Are you sick?
Papa!
Hey, mister!
I need help!
Papa's acting weird!
Over there! Please get him!
Hurry! Hurry!
What's the matter, sir?
What was that all about?
Is something the matter?
What's wrong with you?
Don't be mean to my papa!
The glasses...
The glasses are calling me!
Papa!
Are you all right?
What was wrong with that man?
Hey...
was that really your papa?
Where's your mama?
She died... last year.
I see...
Isn't it a pretty doll?
You pull the string
and it talks.
I can't believe it's
been three days,
and still no sign
of Sachiko's father.
Could it be one of
those disappearances?
Forty-two people have gone
missing over the past two months.
I wonder what could
be causing it...
Well? Did you learn something?
Yes.
Everyone who disappeared
had just bought new glasses.
What does that mean?
And they all bought those glasses
from a boutique called Kagemura.
I'll go.
I'll investigate the boutique.
But Shocker could be involved.
We can't let you visit
such a dangerous place.
But the people didn't go missing
inside the shop, did they?
That's true enough, but...
I'll be fine, then.
I've been wanting to buy
some sunglasses anyway.
Please, Takeshi. Let me do this.
I wish I could go with you,
but there's an
experiment I need to run.
The lowest tone mammals
can hear is 16 to 20 hertz.
The highest is
around 25,000 hertz.
But dogs can hear
sounds at 35,000 hertz.
But that day,
with my modified hearing,
I heard the sound of a
vibration inaudible to others.
What was that sound?
Where was it coming from?
The glasses...
The glasses are calling me!
Was the sound coming
from the glasses, then?
I just got back from
the glasses shop.
The clerk was a little creepy,
but nothing else seemed odd.
Yeah.
I bought some really cool ones.
I'm going to run a few more
experiments, then come by.
Don't put those sunglasses
on, no matter what.
Is that understood?
Hello?
What's going on?
Shocker is calling you!
Now, come!
Come to us at once!
Takeshi... save me!
Hello?
- The glasses won't come off!
- Hello? Hello?
Hello? What's wrong?
Hello?
What's wrong, Ruriko? Hello?
Midorikawa Ruriko
Damn...
The glasses must contain
a special sensory device
that can receive signals and
images on a certain frequency.
They use that to control
people and make them disappear.
Only Shocker would do something
so evil on such a broad scale...
Kagemura Glasses
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Now, face me!
These nine are on
disposal duty this week!
Out of all the people who have
gone missing to join Shocker,
you all have proved
exceptionally weak.
Your inability to endure further
labor at our gas production facility
has made you disposable.
No! Please! Stop!
Be quiet!
The best of you are altered and turned
into Shocker combatants, like these.
Enough!
Execute them all as part
of the gas testing process!
Open the gas valves.
Ma'am!
It's too cruel...
Hey, look at this.
So you're part of this, too.
I've been waiting for you
to track us back here.
But you can't interfere
now, can you?
Why are you doing
something so cruel?
We need poison gas to
take over the world!
I see...
So you're a factory foreman?
Go, take her.
Hongo Takeshi.
Receive an injection from
this poisoned needle.
If you do,
we'll spare the woman's life.
But we're not just
going to kill you.
We're going to paralyze you,
then give you a complete cyborg surgery!
All right... inject me.
Just release her, please!
KAMEN RIDER
Now, show me the way.
Open the door.
Damn...
Now everyone, run away! Hurry!
Get out, everyone!
Why won't you move? Run away!
You need to get out! Hurry!
The stairway at the end
of the hall to your right.
Get away, hurry!
Are Ruriko or
Sachiko's father here?
Hurry, hurry!
Run away!
Hurry!
I'm glad you're all right.
Now, hurry!
How dare you...
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Help me!
Takeshi is still in there!
He'll be fine.
He's not in there any longer.
Now, let's go.
Hurry!
I don't want Ruriko to know
about my cyborg modifications.
Not until I can
return to normal...
Here, Sachiko!
Your papa's back.
Papa!
Papa, where have you been?
Tell me!
Oh no...
His memory has been erased.
Is there any way to cure it?
Well... he should return
to normal soon enough.
But he probably won't remember
the gas factory when he does.
It's an awful thing
to do to someone...
Papa, are you still mad
I broke your glasses?
You are responsible
for this failure!
Please... speak to
Shocker's boss on my behalf!
Please... please!
Shocker has no room for failure.
Bee Woman will avenge you.
So quiet down and
take your punishment.
If you fail, too...
Die!
The great fool.
I let the girl escape
because I had a plan for her!
I doubt Shocker will
just let this go.
Yes.
There's no knowing
what they'll try next.
Here, I made it as
delicious as I could.
Oh, thank you!
Hey...
Ruriko...
What's wrong with you, Takeshi?
What have you done, Ruriko?
This is what did it?
That thing?
They were controlling her with
those special sound waves again.
I happened to hear the
sound, and it tipped me off.
So they stuck this on Ruriko
and returned her to us?
What a cruel thing to do...
I think I can trace this sound back to Bee
Woman without having to follow her orders.
Please, look after Ruriko.
Okay.
Bee Woman!
People like you, who steal freedom
and disrupt peace, must pay!
What absolute tripe!
Try me!
Rider Kick!
I can't thank you enough...
Oh, it's nothing.
Papa!
Sachiko!
Come right here!
Papa's feeling much better!
Papa!
In some of the cars on this highway...
In fact, in places all over the city...
Shocker's minions lurk, plotting to
alter people to serve their own goals.
And every one of
them must be stopped!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Cobra Man!
Cobra Man's gang attacks the Ministry
of Finance's gold repository,
and Kamen Rider pursues him
to his base in the deep grass.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Cobra Man!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!