KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Shirakawa Optics
Research Institute
What a horrifying
thing we've created.
But its announcement will
be your ticket to fame.
No... we can't do it.
I don't plan to announce this.
Why not?
It's an amazing opportunity.
Shibata.
What if it were to fall
into the wrong hands?
Humans invariably find a way to misuse
any valuable scientific achievement.
Then you're going to abandon
your invention entirely?
A scientist cannot
bury his own invention.
It would be like
killing his own child.
It's too painful.
Why don't we print all the formulas
and blueprints on microfilm
and seal it away somewhere?
Yes...
Let's do it.
That's our only
choice, isn't it?
Then...
Where shall we hide it?
I'd better not tell you that.
Please don't tell anyone
about this laser.
I won't. I promise.
But his assistant, Shibata,
didn't come to work the next day.
He was secretly a member of Shocker's
worldwide information network.
I will convert you into a
glorious Shocker commander
and grant you a special mission.
Now, rise.
You are now my loyal
warrior, Yamogerus.
The Murderous Yamogerus
Now, go! Test your power!
Climb.
Jab!
Good, good!
Jab, jab!
Right! Left! Good!
Another jab! Left!
Jab, jab!
Right!
Jab, right! Left!
Good! Jab!
Jab, jab!
Right! Left!
The test was a success.
Come on, let's race!
Okay, you got it!
Hey, Takeshi!
I won!
Look at that reckless driving...
They're chasing that car!
What do you people want?
Come with us,
to a Shocker outpost.
Come on! Hurry!
Shirakawa
You really don't know
why they'd be after you?
No, I don't.
You don't know why your assistant
before me quit abruptly?
I couldn't tell you.
Why should I care about
someone who's gone?
But those people...
Shocker, was it?
They said something strange...
If you're just going to quibble with
me, you can quit, too!
What's wrong, Machiko?
A m-monster!
Don't be ridiculous.
It might be those
people from before.
Mr. Shirakawa...
Is there anything in your
research that they might be after?
Don't be absurd.
It's not possible.
If there is,
we need to take action immediately.
Yes? Shirakawa here...
Ruriko,
it's from someone named Hongo.
Hello?
Takeshi!
Where have you been?
How'd you know I was here?
Forget that and listen.
You should probably
stay out of this.
Leave everything to me.
I think I'm doing pretty
well, actually.
Here, Machiko. Happy birthday.
I'll never take it
off, even in the bath.
This jewel will protect
you, Machiko.
And I'll protect
you, Big Brother.
Don't start with me, you!
Wait!
Damn...
KAMEN RIDER
Hey, Ruri.
What's got you
looking so serious?
Don't disturb a great
detective while she's thinking!
That reminds me.
Mr. Hongo had the same
scowl on his face before.
He just drank his
coffee and left.
You're searching for
something in a hurry, right?
He must have invented
something Shocker wants.
Ruriko.
It's terrible.
Machiko...
What?
She's been kidnapped.
I put... in her locket...
Calm down.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I invented a laser of
such terrifying power...
What's going on here?
It's happening...
exactly what I was worried about!
What a nasty business...
Human bodies reduced
to just their bones...
Shocker altered the laser you
made into a weapon, didn't they?
I never should have put the
microfilm into that locket.
Machiko is dead, isn't she?
I'm sure she's not...
Think about Shocker's usual MO.
They're not going to be satisfied
with two or three deaths.
Listen to me.
For our next stage, we're going
to expand the scope of the plan.
Destroy a plane with that laser.
Make the world's skies the
sole domain of Shocker!
We'll need the aid of Shirakawa
to create a device that powerful.
Bring Shirakawa to me!
It's no use.
Machiko must be...
Don't give up hope yet.
As Shocker ramps up
their evil plans,
I'm sure they'll
decide they need you.
But... my sister is the most
important thing in my life!
That's what I'm saying.
Shocker knows that, and...
What did you say?
Kill Machiko?
That's right.
We'll use that laser to
burn her down to her bones.
If you don't want to see
your sister's skeleton,
come to the place I'm
about to tell you.
And don't tell Hongo.
Mr. Shirakawa!
Mr. Shirakawa?
Shocker called him out!
Strange...
There should be a
building around here.
Once it's finished,
you'll give Machiko back, won't you?
Finish it, and then we'll talk.
It's that way.
Thank you.
I see...
When I was doing the pencil
scratchings, I got it one street off.
She's tracked us down, eh?
Excellent.
Ruriko!
Go! Hurry!
Bye-bye!
Wait!
It's complete.
Give it here!
But it's...
Now give Machiko back to me!
Shut up.
Perfect timing.
We'll make the Kamen
Rider our guinea pig.
Learn your lesson yet?
Now the Danger Light will
make quick work of you!
Big Brother...
Big Brother!
That's the Danger Light...
If scientists don't consider the
harm their inventions might do,
they can lead
humankind to tragedy.
Let's forget this invention.
Machiko.
That's a wonderful
brother you have.
Even in times of peace, Takeshi could
not afford to forget Shocker's presence.
As long as Shocker was out there, creating
cyborgs and plotting world domination,
The Kamen Rider Hongo
Takeshi's battle would continue.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
Lizardlon and
The Monster Army!
is Lizardlon and
the monster army.
Shocker revives the ten monsters
Rider defeated in the past,
and sends them after Rider
led by the powerful Lizardlon.
How will Rider fight them?
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Lizardlon and
the Monster Army!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!