KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Washikamigiri's
Human Hunt
Pops, we're going on ahead!
That's not fair!
We're heading for the summit of Mount Omuro!
See you!
Hey!
Darn it.
Those annoying kids roped me into this,
and now then they want
to run off by themselves!
What was that?
Hey, we should get some lunch, too.
I'm taking one more.
Let's check out the telescope.
Takeshi, let me see!
Sure.
Let me at it!
How can you eat so much, Choco?
But fall is about food!
You want mine, too?
Papa!
What's that mountain called?
That?
That's Mount Togasa.
Huh? What was that?
Papa! I need a ten-yen coin!
You've seen enough.
It's about time for the
hotel shuttle to arrive.
Let's go.
That's weird...
Maybe my eyes were playing tricks on me?
Keita, watch where you're going!
You all right?
Yeah.
Hey, did you guys see
something weird over there?
I didn't see anything.
Keita, you need to watch
where you're going.
Now, let's go.
Goodbye.
Bye!
I was sure I saw it, though.
It looked like a yellow board,
but then it took a human shape.
That sounds right.
Papa.
How long to the Tokyu Hotel?
How long...
Huh?
Where's that smoke coming from?
It's a mountain fire!
K-Keita, hurry!
Papa! I'm scared!
It'll be all right. This way!
Come on!
Get under the bus!
I am Gel Shocker cyborg Washikamigiri!
All humans are my prey!
Capture every one of them!
Operation: Human Hunt was a success.
I'll use this method to acquire
a large number of humans.
Washikamigiri.
You must not let anyone who
witnesses your plan go free.
I have traps everywhere.
They will not escape.
Good.
What a nice place.
Hey, hurry! Hurry!
Isn't this pretty?
Yeah.
I know! I want to see the begonias!
- Yeah!
- Shall we?
H-Hey, wait for us!
They're hopeless!
We don't get time off very often.
Let's take it slow.
Hey, that's no way for the
Rider Corps Captain to talk.
Ah, well.
Let's take a nice, relaxing bath.
Yeah, let's do it!
We should be safe now, I think.
Those scary people we saw...
They look just like the one
I saw through the telescope!
I see...
Help me!
- Someone's there!
- Please!
Someone help me!
Are you sure?
It's all right.
I'm right here.
Please...
I'm... I'm caught in this trap.
This is awful!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Try to bear it...
What wonderful water!
It's been a while since
we relaxed like this.
Pops.
Are you planning to wear
your clothes in the bath?
I just asked at the front
desk. They're in a panic.
A hotel shuttle that left Mount Omuro
two hours ago hasn't arrived yet.
Where are you going?
We're moving out.
Where are the girls?
They went to see the
begonias in the greenhouse.
Contact them at once.
Right!
I want one of those!
No way! I hear they're 50,000 yen apiece!
- I wonder if this one's edible!
- 50,000 yen?
Oh, you!
Emergency! Emergency!
We're moving out!
Moving out?
Learned anything?
Afraid not.
If only the people are missing, then...
Well? What's it looking like?
What in the world happened here?
The microbus' engine is just fine.
If it wasn't a breakdown...
Gel Shocker, then?
Sounds like it...
Pops, I say we split up and search.
- I'll check this way.
- Yeah.
Me, too.
That means we'll go this way.
Papa, let's go to that lodge.
Right.
Hello? Is anyone there?
Hello?
Let's just go in for now.
Papa, there's no one here.
- Thank you for this.
- It's nothing.
You should lie down.
Right.
It won't open!
What did you say?
M-Monster!
There's a monster heading this way!
What did you say?
I'm scared!
I-It's all right.
I'll figure out something!
It's no use.
Keita.
Keita!
Listen. Stay right there.
I'll take this.
Carry them out!
Papa!
Hey, son.
What's wrong?
My papa was taken by a monster!
A monster?
Hey, kid... could you tell me more?
Gel Shocker really is behind this, then...
Darn it...
The Kamen Rider Kid Corps
can't let this stand!
That's right!
Here, have some.
Eat it.
Cheer up, son.
I promise I'll save your father.
Where are Taki and Yuri?
They haven't called back yet.
Should I contact them?
No, don't.
We don't want the enemy to
pick up our transmission.
If we preserve the humans in this form,
we'll have them at our disposal
whenever we need them.
Excellent.
Divide them into those to be made into
monsters and those to be made into combatants.
After we modify them, victory will be ours.
Washikamigiri.
Do not forget your other mission.
Sir.
I swear, I will remove the Kamen
Rider's head with my scythe!
Good. I look forward to it.
KAMEN RIDER
Mr. Taki! Mr. Taki!
Hey!
Hey! Over here!
What's the matter?
I'm caught in a trap! I can't move!
A trap?
I'm on my way!
Mr. Taki!
- Of course.
- Help me out, here!
Ready? One, two...
It's no use.
- Right!
- Use the transmitter.
Yuri here.
Mr. Taki's caught in a trap.
Come quickly!
I'm Gel Shocker's Washikamigiri.
Would you be Taki, then?
I caught a bigger prey than I expected...
What now? You're trapped!
I'll foam you into a cocoon. Rest well!
- Hold it!
- Taki, this one will finish you!
I'm your opponent, Washikamigiri!
I've been waiting, Kamen Rider!
Perfect timing!
I'll finish you all off at once!
Taki! Are you all right?
Get him!
Have a taste of my feather missiles!
How do you like that?
It's hot... I feel hot all over.
Suffer!
I combine the powers of
an eagle and a mantis!
Die, Rider!
I've done it!
I've finally finished Rider!
Don't celebrate just yet.
We can't be sure until
we find Rider's body.
Combatants, find him!
Washikamigiri.
Free the humans preserved in your foam,
and modify them into combatants!
Sir!
Perform the modification surgery at once!
Washikamigiri's blood...
Where could he have gone?
One of his feathers...
Apply the restoration fluid!
Unforgivable.
Modifying people to suit their purposes...
Just like they did to me, long ago...
Fortunately, I escaped before
they modified my brain...
All right.
I need to stop that
surgery, no matter what.
Heart rate has dropped by thirty.
Prepare to staunch the bleeding.
Head incision complete.
Are you ready to remove the heart?
Hold it!
Damn... Rider, you survived?!
Washikamigiri, it seems you failed.
General Black.
This time, I will defeat Rider for sure!
Watch me!
Do not return here until Rider is dead!
All right... let's step outside!
With pleasure!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
Washikamigiri! Tear Rider's
head from his shoulders!
You...
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Kick!
Rider Jump!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Defeat Rider!
Rider, Rider!
Rider!
Hey!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Goodbye!
- Oh, it's nothing, really.
- I can't thank you enough.
Mr. Hongo! Say hi to the
Kamen Rider for me, okay?
I certainly will.
Ready to go, Taki?
Yeah.
Well, goodbye!
Goodbye!
Washikamigiri's terrible plan was foiled.
But Gel Shocker would return
with more mysterious schemes.
Ride on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
A deliveryman of doom
appears from the darkness.
That's when I, the great
Spiderlion, show my power!
The deliveryman of doom
is whispering again...
"Kill Kamen Rider soon!" it says!
Gel Shocker's Deliveryman of Death!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!