KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The True Identity of
Gel Shocker's Leader!!
A deadly battle between Kamen Riders
and Shocker Riders has broken out
over the secret behind
Gel Shocker's leader.
Six Shocker Riders surrounded
the first and second Kamen Riders.
And the computer tape filled
with secret information
was on the verge of being stolen!
Rider's in trouble!
Rider!
Hang in there, Ichimonji!
You too, Hongo!
All right... we'll hit them all at once!
Withdraw!
Chairman!
Look! The Riders have lost!
Still alive, are they? Go!
You keep watch!
Chairman!
Stay quiet, guys!
Mr. Tachibana!
Mr. Kogure!
The Anti-Shocker Alliance is with you.
The Kamen Riders are struggling...
I'll support them with a gas shot!
Where did the Riders go?
Don't let them escape!
Now! Let's go!
Right!
Rider Double Jump!
Oh no! The Riders are after the helicopter!
All right... we got a hostage.
Let's get back!
We almost had them!
General Black.
The Kamen Riders have escaped,
you lost your hostages,
and the computer tape is back
with the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
What do you intend to do about this?
Worry not, sir.
I have another plan in mind.
We're sure of it this time.
This is the correct computer tape.
Certainly.
By the way, when will you have it ready?
The computer that Gel Shocker damaged
will be repaired tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning, eh? I can't wait.
I know. Why don't you come to watch?
We'd love to!
- Right?
- Yes.
Well... as long as they don't make
another try for it, at least...
If I seal it in here,
not even Gel Shocker will find it.
Where's Raydokuga?
He hasn't moved since we brought him.
He has the power to put others to sleep.
I guess he can self-hypnotize, too.
Yes...
It's all riding on tonight.
Taki, keep a close watch.
What will you do?
Since I happen to have both
Hongo and Hayato both here,
we'll have a long overdue training session.
Those six Shocker Riders
are powerful, after all.
Go for it. I'll handle things here.
All right.
These training grounds
are where you've put your lives
on the line to acquire new abilities.
This time, we're facing
the six Shocker Riders,
who have the same abilities we do.
We need to defeat them.
Pops. Please, train us!
Please!
The individual abilities of the
Shocker Riders are equal to yours.
And they also have special
abilities unique to monsters.
They won't be easy to beat.
But to fight against Gel Shocker...
is the path we've been given.
Good.
Then we'll have some
special training today.
I want you to run in a circle around me!
Go on!
Right!
Speed up more!
Faster!
More speed!
This is Rider Wheel Training!
Speed up!
Now, jump!
That's not enough!
You need more speed!
Run again!
Go faster!
Faster! More speed!
Well? Haven't you gotten a
transmission from Raydokuga yet?
There's nothing on the radar screen.
He should start putting out
radio waves any time now.
You must be excited.
When he wakes up, we get to extract
the location of Gel Shocker's base from him.
Want to see?
He's still asleep, as you can see.
I just saw him move!
What did you say?
Hey!
He's still fast asleep...
Maybe I imagined it...
General Black, the radar's picking up
Raydokuga's transmission.
Right... find him!
Slug Mushroom! Prepare to deploy!
I'll destroy the Kamen Rider at last!
You were killed by Shocker.
Now, at last, my long
journey will come to an end.
Once we know their leader's identity...
That's right. Your long
journey is at an end!
Who's there?
Give me the computer tape.
I might even spare your life!
I won't! You'll have to kill me first!
Fool.
I have other ways to take it from you.
If you want to die... I'll oblige you!
Mr. Kogure! What's the matter?
Open the door!
Mr. Kogure! Speak to me!
Mr. Taki...
A new monster...
attacked me out of nowhere...
The tape?
Is the tape still in the safe?
It's there.
Damn, Gel Shocker has a
new monster already?
What's going on? An earthquake?
Anti-Shocker Alliance...
your guards cannot stop me!
That voice sounds like Raydokuga!
He's awake!
Right!
He escaped!
It's not possible!
What's this smoke?
Raydokuga!
None can oppose Gel Shocker and live!
What was that?
Damn!
Gel Shocker... transform!
KAMEN RIDER
Hey, speak to me!
Speak to me!
Mr. Taki, I'm sorry.
Raydokuga got away!
Where's Mr. Kogure? Is the tape safe?
Don't worry. They're both just fine.
Glad to hear it.
As long as the tape's safe,
we've still got the advantage.
Taki!
Sorry, Hongo.
Raydokuga got away.
If Raydokuga is out there,
we can't afford to sit around.
He'll probably be back with
those awful Shocker Riders.
Yeah. Let's move to the computer room.
Now we'll finally know the
identity of Gel Shocker's leader?
I'm turning it on.
"Gel Shocker's leader is in Japan.
Location: 70 degrees to the northeast.
Distance: 120 kilometers."
That's here!
Near Mount Tsukuba.
That's where their leader is?
Right. Let's get going now.
We'll finally avenge everyone we lost.
Look out!
Raydokuga!
You followed us?
That's right!
I won't let you reach our leader!
Pops, go on ahead!
Right!
Rider Transformation!
Transform!
Rider Drill Shoot!
You think they'll be enough to stop them?
Don't worry.
There's always a Kamen Rider on our side.
The Kamen Riders!
We're almost to our destination.
You think we'll find their
leader in a place like this?
There should be a base hidden
somewhere around here.
Let's investigate.
Where is the entrance to your base?
Talk!
Got it.
- Right.
- Let's go!
Here it is.
What's that?
It's their leader!
Let's find out who it is!
There's no one here!
You've finally arrived,
first and second Kamen Riders.
Finally arrived?
You mean this was all a trap?
Precisely.
A trap to wipe Kamen Rider
from the face of the Earth.
I leaked false data to the Anti-Shocker
Alliance's computer that I was here.
Damn...
The end of Kamen Rider is near.
Now, die at the hands
of the Shocker Riders!
Mr. Kogure is missing!
So is Chie!
Mr. Kogure!
Have you gone mad?
Kogure is dead.
I'll show you who I really am...
I am Slug Mushroom!
What did you say?
Slug Mushroom?
You see?
This girl is all that remains
of the Anti-Shocker Alliance!
Run!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Taki!
Rider Kick!
- Right!
- Let's go!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Riders... you can't escape now!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Kamen Rider is dead.
Not even he can stand
against six Shocker Riders!
Shocker is coming
And you'll all follow soon after!
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
Let's go! The Rider Wheel!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Right!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Let's go, Ichimonji!
Right!
Wait!
You survived?
The fakes are all dead.
An imposter can't beat the real thing!
Run!
Right! Now!
Rider Double Kick!
The two Kamen Riders had escaped the
terrible trap set by Gel Shocker's leader.
But when would they
finally learn his identity?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The monstrous Garaox
breathes out a deadly gas.
The gas causes anything it touches to
rise into the air like a hot air balloon.
A breathtaking fight unfurls between
Garaox and the Kamen Rider
in a vehicle 500 meters in the air.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider!
The Monstrous Garaox's
Flying Cars!!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!