KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Hiruguerrilla of the
Vampire Swamp
Hey! I got one!
That's so cool.
Wonder if I'll catch one, too...
Hey, what's this?
It's sucking my blood!
Is that a leech?
What? A leech?
Hey, there's one on your
face, too!
Help!
There's so many!
Now, my blood-sucking leeches...
It's my turn to
suck their blood.
Return! Return to me!
I'm going to have my fill of
their healthy young blood.
Hiruguerrilla's limbs function
like blood-sucking leeches,
allowing him to
drink human blood.
Take them away!
He's a terrifying blood-sucking creature
created by Shocker headquarters.
A truly devilish invention.
Take them!
"Three children
gone missing," eh?
Three days later,
and they still don't know anything.
If they were all
taken together...
It can't be a kidnapping.
They said they went digging
for crayfish, right?
You think they
fell into the pond?
The police dredged the pond,
but they couldn't
find any clues.
Right, Mr. Chairman?
Right.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Shocker, you think?
We can't be certain yet.
I'm going to go looking.
One of the missing boys is the son
of a photography mentor of mine.
Every time I think about him,
I just get so restless...
Of course you do.
And what about my old friend?
He's taken off every day since
then from his photography job...
He insists he's going
to find Hisashi himself,
so he spends every
day searching...
Hisashi, where have you gone?
Hisashi...
Go, Hiruguerrilla.
Go, and suck that man's blood!
Hisashi, I know where you are.
I know you're somewhere
near this pond.
There's some kind of terrible
secret in this place...
Hisashi.
That's what my gut tells me.
A leech?
Leeches, in a place like this?
Leeches!
Monster... are you the
one who took the children?
We'll replace the blood
that Hiruguerrilla drank
with this fluid.
This will turn him
into a mindless slave.
Now... to work, at once!
Doctor Shinigami.
Was the experiment a success?
Yes.
Any human whose blood is
replaced with the green drug,
adult or child,
will be reduced to the intelligence
of a primitive ape-man.
They will serve Shocker's will.
He hasn't been back
since last night?
Yes...
I just don't know what to do.
Have you told the police?
I have.
They investigated at once,
but they couldn't find him.
They did find this in the
grass near the pond, though.
Is that his?
A clue?
It's halfway through
the film roll.
Let's develop it.
Dark Room
I knew Shocker was behind this.
There's more to that
pond than meets the eye.
Let's go.
It's quiet.
Too quiet...
What's that hall?
Seems suspicious.
Let's investigate.
Wait.
I think there's
something lurking nearby.
What's wrong?
Ichimonji Hayato and Taki.
I'm going to force you
to fight separately!
Transform!
Taki! Taki!
Hang in there, Taki!
Taki!
Die, Rider!
Shocker monsters...
We'll settle this another time!
Damn...
KAMEN RIDER
Letting Kamen Rider track us here
was a foolish mistake, Doctor Shinigami.
I am aware.
I will move on to Plan B.
Thank goodness!
Doctor. Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Here's the man you should thank.
Mr. Chairman...
Yamazaki residence.
Oh, Emi!
Mr. Taki's all better!
We're heading over
to see you now.
Yeah!
We heard you were lonely
without your husband,
so the Chairman and Hayato...
But won't that be more trouble?
No, not at all!
Leeches!
Help!
I'm going to suck your blood!
All of your blood!
That's strange...
I wonder what happened.
A leech!
Leeches!
Help me!
I made this drug myself.
When one of our
slaves drinks this,
they will return to
their old selves.
Where am I?
You're that monster!
Damn you!
This is Hiruguerrilla,
a cyborg I went to
great lengths to create.
Damn you...
Calm yourself.
Look at this!
Hisashi! Eiko!
Eiko!
Sad to see, isn't it?
Well? Do you want to see
them restored to normal?
Spare them...
Please,
turn them back to normal!
I'll do anything you want!
Please!
Hello?
Is that you, Mr. Yamazaki?
What's going on?
Where are you?!
I'm underneath
the vampire swamp,
taken hostage in Shocker's base.
Yes...
They have Eiko and Hisashi
as well as Yuri and Emi.
Them, too?
Damn...
Hayato, there's a cave
on the edge of the swamp.
If you come in that
way, you won't be seen.
Please...
Understood.
I'll come save you at once.
Just hang in there until then!
Well done.
Now, take him to the basement.
Wait!
That wasn't the deal!
Be quiet!
Take him away.
Hiruguerrilla.
Hayato will be
coming here alone.
Drink his blood before he
can become the Kamen Rider.
Sorry, but I won't be
walking into your trap.
I knew there was something
to this place from the start!
Mr. Yamazaki!
Ichimonji!
Where are the others?
They've been turned into slaves.
Damn.
What an awful thing to do...
Ichimonji!
The medicine to restore them
is in the room down below.
All right. Stand back!
Now, hurry!
Run, quickly!
Hayato's here!
Get him!
This is the medicine.
Mr. Yamazaki...
leave this to me.
You get to safety!
But...
Move!
Not one more step, Ichimonji.
If I press this switch,
the bottom will come
out of the swamp,
and the water will fill
this place instantly.
The slaves will all drown!
Damn...
Kill him, Hiruguerrilla.
Mr. Yamazaki!
Ichimonji!
What now?
Hayato's in trouble.
Pops!
Now, I shall turn
you into our slave.
Hold it!
Run!
Get this medicine to Hayato!
Got it!
Taki! This way!
On your feet, slave!
At last,
Ichimonji Hayato is my slave.
Begone, insects!
Or do you want to end
up like Ichimonji?
Hayato!
Damn...
What have you done?!
Fight, my slave!
Go!
It will be excellent to watch
you take each other out!
Damn... I need to push the
lever to drain the swamp!
Taki!
Hayato!
Wait, you!
Pops! Go save the
people in the cells!
Right. Leave it to me!
Hold it!
Transform!
Face me, Hiruguerrilla!
It's time for my revenge!
You're talking nonsense.
Destroy him, now!
Rider Kick!
You won't escape
me, Hiruguerrilla!
The Kamen Rider can unleash his power
as a tremendous electrical charge.
Rider.
Where are the others?
The medicine restored
them all to normal.
I'm so glad.
We're saved!
It's Hayato!
Hayato!
Hip-hip hooray! Hip-hip hooray!
The terrible monster
Hiruguerrilla was defeated.
But where would Doctor
Death head next?
And what is the next monster that
Ichimonji Hayato would have to face?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Isoginchack!
He attacks Kamen Rider with 100
meter-per-second wind speeds.
The tornadoes generated
from Isoginchack's mouth
engulf one person after another.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
The Man-Eating
Monster Isoginchack
in "The Man-Eating
Monster Isoginchack!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!