KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Shinigami Chameleon
Sunada Gallery
Is someone out there?
I... I don't believe it!
Who would play such
a disgusting prank?
Lieutenant Commander Tatsuo Sunada
of the former Imperial Japanese Navy.
Who's there? Where are you?
Former submarine captain Sunada.
I wish to know the location of the Nazi
secret you buried twenty-six years ago.
I don't know what you mean.
I am Death itself.
If you value your life,
you'd better talk.
That won't work...
Where are you?
Show yourself!
Now, talk!
Where did you hide
the Nazi secret?
I don't know...
what you're talking about!
Silence!
Shocker's already
run an investigation.
They know you're the last man
alive who knows of the Nazi secret.
You'd better not play
dumb, unless you want harm
to befall your precious
daughter in the hospital!
Threaten me all you want...
What was that?
This monster can hide anywhere by changing
its colors to match what's behind it.
Looks like someone had
a good time tonight.
That's not safe...
What if he gets hit by a car?
Shiro.
Why don't you get him home instead?
We'll be fine.
Surely you jest!
Look out!
What are you doing, silly?
What's wrong?
What's got two empowered women
like you looking so frightened?
G-G-Ghost!
What's the matter
with you people?
You look like you've
seen a ghost...
We have!
What?
One man... with two shadows!
Not possible.
I hear it...
The sound of someone
being dragged along.
Hongo Takeshi had been altered.
The process gave him hearing many times
more powerful than an ordinary human's.
Papa...
just wait a little longer.
I'll have a great
present for you soon!
I know my fragile constitution
puts you through a lot of trouble,
so this is my way to thank you!
Papa!
Papa... what's wrong?
Papa...
I'm scared!
Awaken, Sunada.
What am I...
Yumi!
Now, how long will you keep
up that bravado of yours?
- Yumi!
Torture the girl until he talks!
Papa!
Yumi's...
Yumi's just had surgery.
You'll kill her like that!
Well, which do you value more?
Your daughter's life,
or the Nazi secret?
Inside the model, then?
You...
Shocker.
I've been outside
listening this whole time.
I don't know what you're planning,
but I won't let you have this!
Papa...
Hey, now.
Don't worry.
I'll get your father
back from those bad men.
You will?
Yes, I will.
But in the meantime,
you have to work on getting better.
You're a nice guy, mister.
You can borrow that
model if you want.
It's very important to
Papa, though...
So it was Shocker?
Yeah.
But why would they
be after this?
A map!
These are the upper
banks of the Tama River.
Dam construction.
The X on this map...
Hey! Fire in the hole!
What's a cave doing here?
Hey, look at this!
It looks pretty deep...
You think there's a
treasure in there?
No way...
We should probably look into
it, though.
Yeah!
A ghost!
What's all this about?
A g-ghost...
He's found it, I see.
This will save me time.
That Shocker agent before
mentioned a Nazi secret.
This box has the Nazi
symbol, the Hakenkreuz.
If Shocker is after it...
what secret could it hold?
What is the connection between the
Third Reich, Nazi Germany, and Shocker?
There they are!
All right...
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Tell me...
What meaning does the swastika,
the Hakenkreuz, hold to Shocker?
What secret does
that steel box hold?
Tell me!
He's dead...
But if I can open
that steel box,
it will surely give me some
new insight into Shocker.
That Kamen Rider...
I'll kill him with my own hands.
He must have a weak
point somewhere.
KAMEN RIDER
Loyal scientists of Shocker.
The appearance of the
Kamen Rider has caused
our world domination
plans to fail repeatedly.
I want you to thoroughly research
all of this Kamen Rider's abilities
and discover his weak point.
Rider's power comes from the
windmill dynamo in his belt.
And the skin on his chest
is completely bulletproof.
The slits are his radiators.
He can jump 15 meters.
His arms and legs possess
incredible destructive power.
Shocker's scientists
poured all their efforts
into discovering the
Kamen Rider's weak point.
The Kamen Rider
can be weakened by stopping the
spin of his windmill dynamo,
then trapping him in a
locked room one meter square.
A locked room?
And that will
render him helpless?
Good.
Prepare the trap at once,
for whenever the
Rider next appears.
There you are!
Hey, you're late!
We were worried!
Did something happen?
Yes...
I was attacked in the dump.
So Shocker did
make an appearance?
Shocker?
It appears that this box
is very important to them.
Mr. Tachibana.
Give me a tune-up, okay?
Of course!
Hey, Hongo! Where are you going?
I'm going to open this.
Wait, Takeshi!
Well, Abe?
Quite a curious box, isn't it?
It's made from a special alloy.
But I'm not sure if I can open
it, Hongo.
This box doesn't have a lid.
No lid?
I want to find out what's
inside, but...
Could I look after
it for a while?
I might figure something out.
That sounds great!
But...
But what?
Don't push yourself too
hard, all right?
Right.
Hey!
Jonan University Biochemistry Laboratory
After you.
Shinohara Hospital, please.
Yumi's going to be so thrilled.
Keep it up!
You want to surprise Papa
when he comes home, right?
I don't want her to
end up like me...
All alone, because of Shocker.
We need to crush Shocker...
for Yumi's sake, as well.
Excuse me, sir.
I don't think this
is the right way.
Hey.
Can't you hear me?
Hey!
Why are you stopping?
You!
Shocker...
The sleeping gas
knocked Takeshi out.
But his enhanced
constitution grants him
recovery speeds ten times
faster than an ordinary person.
Damn...
We've finished
Hongo and the girl.
Good.
Now we just need to
retrieve the Nazi steel box.
Jonan University Biochemistry Laboratory
Later than I thought...
I'll save the rest for tomorrow.
Testing Room
Heading home, Mr. Abe?
Mr. Tachibana...
Did Hongo send you here?
More or less.
Where's the box?
The testing room.
I think Hongo's
getting paranoid.
I doubt anyone's going to
come trying to steal some box.
I hope you're right, of course.
Anyway,
be careful on your way home.
Excuse me.
Good night.
But where's Hongo himself?
He should be here by now...
Shiro, go call him.
But...
Why are you looking so scared?
A young man like you
should be braver than that.
Okay...
Now hurry up.
Gosh, it's dark in here...
Is this it?
That boss of mine is
such a slavedriver...
It sure creeps me out when
it's quiet like this...
That's odd.
No one's picking up.
He's not picking up, Boss.
That sounded like Shiro!
There you are, you monster!
That's the box.
Hurry!
How far are they going
down the Tomei Expressway?
I might be able to
infiltrate Shocker HQ.
Lake Biwa!
Here's the Nazi steel
box that Sunada hid.
Well done. So this is the one...
Bring Doctor Heinrich here.
Doctor Heinrich, behold.
We have the box you've
been searching for.
Boss.
With this box, Shocker will take
control of the world economy.
How is it opened,
Doctor?
A device inside the box is constantly
emitting a certain wave frequency.
If you hit it with waves
of the same wavelength,
the box will open itself.
You need this device to open it.
Wait.
I've just received a message.
An emergency transmission
from our Tokyo Branch.
Leader!
Chameleon Man.
It seems you've brought us a wonderful
prize, in addition to the steel box.
What?
You sent six men to
Jonan University.
But one of them
is still in Tokyo.
Six minus one is five.
One of your men is an enemy!
An enemy? Who?
Hongo Takeshi...
The Kamen Rider!
Shocker Leader...
I will expose you!
Hongo Takeshi successfully
infiltrated Shocker HQ.
But a terrible trap awaited him.
Kamen Rider is in peril!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The latest assassin sent by
Shocker HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Chameleon Man.
Takeshi continues to fall.
What is the Nazi secret?
And what has happened to the
kidnapped Lieutenant Commander Sunada?
Next week's Kamen Rider
moves from Tokyo to Osaka,
in "The Shinigami Chameleon!
Showdown at the Old World's Fair!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!