KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Rock Monster Unicornos
Versus
the Double Rider Kick
Preparations are all complete.
Good.
Then let us begin.
Dissolve the powdered blood we
recovered from the unicorn fossil.
Now... we'll use it to make this
evil man into the cyborg Unicornos.
Initiate the blood
transfer at once.
Good... the surgery is complete.
Letter from Hongo.
Thanks.
What's this?
Everyone's out today?
Yeah, they're hiking
to Okutama today.
Well, good for them.
So, what does it say?
"Ichimonji.
By now I'm sure you've heard of the
recent discovery in Europe of a fossil
belonging to that one-horned beast
written of in Greek and Roman legend:
a unicorn.
I'm sending a picture
of the fossil.
Unfortunately,
someone stole the fossil.
I just received word that it was
recently brought to Japan by Shocker.
My dear friend Ichimonji Hayato.
I'm sending you this warning
from far-away Europe.
Keep an eye on Shocker's Japan Branch
now that they have the unicorn fossil.
See you around."
Damned Shocker...
What are they plotting this time?
This is so cool!
Hey, want to go in there?
Okay!
Excuse us a minute.
Hey, hey!
Hibara Limestone Cavern
I bet we'll find Hell
Valley, the Sanzu River,
and even Sainokawara!
It sounds fun!
Let's go inside.
We're going with you!
Hey, be careful!
Don't get lost!
Awesome!
It's so pretty!
I wonder what's down that way!
I wonder what that is!
I dunno!
Isn't it pretty?
I'm going in!
Wait for me, Goro!
It says "White-Robed Kannon!"
So cool!
Isn't this a dead-end?
No problem!
What's going on?
It's very disturbing...
It sounds like an animal!
And it's coming closer!
Darn it...
You're a Shocker cyborg, aren't you?
Maybe I'll show
you what I can do!
Ready?
Hello? Tachibana Raci...
Pops? This is Taki.
Goro and Emi went missing?
Where?
The limestone caverns?
Okay, let's go.
Hayato! Over here!
Emi! Emi!
Goro!
Hey!
Pops!
Sorry to drag you out here.
We've searched everywhere
and can't find them.
I see...
Have you looked over there?
They couldn't fit in there.
It's too small!
But we should
look, just in case.
- Taki.
- Right.
No, nothing.
Taki, wait a minute.
Look at this.
What is it?
These are...
Those are Goro and Emi's shoes!
What's the matter?
It seems unbelievable,
but I think these
are Goro and Emi.
What did you say?
You think they've
been frozen over?
No... this isn't ice, but rock.
Anyway, let's take them to
Doctor Oshita's laboratory.
It's nearby.
They're playing
right into my hands.
Ichimonji Hayato...
I'll teach you a
lesson very soon.
Oshita Institute
of Space Research
It's not working.
It's not even making a dent.
Just what is it made of?
It's clear that the outer
layer is rock, but...
Doctor.
Are you saying there's no way to
get Goro and Emi out of this rock?
But, Doctor...
The super energy beam you just completed
would surely cut through the rock.
Super energy beam?
No... I'll never make it again.
What do you mean?
The power of the beam terrified even
me, its creator.
If it were to fall into the wrong hands,
it would mean the end of humanity.
I locked the notebook detailing the
beam's creation process in a safe,
and swore never
to open it again.
Unicornos.
The time has come
for you to act.
Go, and steal Oshita's
notebook from that safe.
Shocker requires the super
energy invented by Oshita
to destroy humanity.
Go, Unicornos!
Then, Doctor... you'll create the
super energy beam for us once more?
Yes. I can't argue
with your passion.
I promise to create it
as quickly as possible,
so we can save your friends
encased in the stone.
Do you mean it?
I do.
My assistant Kobayashi is
preparing it right now.
Open the safe!
Open it now!
Hold on! I'll do it!
I'm opening it now.
You tricked me!
- The laboratory!
- Got it!
Ichimonji Hayato!
You...
Shocked, are you?
I am Unicornos.
Unicornos?
Are you their unicorn cyborg?
That's right.
I've come to steal the secret
of the super energy beam!
What did you say?
Come down here now!
Get them!
Die!
Transform!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider!
We'll finish this another day!
Be ready! You hear me?
Damn... where did he get off to?
KAMEN RIDER
Hibara Limestone Cavern
Damn... there must be a Shocker
base around here somewhere.
Shocker... show yourselves!
Unicornos...
Damn...
What will you do now?
Your legs have turned to stone!
You can't even
walk, let alone run!
Damn...
Transform!
These are his notes on
the super energy beam, eh?
Hongo to Ichimonji!
Hongo, is that you?
Hayato,
I've been looking for you.
Where are you now?
Give me your location!
First, track this cycle with
your directional wave detector.
It should lead you to
Shocker and Unicornos.
You need to destroy him. Please!
Understood.
All right...
minus seven degrees, then?
Right... through here, then?
Taki!
Taki, speak to me!
Taki! Speak to me!
Hongo!
I've stolen the notes.
Well done, Unicornos.
Now we will be able to
create the super energy beam.
This is a mini-transmitter.
Wretched Kamen Rider...
he set us up.
Is he trying to
locate our hideout?
There's no need to
worry, though, Doctor.
He's currently...
You're the Kamen Rider!
Don't look so surprised!
There's more than
one Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi...
You're back in Japan, are you?
That's right.
I came here from Europe
to destroy Shocker!
Get him! Kill him!
Hold it!
You handle them, Taki!
Got it!
See to it, Doctor.
Doctor!
Damn you, Shocker...
This time, you will pay!
Transform!
Get him!
Give me that notebook!
I'll turn you into stone, too!
Just try me!
Hongo, watch out!
Hayato!
Not so fast!
Unicornos!
Hongo, be careful!
Let's go!
Where has Unicornos gone?
He's over there!
Now!
Rider Double Kick!
Unicornos became a fossil again.
It's going to explode!
Take it.
What?
You're leaving again
without seeing the others?
Yes.
Shocker's got more plans for
Europe, after all.
Then maybe it'll be
my turn to save you.
Well, see you again.
Look after the others.
Doctor Shinigami's plans to steal the
secrets of the super energy beam
were crushed by the
two Kamen Riders.
But Shocker wasn't
about to relent.
Where would they strike next?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monster bird Gillgaras.
The "dead man gas" it breathes
turns people into mindless killers
who try to murder indiscriminately.
Shocker plans to use this gas
to destroy all of humanity.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
My Name is
Monster Bird Gillgaras!
in "My Name is Monster Bird Gillgaras!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!