KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Terrifying Unidogma
+ Ghost Monsters
What was that flash?
It's a parachute!
It's heading for the
graveyard outside town!
I was sure this was the place...
It's flashing!
Over there!
Here it is.
All right, get to work!
Let's go.
I wonder what they buried...
A sea urchin monster!
It's alive!
You've seen the great Unidogma...
I cannot let you live!
Someone help!
Help!
Good.
Mom! Dad!
I saw a sea urchin
monster in the graveyard!
Dad?
Dad!
Dad is...
Mom! Mom!
Mom is, too...
That should take care
of the whole village.
Go and count them up.
That voice...
They're coming this way!
Kunihiro Ikeda and his wife, Tokie.
Their son Kunio isn't here.
That boy, eh?
Find him!
Fools!
Don't make such a fuss
over one little child.
The most important thing now
is to make more and more Unidogmas.
Don't let a single person
enter that village.
And if anyone does enter...
do not let them leave!
Boy, the air really is better out here.
No sign of Shocker, either.
It's been a while since
we could relax like this!
Don't relax too much.
We'll be heading home
after we pay our respects.
Oh, come on.
Don't be like that.
Shocker's not going to wait around
while I'm visiting a few graves.
Well, let's get going.
Right.
- It should be right up here.
- Right!
Tachibana Tobei!
What?
What's he doing in this village?
Has he caught wind
of our plan somehow?
Counter-soldiers,
finish off Tachibana Tobei!
Be patient!
We can finish him off any time.
We must deal with Tachibana carefully,
or we might spur Kamen Rider to action.
As long as he doesn't catch on, let him go.
Continue your surveillance.
Tachibana Family Grave
It's a pretty creepy graveyard...
Don't say that, or a ghost
might just haunt you!
Stop that! Chairman, you meanie!
A ghost!
Hey, don't scare us like that!
Help me, mister!
Help you? What happened?
My mom and dad... everyone
in the town has been killed!
Killed? Really?
Could you tell us the whole story?
We might be able to help.
Okay?
Just calm down.
What do you mean, your parents
and the townspeople were killed?
Come on! Hurry!
It's right here.
They were killed!
Kunio.
You need to study,
not play around all the time.
Can we help you?
Oh, well...
Your son said the strangest thing...
He said you'd been killed.
Kunio, are you lying again?
He's really quite a problem child.
No! That's not my dad!
That's not my mom!
Kunio! Enough!
This is all nonsense.
Let's go, Chairman.
Well, we'll be going.
Wait! Please believe me!
Kunio!
Excuse us.
Code number zero here.
HQ, over.
Yes, Chairman? HQ here.
Yes.
Pops. Was it nice being
back in your hometown?
Yeah, I feel refreshed. 2Z4.
2Z4?
2Z4... is that a code?
I'm leaving the village now.
I should make it to Tokyo
around seven o'clock.
That fool, Tachibana...
He's leaving the village
none the wiser!
Chairman?
What child would ever lie
about his parents being killed?
Then you think the parents
we saw were... you know?
I'm going to find out what
those "ghosts" really were.
Who are you people?
Who are we, you ask?
Help!
Let me go!
This village is under Shocker's control.
Its people are being used to create
more and more Unidogmas.
Shocker?
Behold...
It's a Unidogma egg in
the process of hatching.
If we feed it this child's
cells, it will be complete.
Do it!
Help! Someone help!
Help! Someone!
Help!
Someone help!
Hey, Yokko.
Tachibana!
I knew it...
Shocker was behind those ghosts!
- Run!
- Okay!
Get them!
Pops's message contained the code 2Z4.
"I've located Shocker."
But that's some rotten luck...
running into Shocker when
he goes home to pay his respects.
Maybe it's all about his attitude.
Okay, let's hurry.
What's that?
Is this the Shocker monster?
Taki.
If the monster is here, then only
combatants are holding Otake Village.
That means I can handle it myself.
I'll help the Chairman and Yokko.
Right.
Where are you?
Show yourself, new Shocker monster!
If you want to see me, come find me!
Rider Transformation!
Shocker cyborg...
Am I?
Is that what I look like?
Kamen Rider...
The Shocker cyborg you're
searching for is Unidogma...
He's in Otake Village.
Unidogma...
Then, what are you?
What indeed?
You'll learn what I am soon enough!
If Unidogma is in Otake Village,
that means Taki and Pops are in danger.
KAMEN RIDER
It's Taki!
Taki has arrived!
What?
Good...
Seal off all entrances to the village!
If that brat Taki is here,
that means Hongo Takeshi...
the Kamen Rider will come soon!
Everyone, take your positions!
Wait!
Be patient, Ambassador Hell.
My leader.
But if the Kamen Rider arrives,
he'll threaten our plans!
The Kamen Rider will not arrive.
What did you say?
What exactly do you mean?
Listen only to my orders.
The Kamen Rider will not arrive.
You can finish off Shocker's
enemies at your leisure.
Y-Yes, sir...
Is this the place?
Chairman!
Taki?
Calm down, you guys!
The Shocker monster isn't
in the village anymore.
You mean it?
Open the door!
You're sure the monster's gone?
Hongo's holding it off.
It's all small fry here.
Now, come on out.
Isn't that great, Kunio?
Who's this kid?
A witness to Shocker's plan.
Please avenge my mom and dad!
You mean...
Unidogma killed them.
All right...
I hereby appoint you to the
Shocker-fighting Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
You mean it?
Captain, I'll show you the way!
Great.
Let's blow this joint, then!
I think I prefer Tokyo anyway!
Okay, let's go!
Go that way!
Taki and Tachibana
are heading for area B1F.
Hey...
This road isn't safe.
Go that way, then!
Right.
Direction changed to area B1R.
Damn... they're trying
to keep us trapped here.
Kunio, is there no other way?
You can go through the graveyard
and across the mountain!
Great!
They're heading just where
we want them to go.
Hongo Takeshi!
I'm right here!
Talk! Where are you sending them?
Well?
I see... you're sending
them to the graveyard?
It's creeping me out that
we haven't seen any combatants.
I feel the same way.
But it's better that
we don't run into any...
Hold on!
Hey... you okay?
Let's go!
- Be careful!
- Right.
Finally... Shocker combatants!
Monster!
That was a dirty trick...
Silence!
To create more Unidogmas,
we need living humans.
Unidogmas?
I won't let you eat us.
Listen to me!
By feeding them human cells,
we'll produce more
and more Unidogmas.
I will make Japan into
a nest for Unidogmas!
So you're going to eat
everyone in the country?
Shut up!
First the boy,
then the woman.
Hongo!
You wretch...
Unidogma, I won't
let you create a successor.
Silence. Get him!
Pops, run!
Hurry!
Damn you...
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
Rider Transformation!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Dogma Fire!
Rider, Rider!
Rider Punch!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider Drill Shoot!
Rider, Rider!
My leader.
I must know...
You said the Kamen
Rider would not appear.
Why then, my leader...
Silence, Ambassador Hell.
The failures are all on your head.
Go on, look at the screen.
Do you know what that is?
A cyborg I've never seen before...
My leader.
What is the meaning of this?
I have no need to tell you.
All right.
If you drive me to it, then...
I swear to work hard as a member
of the Kamen Rider Kid Corps,
to uphold justice and peace.
We're counting on you.
The Shocker cyborg
Unidogma was defeated,
but uncertainty hung heavy
around Hongo Takeshi.
Who was that powerful unknown
enemy that had appeared before him?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The rattle of a snake comes
from Ambassador Hell's body.
Glinting blue eyes pierce through Rider.
Stay tuned to this channel next week for
"Ambassador Hell!! His Fearsome True Form?"
Ambassador Hell!!
His Fearsome True Form?
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!