KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Demonic Assassin
the Eerie Fly Man
Look alive already!
You jerk! What are you doing?
- Bye-bye!
- Let's go!
One, two! C'mon, everyone!
There's lots of cars,
so watch yourselves at the crosswalk!
Look both ways before you cross!
Got it?
Let's go!
Thanks, mister!
Thank you!
Hey!
Tachibana Racing Club
You bastards...
We barely touched him.
Shut up.
It's their fault
for being so slow.
How can you say that?
Catch you later!
- Hey, wait!
- Wait!
Catch them, Hayato!
All right, Goro.
Leave this to me.
- Taki, you handle things here!
- Right.
Damn them...
Damn...
Give it more speed!
You'll never catch me!
Hold it! Stop, you!
Shut up! Catch us if you can!
Stop!
C'mon and catch us!
Damn...
Why you...
You people... Don't you care?
You hit a child back there!
Wait!
Why, you...
You call yourself human?
Shut up!
Japan's overpopulated anyway.
We'd be better off with a
few less people in the world.
You'll pay for that!
Why you...
Wait, you!
This is the man we've
been waiting for.
The blood that runs through
his veins is as cold as ice.
Capture that man!
Transform him into Fly Man!
Ichimonji Hayato...
You'll never find him now.
Sorry, Hiro.
It was my fault.
Mine, too. It's okay.
I'm just glad it wasn't serious!
No more need to worry, ma'am.
He'll be discharged
in two or three days.
Thank you so much.
Goro,
you really don't have to worry.
You haven't done anything wrong.
All right?
Ma'am, can I stay here
until Hiroshi feels better?
Please?
It's okay, right, Hiroshi?
Complete the surgery quickly.
Fly Man is the cyborg that
will defeat the Kamen Rider.
The surgery is
proceeding smoothly.
Hayato.
I found out where the
hit-and-run driver lives.
What? Where is it?
Doctor Shinigami.
I want to kill Ichimonji Hayato.
Where can I find him?
Fly Man.
I see your demonic blood is
already racing for the kill.
In that case...
Administer this drug to the members
of the Tachibana Racing Club.
What will this do to them?
Those who have taken that drug
can be controlled with the
command sound waves you emit.
Can they?
You hate Ichimonji Hayato.
You wish to kill him.
Which means that anyone who takes
that drug will also be consumed
by a desire to kill
Ichimonji Hayato.
I see.
When I think about how
I want to kill him,
the people around him
will feel the same way.
Very interesting.
Go, Fly Man.
Go, and kill Ichimonji Hayato!
Yes. I will kill him,
no matter what it takes!
I have everything I need!
Is this the house?
What's that sound?
They're making us wait a while.
I wonder what they're doing.
Where's the lady of the house?
She'll be here very soon.
Just wait a bit longer.
The maid told me everything.
Mr. Tachibana?
Are you the one claiming
Osamu hit a child and ran?
I don't believe
he's capable of it.
Just what proof do you have?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Your son hit a
child with his car.
Pure hearsay.
I did not raise
my Osamu that way.
That's right... your maid said
Osamu's been gone for a few days.
Are you worried about him?
No, not especially.
He's gone to a friend's
house to study.
I trust him, you see.
Now, don't let your
coffee get cold.
It's a truly fine Italian roast.
Enjoy yourselves.
I guess we'll come back later.
I can see we're not
getting through to her.
What did you say?
Oh, nothing.
I see... very fine coffee.
Drink up, Yuri.
We might never drink
something so fancy ever again.
- Thank you very much.
- Help yourselves.
- She creeps me out.
- Come on, she can hear you.
She's creepy,
but her coffee is excellent.
Come on, let's go.
Right.
Mr. Chairman...
- Pops!
What happened?
Yuri! What's wrong?
Pops, Yuri... what's wrong?
Taki.
Look at their eyes.
They're not in their right mind.
What's happening here?
What happened to those two?
It must be Shocker.
Taki... be careful.
Who is it?
Who's that over there?
Help! Someone!
You've shown
yourself, Shocker...
KAMEN RIDER
Transform!
Wait!
Rider...
we'll finish this later!
Damn... where's he gone?
He's a fierce opponent.
Do we really have to tie them all up?
Poor things...
Mika. They aren't in
their right minds.
But...
They tried to kill us, remember?
What are you doing?
It's ammonia.
It'll wake them up, I hope.
It worked!
Mr. Chairman, Yuri.
Yuri! You're awake!
Why are we tied up?
What's going on here?
You don't remember
what happened before?
Untie me, quickly!
I'm so glad you're better!
The drug will remain
effective for three days.
At least for the next two
days, your command sound waves
will make Tachibana Tobei—Ichimonji
Hayato's most trusted comrade...
An assassin out for his life.
Doctor, why don't we administer
this drug to every person in Japan?
Wait.
First, administer it to Goro and
Emi, the remaining club members.
Go, Fly Man!
Here we go.
Want me to feed you?
It's okay, Goro.
I'm feeling a lot better.
No way! You have to rest!
Goro... you still feel
responsible, right?
Just eat up, okay?
Here!
Where's your food, Goro?
Emi's gonna bring it by later.
Just go ahead and eat, okay?
Goro! I brought your food!
Let's have our lunch, too!
Sure thing!
Here, Goro!
So good!
Can't breathe...
Goro? What's wrong?
It's hard to breathe...
Goro! Emi! What's wrong?
I'll kill him.
I'll kill him!
I'll kill Ichimonji Hayato.
Tachibana Auto Corner
"Closed today."
That's strange...
Hey, you two are back already?
All finished at the hospital?
Hello?
Oh, Taki? Yeah, it's me.
What is it?
Hayato, Hiroshi is missing.
Did Goro and Emi check him out?
What? Hiroshi isn't there?
Wait a minute.
Where did Hiroshi go?
I do not know.
Did anyone see Hiroshi go?
Nobody, then?
That's strange...
Look out!
Hayato!
Damn...
The chairman and Yuri are
still under Shocker's control!
Hello? Hello?
Hayato!
Hurry!
- I'm scared!
- It's okay. Hayato is here.
Hayato!
Taki! Take care of the others!
I'll get the monster!
Got it! Leave it to me!
Take her, too!
Run!
Hurry!
- Are you all right?
- You two, get in there.
Right!
This way!
Transform!
Try me, Shocker!
I'll finish you this time!
After him!
Rider Flip-Kick!
You did it!
Yes...
Where am I?
Hey, you're back with us.
- Hey...
- Where in the world are we?
What's going on here?
Looks like they're
finally back to normal.
Hiroshi!
Goro!
I thought you were
in the hospital.
I'm all better now!
But are you sure they're
all back to normal?
They're fine.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Who's back to normal?
Someone tell me! Please!
Ichimonji Hayato,
the Kamen Rider,
had foiled Doctor Shinigami's latest
terrible plan, involving Fly Man.
But Shocker would
surely attack again!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monster-bird Pranodon.
It uses Taki and Emi of
the Tachibana Racing Club
to try to assassinate
Ichimonji Hayato.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Bird
Pranodon Attacks!"
The Monstrous Bird
Pranodon Attacks
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!