KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Beaded Lizard Man
Deathmatch in Fear Valley!!
Otaguro
Research Institute
Yamamoto, the X-Alpha fluid.
Yes, sir.
Doctor.
Do you think we can really revive a
dog that's been dead for three weeks?
Is everything in place?
Yes.
Doctor! The dog's alive!
Doctor! Doctor Otaguro!
Yamamoto.
Doctor.
Yoshiko...
We've finally done it!
Yes.
We brought a dog that's been dead
for three weeks back to life.
Doctor...
It's wonderful.
Doctor.
- Yamamoto.
- Yes.
Now that we know the
X-Alpha fluid works,
we must begin clinical trials at
Johoku University first thing tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Take the X-Alpha fluid
to the university for me.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you later, Yoshiko.
Okay.
Thank you. I owe it all to you.
Really, Doctor...
What's the matter?
- Wh-What are you doing?
- You must die!
I'm the kind of man who always
gets whatever he wants...
Monster!
Run, if you think you can...
But you cannot escape
the great Beaded Lizard Man!
Doctor...
Yoshiko...
Damn!
Why did you kill him?
If you had left Yamamoto alive,
we could have extracted the
secret of the X-Alpha from him.
We should just abduct
Doctor Otaguro himself and...
Wait. Just wait a moment.
If we kidnap Otaguro
now, Rider will catch on.
Then...
should we give up on the X-Alpha?
No.
Shocker must obtain the
X-Alpha at any cost,
to further advance our
own scientific prowess.
Look at the screen.
This woman is Otaguro's other
assistant, Yoshiko Hashimoto.
The only way to complete the plan to
enhance our scientific capabilities
by stealing the secret of the
X-Alpha, without Rider catching on,
is to use this woman.
Yes, sir.
Steal the secret of the X-Alpha
fluid without Rider catching on!
Shocker's plan was to use
two doctors from England
who died two years ago,
said to be the greatest in their fields...
The physicist, Doctor Edward,
and the mathematician, Doctor Kaines...
Whose bodies they stole from
cold storage in a London museum,
revive them with
the X-Alpha fluid,
and force them to create
deadly weapons for Shocker.
Go, Beaded Lizard Man.
Abduct Yoshiko Hashimoto.
Hashimoto
Good morning.
Oh, Goro, good morning.
Where's Kiyoshi?
Hold on just a minute.
I'll call him now.
Kiyoshi?
Better hurry,
or Goro will leave without you.
See you later, Mom, Dad.
Okay, hurry up, now.
Okay.
Kiyoshi. Take care, would you?
Don't forget anything, okay?
Okay.
Okay, go on.
See you later.
Oh, no!
I forgot my homework again!
Oh, come on!
Go! Go to Otaguro's laboratory!
Someone help me!
- Help me!
- Go!
It's Kiyoshi's sister!
My sister!
It's Shocker!
Darn you, Shocker!
What? Your sister
was taken by Shocker?
What would Shocker
want with his sister?
Do you think Shocker
might have already...
Hush!
Oh, Tokko! Don't you even
realize how Kiyoshi must feel?
Sorry...
If they kill my
sister, I'll die, too.
It'll be okay, Kiyoshi.
We have Mr. Hongo Takeshi
and Mr. Taki on our side.
I just know they'll
save your sister.
Right, Chairman?
That's right.
Goro's exactly right.
Come on... it's not good
for a boy to cry like this.
If the Kamen Rider saw you
crying, he'd have to laugh!
Good morning!
How's everyone doing?
Not well at all, I see...
What's going on?
Shocker kidnapped
Kiyoshi's big sister.
What did you say?
When did this happen?
Just now.
I believe Kiyoshi's sister is an
assistant at Otaguro Laboratory.
Doctor Otaguro is one of Japan's
most famous biochemists.
Yeah, he's in my department!
There have been rumors that he's
doing some groundbreaking research...
You think Shocker is after that?
Taki, let's head for
Otaguro's laboratory.
Doctor!
Yoshiko!
Wh-Who are you people?
Otaguro.
I wish to trade the X-Alpha
fluid for this woman's life.
Doctor!
X-Alpha?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Is that your final
word on the matter?
Even now?!
Help me!
Wait a minute. Wait!
I'll give you the documents...
Hold it!
Doctor!
Doctor! Are you all right?
Taki!
Damn... you won't get away!
Wait, you!
Damn...
Rider Transformation!
There you are, Rider!
Drop the caltrops!
Jump!
You won't escape!
Let me go!
Take the girl!
Yoshiko!
Damn you, Shocker...
Fight me, Rider!
Beaded Lizard Man!
Wait!
Help me!
Yoshiko!
Die, Rider!
What do you think of my venom?
If you'd been a normal man,
you'd be melted by now!
My body's... going numb!
Your end has come at
last, Rider!
Rider, fall to hell!
Now I'll cut the rope!
KAMEN RIDER
Our plan is going perfectly!
Ambassador Hell.
Haven't you acquired
the X-Alpha fluid yet?
Just leave it to me.
I nearly have it!
Beaded Lizard Man has put an end to the
Kamen Rider, our greatest obstacle.
So, next time...
Ambassador Hell,
the Rider still lives.
What did you say?
You realize that failure means
death, do you not?
But I will give you
one final chance.
That Kamen Rider has
the devil's own luck...
I'll have to get Hongo and Taki to
bring Otaguro's documents themselves!
Help me!
It'll be all right, Kiyoshi.
Just eat up, okay?
Isn't there anything we can do?
Poor kid...
Seriously...
Takeshi! You need to rest!
Where's Taki, Pops?
Otaguro's laboratory.
Takeshi, wait!
You're in no condition for this!
Let Taki handle this!
Let me go!
You great fool!
Give some thought
to your condition!
Pops...
Let me go, Pops!
Help me!
The tests are going swimmingly.
Turn off the buzzsaw.
Hongo Takeshi and Taki will
surely come to save her.
This electrical current is
passing through this circuit
and through the woman's body.
When Hongo sees her,
he'll try to save her by
turning off the electric saw.
When he touches the woman,
it will immediately
send electricity through
the bombs placed
all around the base,
causing a massive explosion!
They're going to kill Yoshiko.
What... what should I do?
Doctor, you should wait.
They'll want to ransom Yoshiko
to get the X-Alpha documents.
We can't lose our patience.
We need to wait for now.
But there's no way we can just
hand them the documents...
Shocker!
Help me!
Someone help me!
Well, Taki?
Interesting show, isn't it?
You're... Ambassador Hell!
Help me!
It's currently 2:15.
At 2:30, this saw will
bury itself in her body.
If you don't want her to die,
you must bring the documentation on the
X-Alpha fluid to Fear Valley by 2:30.
Fear Valley?
Just fifteen minutes left...
But the documents must be
brought by Hongo and Taki.
Understood?
X-Alpha-related Documents
Take them.
Doctor...
Please, save Yoshiko!
There's no replacement
for a person's life.
Doctor...
Taki, please.
Please, save Yoshiko.
Taki took the documents to
Shocker, by himself?
Rider Transformation!
Hey, Shocker!
I brought the documents!
Come out now!
Taki... you fool!
Yoshiko!
Help!
Beaded Lizard Man,
the Kamen Rider has appeared.
There you are, Rider!
Come to watch the
explosion, have you?
Two minutes remain!
Rider, hurry! Hit the switch!
Don't do it!
The switch is designed to set
off bombs all around the base!
All right...
Taki, hurry!
Find the explosives!
We don't have much time! Hurry!
Yoshiko...
Rider! Hurry, before Yoshiko...
Got it.
The bombs are gone.
I'm turning it off!
Are you all right?
Yes...
There you are, Shocker!
Taki! Take Yoshiko and run!
Right!
Hurry!
Die, Rider!
Damn you...
Without that tongue,
he'd be an ordinary opponent...
All right, now!
Rider Kick!
Rider Head Crusher!
I have won.
Kiyoshi!
Sis!
Sis...
Kiyoshi!
I'm happy for you, Kiyoshi.
Takeshi!
- Sorry I'm late!
- Takeshi!
Where have you been?
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
I owe you all a great debt.
Yes. Thank you all so much.
Hey, save your thanks
for the doctor.
His willingness to
hand over the documents
is what saved your life.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go.
Yeah.
Wait a minute! Hey, hang on!
Aw, man...
The Kamen Rider, Hongo Takeshi,
had defeated Beaded Lizard Man and kept
the X-Alpha fluid out of Shocker's hands.
Ride on, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the Monstrous Worm-Man.
He uses a terrifying killer
rings to throw Rider to his doom.
But Hongo Takeshi
revives with Rider Power.
Go, our Kamen Rider!
Join us next week for "The Monstrous
Worm Man of the Bottomless Swamp!"
The Monstrous Worm Man of the Bottomless Swamp!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!