KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Papa, isn't it pretty?
I'm gonna pick more...
Don't go too far.
What's wrong?
That did it!
Now, now. It's just a frog.
He should be here by now...
Papa, who are you waiting for?
Come along, Rumiko.
Okay.
Japan in Peril!
Gamagiller's Invasion
Excuse me. Are you Ichimonji Hayato?
How do you know me?
I need help from you... and by
that, I mean the Kamen Rider.
Origuchi Institute of
Crime Research
I know about Shocker, too.
Impressive, right?
Yes...
I was looking into Shocker's activities,
when I stumbled upon
a terrible plan in the works.
Rumiko!
What?
Stay close by, would you?
Fine...
I can't help but feel
like someone's after me.
This way, please.
This isn't good. Damn that Hayato...
This area, Kurobe Gorge,
is Japan's weakest geological point.
The east and west sides have
completely different geological makeups.
Our plan to cause a nuclear explosion here,
tear the land in two,
and take over Japan in the ensuing
chaos is proceeding smoothly.
The special nuclear bomb will
arrive from the homeland
to our secret airfield
before the day is out.
But how do you explain...
your inability to kidnap the daughter
of Origuchi, who's caught on to our plan?!
He was on guard for a
kidnapping while he was outside.
I couldn't get close.
Gamagiller, test out your nerve gas.
Bring a prisoner here.
What are you doing?
Damn it... let me go!
Damn it!
Help me!
No one would ever believe
a word a man like that said.
First, take his daughter hostage.
Then see to it that he can
never reveal Shocker's secrets.
Understood?
Origuchi Institute of
Crime Research
All right, go to it!
Damn it...
No one may enter without
an appointment in advance.
Please leave at once.
Recognize that I've taken
your picture as well.
Damn... his security is airtight.
All right... go around behind!
Look at this.
It's the proof that they're still
hanging around the estate.
Where's your daughter?
My assistant let her play in the yard.
Are you certain that's safe?
Yes. No one can enter the yard.
She'll be fine, as long as
she doesn't leave the grounds.
There!
I'm so sorry!
You hit it too hard!
I'm sorry.
I wonder where it went...
Rumiko! Did you find it?
It's not here...
Not here...
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Time to eat!
Goro, you're here, too?
That's trouble...
Let me guess.
"What am I going to do?" Right?
- Yes, actually.
- I figured.
We didn't bring any for you.
Sorry.
Normally we'd treat you first, but...
But you're a big boy now.
No problem! I've got...
Ta-dah!
Look? I'm gonna stick it on you!
See? I'll stick it on you!
I'll stick it on you!
Okay, let's go home, froggie dear.
Now, all for me!
Delicious!
What's all this?
It was just awful!
Goro was so mean!
He's eating it all!
That's not nice!
Indeed I am.
Is this it?
I'll stick it on you!
Can we have these?
Just whose side are you on?
Yeah, we bought those, you know!
You'd better pay us back later.
Taki! Phone for you!
From who?
Ask them yourself.
No fury like a woman starved, huh?
Oh, please!
Hello?
Oh, Hayato?
What's that? A frog monster?
- Shocker again?
- A frog?
Mr. Origuchi, try to stay strong.
This file is what Shocker is after.
There's no question they'll
ask for it in exchange for Rumiko.
But I'd even arranged a witness...
I was going to tell the world
about Shocker's evils!
I can't do anything
while she's their hostage!
Is this the witness?
Yes.
The survivor of a four-man expedition
in the Alps that was attacked by Shocker.
She apparently heard the word
of their plan to split Japan in two
from the mouth of their leader himself.
From their leader?
Then... she met their leader?
Yes, but she lost her
memory right after,
and now all she has is the vague
memory of having seen him.
But... if I could just project her
memories onto this brainwave screen...
I'm sure we'd get an
image of their leader!
Hurry!
Help me!
I knew you'd come, Ichimonji Hayato!
Take her away, quickly!
Right!
Transform!
Rider... we'll meet again!
Hurry! Quickly!
So that's the way in?
KAMEN RIDER
Damn...
What an awful way
to treat such a little girl.
Get going.
Take the girl to an underground cell.
Rider, there you are!
- Let's get out of here!
- Right!
Damn!
This is how they
plan to conquer the wo...
Papa!
Rumiko!
These are the men who saved Rumiko.
Really... you did it?
Oh, thank you!
Rumiko... I'm so glad you're safe.
- Papa!
- Rumiko!
This way! Hurry!
I just hope this machine
can relay her memories.
Please, try.
Are you ready?
Slowly and calmly,
remember what happened
when you met Shocker's leader.
Try to focus your mind.
I can see something...
but I don't know where I am.
I think this is where I woke up, after
falling into that cave in the Andes...
You found yourself inside Shocker's cave.
Is that right?
Yes.
But then I lost consciousness again...
Hours passed, didn't they?
Days passed, didn't they?
Isn't that right?
And then you found yourself
standing in front of a strange door...
I could hear someone
giving orders beyond it.
Then someone else, calling them "leader."
Did you open that door?
No, I didn't...
I just peeked in through the crack...
You saw it, didn't you?
You saw the identity of their leader!
Yes... I did see it!
It gave some kind of order.
What did it say?
I think it said...
"Go to the secret airfield in Tokyo."
Secret airfield?
At 3 o'clock on October 10th,
we'll transport the nuclear bomb.
Do not let anyone find out.
October 10th?
That's today!
Anything else?
I don't know...
Try harder! Kinuko, you're almost there!
I can see him clearly now...
Almost there!
I'm remembering...
- Kinuko! Kinuko!
- Kinuko!
Oh no!
Shocker's on their way in.
Take Kinuko to safety, to the second floor!
Right!
Hurry!
Take this, you monster...
I never thought I'd have
to use this system,
but Shocker will make fine guinea pigs.
Damn you, monster!
Crime Investigation Report
Origuchi Crime Research Institute
Taki, stay alert.
Right. Leave it to me!
Finish them off!
Unload the bomb!
This is the nuclear bomb in question.
It has the power to tear Japan in two!
Give my regards to Colonel Zol.
Gamagiller, this is it.
We're counting on you!
There you are, Rider!
What's wrong with you,
Gamagiller? Kill him at once!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Rider... catch me if you can!
What now, Rider?!
Rider Jump!
Nothing personal, but we'd
better go our separate ways.
Go on.
Bye-bye!
I feel much better.
Now we can eat ice
cream without fear.
You think so, huh?
Rumiko! Let's go catch another frog!
I don't like frogs.
But if you want ice cream,
I'll happily join you.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Yeah!
I'm glad you're better.
Even though you lost your memories...
Maybe it's a good thing that
you forgot your traumatic past.
Leave future battles with Shocker to me.
Shocker?
I'm sorry. I don't remember anything.
Don't be mean, Papa.
This man saved my life.
That's right, he did.
But, is Shocker real?
It's better if you don't
know, Mr. Origuchi.
See you.
Later!
In the end, Shocker's evils
remained unrevealed to the world,
because Kinuko and Origuchi
had both lost their memories.
But Ichimonji Hayato's battle
against Shocker would continue!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the killer queen ant, Arichimedes.
Colonel Zol plans to conquer Japan
using the formic acid
she spits from her antennae.
Ichimonji Hayato and his
allies stand in her way.
Join us next week for "The
Killer Queen Ant, Arichimedes."
The Killer Queen Ant
Arichimedes
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!