KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
To prepare for Gel Shocker's all-out attack,
Leech Chameleon is working to
revive their old monsters.
Hongo Takeshi learned of their
plan and infiltrated their base,
but he fell into Leech Chameleon's trap and was
left unable to transform into Kamen Rider.
Twenty.
Fifteen.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Gel Shocker Destroyed!
The Leader's End!!
No...
Yuri...
Have you forgotten the second Rider?!
Damn! When did you get here?
Taki... save the others!
Right! Hurry, to safety!
This base will explode in five minutes!
Hayato!
Hurry, Hongo. Transform!
Right.
Rider Transformation!
Find the time bomb!
Right!
I hear it... a ticking sound!
Just thirty seconds left.
Okay...
Head Crusher!
There it is!
Not so fast!
Hayato, go!
Right!
Hongo, I've turned it off!
Good!
Now, Leech Chameleon...
Where is General Black?
Confess!
Riders One and Two...
General Black!
- Come out!
- We have Leech Chameleon hostage!
Kamen Riders...
I'll release the prisoners we were
using for Gel Shocker experiments.
You release Leech Chameleon.
Release the prisoners?
Very well.
What are your terms?
Come to the Hall of Monsters
at Pal Pal Amusement Park!
Tomorrow morning at 4:00.
All right.
Pal Pal Amusement Park
This is the Hall of Monsters?
They couldn't have picked
a more appropriate place.
It'll be dawn soon.
What are those?
They're skilled likenesses...
It's 4:00!
Where is General Black?
We've brought Leech Chameleon!
Welcome,
Kamen Riders
You've finally arrived... Hongo
Takeshi... Ichimonji Hayato.
I'm right in front of you!
Is Leech Chameleon...
General Black is...
That's right.
I was throwing my voice with ventriloquism!
All to lure you this building!
What are you after?
I, Leech Chameleon, have brought
all the monsters back to life!
What?
Fools... watch closely!
Witness Leech Chameleon's true face!
General Black...
Just as we thought!
What do you mean by that?
You've underestimated us, General Black!
We know Gel Shocker commanders-in-chief
are always monsters.
We walked into your trap
to expose your true face!
Curses!
Wait, Hongo! Hayato!
I'll tail the monsters.
You chase General Black.
Right.
Hayato, transform!
Got it!
Transform!
Rider Transformation!
Hold it!
Let's go!
Fight me, Riders!
Die, Riders!
Damn you, Kamen Riders!
The time has come.
My role has ended.
I choose to die in glory.
Riders... listen carefully.
The one who laughs last...
The one who laughs last is Gel Shocker!
Glory to our
great leader!
General Black is dead.
Gel Shocker's commanders were
all brave in their own way.
This leaves only their leader.
I hope Taki tracked them back successfully.
KAMEN RIDER
Listen, Taki.
Don't chase them too far.
Gel Shocker's leader
will be there this time.
Got it.
I'll leave their leader to you two.
That's strange...
I can't imagine why they'd
meet their leader here.
Right...
They disappeared.
When did they disappear?
You...
Taki, you've outlived your usefulness!
How do you like it, Taki?!
Our General Black was
an excellent leader...
He set one last trap,
knowing it would kill him!
One last trap?
He'd lure Hongo Takeshi and
Ichimonji Hayato to us...
then let us kill them in front
of you and the Rider Kid Corps!
It must be them!
Hey, Hongo.
We've been waiting to
hear from you all night.
Members of the Rider Kid Corps.
That's the Gel Shocker leader's voice!
Your organization is hereby dissolved.
Dissolved?
Don't be ridiculous!
We'll never dissolve as
long as you're around.
Today, Gel Shocker will mount
a massive attack on Japan.
Japan will be ours by the end of the day.
Kamen Rider will stop you!
You can see for yourselves
how your Riders die.
How our Riders die?
We'll escort you all to the
their execution grounds.
What did you say?
You...
Didn't Hongo and Ichimonji finish you off?
We're here to take you to the
Riders' execution grounds.
Get them!
Taki, can you hear me? Taki!
Taki here.
The bridge over Lake Hamana looks suspect.
Okay, don't move.
We're on our way.
Hongo. It's not me!
That isn't my voice!
Your protestations fall on deaf ears, Taki.
Our computer can produce a
voice identical to yours.
Not even Hongo Takeshi can catch on.
What are you going to do with them?
I will execute them in the
Japan Gel Shocker headquarters,
located beneath Lake Hamana
in the center of Japan.
This is the place Taki mentioned.
Taki!
Welcome, Hongo Takeshi! Ichimonji Hayato!
Gel Shocker's leader...
It's time for Gel Shocker's
final show of hospitality.
Ghosts out of hell!
Don't let your guard down.
- Transform!
- Rider Transformation!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Kamen Riders...
You've shown yourself at last, Leader...
Defeating you will restore
peace to our world!
Foolish Kamen Riders!
Behold!
- Taki!
- Pops!
Riders!
Go save your allies!
Riders, stay back!
It's a trap! Stay away!
Look out! Stay back!
Don't come here!
- Yeah.
- Are you all right?
Hang in there!
Dig deep and stand up!
Hang in there, Hayato!
If we die now,
this will all be for nothing!
Riders, get up!
Ichimonji...
- Riders!
- Hang in there, Riders!
Hongo...
Hayato...
Riders!
Kamen Riders...
Leader... there's nowhere to run now.
Wait!
Abandon your quest for world domination.
Show us who you really are!
Rider... you've finally seen my true face.
So that's what their leader really was?
You've brought about
the end of Gel Shocker...
But I'll make sure you join us in hell!
This is the end of Gel Shocker.
Now, die with me!
A dramatic end for Gel Shocker's leader...
Hongo.
What's that?
Their leader's real brain.
Their base blew up.
You think it took the Riders with it?
The Riders...
That's the Cyclone!
Tokyo International Airport
Taki, take care of yourself out there.
Pops.
It's hard to say goodbye.
I'd like to head out
without seeing the others.
Don't be so stubborn.
Come on.
I'll never forget you guys.
Taki...
The days have been long and hard.
With peace restored, they'll
feel like good memories.
That's right.
Taki, come see us again, all right?
Right.
Mr. Taki.
We'll make sure the Rider Kid
Corps keeps going strong.
I'm counting on you.
Mr. Taki, take care.
Captain Taki!
Come back and see us again!
Yeah, you'd better!
Well, it's time.
Let me do the rest on my own.
Take care, all of you.
That's his plane!
Mr. Taki!
Gel Shocker was destroyed,
and their terrifying leader had died.
The Kamen Riders, Hongo
Takeshi and Ichimonji Hayato,
had survived their deathmatch
against Gel Shocker,
and their long trial had ended.
It was time for peace to return!
The End
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!