KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Enroll in the
Gel Shocker Terror School!!
You have been chosen!
You will now join
Centipede Tiger's Terror School!
Is that understood?
Yes, I would be delighted.
Who's there?
Wh-What are you doing?
Just what it looks like!
Your daughter will join Gel Shocker!
You monster... give Wakako back!
Resistance is useless!
Wakako!
That's strange...
The message tube is empty again!
Let me see.
This is the eighth one this week.
The Rider Kid Corps are slacking!
Don't be stupid.
The Rider Kid Corps are made up of
Japan's most accomplished boys and girls.
They wouldn't just mess up like this.
Hey, Chairman... you think something
could have happened to them?
If you think that, go write
down pigeons' numbers
and the addresses of their owners.
You think I need your instructions?
I already did it!
I'm curious, too. I'll look into it.
That's strange...
What is it?
These kids all live
in the Tanzawa District.
That's convenient for our investigation.
Yeah.
Run!
Gel Shocker...
You won't get away!
Wait.
If they've sent combatants,
a cyborg will soon follow.
I hear it now...
Sounds like an insect...
Hongo Takeshi.
My name is Centipede Tiger!
I knew you'd be here, cyborg...
What's your goal?
We have one goal...
To create a new organization
within Gel Shocker.
And their first task will be to fight you!
A new organization?
Presenting, the first class
of the Gel Shocker Terror School!
The Tanzawa District members
of the Rider Kid Corps...
Centipede Tiger...
Your new organization... could it be...
It is, Hongo Takeshi!
Allow me to introduce Gel Shocker's
new organization, the Gel Shocker Kid Corps!
Speak to me, Kishi! Hirai! Ota!
Taki, Gel Shocker has brainwashed them.
I'll defeat him!
Get him, children Gel Shocker!
Do as we taught you in Terror School!
Hongo! I'll handle the kids.
You go after Centipede Tiger!
Got it!
Centipede Tiger... return
the children to normal!
Does it vex you, Hongo Takeshi?
Soon, Gel Shocker will have every member
of the Rider Kid Corps under our control!
I won't let it happen!
It's too late!
We're already outside the Rider
Kid Corps headquarters!
Taki, they're after HQ!
Get back!
Good luck, Hongo!
Get him, Gel Shocker Kid Corps!
Rider Transformation!
Rider Kick!
Centipede Punch!
Well?
My power is greater than Rider's!
Chairman!
Where are Naoki and Mitsuru?
Oh, you're both safe...
Listen, you'd better stay here for a while.
That's kind of you...
You guys...
Chairman... run!
Where should I run to, Taki?
They got to you, too... Chairman?
I am the Chairman.
But I'm not the Chairman
of the Kamen Rider Kid Corps,
but the Chairman of the
Gel Shocker Kid Corps.
Taki... you too will join
the Gel Shocker Kid Corps, too.
The Kamen Rider Kid Corps
headquarters will become
the headquarters of the
Gel Shocker Kid Corps.
Damn it...
Hongo...
Almost done...
What's the matter with you?
I'm so sorry...
Are you all right?
It's Mr. Hongo!
Mr. Hongo, I'm Tatsuji Yamanobu
of the Rider Kid Corps!
You're a part of the Corps?
Run! Gel Shocker is after me!
You need to run, understand?
Hang in there!
We can't leave an injured man behind!
Big Sis, let's take him to
the shed around back!
Sure.
- Hang in there!
- Run away... run away, quickly!
Tatsuji, hold him steady!
You should be safe here.
Sis... I don't think anyone followed him.
We need to call a doctor.
Who are you?
I'm looking for someone.
Did an injured man enter here?
No... no one's here!
Talk! Confess, or I kill the boy!
Tatsuji!
Let me go!
Sis!
Tatsuji!
Sis, don't tell them!
I'm a member of the Rider Kid Corps!
We fight for peace and justice!
Peace and justice?
Is that really more important
than your brother's life?
Wait!
Tatsuji!
Don't tell them!
Forgive me, but I can't just let you die!
No!
The shed out back.
Go!
I hate you, Sis!
Boy... I'll bring you to join
Gel Shocker's Terror School as well.
Hongo Takeshi... I'll burn you
to death inside that shed!
Centipede Tiger...
Withdraw!
An underground storehouse?
There's no way out like this...
Rider Transformation!
KAMEN RIDER
Tatsuji...
Tatsuji!
They burned him to death...
Forgive me, Mr. Hongo.
I wanted to save my brother so badly...
I was wrong.
Yumi!
You weren't wrong at all!
Who are you?
Human life is more important
than even peace and justice.
Don't worry.
I swear I'll bring Tatsuji back to you...
on my name as the Kamen Rider!
Kamen Rider...
Brilliantly done, General Black.
Hongo Takeshi has died in agony,
and we'll turn all of the Rider
Kid Corps into the Gel Shocker Kid Corps.
Centipede Tiger's Terror
School will train them well.
Then I'll send them to incite
destruction all over Japan.
As Gel Shocker combatants,
they must follow the rule
and take the gelper drug.
I've already seen to it.
I'm bringing the gelper
drug to the Terror School.
Gel Shocker's ironclad rule:
the gelper drug.
Once taken, it must be taken again
every three hours, or the user will die.
It's a horrifying drug used by
Gel Shocker to guard against betrayal.
Are the kids in here, then?
Repeat it one more time.
Always aim to penetrate
the heart of the adversary.
Good, well done.
Today's kill class is over.
With the new arrivals, our initial
class is up to fourteen members!
Now it's time to swear
your loyalty to Gel Shocker!
The first article of the
Gel Shocker Children's Charter?
Bring chaos and evil to Earth.
Peace and justice are our enemies.
Now, sit down and enjoy your lunch.
Does it contain the gelper drug?
Of course.
You have a special lunch today.
Thank you very much!
The gelper drug should put them to sleep
for an hour the moment it's taken...
Hey, are you sure you
put the gelper drug in there?
Yes!
Centipede Tiger...
What those children
are eating is mere flour!
There's no gelper drug in there!
Damn you, Kamen Rider!
Get them, child combatants!
Stop it! Stop it!
Get back!
Stop it!
Taki...
Take care of the children!
Now, get back!
Get back!
I am the Captain of the
Gel Shocker Kid Corps.
What did you say?
Taki... they've gotten to you, too?
Kamen Rider... you have no allies left.
Rider Corps HQ is now Gel Shocker Corps HQ.
Die!
Taki... stop this!
Stop it!
I see...
All right!
Taki!
Taki...
Die, Rider!
Taki!
Stop this, Taki!
Stop it!
Stop it, Taki!
Not one more move, Rider!
Look closely...
When I give the order, the children die!
Understood?
One word from me, and the
children will all jump off the cliff!
Are you willing to let that happen?
Wait!
Centipede Tiger... what is it you want?
Your life.
Damn you...
The children's lives are irreplaceable.
All right... do as you will!
Get him!
Now, combatants!
Rider can't fight back!
I'll deal the finishing blow!
I cannot die.
If I don't defeat Centipede Tiger,
he'll control the children forever!
Rider Hammer Kick!
Jump!
Jump! Jump, damn you!
Hold it!
You...
I feel like I was having a nightmare...
Captain Taki! Captain Taki!
Hey... are you all back to normal?
Yes!
Then where's Rider?
Tatsuji!
Where's the Kamen Rider?
Let's find him, everyone!
Okay!
The Kamen Rider died
destroying Centipede Tiger!
Gel Shocker must take
advantage of this opportunity.
Go, future hope of Gel Shocker!
Rider!
To save the Kamen Rider Kid Corps,
the Kamen Rider exploded with
the powerful enemy, Centipede Tiger.
Is Kamen Rider still
out there somewhere?
And what was the shadow that
we saw inside Gel Shocker's base?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassins sent by
Gel Shocker to kill our Kamen Rider
are the fake Kamen Rider
and the monstrous Flytrap Bee.
As an Anti-Shocker Alliance made up
of Gel Shocker's victims comes to light,
the Kamen Rider will face the Shocker
Rider in a deadly Cyclone match.
Join us next week for
"Evil! The Fake Kamen Rider"
Evil! The Fake Kamen Rider
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!