KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Kamen Rider Dies Twice!!
The new secret organization that took
Shocker's place, Geldam-Shocker,
under the leadership of Japan
Branch chief, General Black,
came after the Kamen Rider with
the powerful monster Ganikomoru.
It was a long, brutal battle.
But an aerial dogfight between
Kamen Rider and Ganikomoru,
ended with both plunging
into the ocean in flames.
Rider!
Kamen Rider's been killed!
Kamen Rider isn't dead!
He can't be dead!
That's right...
He might already be back at the Rider
Corps HQ, waiting for us to join him!
Right, Chairman?
Yes... that's right.
Of course that's right.
Anyway, girls, let's get back for now.
Welcome back.
How'd Kamen Rider do?
Where's Kamen Rider?
Hey, it's not true that
Kamen Rider is dead, right?
Hey, it's not true, right?
Right?
I guess he is dead...
Yeah.
Now, this is no time for crying.
We don't know for sure that he's dead.
We still have hope.
Listen to me.
Even if...
Even if the Kamen Rider is dead,
the Kamen Rider Kid Corps remains.
Be strong!
The chairman is right.
From now on, we need to fight the
terrible Gel Shocker with our power alone.
To protect peace and justice.
Now, cheer up!
Chairman.
Who sent that here?
That's a funeral arrangement...
What's this?
"Our deepest condolences
for the death of the Kamen Rider.
General Black, Geldam-Shocker
Japan Branch Head."
What a nasty thing to do!
Hey, do you hear that?
It's a time bomb! Get down!
Captain!
Mr. Taki!
Do you see now?
The terrible lengths to
which Gel Shocker will go...
Taki! Get a hold of yourself!
Hey! Taki!
Kamen Rider is gone,
and that impudent Rider Kid Corps
will be crippled by our present.
Now we just need to take advantage of that.
General Black.
I'm pleased to see that Gel Shocker
is off to an orderly start.
Of course we are.
But one potential liability remains.
The failed scientists
of the former Shocker, yes?
When will you rid us of them?
I plan to release them.
Release them, General Black?
Yes.
Release them.
But I'll do it in my own way.
Attention, scientists.
General Black has decided,
in his great magnanimity,
to release you all.
Release us? Really?
Do you mean it?
I can go home!
I can see my wife and child!
I'd resigned myself to execution...
You're really going to release us?
General Black does not lie.
You mean it?
In ten minutes,
you will leave here in a bus.
Prepare for departure immediately!
I don't believe it.
They wouldn't just release people
who know so many of Shocker's secrets.
This might prove useful, just in case...
It's been years since I
last saw the outside...
Yeah, you're right...
That blue sky and green mountains
are a sight for sore eyes!
You said it!
Are they really just going to send us home?
Hey, why are we stopping here?
Did the bus break down?
I know my way around a machine...
I can help if there's a breakdown.
It's not a breakdown.
We're running an experiment here.
An experiment? What kind?
Silence.
Gel Shocker is executing a deadly plan to
to kill all of the people
in the Greater Tokyo area.
You will be the guinea pigs for that plan.
No! That's not what we were promised!
That's right!
General Black said he was releasing us!
Precisely.
You were told you'd be released.
We never promised you
would be released alive!
Damn you! I won't go down that easily!
Gel Shocker cyborg, Scorpiontokagesu!
My body is filled with a gas that will
destroy all oxygen in the air instantly!
I will now perform the test!
Stop it! Stop it!
Help!
General Black.
The oxygen-killing gas that Shocker
developed has proved remarkably effective.
If we release fifty kilograms
of the gas into the skies above Tokyo,
we can kill ten million
people in an instant!
Silence.
I didn't have to wait for
your report to know that.
Check the bodies of the
deceased human guinea pigs,
then dispose of them.
One left, eh?
Hurry it up.
He's not here!
He couldn't have gotten far!
Find him!
He's not here!
Find him already!
Try the other way!
I won't die until I see my wife again.
Takeshi...
Are you really gone?
I put on a brave front for the others,
but I've really lost
the will to do anything.
My dreams, my hopes...
How do I find enough peace of mind
to continue the fight against evil?
Please, rest in peace.
Mine Hospital
This woman's husband, Shintaro Mine,
left for South America a year
ago to study contagious diseases there,
but has since gone missing.
He sent me a postcard after he arrived,
but I haven't heard anything since then.
Darling... where are you now?
What was that sound?
Talk!
Tell me!
Where is your husband, Shintaro Mine?
Mine Hospital
No one's followed me...
Gel Shocker must not have noticed my escape.
I should be safe...
No sign of him in the hospital.
I see.
So he hasn't arrived yet.
But we know he'll come soon enough!
Set up an ambush!
I knew he'd come!
The stubborn fool...
Run, darling!
Mine!
Don't run, or your pretty little wife dies!
You think that disguise has us fooled?
Have you lost your mind, Shintaro Mine?
I'm as sane as can be,
Scorpiontokagesu of Gel Shocker!
That voice...
Hongo! You survived?
I was wounded in the battle with Ganikomoru,
but Doctor Mine nursed me back to health.
Now's my chance to save her!
Rest easy. Your husband is safe!
Hongo Takeshi.
I feel very fortunate to run into
you here while cleaning up business.
When I kill you, the name of Scorpiontokagesu
will live forever in the annals of Gel Shocker!
Go, get to safety!
You won't escape!
KAMEN RIDER
Wait!
Gel Shocker... I will fight you!
It's Hongo! Get him!
Rider Transformation!
Try me!
Rider! You think you can
fight me in your condition?
I need a little more time to fight
this cyborg on equal footing...
It seems I've not fully recovered yet.
Rider, I've won!
Double Hold!
Scorpiontokagesu...
we'll finish this another day!
Is that true? You're sure of it?
Yoshiko, you're sure of it?
Yes, that's what he said.
So he really is alive!
Kamen Rider is alive!
That's great! Kamen Rider forever!
I had a feeling he'd be all right!
Oh, please! You were the
biggest wreck of all of us!
I heard you crying in
the bathroom, too, Yokko!
We need to tell the Chairman.
Where'd he go?
That's odd...
Is this Hongo? Taki here.
I have a message for the Kamen Rider
Kid Corps acting under Captain Taki.
General Black...
Tell the Kamen Rider this:
Gel Shocker currently holds
the lives of the 10 million residents
of Greater Tokyo in our hands.
We're about to remove all the
oxygen from the skies above Tokyo.
You have thirty minutes until this happens.
Please. That's impossible!
Ask Mine there if it's possible or not.
Darling...
Scorpiontokagesu's oxygen-killing
gas really is that powerful.
What's your message for Kamen Rider?
I have one condition:
The Kamen Rider must submit
to Gel Shocker's scalpel,
so that we can make him
a cyborg fully under our control.
This action will save
the lives of 10 million people.
We'll meet him at the Kamen
Rider training grounds.
The Kamen Rider training grounds...
That's it.
Maybe that's where Chairman Tachibana is!
Gel Shocker!
Damn you...
You already killed Takeshi...
What more could you want?
Don't play dumb with me.
Hongo Takeshi...
No, the Kamen Rider merely
let you think he was dead,
to try to get the drop on Gel Shocker.
But it didn't work.
He's on his way here!
What did you say?
Did you say that Hongo is alive?
Yes. He is.
We nearly fell for your little act,
which allowed him to almost foil
our Operation: Bloodless Tokyo Takeover.
Then Hongo is alive!
He's really alive?
Is now the time to celebrate?
Tachibana... we're going to
use you to finish off Hongo Takeshi!
Use me?
Now that I know that Hongo is alive,
I'll never let you use me.
I'll gladly die for our cause.
Yes... I'll rather kill myself!
I'll do it, to help Hongo!
I won't let you die that easily.
Taki Kazuya is approaching!
All right... capture him, too!
Taki!
The fool! Coming here
in complete ignorance...
What? He disappeared!
Find him!
Rider!
Taki!
What's the plan, Rider?
We prevent Scorpiontokagesu from
unleashing his oxygen-killing gas.
Get them!
Look out!
Taki! Look after Pops!
Kamen Rider... I'll unleash the
oxygen-killing gas right before your eyes!
I won't let you do it!
Kill him!
Rider, you'll never
interfere with us again!
Damn...
Watch closely!
The wind direction is perfect
to carry the oxygen-killing gas!
Soon, 10 million people will die!
Kamen Rider!
Scorpiontokagesu's weak point is his back!
Aim for his back!
Thank you!
Rider Reverse Kick!
Rider! I'm so glad you're safe!
Sorry I worried you, Pops.
It's all right.
I'm just glad you're all right.
Rider, you should thank
the Mine family, too.
Geldam-Shocker's monster Scorpiontokagesu
was defeated by the Kamen Rider,
but General Black already has
a terrifying new plan in the wings.
Ride on, Kamen Rider, Hongo Takeshi!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
A mysterious shadow creeps up on you.
I, the deadly Kurage Wolf, will use the
30,000 volts of electricity at my command
to turn Tokyo into an inferno.
Kamen Rider! I can't wait
to throw down with you!
The Monstrous Kurage Wolf
The Rush Hour of Terror
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!