KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Deadly Blood-Sucker!!
Give It Your All, Rider Kid Corps
What was that sound?
I was sure that I locked it...
Operating Room
What are you doing over there?
Answer me!
You want to see?
Someone! Someone come help!
No! No!
Everyone else in the hospital is dead.
Woman... you're the only one left!
Kamen Rider
Kid Corps Headquarters
Naoki and Mitsuru are now official
members of the Rider Kid Corps.
Kamen Rider Kid Corps
I pledge to fight Shocker,
to maintain peace...
and justice in our world!
Give it your best. Right?
Yes, sir!
Great.
Choco.
Here.
Captain Taki, if you please.
Captain? You're making me blush...
Don't be bashful!
Okay, then. My first act as Captain.
They're for sending messages
among the Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
Fly straight, okay?
Go!
Now we'll know the minute
Shocker tries something.
I think we're gonna be busy!
5668. Is that your registration number?
Let's do our best!
Hey, Tatsuo!
Yes?
Tatsuo, I'm heading out.
Dad, I'm a member of
the Kamen Rider Kid Corps!
Great.
I'm a security guard and you're a member
of the Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
Well, give it your best.
Where are you working tonight?
The West Tokyo Blood Bank.
Blood bank?
Yes.
Apparently, someone's been
stealing the precious blood
from blood banks in the area lately.
Take care, okay?
Now, I'll be fine.
You keep the doors locked
and take care, too, okay?
See you later!
All right, I'm off.
West Tokyo Blood Bank
Hey... why in the world would
someone attack a blood bank?
That's a very good question.
I hear the local hospitals are in trouble.
There's not enough blood for transfusions.
Yeah...
Who are you?
Give me the blood.
What are you talking about?
There's no way we can do that!
I want the blood in there.
What?
Hey, her shadow...
Why are you the only one without a shadow?
You saw it, then... did you?
A monster!
The blood! Give me the blood!
Damn!
Doctor!
Will this blood be enough
to perform as many cyborg
surgeries as we ask for?
If I may, Ambassador,
it's best to use young
blood in our surgeries.
The younger, the better.
We'd prefer children's
blood, if we can get it.
I see...
Children's blood, eh?
Excellent.
Shiraculas.
Acquire children's blood
by any means necessary.
Yes, Ambassador Hell.
When you drain a human's blood,
that person becomes your slave.
Do it!
See it done!
The vampiric Shiraculas
could suck human blood.
Shocker's human hospital
could then use that blood,
and the people he drained
would become his slaves.
He is a truly terrifying cyborg.
Okay, kids! Gather 'round!
We've got nice things for you!
What do you want?
How about a caramel?
Dad's been gone a long time...
He'd normally be back by now.
Bring more friends by to see us.
Okay.
Tatsuo!
Hey, it's you guys.
Let him take your blood, too.
My blood?
Yeah, you need to join us.
But we're already friends!
No, you need to join Shocker.
Shocker?
Hey, how do you know about Shocker?
Listen, Tatsuo! Get in the
van and let them take your blood!
No way! I'm out!
Wait up!
Wait!
Dad! Help me!
Tatsuo... let Shocker take your blood!
Dad, don't... don't tell me...
Tatsuo, listen to your father!
No! Stop it!
Let me go!
Tatsuo! Tatsuo!
Stop it!
It's a pigeon!
Huh? There's no message...
He must not have had time to put one on.
Yuri, investigate 5668.
Let's see... 5668...
Kamen Rider Kid Corps
member Tatsuo Ito.
He lives in Oki Apartments 1-4.
Here.
Let's check it out, Taki.
All right.
Mr. Ito!
Tatsuo!
Taki, keep an eye out.
Right.
Hey! What's going on? Hey!
I don't like this one bit...
It's like a ghost town in here.
What happened? Speak to me!
I'm scared! A monster...
A monster?
What are you doing?
Let me suck your blood!
Hongo!
KAMEN RIDER
Taki!
Where are you?
Show yourself!
Come out!
Hongo Takeshi... I will suck your blood!
What's going on?
What are you doing?!
A Shocker cyborg...
The vampiric Shiraculas!
Are you the one drinking the blood
of the people here and controlling them?
Shut up!
Taki!
Rider Transformation!
Curse you, Rider!
Takeshi.
Isn't there any way to fix Taki
and the people of the apartment?
If I could find the Shocker human hospital,
I'm sure they'd have an
antidote there, but...
Don't worry.
I'm sure Naoki and the others will
find the Shocker blood donation van.
Listen up.
We need to find the Shocker
blood donation van.
If you find it, contact HQ
with your pendants at once!
Okay, let's go!
You check in with Mitsuru.
We're going to do more searching.
Sure thing. Be careful!
There it is!
I just got word from Naoki.
I'll let Mr. Hongo know!
So frustrating!
I can't ride any further.
We lost it.
It's the Cyclone!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Kamen Rider! The Shocker van went that way!
Good. You've done well.
You've served the Kamen
Rider Kid Corps well.
Thank you.
Help Mr. Taki and the others quick, okay?
I will.
Go, Rider! Go!
Good luck!
I can't let them know I'm here...
All right...
There must be an antidote here.
Tell me... where is the
antidote to Shiraculas's venom?
I... I don't know!
The blood is moving...
Rider...
You'll never get that antidote!
Shiraculas!
Doctor! Take this and go!
Hold it!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
Hold it!
with its armies made of demons
Give that to me!
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
All right... Now!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider Dropkick!
Rider, Rider!
We, the Kamen Rider Kid Corps,
do solemnly swear to continue our service.
We swear!
The brave actions of Kamen Rider
and the Kamen Rider Kid Corps
put an end to Shocker's
bloodsucking monster, Shiraculas.
But the planet was not
yet free of Shocker's evil.
Go, Hongo Takeshi, the Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Did you hear that scream?
Next week, I'm gonna invite
you all to the house of terror.
You can enjoy watching the rose cyborg
Bararanga beat Kamen Rider to a pulp!
The Monstrous Poison Flower Bararanga
Secret of the Terror House
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!