KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Sludge Monster's
Terrifying Killer Smog
Hey... the cops are on their way.
Take us out already!
Didn't you hear me?!
Hey— What's wrong with you?
Damn...
Make preparations for the cyborg surgery.
We will now test the potency
of Utsubogames's killer smog.
Initiate the test!
Please! Please help me!
Help! Help!
Please, save me!
Turn on the ventilator.
Hey, guys! We're saved!
We're still alive!
What is the meaning of this?
Utsubogames's killer smog
should have the power
to reduce a human to
their bones in an instant!
Call in Utsubogames!
Why aren't you making use of
Gel Shocker's prized science, Utsubogames?
Sludge. They won't make me any sludge.
The most important ingredient
in my killer smog is sludge!
Wait a minute.
Look over there.
We've created plenty of sludge for you.
Yet you claim it's not sufficient?
General Black.
That sludge is far too
weak for my purposes.
To create my killer smog,
I require more filthy sludge,
like that found in Tagonoura
two years ago!
I see.
You're a cyborg created from a moray eel
born and raised in the
3000ppm sludge of Tagonoura,
fused with a sea turtle.
It's no wonder you require
only the finest sludge.
I fear we of Gel Shocker
cannot produce it,
as we lack the correct pollutants.
You expect me to accept
that, General Black?!
Calm down.
If we can't make it,
we'll have someone else do it.
Utsubogames, the pollution center...
Bring me someone from
the pollution center!
Mr. Okazaki,
burning the midnight oil, I see.
Yes.
I have a biochemist friend who's studying
the microbes that live in sludge.
His name is Hongo.
He asked me to run this experiment.
What could live in such
a filthy environment?
Well, just make sure
you turn everything off.
Sure.
Who are you?
What are you doing?!
Wh-Who are you?
Sludge... I want you to make me sludge!
Make me the most filthy sludge...
the sludge from Tagonoura two years ago.
What did you say?
You're a madman!
Who are you?
You possess an array of perfect pollutants.
It should be easy for you
to make the sludge.
- Come with me!
- I don't think so!
Municipal Pollution Center
Hey, Okazaki!
Hey!
What's wrong? Hey!
What happened here?
A monster... a monster...
A monster?
Hey! What's this about a monster?
Hey!
Could it be... Gel Shocker?
Is it finished yet?
It's finished now.
Good.
Utsubogames!
This is it!
This is what I've longed for!
Utsubogames, it's time to
put your power to the test.
Initiate killer smog experiment!
Preparations complete!
You're burning the fish!
Oh no!
Dear! I need help!
What's wrong?
Hey, speak to me! Hey!
Then... you think your friend Okazaki
was kidnapped by Gel Shocker?
Yes.
It's a messenger pigeon!
But what would Gel Shocker want with
a pollution researcher like Mr. Okazaki?
It's not hard to imagine.
They'd kidnap the prime minister himself
if he had something they needed.
Emergency! Emergency!
What's all the hubbub?
Dozens of human skeletons were
found at Shirayuri Apartments!
What?
A member of the Rider Kid Corps
found it on the way back from school.
Shirayuri Apartments, eh?
Let's go, Taki!
Yes? Headquarters here.
What? Mr. Okazaki?
Hello? Hongo here.
Help me, please! Gel Shocker is after me.
Gel Shocker is trying to destroy Tokyo,
using a terrible smog that
reduces humans to their bones.
What did you say?
Where are they?
Where are you right now?
Okazaki! Can you hear me?
Tell him! Tell him right now!
A broadcast tower in Tamakyuryo.
Who's there?
Nothing there...
Okazaki!
Hey! Are you all right?
Hongo, thank you for coming.
Of course.
Okazaki, you said Gel Shocker
was using killer smog to attack Tokyo.
What are you talking about?
I...
Hurry!
KAMEN RIDER
Utsubogames!
Rider Transformation!
Try me, Gel Shocker cyborg!
I was hoping you'd be here.
You'll be the first victim in my plan
to destroy Tokyo with killer smog!
Rider Throw!
Rider!
You're safe!
Rider, now's our chance.
I know the way into Gel Shocker's base.
Right here.
Quickly... before we're found! Hurry!
Mr. Okazaki, where is the way in?
I don't see anything...
Oh, it's here...
Your grave, that is!
- Okazaki!
- What did you say?
- Taki!
- Rider!
Damn...
You're General Black from Gel Shocker!
You've fallen into our trap, Kamen Rider.
Then Okazaki was... damn.
He's of no more use to us.
You can all die together.
Proceed!
Ready to die, are you?
Taki! Be careful!
That's killer smog!
So this is the end of the Kamen Rider.
Don't breathe! Hold your breath,
if you don't want to die!
There's just a lake on the other side.
All right... Rider Punch!
Taki, let's go!
Hold on tight!
Rider has escaped!
Why aren't you pursuing him?
Wait, Utsubogames.
We have another option.
What other option could
we have, General Black?
This.
Rider won't have noticed that I implanted
a sound wave receiver in Okazaki's brain.
Go to Hongo Takeshi's apartment!
This time, I'll finish
Rider once and for all!
Follow me!
The pollution center and Gel Shocker...
Hey, Hongo. Why do you think
Gel Shocker was after Mr. Okazaki?
I don't know.
I'm sure Okazaki will explain
everything once he's awake.
Anyway... be careful, Taki.
Gel Shocker will probably
come after him again.
"Wipe out anyone who
knows the secret," right?
Looks like he's awake.
Okazaki. Okazaki.
It's me.
Do you remember me?
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey!
Hongo!
There you are...
We were waiting for you!
This time,
I'll finish you all off together!
Get them!
Taki, they have the advantage here.
Run to the roof!
Right!
Hurry!
Hongo!
Damn you...
You did well.
But we really are finished with you now!
Take them away!
It seems it's finally the end
for you, Hongo Takeshi. Taki Kazuya.
Don't worry...
I don't expect this to
be enough to kill you.
I'll reduce you to your bones
with my killer smog!
When that's over, I'll execute
my plan to destroy Tokyo!
The wind seems to be
blowing the right way...
If I unleash my killer smog now,
the entire city will be destroyed.
Are you ready to die now, Hongo?
Hang on.
What in the world did you
kidnap Okazaki for?
I had him create the sludge
I needed to make my killer smog.
Now, Hongo... you will be the first to die!
Die!
Hongo!
He's gone!
Where have you gone, Hongo?
Let's go!
Kamen Rider!
Well? Can't blow that killer
smog anymore, can you?
Don't underestimate me, Rider!
Taki, you handle the combatants!
Right!
Damn...
Then I'll use my final weapon!
Rider Punch!
Rider Kick!
You're safe now!
Hey, speak to me!
Hey, what's going on with him?
Gel Shocker must have implanted a device
in his head to make him follow orders.
Then if we remove it with surgery...
Yeah, he'll be back to normal.
Good. That's a real relief.
The Kamen Rider, Hongo Takeshi, foiled
Utsubogames's terrifying killer smog plan.
But Gel Shocker's ambitions
would not be crushed so easily.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Listen, my Gel Shocker.
Let us celebrate the birth
of Gel Shocker's Washikamigiri.
General Black, I will use
my terrifying missile bombs
to see through our evil
Operation: Human Hunt.
Let's meet again next week for "The
Monstrous Washikamigiri's Human Hunt."
The Monstrous
Washikamigiri's Human Hunt
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!