KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Tokyo Penitentiary
This prison houses a man
serving a life sentence
for atrocious crimes such
as armed robbery and murder.
Hey, wake up. It's 6 o'clock.
Hey, No. 13.
That's your wake-up call!
Wake up already!
Shut up!
Why do I have to wake up
at 6 o'clock every day?
You piece of trash...
Don't complain.
I've been here for five years.
How long are you
going to keep me here?
I don't know.
But you're serving a life
sentence, remember?
What was that?
Damn you, open up!
You can't keep me here anymore!
Let me out!
Open up! Open up, damn you!
Open this door!
Don't you hear me, you bastard?!
Who are you people?
Come with us.
Come!
What? What are you doing?
Shocker has long sought a man
of your cold-hearted brutality.
What do you want with me?
To plunge the world into chaos
and bring humanity to heel.
Sounds fun to me.
I'll join you,
if you'll have me.
You will be made to bathe in poisonous
mushroom extract for one week's time.
Now, take him away.
And so, one week passed.
Poisonous Monster
Kinokomorg Attacks!
Your name will henceforth
be Kinokomorg.
What's this powder?
Don't touch it!
They're poisonous
mushroom spores.
Spores?
And anyone who touches
those spores...
Kimiko! Go for it!
Hiroshi, hang in there!
You're both doing great!
Keep it up!
Sorry about that!
I don't see it...
Where could it have gone?
There it is!
Hiroshi...
Someone, help!
Take her away.
Give Kimiko back!
Where could Kimiko
and Hiroshi have gone?
That mushroom monster...
It must be a member of Shocker.
Let's follow them back,
then let Hayato know.
Look! They're heading
for those power lines!
But that's a dead end!
It disappeared...
Where could it have gone?
What a mystery...
Let's go look!
The tire tracks end here...
Strange, isn't it?
There must be an
entrance somewhere...
But I don't see anything!
That's so strange...
You'll never see through
my special optical barrier!
Emergency!
Children, kidnapped?
Where did the truck go?
It passed under the power
lines, but...
It vanished into thin air.
It's true!
Contact with
Kinokomorg's spores
immediately paralyzes
the unfortunate victim.
If we bring those humans
back and modify them,
the world will soon
belong to Shocker.
It is Shocker that gave you
new life as a mushroom man.
I am grateful for it.
Use your great power to
bring us more allies!
It's easily done.
Leave it all to me.
I love to cause
suffering to humans!
Suzumi Ghost Parade
Come and see, come and see!
It'll be scary! Very scary!
Come, come!
Come see the scary ghost parade!
Hey,
what are you guys advertising?
A ghost parade!
So scary!
Come on! Come join us!
Hey, where are you doing it?
That way.
Let's go, everyone!
I knew it!
We're going pretty far out...
Is there really an
amusement park around here?
That's weird...
What are you doing?
It's a real ghost!
Run, everyone!
Help!
Help, someone!
Ow! Hey! Someone help!
Stop it! Stop!
Monster! Stop it! Monster!
Stop it!
Now, take the children.
Transform!
What have you done
with the children?
That truck there!
We have to save the children!
Hurry!
Kamen Rider!
Go, save the children... Hurry!
It's not over yet...
KAMEN RIDER
Sorry for the wait.
What happened?
Did you learn anything?
Not much, yet.
It seems to be a plant-based
toxin, at least.
Not a virus, then?
No.
But I can tell it's quite toxic.
Hey, Koike.
You're saying that even if they
survive, they'll never recover?
Hold on, now.
Give me some time
to run more tests.
But what will happen to the
children in the meantime?
The spores that attach to the people
are not yet sufficiently contagious.
Until our experiment succeeds,
we cannot have people learning
the secret of their paralysis.
You must retrieve
those children at once!
Hiroshi and Kimiko disappeared
from the tennis court.
And these children have been
unconscious all this time...
Just what is Shocker
plotting to use
these innocent children for?
Shocker! What are you
using the children for?
Well?!
This isn't over!
Hold it!
Strange...
What does Shocker want with
these paralyzed children?
These children might just hold
the key to solving all of this.
I've got it, Hayato.
What?
Have a look.
The children's bodies are
covered with a kind of poisonous
mushroom spore I've
never seen before.
Poisonous mushroom?
I see...
If those spores get any stronger,
they might be able to reproduce.
That would have dire
consequences for all of us.
I need to find a medicine to fight
it, and soon.
Meanwhile,
Shocker was infecting the children
with a new poisonous
mushroom extract.
These children's condition
will relapse in 24 hours.
Anyone who touches these children
will be infested with the spores,
and collapse one hour later.
This will lead to mass panic!
It wasn't there when I
watered it this morning...
Don't touch it!
What if it turns
out to be poisonous?
What's going on?
There's a strange
mushroom growing here.
Mushroom?
It's mechanical.
Shocker's been listening
to all our conversations.
Impressive, Ichimonji Hayato!
You caught on very quickly.
I'm willing to return the
children you're looking for.
What did you say?
I'm saying I'll
return the children.
Come and get them.
Name the place.
Wait, Hayato.
This could be a trap!
Are you afraid,
Ichimonji Hayato?
Name the place!
He's here!
He's taken the bait, then.
Help!
If you want us to spare the children,
you'll need to join Shocker!
You really think
I'll agree to that?
Would you rather watch
the children die?
Damn...
You fiends!
Transform!
Kamen Rider!
Get him!
Rider!
Rider! Where are the children?
Up there!
All right, let's go!
Right!
Come on, guys!
Hurry up!
Miss!
Hey!
We got the children out safe!
Get out of here, fast!
Rider!
Hurry!
Hold it!
I'll put an end to the
Kamen Rider at last!
Do it!
The Kamen Rider is in his
most dire straits yet.
Will Shocker finish him off?!
You need to get up,
to keep peace in our world!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is once again the poisonous
monster Kinokomorg.
Kinokomorg has used his poison to
make Ichimonji Hayato his prisoner.
Can our Kamen Rider
turn things around?
A stunning battle unfolds
in the creepy Shocker base.
Join us next week for
"Defeat Kinokomorg!"
Defeat Kinokomorg!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!