KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
The Eerie Spider Man
Not bad at all.
But I'm not sure you'll win the grand
prix with times like this, Hongo.
You're such a stickler,
Mr. Tachibana.
All right...
I'll go around again.
And I'll take ten more
seconds off my time!
Good.
He can be such a child...
But he's a first-rate rider.
No one would believe he's
also a leading scientist
at Johoku University's
biochemistry lab.
Never seen them around before...
A challenge, is it?
Okay...
They're clearly after me.
All right...
I'm going to find out
what you're up to.
What is this place?
Let me go!
Hongo Takeshi.
Welcome to Shocker!
Shocker?
What is he talking about?
Hongo Takeshi heard
the word "Shocker."
Shocker is an evil
organization whose influence
stretches to all
corners of the world.
For some reason,
they had brought Hongo Takeshi
to their secret base in
a remote area of Japan.
Shocker is a truly
terrifying organization,
which plans to alter humans in
countries all over the world,
and use them as pawns
for global domination!
We are seeking a man
with an IQ of 600
and superior athleticism.
You have the honor
of being chosen.
No... I'll never join Shocker!
It's too late to protest, Hongo.
You are all but a member
of Shocker already.
It has been one week since you
were brought here, unconscious.
Shocker's scientists have used
that time to alter your body.
You are a cyborg!
Cyborgs will control
the fate of this world,
and I will control the cyborgs!
The world will be
mine to command!
Cyborgs?
You expect me to believe that?
If you refuse to believe,
then I will show you!
Good.
I'm about to channel 50,000
volts through your body.
It would fry a normal man
to a crisp in an instant.
But your cyborg modifications have
imbued you with the power of wind.
Your body will not
suffer a single burn.
The only reason you feel pain
is because I have not completed
the alterations to your mind.
Once the brain alterations are complete,
and you become a slave to your orders...
Then, you will be a
true cyborg of Shocker!
I'd rather die than serve you!
That's what they all
say, at first.
In time, they become
grateful to serve Shocker.
Begin the alterations
to Hongo Takeshi's mind.
The generator's been destroyed!
Find the one
responsible at once!
You're...
Doctor Midorikawa!
I was sure you'd gone missing...
Shocker is behind it all.
Oh, no... we have to escape!
But how...?
There's an exit above
us, through the ceiling.
We can't break through.
It's too high!
Hongo. You snapped those
iron chains effortlessly.
That's an impossible act for a human...
but you are a cyborg.
Ironically, Shocker's experiment to
imbue your body with the power of wind
has charged your body
with devastating strength.
Impossible...
You can do it now,
I promise you.
We have no time to lose.
Try it, Hongo!
He's gone!
He escaped out the ceiling!
Hongo! Hongo!
Hongo...
All who betray Shocker must die.
That includes your
only daughter.
-My daughter... Ruriko!
-Die, Midorikawa!
Please, don't kill my daughter!
It can't be...
KAMEN RIDER
Johoku University
School of Literature
You scared me!
Wait up!
What's wrong, Ruriko?
You look kind of distracted...
Is anything wrong?
Hey, Hiromi...
do you see anyone following me?
No one.
You're being weird, Ruriko.
I feel like someone's been watching
me these past three days...
Midorikawa's daughter Ruriko
and her friend have passed by.
Good.
Use the daughter to lure
out the good doctor.
Where shall we strike?
At the café where
Ruriko works...
Or on her way there, perhaps.
Hiromi...
Hey.
- There you are!
- Boss!
I was so scared...
Scared of what?
We saw these strange men...
Strange men?
I don't see anyone.
It's not nice to
tease your elders.
Get on in.
I'll take you right to the café.
I heard your
father's been found.
My father?
Here's the location.
Later!
What are you doing?
This isn't her!
The one that left in the car...
I knew my father was alive.
Toura Pier, warehouse 50...
Ah, do you think I've
done the right thing?
If anything were to
happen to Ruriko, I...
Don't worry.
You absolutely did
the right thing.
You're the only one who can testify to
the world about Shocker's terrible plan!
I know. I know that...
But I feel so powerless
to fight them...
I'll be doing everything I
can, too.
I will fight to
liberate humanity!
Doctor... you must have
more faith in yourself!
Doctor.
Your daughter will be here soon.
Buck up, all right?
That's right...
I have many times the
strength of a normal man.
And I can't control
it, either...
The cyborg part of me
that's no longer human.
Doctor.
Will I...
Will I remain a cyborg
for the rest of my life?
I'm so sorry, Hongo...
This is all because I
chose you to help me...
You recommended me to Shocker?
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Hongo.
Who is he arguing with?
Someone who didn't know me might think
I was an alien from a distant planet.
But at least...
The doctor and Mr. Tachibana
will understand me.
Hongo! Can't breathe...
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor!
What are you doing to him?
Doctor! Doctor!
Father!
Doctor!
Doctor...
Father!
Look out!
It's not safe here.
We need to go!
I saw you strangle
my father to death...
Now you want to save me? Why?
No! I'm not the
one who killed him!
I heard you arguing with him.
And I saw what I saw!
I saw you kill my father!
Yet you still claim
it wasn't you?
It wasn't me.
I tried to save him!
Please, trust me.
Your father and I
are on the same side.
Murderer!
There you are...
This time, I will finish you!
Is she all right?
She's unconscious.
Please take her.
Hongo Takeshi is putting his life
on the line to fight Shocker.
Doctor Midorikawa,
who understood him and helped him,
is now dead by Shocker's hands.
And the doctor's only daughter, Ruriko,
believes Takeshi is the murderer.
Will he ever be able
to prove his innocence?
More of Shocker's terrible
monsters are waiting in the wings.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the terrifying Bat Man.
The monstrous Bat Man spreads his
terrifying virus among the people.
As sparks crackle in the night
sky, how will our Kamen Rider fare?
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Terrifying Bat Man."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!