KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Reborn Cobra Man
We Buy Dogs and Cats Ayakoji
Biological Research Facility
Ayakoji Biological
Research Facility
Right this way.
Next, please.
Next.
Next, please. Come in.
This way, we can prepare the
animal blood to revive Cobra Man,
while choosing the best of the
humans to become combatants.
Cobra Man.
I will restore the body that
was damaged by Kamen Rider.
Cobra Man targeted the Ministry
of Finance's gold reserves,
but failed due to the
Kamen Rider's interference.
Cobra Man,
injured by the Kamen Rider,
was about to receive surgery that
would bring him back to life.
You'll pay soon, Kamen Rider.
What's the matter here?
Oh, Toru's dog went missing.
Dog?
Oh, that reminds me...
There's a place that's paying
a lot of money for dogs.
One of our customers
mentioned it.
You think someone stole
Toru's dog to sell it to them?
If they did...
That's so sad for Toru.
Isn't it?
The place
buying dogs is the Ayakoji
Biological Research Facility.
I've seen the signs.
Ayakoji Research Facility?
Hey there.
What are you crying about, Toru?
Come on, Toru.
I'll buy you a treat.
Thanks again.
Oh, not at all.
Toru's such a good kid.
Well... with his mother gone,
it can be hard to keep up with him.
You have to work on
Sundays, too?
Yes.
Well... I'm afraid detectives
don't get days off.
And with a new rash of
mysterious disappearances,
I don't even have time to sleep.
Mysterious disappearances?
Yes.
We're no longer
buying dogs and cats
I guess this is the place
that's buying dogs...
That's right...
maybe my dog is here, too!
Toru, what are you doing here?
Go home right now.
Dad,
I think Taro might be in here.
If he is, I'll bring him back.
You mean it?
Yes.
Toru, have I ever lied to you?
Go on, now.
Excuse me. I'm with the police.
I want to talk to
whoever's in charge here.
Come in.
Wait here, please.
Everyone who disappeared sold
an animal to this facility.
I don't like it.
There's something more
to this laboratory...
Rise, Cobra Man.
You are restored.
Cobra Man.
I have brought you back to life.
You died in your fight
with Kamen Rider,
but I have breathed your
devil's life back into you.
Now, rise!
Rise, and fight Kamen Rider!
All of you.
Congratulations on Cobra
Man's successful surgery.
Just today, a large amount of gold bullion
Ministry of Finance
was transmitted from all over
Japan to the Japan Gold Repository.
A few days from now,
a ship called the President will arrive in
Yokohama Harbor and
take that gold away.
It's valued at billions of yen.
You must steal that gold.
If you fail,
you will pay for it with your lives.
This is the law of Shocker.
I pray for your success.
Dad's been gone a while...
A monster!
Here.
You're saying you saw a monster
at Ayakoji Research Facility?
Yeah.
I think it ate my dad.
Could Shocker have
created a new cyborg?
Welcome, Mr. Hongo.
Takeshi.
What'll it be? Coffee?
Takeshi, perfect timing.
Now, begin the experiment.
Don't kill me!
Cobra Man.
These men are garbage,
unfit to become Shocker combatants.
They're perfect test
subjects for you.
And to test your
power, as well...
You came right to us, Detective.
Now die,
to test Cobra Man's power!
I knew Shocker was
involved in this!
Die!
Now, Cobra Man...
Begin the test!
Please, don't kill me!
Don't kill me!
The experiment is successful.
Who... Who are you people?
Now, talk!
Where is Detective Koga?
In... the forest around back...
What?
KAMEN RIDER
Now, this man!
Please... don't do this...
Fix your aim!
Hold it!
Cobra Man... you're alive?
Kamen Rider.
Shocker's power knows no limits.
This time, I will perform
the surgery on your brain...
And I will bring you
into Shocker's fold!
Burn the Rider to death!
Mr. Koga!
Hey, Mr. Koga!
The culprit...
where did the culprit go?
Mr. Koga... you can't pursue
a culprit in your condition.
Come on.
But...
Come on,
let's get you to the hospital.
No...
I must capture the culprit!
Mr. Koga! Mr. Koga, wait!
M-Monster...
Mr. Koga!
Good grief.
What a difficult detective!
Look at my face!
This is all your fault!
Die!
Die, you wretch!
Damn you!
Wait!
Ritsuko Ayakoji...
Your usefulness is at an end.
What did you say?
I was merely using your skills
to bring Cobra Man back to life.
You tricked me...
Damn you!
But it's too late
to save you now.
Cobra Man, kill that woman!
Cobra Man, the President has
arrived in the Port of Yokohama.
The gold will be brought there tomorrow
from the Japanese Gold Repository.
Attack it, as we planned.
What?
Mr. Koga went to
the gold repository?
Yes.
We tried to stop him, but...
Toru said that some gold
was being transferred today.
I'll bet you Shocker
revived Cobra Man
to get at that gold.
Takeshi, you mean...
There's no way I'll let
Shocker get away with it.
Looking good.
Anything out of the ordinary?
No, sir.
Mr. Koga.
We won't have a repeat of last
time, will we?
No need to worry.
We have police stationed
along the route,
and the President in
the Port of Yokohama has
been cordoned off,
with lots of security.
Mr. Koga.
Hey there, Hongo.
Could I have a word, Mr. Koga?
Excuse me for a minute.
How can I help you?
Mr. Koga.
Shocker is after this gold.
You should call
off the transfer.
Shocker?
What's that?
A secret organization
bent on world domination.
Hongo, what in the world
are you talking about?
Our department hasn't
heard anything about this.
But I...
Look... even if an organization
like that did exist,
the Japanese government won't be
cowed by some petty band of thieves.
If we canceled the transfer, the Japanese
police would become a laughingstock.
Just leave this to us.
Nobody knows about
Shocker's existence.
Fighting Shocker by myself
is the only path I have.
With security like this,
nobody can interfere.
Don't you worry.
On the honor of the Tokyo Police
Department, I'll get that gold to Yokohama.
When, where,
and how will Shocker attack?
I knew it.
No sign of this 'Shocker' at all...
Hongo must enjoy scaring people.
What's the matter, Mr. Koga?
You're talking to yourself...
Oh, I was just saying that
the mission's going smoothly.
True.
Wow, that's broken!
Hurry it up!
Hold it!
The Kamen Rider! Get him!
Rider Fight!
Rider Throw!
Hey there!
Dad got a commendation
from the commissioner.
Hey, you don't need to say that.
So cute!
My, my, a commendation!
Isn't that nice?
Right this way.
A coffee for Mr. Koga.
Here you are.
Shocker never showed
up in the end...
But I just can't figure it out.
Who got the bullion
off the boat?
I assumed it was you, Mr. Koga.
Don't be ridiculous!
I got knocked out by
the boat explosion!
Let's tell everyone it was
me, then.
Please, you couldn't
do something like that.
But who could it have been?
Hongo Takeshi saved Japan from
Shocker's evil once again.
Will he ever get to be
a normal human again?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Gebacondor.
He drinks the blood of young women and
he exceeds Rider in destructive power.
One by one, white wedding
dresses are stained in blood.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Blood-Sucking
Monster Gebacondor."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!