KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
In the dark corners of this
peaceful-looking town
lurks the evil organization, Gel Shocker.
It is the mission of Hongo Takeshi, the
Kamen Rider, to expose and eliminate them.
It is for this reason that
Gel Shocker considers Kamen Rider
to be their greatest enemy.
General Black has once again
received the order to kill Rider.
What cyborg monster will
he choose to send today?
Rider in Peril!
Isogin Jaguar's Hellish Trap
Isogin Jaguar.
Kill Hongo Takeshi, the Kamen Rider.
That is the reason we
made you what you are.
Killing the Kamen Rider will
bring joy to Gel Shocker.
It will bring joy to me, General Black!
And, Isogin Jaguar...
It will bring joy to you, too!
Isogin Jaguar... kill the Kamen Rider.
Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him...
You must kill the Kamen Rider!
You exist to kill the Kamen Rider!
Kill him!
No... I can't do it!
I can't kill anyone!
I could never do something so awful...
I can't do it!
Kill him! You must kill him!
Kill him!
You are no ordinary human.
You are a cyborg we
created... Isogin Jaguar!
Yes. You are Isogin Jaguar!
Now you must go!
Go forth, and kill Kamen Rider!
You saw me, did you?
No, I didn't!
How many days has your
father been missing, now?
Ten days now.
We've done everything to find him,
but we haven't found
the smallest trace...
Cheer up already, Maki.
Mr. Taki of the Rider
Corps will be here soon!
There he is!
It took you long enough!
Hey, Choco.
You said something was up?
Wait. This isn't a date, is it?
Don't be stupid.
This is no time for jokes.
This is my friend, Katsuragi Maki.
Her father went missing ten days ago!
Missing?
Any idea where he went?
Mr. Taki.
Maki lived alone with her father...
Just leave it to me.
We'll get the entire Kamen
Rider Kid Corps mobilized and...
- Hurry!
- Mr. Taki!
Mr. Taki, hang in there!
Send a pigeon back to HQ!
Right!
Chairman!
What's all the hubbub, now?
Choco... Choco's friend
was taken by Gel Shocker!
What?
Damn... this is terrible.
And right in front of Taki, too...
Yuri, Yokko, Naoki, Mitsuru!
Request aid from the Kamen
Rider Kid Corps at once!
Right!
What should the message be?
"Find a red-and-yellow rally car."
Right!
Find a red-and-yellow rally car.
Is that you, Takeshi?
Gel Shocker kidnapped a friend of Choco's.
Taki is tracking them via helicopter.
Takeshi, we're counting on you, too.
Roger.
It's the red-and-yellow rally car!
What?
You found the red-and-yellow rally car?
It's Chiba-bound along Route 128!
Understood.
Damn... that's in the other direction!
There it is...
It won't get away!
That fool Hongo Takeshi didn't
realize this was a trap...
That we intentionally used an eye-catching
car that even a child could recognize,
and drove in a way to call attention!
This isn't good... he's going to lose me.
Rider Transformation!
KAMEN RIDER
Who are you?
Kamen Rider!
I am a Gel Shocker cyborg... Isogin Jaguar!
You... return Maki!
What was that?
Isogin Jaguar Feeler Camouflage!
Taste the poison of Isogin Jaguar!
Isogin Jaguar Killer Feeler Hold!
Well, Rider?
Are you impressed by my power?
Die, Rider!
Damn... I was hoping I could find that
rally car around here, but...
There it is!
Maki!
Hongo!
Stay back! That's a fake!
Maki is here with me!
Dad!
What?
Hongo!
Hey...
Maki...
Hongo... Hongo!
Don't worry. I'm right here.
Rider!
Taki... I see Maki is safe!
Yes... and we also found her father.
Damn!
Rider, listen to me!
- What is it, Taki?
- That's...
That's my father right there!
What did you say?
Damn you, Rider!
Rider!
I see... I understand now!
The transformation device is in the head.
If I can just destroy it...
Rider Point Kick!
Dad!
Stay back! He's not your father anymore!
It's not safe! Stay back!
Kill the Kamen Rider!
Kill him!
You must kill him!
Dad!
Dad...
Maki!
- Dad!
- Maki!
- Maki...
Maki...
Dad...
The horrors wrought by Gel Shocker
are the same as the horrors wrought by war.
They'll happily tear apart
families if it serves their ends.
Kamen Rider...
keep fighting! Save them all!
Keep fighting, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Listen, my Gel Shocker.
Let us celebrate the birth of Utsubogames.
Utsubogames...
Use your killer smog
and steel-cracking shell
to destroy Rider!
Gentlemen... let us
meet again next week,
for "The Sludge Monster's
Terrifying Killer Smog."
The Sludge Monster's
Terrifying Killer Smog
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!