KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Jump! Jump, damn you!
Hold it!
You...
In order to save the Rider Kid Corps,
the Kamen Rider sacrificed himself
to destroy the powerful Centipede Tiger.
He hasn't been seen since.
Is Kamen Rider still out there somewhere?
Evil!
The Fake Kamen Rider
H-Help me!
I don't want to die!
It's too late for that!
You are needed to test the power
of the latest Gel Shocker cyborg!
Die, dissolved by my flytrap fluid!
My abilities are flawless!
Are they really, Flytrap Bee?
Can you beat me?
You've shown yourself, Kamen Rider!
Go on and try me.
Rider Kick!
That's enough, you two.
The experiment is over!
Flytrap Bee...
If the two of us work together...
no one on this planet
can hope to stop us.
Even if the real Kamen
Rider is still alive!
My leader.
The Shocker Rider is ready for action.
I'm very pleased, General Black.
Give orders to the Shocker Rider.
What orders would those be?
There's been a group trying to track
and stop us since our Shocker days.
You must destroy that group.
The Anti-Shocker Alliance, you mean?
They'll likely try to join hands
with the Rider Kid Corps.
If we send the Shocker Rider at them,
he'll destroy them with ease.
General Black.
The computer has a report.
All right, put it through.
Urgent situation in process.
Anti-Shocker Alliance computer
has discovered our leader's identity.
General Black, delete that data!
Sir, I will deploy the
Shocker Rider at once.
Well, Naoki?
Any word on Kamen Rider?
No...
But let's get looking again.
We can't give up!
I'll stop by HQ.
Me, too.
They might have heard from him by now!
Yeah!
Kamen Rider
Kid Corps Headquarters
Hey, you guys.
We want to help.
Sure.
Don't just stand there, help us out.
Chairman. Have you heard anything yet?
It's been a whole week...
Cheer up, now.
Kamen Rider will return to us.
Chairman!
What is it? Word from Rider?
No, but it might be related.
Well, out with it!
We got a call.
They want to pass information
about Gel Shocker to Kamen Rider.
Okay, I'll take it.
They already hung up.
They just said to come to
Takeyama Pier by 10:00 AM.
It's the time they gave us...
Are you Mr. Tachibana Tobei?
You have information on Gel Shocker?
Our group wants to meet you.
Any proof that you aren't with Gel Shocker?
What are you doing?
Gel Shocker!
They're constantly tailing members
of the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
Anti-Shocker Alliance?
Yes. I'll explain the rest later.
Please, get in the car.
I've brought Mr. Tachibana.
You're the Anti-Shocker Alliance?
I'm Seiichiro Kogure.
Gel Shocker is after us.
Forgive us for dragging you
out to a place like this...
Our organization is worldwide.
I never knew...
Its members are victims of Gel Shocker
from all over the world.
They killed my only son.
They killed my mother, as well.
Well, allies are always welcome
in the battle for justice.
I'll gladly work with you.
What did you want with me?
Our computer has identified
the identity of Gel Shocker's leader.
Their leader's identity?
The data will arrive at Shimoda
in Izu at 4:00 this afternoon.
If we go, Gel Shocker will track us.
That's why we were hoping the Kamen
Rider could bring the data to us.
The Kamen Rider?
Mr. Tachibana. I beg you.
Room 406 in Hotel Masaki in Shimoda.
I'm staying there under
the name Ishigami Chie.
Pops.
I'd love to agree,
but we don't know whether
Kamen Rider is dead or alive.
I know that.
But I couldn't tell them that
the Kamen Rider is missing.
If I had, one of them would go.
Then Gel Shocker would kill that person.
Are you sure that the Kamen
Rider is never coming back?
If we want to get to Shimoda
by 4:00, we'd better leave soon.
All right. I'll go.
I'm on my way.
Will you be all right by
yourself, Mr. Taki?
No way out but through.
Taki. Good luck!
Right.
Rider!
I figured this would happen!
I'm sorry to worry you all.
I thought it best to go into hiding until
the injuries Centipede Tiger gave me healed.
So you're all better?
I'm fine.
That means Mr. Taki doesn't have to go!
Where were you going?
Tsumekizaki Lighthouse in Izu.
I see. I'll accompany you.
I'll hear the rest later.
Great.
Well, that's a load off my mind!
Yeah!
467.
148.
If you would.
I will.
Is the identity of Gel Shocker's
leader really in here?
Don't do it, Taki.
Our job is just to deliver it.
But...
Gel Shocker combatants!
Rider, take care of the case.
Got it.
Hurry!
KAMEN RIDER
Hotel Masaki
They're late...
They should have been here by now...
It's no use.
The Kamen Rider isn't coming!
It can't be...
You ridiculous woman!
What a great fool you were
to pit yourself against Gel Shocker!
How did you know I was here?
The Kamen Rider told me!
The very same Kamen
Rider you put your faith in!
No!
Hongo Takeshi!
I see... you survived, did you?!
As long as Gel Shocker
survives, I'll never die!
Die!
Get to safety!
Rider Transformation!
Listen to me, Rider!
The Shocker Rider has
already made his move!
What? Shocker Rider?
Where is he?
- Help!
- Who can say?
I'll finish things with you later!
Kamen Rider...
You're safe now.
I knew you'd come.
Where's the data?
What data?
What?
You traitor...
You can't fool me any longer.
The Kamen Rider really
is working with Gel Shocker!
No!
I see...
The one who went to get the
data was my exact double...
The Shocker Rider!
There are two Kamen Riders?
You're saying it was the fake
who went to get the data?
I will prove my innocence, I swear.
If he isn't stopped,
all our efforts will be in vain.
I won't let it happen.
I swear, I will retrieve that data!
Once I get rid of this,
the identity of Gel Shocker's leader
will remain a secret forever!
Rider!
What are you doing there?
Well... I just wanted to know their
leader's identity as soon as possible.
Earlier, you told me not to bother!
Now, now. Let's take that
to the Anti-Shocker Alliance first.
I can't let you do that.
My mission is to destroy
the contents of this tube.
Rider... have you gone mad?
I'm perfectly sane!
Rider! Don't tell me...
Kamen Rider!
Shocker Rider!
It's time to expose you!
But can you, Rider?
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
We will erase the ally
of justice, Kamen Rider,
and let the Shocker Rider take his place!
The name Kamen Rider
will forever be cursed!
Sorry to disappoint, but the name
Kamen Rider will never be disgraced!
It's two against one!
Victory is ours!
Rider Kick!
Now!
Our Kamen Rider faces
an unprecedented trial
against Gel Shocker's monstrous
Flytrap Bee and the Shocker Rider.
Can he make it out alive?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
In their quest for world domination,
Gel Shocker has created six Shocker
Riders identical to the Kamen Rider.
Their objective is to recover
the data on their leader's identity
from the Anti-Shocker Alliance.
The first and second Riders
face a battle to the death
against the Shocker Riders
in a desolate savanna.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider!
The 8 Kamen Riders
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!