KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Fire-Breathing Caterpillar Monster
Dokugander
Professor, the paths split up
here and meet up further on.
I'll take this path, then.
Sounds fine.
But if you find any rare insects,
don't keep them to yourself!
See you.
Professor,
watch your step, okay?
Don't you worry, now!
This is spectacular!
What an unusual insect!
A caterpillar like that
would be a major discovery!
H-H-Help me!
H-Help me!
Okay, let's take a short break.
The air really is
nice in the mountains!
But all the dirt and
dust is ruining my looks!
Come on, don't sweat it.
That's not nice.
You just don't understand women's
feelings, Mr. Chairman.
There's a river over there.
Let's sit by the
edge for a while!
Yeah.
The barbarians can stay here.
What kind of way is that for the
Racing Club's first students to act?
I'm not sure washing their
faces will do much for them!
This way.
Hup.
Through the glow of the fireflies
Oh?
I hear singing.
And the snow out the window
It's "The Glow of the Fireflies."
We've spent days and months
The graduation song? Why now?
Motosugi Elementary School
East Valley Branch
Reading and reading
After the passage of years,
that cedar door opens
And this morning
We make our final goodbye
They all look so sad...
It doesn't look like
a graduation to me...
Well, this is goodbye.
Take care on your way
home, all right?
- Goodbye, Teacher!
- Goodbye! Goodbye!
Take care on your way
home, all right?
Goodbye, Teacher!
Goodbye!
Ma'am... what's going on here?
Did you girls come here
to look at the waterfall?
No, we're on a drive.
That's fine,
but just stay away from the waterfall.
Why?
Anyone who goes to the
waterfall goes missing!
Really?
Hey!
We all decided to abandon
the village tomorrow!
Why are you abandoning
the village?
We've had enough of
this awful place!
People from the village
keep disappearing,
and there's all these sightings
of a giant caterpillar...
I'm leaving this village
as soon as I can.
A giant caterpillar?
Yes.
What are you people
even doing here?
You should get your things packed up
soon, too, ma'am.
Is there really a
giant caterpillar?
I haven't seen it myself,
but the people of the village
say it's as big as a man,
and that it eats people.
Should we go and look?
Wait for me, everyone!
Be careful!
Wait just a minute.
What's the matter?
Have you seen a man about 50 years
old, wearing a white hunting jacket?
No, I haven't. Have you?
No. Let's go.
What's taking those
girls so long?
I'd better go looking for them.
Hey, it's the girls!
You left us waiting
long enough...
Oh, excuse me...
So it wasn't our
little firebrands, eh?
But they really have
been gone a long time...
I met some girls heading
for the waterfall.
Did you? Thank you.
So irresponsible...
Let's get the heck
outta this village!
You people should leave this
mountain as soon as possible!
Sorry,
but we're waiting for someone.
Sorry to tell you,
but they're not coming back.
The caterpillar monster's eaten
them, I tell you!
Caterpillar monster?
There's a huge caterpillar
stalking the village.
It eats people!
We're all working on
abandoning the village now.
You'd better hurry!
What nonsense...
Hayato.
Yeah...
let's head for the waterfall.
It's nice and cold.
You think there could be a
Shocker base in the area?
You think there's really
a man-eating caterpillar?
What do you think?
Well,
I certainly hope there isn't...
I feel like the weather's
turning strange...
Perfect time for ghosts...
Monster!
What is it? Where?
Oh, please.
It's just a caterpillar.
Don't scare us like that.
A third-degree black belt
shouldn't startle so easily.
But I just hate caterpillars...
Oh, please.
It's just a little bug...
Hello there, dears.
Might I ask what
you're doing here?
We found a caterpillar,
that's all.
All that fuss over one
little caterpillar?
Don't be rude.
I can't help not liking them.
Do you have a problem with that?
I do beg your pardon.
But, my dears...
There's a man named Tachibana
waiting for you just down the road.
Oh, of course.
We totally forgot!
No need to worry.
He's waiting for you in
the nearby mountain lodge.
Mountain lodge?
You took so long to return that
he went to the mountain lodge
intending to use their
phone to call the police.
Oh, I see...
Will you show us the
way, please?
It would be my pleasure to
escort such fine ladies.
Follow me.
Mari!
Hiromi!
Mr. Koizumi!
There's a caterpillar monster!
Okay, I'll go this way.
You go that way.
Right.
Strange...
Where did that man head off to?
He disappeared the moment
he brought us here.
Don't you find it strange?
It's locked from the outside!
What?
Really?
What's going on here?
Shocker!
You've interfered in Shocker's
plans for the last time.
The Kamen Rider will
surely follow you here.
Then we will kill him.
Mr. Chairman!
Sorry... they got me, too!
Now only one remains...
The Kamen Rider.
Once he arrives,
you will all be sent to hell together.
KAMEN RIDER
Mr. Koizumi!
It's the professor's camera!
Mr. Ichimonji,
I know this is his camera!
He's been here!
Mr. Yoshioka.
Is it possible Professor Koizumi
lost his footing and
fell from that cliff?
I'm going to investigate.
Right.
Will you be all
right by yourself?
I'll go get help!
Boss, Ichimonji Hayato
is in the area.
Good. Hold them in
the underground cell.
There you are, Shocker...
Transform!
Are you leading
Shocker this time?
Emergency! Is anyone here?
Is anyone here?
What's going on?
My professor fell
from the waterfall.
Please,
won't someone come with me?
What? Again?
I'm sorry, but we're the only
ones left in the village.
What did you say?
We need to leave the village
fast, Teacher!
What's the matter?
There's a large,
man-eating caterpillar.
Then what that man
said was true...
Get in there. Go on.
Rider will come to save us.
I know it.
But how do we tell
him where we are?
As long as he finds my pipe...
My pipe has a powerful
transmitter installed in it!
Where is Mr. Tachibana?
Why should I tell you?
You'll soon be dead,
at the hands of Dokugander!
It's a transmitter...
If I trace it back,
I'll find Mr. Tachibana.
Inside the waterfall, then?
Prepare to execute the hostages.
We'll give the Kamen
Rider a real show.
Hey... time to come out.
Damn you, Hayato...
why didn't you notice my pipe?
Stupid fool...
Get out.
Damn!
You've fallen for my trap...
Now, Kamen Rider,
I've prepared quite a show...
Rider!
Rider! I'm sorry!
Rider...
you can stand there and watch.
Stop this! Stop it!
Rider... surrender to us!
Come on, Mari!
Now, get him!
Come on, let's go!
Take this! And this!
Rider Kick!
That's...
Did Dokugander
enter a cocoon?
Come and see us again!
Thank you for everything.
Take care, take care.
We'll be back some time!
Goodbye!
Bye!
Okay, let's go!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Goodbye!
Bye-bye! Goodbye!
Come back soon! Goodbye!
Come back some time, mister!
Goodbye!
That's that Shocker cocoon...
I can't thank you enough.
I'm so sorry to hear
about Professor Koizumi.
Let me take you to the
foot of the mountain.
Thank you.
Shocker's cyborg, Dokugander,
had transformed into a giant cocoon.
What terrible power will that
cocoon unleash on Kamen Rider?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Dokugander,
whom he faces in Osaka Castle.
After his loss to Kamen Rider,
he escaped in a large cocoon,
but appears once more in Osaka
as an adult poison moth monster.
A deathmatch unfolds in Osaka Castle
between Rider and Dokugander.
Join us next week for "Dokugander,
Battle at Osaka Castle!"
Dokugander,
Battle at Osaka Castle!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!