KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Wolf Man's
Killer Party
Jingle bells! Jingle bells!
Jingle all the way!
Hey, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Hey, say it!
Jingle bells! Jingle bells!
Jingle all the way!
What is it?
Gotta pee...
Oh, hell...
Boy, it's getting cold...
Better go, better go...
Let's put this here...
Hey, Igami!
I'm coming with you, Igami!
Where'd he go?
I don't see him...
That hurt!
What's all this?
What's the matter with you?
What happened to you, now?
Get a grip already!
S-Save me!
Don't let him escape!
He's a valuable test subject!
Colonel Zol, sir.
As you can see, the Wolf Virus
has turned him into a wolfman.
Silence!
If we let this test wolfman
run loose in the city,
the Kamen Rider will get
wind of Operation: Wolf.
Dispose of the body at once!
A present for his
child, perhaps?
That wolfman took
my doll away...
Wakakusa Nursery School
There we go.
Almost done.
They're all good kids.
I'm sure Santa will bring
them wonderful presents.
What do you want, son?
I'd rather meet Kamen
Rider than Santa Claus.
Me too!
Kamen Rider, eh?
Okay! Big Brother Taki
will bring him by.
Right, Hayato?
That's right.
Isn't that nice?
It looks beautiful!
You did such a nice job!
Teacher, we've got big news!
On Christmas, we're gonna get a visit
from Kamen Rider instead of Santa Claus!
Really?
Mr. Ichimonji, Mr. Taki...
Are you sure you want to
make promises like that?
I wouldn't want to disappoint
them, Ms. Sanae.
That's right.
But we're missing our
brightest voice...
Where's Kumi?
What's the matter?
She came down with a
sudden fever last night...
Big Bro!
Get well soon, okay?
Big Brother Hayato...
That wolfman took my doll!
Wolfman?
He sounds like a bad man.
Maybe you'll get a new
doll for Christmas, then.
I'll be hoping for you.
It's true, though.
There really is a wolfman.
Hayato...
you think I'm lying too, don't you?
Not at all. I believe you.
You'd never lie, Kumi.
Then will you get my doll
back from the wolfman?
Sure thing.
So get some rest.
I thought the dead man was bringing
this doll home, but I was wrong.
This isn't a brand new doll.
There was a shoe with
it, wasn't there?
Here.
"Wakakusa Nursery
School, Kumiko Hayase."
A witness, perhaps?
Hayato.
You don't really believe
that little girl, do you?
Actually... the fact that she's a child
makes me more inclined to believe her.
Besides, two men went missing
in this area last night.
Sheesh...
I really don't think
this is gonna pan out.
Taki!
Something did happen
here last night.
Maybe Kumi happened to see it,
and her fear gave her a fever.
And you think it was
a wolfman she saw?
And what are we doing?
W-We came looking
for a child's doll.
A child's doll?
I haven't seen
anything like that.
And this area is off limits.
Taki. Let's head back.
Of course.
Sorry for the trouble.
Wakakusa Nursery School
Would you look at the time...
Are the children
all asleep already?
That's strange.
I was sure I'd closed it...
Hey, girl.
Which one is Kumiko's bed?
What do you want with Kumi?
Tell us! Which is it?
Kumi's is... number two...
Number two?
Hey.
Kumi!
Taki! Look at that!
Would you look at that...
It really is a wolfman!
You...
You're Ichimonji and Taki!
You know our names?
That means...
You're a Shocker cyborg!
Silence!
And don't come any closer,
unless you want the child to die!
Wolfman... look at that child again
with those beady eyes of yours!
What?
Nyah!
Goro! Run away!
Hup!
Well done, Goro!
I thought I was a goner!
We're here now!
Wolf Man...
why are you kidnapping a child?
It's killing you I'm
more concerned with now!
Get them!
Taki, hurry!
Take Goro to safety!
Right!
Grab on tight!
Good luck!
Transform!
Kamen Rider... come to me!
Rider Kick!
Oh no... he escaped!
Kamen Rider...
the next time we meet, you die!
Remember that!
KAMEN RIDER
I did it!
I'm so glad she's safe.
All thanks to Hayato,
who believed that little girl.
But Shocker really
is horrible...
Trying to kill a girl just
for witnessing their plan!
But that wolfman was
just an experiment.
Is that right, Kumi?
Yeah, it is.
I heard everything.
Because I was too
scared to run away!
So, Kumi...
did they say anything else?
Let's see...
Anything will help.
Try to remember.
I remember.
He mentioned "Operation: Wolf."
Operation: Wolf?
What's Operation: Wolf?
Taki, a message for you.
Who's it from?
An emergency message from
FBI headquarters in New York.
They've decoded a
Shocker message.
"At 1 PM today, a Shocker executive
will arrive in Tanzai District.
It's related to Operation: Wolf.
Investigate at once."
Let's find out what
Operation: Wolf is.
It's sure to be trouble.
That's Shocker for you.
They arrived right on schedule.
All right... let's go.
Let's go.
Who are you?
I want to know more
about Operation: Wolf.
Kill them!
Hold it!
Hayato!
Let go... of that bag!
Let's go!
Hayato! You okay?
I know.
This might teach us the
secret of Operation: Wolf.
What's this?
Look!
An invitation from Colonel Zol!
"We're holding a party to
kick off Operation: Wolf.
Please attend in costume."
I'd love to take them
up on that offer.
Same here.
Where is the party venue?
Kindly show me your card.
Of course.
Welcome, gentlemen!
I'm so grateful to have you
all here at this Shocker party.
Humanity's fools are out
there celebrating Christmas.
But this will be the last
Christmas they'll ever enjoy.
Operation: Wolf will put the
entire world into Shocker's hands.
In addition, as the ultimate present
offered at today's Shocker party,
we will slay that perpetual
thorn in our side and his ally!
Gentlemen. Remove your masks!
That decoy message brought
you here as planned...
Ichimonji Hayato!
Ichimonji Hayato.
Too overwhelmed to speak?
Bring the FBI agent disguised
as his driver as well.
That would be impossible.
That voice...
You're...
We knew not to trust that setup.
It was too good to be true!
Then where is Hayato?
Maybe the warehouse
for the Wolf Virus?
Oh no!
- Well?
- I set the bombs in the warehouse.
Let's go!
Get to the warehouse!
Protect the Wolf Virus!
Hayato!
Taki!
I'm fine!
Ichimonji Hayato...
Let us settle this.
Colonel Zol... aren't you going to
bring out your loyal Wolf Man henchman?
Just as you can transform
into Kamen Rider,
I, too, can transform.
Then you're...
a cyborg, like me?
Behold, my true form!
Only a Wolf Man could
execute Operation: Wolf!
Rider... die!
Transform!
Rider! Die!
Rider!
Rider Punch!
Wakakusa Nursery School
Thanks!
Here you go.
Thanks.
But where's Hayato?
He promised he'd bring Kamen
Rider, right?
I wonder what he's off doing...
Kamen Rider!
It's the Kamen Rider!
Hey, everyone!
It's Kamen Rider!
I came, just as promised.
Hold this, won't you, Goro?
- Here, Kumi.
- Thank you!
- Here.
- Thanks!
Here.
Thank you!
See you later, everyone!
Shocker commander-in-chief Colonel Zol
revealed his true form before his downfall.
But Shocker continues to pursue
its ambitions of world conquest
and they will surely send
more powerful enemies, yet.
Ride on, Kamen Rider!
Fight for peace and justice!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Snowman.
We'll see a new Shocker
strategist, Doctor Shinigami,
and the first Rider, Hongo
Takeshi, face Snowman down.
The second Rider, Ichimonji
Hayato, heads for Kyushu.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Deathmatch! The Monstrous Snowman Versus
the Two Riders!"
Deathmatch! The Monstrous Snowman
Versus
The Two Riders
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!