KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Lightning Monster Eiking's
Worldwide Blackout Operation
Strange...
I feel like someone's following me.
But I'm sure that's not true.
Akemi Seki.
Wh-Who's there? Who's calling me?
Akemi, speak!
Where is your father, Doctor Seki, hiding?
I don't know...
My father went missing two years ago.
Doctor Seki has escaped.
He escaped to see you, his daughter.
Now, speak!
My father escaped?
You mean... he's alive?
Don't play dumb with me!
Someone help!
Hey! Over there!
- What is it?
- Let's check it out!
M-Monster...
You saw Eiking, did you? Foolish humans!
Die!
Crash, lightning!
Behold my power!
He will come...
He will come to see his daughter.
That's when I'll strike.
I'll let her go until then.
Hey, sorry. I totally overslept.
Don't sweat it.
We've been walking around
for three days straight.
Anyone would be exhausted.
Still, it's strange...
I was sure I picked up mystery waves within a
ten kilometers radius of these mountains...
Even the FBI's detectors
can malfunction now and then.
Okay, I'll go gather firewood.
Sure.
Who's there?
Stay back!
Hayato!
Keep away!
You can't order me around any longer...
Is somebody after you?
Don't play dumb with me.
You're Shocker's dogs...
Shocker's dogs?
Don't be absurd.
We're after Shocker ourselves.
Really? Is that true?
You really are?
We are.
We're fighting against Shocker.
I'm saved...
Get a hold of yourself.
Akemi... I'll finally get to see you...
Taki. You think he's a Shocker runaway?
What's wrong, Colonel Zol?
You still haven't caught
the runaway Doctor Seki?
The runaway doctor will
surely go to see his daughter.
We have a network set up around her.
It's only a matter of time
before we bring him back.
Doctor Seki is Eiking's creator.
I'd like to build more Eikings,
and use them to take out generators
in the world's greatest
cities, beginning with Japan.
Worldwide Blackout Operation.
We need Doctor Seki to make it happen!
It was I who came up with that plan.
I'm well aware of Doctor Seki's importance!
Colonel Zol.
We got an emergency message
from the third patrol team.
Tire marks were found at 13 degrees.
Put them on the screen.
The tracks were left by two motorbikes.
Could Ichimonji Hayato and that
FBI agent have found Doctor Seki?
Akemi...
He's awake!
Thank goodness.
You're safe now!
Where... Where am I?
We brought you here.
- Did you?
- Yes.
I see.
So I've escaped Shocker...
If you don't mind, we'd like
to hear what happened to you.
I am Toshihiko Seki.
My specialty is marine biology.
And Shocker forced you to work
on their team of scientists?
Yes.
I learned of their terrifying
world conquest ambitions,
and spent two years waiting to escape.
My! Two whole years?
That must have been hard...
I couldn't even stand one day like that!
That's right. I can't stay here...
I need to show Akemi that I'm safe!
You can't do that!
You can't even walk in your condition.
Besides that, Doctor, Shocker is clever.
They'll know you plan to see your daughter,
and they may have prepared an ambush.
Knowing them, it's possible.
But I... I want to see Akemi.
It was the only thing that
kept me going all this time.
If I can't do that...
Leave it to me.
I'll bring your daughter to you.
You will?
Yes, he's very trustworthy.
You can leave it in his hands.
I agree!
Time for Ichimonji Hayato
to show his stuff!
Are you forgetting someone?
What, are you going too, Mr. Taki?
You don't think you'll just slow him down?
Why, you little...
Get out of my way.
So long.
Seki Marine Biology Institute
The Seki Marine Biology Institute.
You think Akemi's safe?
That monster said my father was alive.
If that's true...
I'm sure he'll come to see me.
Father...
Please, come home safe!
You're coming with me.
- I just heard a scream!
- It came from inside!
You handle things here!
Got it!
Shocker cyborg...
My name is Eiking.
Ichimonji Hayato...
The fact that you're here makes
Doctor Seki's whereabouts obvious.
So I'll be taking his daughter
as a hostage in his place!
I won't let you take Akemi!
Fool!
Behold my power!
Crash, lightning!
Wait, you!
Transform!
Get back here!
Kamen Rider...
you've shown yourself at last!
Eiking... If you know what's good for you,
you'll put the girl down
and get out of my sight!
Not so fast, Kamen Rider!
It is I, Eiking, who shall defeat you,
so that you can never
interfere with us again!
Now you'll see Eiking's true power!
Behold, the power of a
million volts of electricity!
Crash, lightning!
That is the power of Eiking!
The Kamen Rider is no match for me!
Hayato!
He got me...
Where's the doctor's daughter?
Shocker has her...
What did you say?
You mean you messed up?
He's a formidable foe...
KAMEN RIDER
I can't apologize enough.
They've taken Akemi hostage, then?
What were you thinking?
How could you come back
after letting that happen?!
Why didn't you go after him?
Why didn't you risk your
life to protect her?
Pops!
Try to keep your head...
Hayato did everything he could.
That's right!
You're being too cruel!
Even Hayato messes up sometimes!
Shut up!
Hayato can't afford to fail.
That's the nature of
Ichimonji Hayato's mission!
And if he dies...
it's all down the drain!
Who would fight Shocker then?
I'm here!
So are you! And Mari, and Yuri!
Even Goro can fight when he has to!
We'll all fight!
Pops.
I... I may have been too
focused on saving myself.
A man focused only on saving himself
can't also risk his life to fight!
Everyone, please, stop this!
I can see my presence has caused
you a great deal of trouble...
Perhaps I shouldn't have escaped.
Doctor. I promise...
I'll bring your daughter
back if it kills me.
It's too late.
They'll have her back in their base by now.
They're probably torturing her...
You're a strong-willed girl...
You still refuse to talk?
Ten more minutes under these lights,
and your face will be
burned beyond recognition!
I'd rather die than talk, if it means bringing
my father back to this awful place...
I... I love my father...
Love him, do you?
The love of father and child?
If you love him that much,
surely you don't want him to die.
Listen, girl.
Under Shocker law, if your
father does not return to us,
we will have to kill him.
That death will be at the hand
of his own creation, Eiking!
You're going to kill my father?
That's right.
You want to let your beloved father die?
Or will you do as I say and speak to him?
Well?
I'll speak to him...
And so, I ended up creating
that ray cyborg, Eiking.
So what is Shocker's endgame, Doctor?
What destruction do they
mean to cause with Eiking?
Eiking's body contains over
one million volts of electricity...
Yes? Tachibana Racing Club...
This is Akemi.
Akemi?
What? Akemi?
Please let me speak to my father.
She only wants to speak to the doctor.
I'll speak to her.
It's me.
Akemi... are you safe?
Go on. Tell him to return.
Tell him.
Speak!
Father... Father!
Get out of there!
Shocker's coming to kill you...
Doctor Seki. If you want to save
your beloved daughter,
come to Ikuta Apartment Complex alone,
tomorrow morning at ten o'clock.
A car will come to fetch you.
If you come back peacefully,
without revealing any information,
we'll overlook your escape
and ensure your daughter's safety.
You're not lying?
I'm a man who keeps his promises.
Listen... just don't say a word
to compromise our plans.
Very well.
Shocker!
Colonel Zol...
Zol! Colonel Zol!
Go on, sit down.
What did your daughter say, Doctor?
Doctor.
Did they threaten to kill your
daughter if you didn't return to them?
Sounds like their usual MO.
That's right. It's absolutely horrible.
Please, say something!
Please... give me some time alone.
That's all I can say right now.
Let's give him time alone, everyone.
Mari.
I can't let my daughter be killed...
Come to Ikuta Apartment Complex alone,
tomorrow morning at ten o'clock.
A car will come to fetch you.
Thank you for all your help.
Go.
Not yet.
Wait until he meets his daughter.
Right. Let's tail them.
Where is my daughter? Where is she?
We're taking you to meet her now.
Just be patient until then.
This is the way to the power station.
The million-volt station
that powers over ten cities?
I see now.
See what?
What Shocker is using Eiking for.
When I flip this switch, it will detonate
all of the bombs we've placed.
It's all finished.
If we blow up this power station,
it will blackout ten whole cities.
Then Shocker will spring into action,
and conquer those cities.
Where... Where is my daughter?
Let me see her!
Doctor Seki.
Eiking... don't tell me, Akemi is...
We're about to kick off
Worldwide Blackout Operation.
Then we'll kill her in the
filthy traitor's place.
Look up there!
Father!
Akemi!
Father! Father!
No! This wasn't the agreement!
Father... why? Why didn't you run away?
Akemi... please, spare her!
Kill me instead!
I can't!
We need you to create more Eikings!
Akemi!
After him!
Don't let him escape!
You're Ichimonji Hayato!
Doctor, go save your daughter!
Eiking... I won't let you
destroy this power station!
It's too late.
I'll blow you up with it!
Detonation team, hit the switch!
Hold it!
I won't let you do it!
Oh no!
No...
Where's Eiking?
Eiking is outside!
Transform!
You won't escape, Eiking!
Nonsense, Kamen Rider!
I'll finish what I started last time!
Get him!
What's taking you so long?
Kamen Rider... It's time we finished this!
Crash, lightning!
I... I need to take the
chance, even if it kills me!
Kamen Rider!
Damn you, Kamen Rider!
You won't get away!
Rider Kick!
I don't know how to thank you.
You don't need to.
Today you taught me the power
that love and trust can inspire.
I'm sure Mr. Tachibana will be happy, too.
Thank you for everything.
I'm glad the power station made it
out with just some minor damage.
Come on, let's go.
Shake a leg.
They managed to prevent Shocker's
Worldwide Blackout Operation.
But enemies more powerful than
Eiking might still lie in store.
Go, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Wolf Man.
A creepy masked party
unfolds on Christmas night.
Colonel Zol risks his
life on Operation: Wolf,
and Taki Kazuya and Ichimonji
Hayato bravely stand to face him.
Join us next week for "The
Monstrous Wolf Man's Killer Party!"
The Monstrous Wolf Man's
Killer Party
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!