KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
What an awful night.
So hot and humid...
Yeah. Maybe we'll get some rain.
Hey, what's with you?
You look like you've
just seen a ghost...
What is that?!
A m-monster!
D-Don't hurt me!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Tokageron and
the Monster Army!
What's wrong?
The entrance is
blocked by a barrier...
What's that?
Created a barrier
wall, did they?
All right...
Authorized Personnel Only
A barrier—in other words, an invisible
wall made from electromagnetism.
Even a nuclear bomb
cannot breach it.
What? The Atomic Energy Research
Laboratory is protected by a barrier?
Yes, sir.
We cannot attack the laboratory
until we destroy the barrier.
And it's too powerful
for us to break through.
Enough of your whining!
Listen to me.
Shocker's Japanese branch is lagging
behind our European and American branches
in forwarding our plans
for world conquest.
That's another reason we need control of
the Atomic Energy Research Laboratory.
That barrier is nothing!
It will bend, as all things do,
before the scientific might of Shocker!
My scientists...
give them the barrier destruction ball!
But sir,
the barrier destruction ball must be
thrown from a distance of twenty meters,
or it won't expel
the necessary power.
Additionally,
the ball weighs five kilograms.
We possess no cyborg strong
enough to throw it twenty meters!
Fools! Make a cyborg strong
enough, then!
Professional soccer
player Ken Nomoto.
He's one of the best center
forward players in the business.
His killer goal shot is
feared by players everywhere.
It's Mr. Nomoto!
Can I have your autograph?
Get lost. Get lost!
I've got no time for kids.
Please sign my book!
Get lost.
Look at you lazy fools.
You'd be in dead last place
if you didn't have me.
Am I right?
Hey, guys.
Let's have a toast,
to the health of the great Ken Nomoto.
Right?
What a bunch of layabouts.
Hey... Hey!
Isn't anyone here?
Who's there?
Ken Nomoto.
Where are you?
You...
Shocker's computer
gave us your name.
Come with me, Ken Nomoto.
I'll make you the most
powerful man in the world.
Don't be stupid.
I don't take orders from anyone.
Bastard...
You cannot escape!
You will join us,
as one of Shocker's cyborgs!
Hey!
Well, if it isn't Taki!
Should you be leaving your wife
alone this soon after the wedding?
She's got homemaker
training to do.
It's important to start early.
And men have their
own work to do.
You cad. Listen to you talk!
By the way, where is he?
Who?
You mean Mr. Hongo!
You're a real mind reader.
You're wasted on this café.
It's not that impressive...
Don't raise him up too much.
Shiro's a simple man,
susceptible to flattery.
I'm not simple!
You're always like this, Boss...
Work matters aside,
I have a question to ask him.
Hongo?
Here's where you'll find him.
Two Security Guards Killed
Toyo Atomic Energy Research Laboratory
Could an International Spy Organization be Behind It?
It must be Shocker
who attacked the
Atomic Energy Research Laboratory
and killed those security guards.
They'll be mounting a new
attack sooner than later.
I'll keep it safe.
If that laboratory is destroyed
and the radiation leaks out,
it'll destroy all of
Tokyo in ten minutes flat!
Leader.
Ken Nomoto's transplant
surgery is complete.
Impressive.
Honored scientists of Shocker,
show me the fusion of
human and venomous lizard!
The power of a venomous
lizard to kill an elephant,
combined with the kicking
power of soccer star Ken Nomoto
has created the lizard
man, Tokageron,
designed to kick the
barrier destruction ball!
Good.
Send our spies to the
research facility.
Find the barrier's weakest
point, then attack.
We will turn Japan's capital,
Tokyo, into a wasteland!
That Hongo is such
a slavedriver...
Making me stand watch
in a place like this...
Where did he even go?
Huh?
That car just passed
by a few minutes ago...
That's the third pass they've
done of the laboratory.
Takeshi was right...
It has to be Shocker!
Ruriko... huh?
She's gone...
That must be
Shocker's secret base.
All right...
I'll find out what's going on inside.
Oh, you scared me!
This might be the era of
women's lib and feminism,
but you must agree that
this is a man's job.
Just wait here, okay?
Hongo will chew me
out if you don't.
See you!
Not even a cat...
What are these?
Oh, please.
They're made out of clay...
What kind of freak would
collect these things?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I am the master of this house.
Why did you break
into my property?
Well, see...
I'm looking for someone.
The only ones in
this house besides me
are these statues.
So you're the one who
collects these weird things?
I am.
Now, I must ask you to leave.
Yeah, fine.
You've got a lousy sense of
taste, though.
I didn't ask your opinion.
Now... go.
We cannot leave that man alive.
I will finish him.
Silence!
Listen to me.
The Kamen Rider
defeated all of you...
In other words, you're losers.
You don't get an opinion.
You will not interfere.
Leave everything to
the great Tokageron!
KAMEN RIDER
Look out!
Taki!
Taki... are you all right?
Ruriko... I'm fine, please...
Rider!
Get to safety! Now!
What is that?
So you're the Kamen Rider
I've heard so much about...
I've been waiting for
you to show yourself.
You're Shocker's new
cyborg, then?
Behold Tokageron's kick!
Rider is...
Don't worry. Rider will win!
Killer Shot!
The Kamen Rider is
no match for me!
I've...
lost...
The Kamen Rider has lost.
I didn't want to believe it,
but I saw it with my own eyes.
Try to take it easy.
Damn... what are we going to do?
You need a week's
peace and quiet.
You need to rest.
I'm serious about this.
Kamen Rider lost
to that monster.
I need to find
out our next move.
At that moment, Hongo Takeshi—rather,
Kamen Rider—was in training.
He was desperate to
perfect a new move that
would get him past
Tokageron's deadly kick.
It's no use.
If I can't endure a few rocks,
there's no way I can beat his kick!
Hongo...
Mr. Tachibana...
Long ago,
I trained you on this mountain
to make you the
world's greatest racer.
It nearly drove you mad,
but you endured everything I threw at you.
Hongo. Will you put
yourself through that again?
All right.
Mr. Tachibana... I will learn to
counter that killer kick of his.
No... I must learn!
All right... Let's go!
You can't just let it hit you!
Use more of your body!
Are you all right?
I see...
If I double the power I
put into the Rider Kick...
Mr. Tachibana,
throw the rock from where you are!
No way! You can't take it!
Please!
All right!
Lightning Rider Kick!
You did it!
Well done.
Taki! Kamen Rider is...
Taki?
Is that Taki's ID?
Taki Kazuya...
FBI special agent?
Of course. He's in the FBI...
That's why he was so desperate to poke
his nose into the investigation...
Which means...
he's after Shocker right now!
With Rider out of the fight, I'll put
my life on the line to destroy Shocker.
That's my mission,
as an FBI agent.
There you are, FBI scum.
Where are you?
The eleven Shocker
cyborgs you saw before
are already on their way to the
Atomic Energy Research Laboratory.
But you will not
leave here alive!
You have to get to
the laboratory...
They're going to unleash
its radiation on Tokyo!
I see...
I can handle things here.
All right.
I can take any barrier
down in one hit.
Rider!
You're all the cyborgs
I killed before!
Shocked, are you?
But cyborgs cannot die...
As long as we repair
the parts you destroyed!
As you can see!
You couldn't even
beat me on your own...
How do you expect to
fight eleven of us?!
Rider Fight!
Rider Kick!
You can die with my
destruction ball!
Rider Fight!
Rider Kick!
Time for my killer shot!
Lighting Rider Kick!
I won!
The Rider Kick beat him!
Rider!
I defeated all eleven monsters.
You're incredible, Rider.
He's wonderful.
He's willing to give his life
to protect people, isn't he?
That's right.
You can't bring peace and
happiness to the world
if you only ever
think about yourself.
That's why he's fighting.
Hongo Takeshi once again saved
Tokyo from Shocker's evil plans.
But Shocker would surely attack again
in their quest to take over the world.
The Kamen Rider would
continue to fight with
no end, for the sake
of peace and justice.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Next week will be the start
of a new Kamen Rider series.
With a new costume and
lots of new things to see,
you'll find thrills and action.
Join us next week for Kamen Rider:
"The Devilish Sabotegron Attacks!"
The Devilish Sabotegron
Attacks!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!