KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Steel Monster
Armadillong
What was that?
Strange...
What was that sound?
You don't think a plane crashed, do you?
- Let's check it out!
- Right!
What a big hole...
Incredible...
You think it came from outer space?
It could have!
It's moving! That thing's alive!
Monster!
Screwball Shot!
Hurry, get inside! Hurry!
Hurry up!
You cannot escape me!
Hurry! That way!
I'll crush you all!
Screwball Shot!
Incredible!
Did you see that, men?
That's the power of Armadillong,
just sent from Brazil to Japan.
Colonel, what's his objective?
Blowing up gasholders.
Armadillong will blow up
gasholders across Tokyo and Osaka.
The flames that rise from the wreckage
will burn Tokyo and Osaka to cinders.
Wait.
Colonel Zol.
That task is much too easy
for one of Armadillong's talents.
Have him first defeat our mortal
enemy, the Kamen Rider.
Colonel Zol, the man from
the mountain cottage...
We can't let him get away.
Armadillong, dispose of him at once!
Hayato!
What's he doing at this early hour?
Some kind of new case?
"Mysterious explosion near
Mount Wakagoma Cottage?"
"At 4 PM yesterday,
a mountain cottage blew up.
The local villagers were crushed inside..."
Is that what Hayato's after?
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
Hey, Yuri!
What are you dressed up like that for?
Isn't it obvious?
It's just what it looks like...
Early morning training!
Hey! Don't interrupt your sensei!
What? You're the sensei?
Well, that's a nice way to start your day.
Come over here, mister!
What's that?
After practice is over, you all
get Kamen Rider pendants?
Yeah!
I get it now...
Hey! Susumu!
Uh-oh! Run away!
Hey!
Help! Help me!
Speak to me!
What's going on here?
You, call an ambulance! Hurry!
Right.
Sir! Speak to me!
Damn... that man did it!
Wait!
Hold on. That man is my prey.
It's none of your concern!
Hey! Wait up!
Give me that!
Give it!
You already have two!
Sorry...
What's going on here?
Yuri's playing karate teacher again,
using pendants to lure in the kids.
Yuri, teaching karate?
This I have to see!
Give it to me! Give me that pendant!
Shut up already!
- Get a grip!
- Ow!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Halt!
Turn left!
Stance!
- One!
- Two!
Susumu!
Uh-oh...
Don't skip out, Susumu,
or you won't get your pendant.
I'm tired, okay?
Monsters!
Susumu!
Maybe they went home already?
That's Susumu's shoe!
The kids were pretty keen
to get these pendants...
What would they be doing here?
Could something have happened to them?
All right... this way, then?
You're a faithful daughter, Connie...
You pursued me all the way to Japan?
But a foolish human like you
is no match for Shocker.
I'll kill you!
There you are, Shocker cyborg!
I am Ichimonji Hayato.
You're not strong enough
to beat him. Stand back.
Try me, Shocker monster!
Damn... it's like his body's made of steel!
Then you've caught on at last.
Now it's my turn!
Screwball Shot!
Ichimonji Hayato... adios!
There you are, Shocker!
If Shocker is here...
Armadillong must be nearby!
- Who are you?
- I'll explain later.
Shocker cyborg...
Where did you take Yuri and the kid?
Die!
Damn you!
You killed my mother,
my father, and my little brother!
Transform!
Kamen Rider!
Kamen Rider... feel the
power of my Screwball Shot!
Rider!
Rider Kick!
Hang in there!
KAMEN RIDER
Wait!
Wait up!
Let me go!
I'm Connie Yamada.
Armadillong killed my family
six months ago, in Brazil.
We had such a happy life together...
Then suddenly, one night,
that monster appeared.
Why would a Shocker
cyborg target your family?
They weren't.
Shocker was testing Armadillong...
That was the only reason it happened.
I see...
By some miracle, I made it out alive.
And so you came all the way
from Brazil after him?
That's right.
I will defeat Armadillong
no matter what it takes.
All right. I'll go with you.
Well done, Armadillong.
Your name will be honored
forever in the annals of Shocker.
Gentlemen.
With the Kamen Rider gone,
Japan is as good as ours.
Our Japan Branch will now
begin its all-out attack.
Colonel, what should we do with
the woman and children we took hostage?
Give them a grand execution
in accordance with Shocker law.
And invite Tachibana Tobei to come see it.
Invite him? A fine idea...
Show him the end that awaits
all who stand against Shocker!
I see another pendant...
This way. Let's go!
Let's watch and see what they're up to.
I see them... five of them.
Not so fast, Connie.
We might be able to beat those five.
But they have two hostages in the base.
Any trouble we start could be bad for them.
There must be a better way...
Light this, and fire it
into one of those trees.
While Shocker is distracted,
I'll charge them.
Who's there?
Show yourself! Who's there?
Let's go!
Thanks!
Shocker HQ! Shocker HQ!
Point A! Point A, respond!
P-Point A here. Nothing to report!
The base is that way.
Right!
There's nobody here...
What's going on?
Did they abandon their base?
Yuri!
A mannequin!
Damn it!
We knew you'd infiltrated our base.
Taki!
Let me go!
Help!
Mr. Taki!
Mister!
Let's delay gratification
and execute you tomorrow.
Oh, honestly!
What? A missing persons report?
Could you wait a moment longer?
Our Yuri is with him, so...
Yes, please...
Where in the world did she take Susumu?
Doesn't she know his parents are worried?
What's this?
Shocker?!
"Please join us at the base of Mount Kitamine
to watch the grand execution
of your club members."
The base of Mount Kitamine?
That hurts!
Look alive, kid!
Keep walking, kid!
Walk!
Go!
Keep going!
Oh no!
Walk!
Go on, get going!
Halt!
I'm going to push you off here.
This is a Shocker execution ground.
No! No!
No!
Let the kid go!
That's enough, Shocker!
It's Rider!
- Get him!
- Kamen Rider!
Taki! Look out!
Get out of here, quickly!
Come on, everyone!
His stomach is his weak point...
Screwball Shot!
Rider Kick!
Rider beat the monster!
Papa, we did it!
We beat Armadillong!
Papa, your home, Japan...
It's a truly wonderful country.
But we know Shocker... they
could be plotting anything next!
Hey, mister, where'd Rider go?
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen Rider,
shattered Armadillong's plan.
But let us not forget behind it all,
irreplaceable lives are being lost
that we may never hear about.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the toad monster, Gamagiller!
Shocker's latest horrifying
plan is to split Japan in two.
Our Kamen Rider learns of the plot,
and pursues Gamagiller to a secret airfield!
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Japan in Peril! Gamagiller's Invasion"
Japan in Peril!
Gamagiller's Invasion"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!