KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous
Namazugiller's Electric Hell
What's that?
This is JW-20.
Unregistered submarine sighted 50
nautical miles off the Boso Peninsula.
This is JW-20.
Fire!
So Shocker's Japan Branch base
is beneath Namegawa Island...
Ambassador Hell...
you've chosen a truly brilliant location.
Come on. The flamingo
dance is starting soon.
Let's go.
Sure, let's go.
Let's get going!
We'd better hurry!
Hurry!
Hurry up, Chairman!
Hey, slow down, guys!
Welcome, Doctor Shinigami.
Ambassador Hell.
Doctor Shinigami... having you all the way
from the South America Branch to join us
will be a true boon for
the Shocker Japan Branch.
But are they saying I can't handle
the conquest of Japan all by myself?
Allow me to show you
what I've brought.
What is this cyborg?
Namazugiller,
created from the electric catfish
that live in the waters
of the Andes Mountains.
Namazugiller?
Well... what can it do?
Enough, Doctor Shinigami!
You've made your point.
The whiskers of the cyborg
Namazugiller can channel 100,000 volts.
Any human who touches those whiskers
will be electrocuted instantly.
Not even the Kamen Rider
can stand against him.
Hongo Takeshi, suspicious of the JSDF
fighter that went down over the Boso Sea,
headed for the Boso Peninsula,
accompanied by FBI agent Taki Kazuya.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- What a great dancer...
Which one?
All of them!
But boy,
flamingos have nice legs, huh?
Don't say that in
front of a lady!
You little brat!
You'll pay for that!
Wait up!
- Stop it, Goro!
- Honestly...
Wait! Wait!
Wait, darn it! Wait!
Let's go that way!
Wait!
Huh? Which way'd they go?
This way, I bet!
You scared me!
Hey, where's Goro?
We lost him in the tunnels!
Hey, come on!
You lost him in there?
It's our necks on the line
if he gets himself lost!
Those caves are big, you know!
Let's go find him!
Emi! Tokko!
I promise I forgive
you, so please come out!
What was that sound?
Who's there? Show yourself?
A monster!
You brat...
Let me go! Let me go!
You'll be my first
victim here in Japan!
Wait.
Why did you stop me?
This boy could make
a valuable hostage
to lure out Hongo Takeshi.
We cannot kill him.
Hongo Takeshi?
Tell me where to find him!
He'll be here soon.
Be patient until then.
An emergency call.
Hongo here. Over.
Hongo? Goro's gone missing
on Namegawa Island!
Missing?
You think...?
It's just what you think!
Doctor Shinigami...
Shocker has taken that
annoying brat hostage.
You...
So you're back in
Japan, are you?
If you value the child's life,
you must leave here at once!
You coward!
Wait, Taki!
Taki!
Taki, you okay?
Damn...
You're fish in a barrel now!
Grenades! Watch out!
Die!
Hongo!
Hey, Hongo! What's the matter?
What was that sound?
Hongo! Respond!
You've shown
yourselves, Shocker...
Try me!
Namazugiller... come forth!
There you are... Shocker cyborg!
Do what you've been longing for,
and kill Hongo Takeshi!
I came from the
Andes to destroy you!
I am Namazugiller!
That must have been
a pretty long trip!
Fight me, Namazugiller!
All right. Turn it on.
Excellent.
The boy's body is now
charged with 50,000 volts.
Rider Transformation!
Let's begin, Kamen Rider!
I'll put your power to the test!
Try me, Namazugiller!
Hold it!
Namazugiller...
that's enough for now!
Withdraw, so we can
embark upon our next plan.
Kamen Rider...
you were lucky this time.
I'm afraid we'll have to
finish this another time!
Let's go.
Namazugiller...
a fearsome opponent.
Rider,
is that the new Shocker cyborg?
I'll give him a beating
the next time I see him!
KAMEN RIDER
My mission in Japan
is now complete.
We need only wait for Hongo
and Taki to walk into our trap.
You've done well, Doctor Shinigami,
but leave the rest in my hands.
Ambassador Hell...
Namazugiller's power
is not without limits.
You must reflect
sunlight off that tower
to recharge Namazugiller's body.
Do not forget.
Hongo.
Pops, where's Goro?
We don't know...
I see. So Shocker was
telling the truth.
Shocker?
We were attacked
on our way here.
Pops,
they've taken Goro hostage.
Hey, Hongo.
Pops and the others are
fast asleep in the hotel...
Should we really be
wasting time here?
Just wait.
We know that Shocker
has a base in the area.
They'll try something
on us sooner or later.
- Goro!
- Where have you been?
Hey, what's going on?
Hey! Tokko!
Emi!
What in the world happened here?
Goro!
It went perfectly.
Take them away.
Hold it!
I won't let it happen.
I see... so that's their game.
Taki!
Goro!
Hey! Is it okay to touch him?
I can withstand a
little electricity.
And the charge has
left Goro's body.
Is this what they
used to control him?
They put an electric
charge in a human body
to create a high
voltage discharger.
If we hadn't interfered, they'd have
electrified the others the same way.
Yeah.
Hey.
Goro's dangerous!
He's safe now, Pops.
You two meanies!
You left me in that tunnel!
Goro!
Goro must have been
attacked in here.
Taki, I'll go this way.
Right. I'll go this way.
Take care.
Okay.
It looks like we're
under the ocean.
Where's the entrance
to their base?
Hongo...
This place will be
your graveyard...
Just go quietly!
Strange...
This tunnel shouldn't
lead to the shore.
Taki.
Hongo here. Respond.
Strange...
All right...
We'll electrify this man,
and force him to
fight Hongo Takeshi.
Taki.
Are you dead?
Taki!
You're safe?
Hongo... die!
Taki! Have you gone mad?
Taki!
Strange...
There's a powerful electric current
running through Taki's body.
I, Namazugiller, will finish you!
The charge has left his body.
Let's do this, Namazugiller!
You persistent fool!
Rider Transformation!
Fight me!
Increase the voltage further!
If I raise it any higher,
he won't last two minutes!
It doesn't matter!
He needs stronger electricity
to defeat the Kamen Rider!
I need more electricity!
I see... he's receiving
the current from there?
All right...
Goro.
I heard them talking...
When I was in Shocker's base,
they said they had to reflect
the sun's light off that tower,
to give that catfish
monster more power.
I see! All right...
Light... give me light!
Wait!
Light...
Everyone! Tie it down, then run!
Emergency, sir!
The reflectors won't move!
What's that?
It can't be...
investigate at once!
Give my body the light!
Give me the light!
All right, now!
Rider Reverse Kick!
Damn you, Kamen Rider!
Well, well...
they're having a good time.
No kidding.
Huh?
Where'd Hongo get off to?
Hongo Takeshi, the Kamen
Rider, defeated the
terrible electrical
monster Namazugiller.
But anywhere he goes,
he'll find a new monster spreading evil,
courtesy of Shocker's ambitions.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Harinezuras.
A Shocker transport carrying
a killer virus crashes.
A peaceful fishing village
is dragged into the chaos.
The Kamen Rider must face a
new monster's killer needles.
Join us next week for "The Monstrous
Harinezuras' Killer Skull Plan."
The Monstrous Harinezuras'
Killer Skull Plan
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!