KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Colonel.
We've received the mummy
Egyptas from the Egypt Branch.
Open it.
The Revived Mummy Monster
Egyptas
Begin Egyptas's life
force transfer surgery.
Shocker had found the 4000-year-old
Egyptian mummy Egyptas in a pyramid,
and brought it back to life, in order to
search for gemstones valued at one billion yen
that the pharaoh Thutmose III
was said to have sent to Japan.
Several days passed.
Colonel.
The life transfer surgery was a success.
Good. Excellent work.
Egyptas, you have awakened
from a 4000-year slumber.
Now, rise!
Rise, and show me your power!
Magnificent!
Egyptas...
Where have the gemstones,
worth one billion yen in modern currency,
been sent to in Japan?
What's wrong with you, Egyptas?
Where in Japan are the
one-billion-yen gemstones?
Tell me. Speak!
Colonel.
Perhaps Egyptas can understand
Japanese, but cannot speak it.
Ancient Egyptian, eh?
Computer, identify someone
who can decipher ancient Egyptian
and bring them to our base.
Egyptas...
The Egyptian monster that
lived back in 1800 BC?
Why are you trying to kill me?
Accompany us to our base,
and we'll spare you.
I see... are you the ones
who killed Doctor Nishida?
Egyptas. Colonel Zol wants him alive!
He's dead.
Report it to Colonel Zol.
Kenzo Goda
Papa! Papa!
Phone call for you.
Oh, dear... sorry about that, Yuji.
Hello?
G-Goda... it's Egyptas.
Egyptas has returned to life!
What? E-Egyptas?
I'm done for.
He took out Doctor Nishida, too...
Why... Why is Egyptas after us?
I don't know. But I suspect you're next.
Be careful!
Ono! Ono!
Ono!
Yuji, go back to your room.
Okay. Nighty-night, Papa.
Good night.
Ono, what's the matter?
What's the matter? Speak to me!
He's dead...
What are these symbols?
They found the same symbols next
to the history professor Doctor Nishida,
who was killed last night.
Is this his ID?
He's a history professor, too...
The burns... the circumstances...
They're a perfect match
for last night's incident.
Taki, there's been another murder.
Another murder? Where?
I'll explain later.
I have a favor to ask in the meantime.
Investigate those strange symbols found next
to Doctor Nishida when he died last night.
Yeah, yeah. I'll do it.
But Hayato... if you think you
can leave me out of the loop here...
Hayato!
Mysterious Late-Night Residential Death
Jonan University Instructor Nishida
Strange Symbols Left at Scene
Strange symbols left at the scene...
Just what do these symbols mean?
Impossible. That 4000-year-old monster
Egyptas, back to life and here in Japan?
It's absurd!
Papa! Help me! I'm scared!
Yuji!
What's wrong? Yuji!
Yuji! Where are you?
Yuji!
Doctor Goda, your son Yuji
is in the custody of Shocker.
Shocker?
Who are you?
Doctor, we wish you to interpret
the ancient Egyptian spoken by Egyptas.
Never.
You think I'd help Egyptas after
he killed Nishida and Ono?
There's no way...
You'd do better not to resist, Doctor.
Look at the television.
Papa! Save me!
Papa! I'm scared!
Help me!
Papa!
Yuji!
Stop it! Don't do this!
What do you say now, Doctor?
Please... Please don't hurt Yuji!
Papa, help me!
Doctor.
Yuji will remain alive until tomorrow.
You'll have to make your mind up by then.
Is that understood, Doctor?
Apparently it means "fire-breathing
monster Egyptas" in ancient Egyptian.
It's a monster believed
to have lived 4000 years ago.
A monster, eh?
That means Shocker's probably
behind the murders, right?
Shocker's found and revived a
4000-year-old monster from ancient Egypt.
And their objective is...
a total mystery, right?
You little...
A monster from 4000 years ago?
It feels so unreal...
But, there's something
a bit romantic about it.
Hey, Yuri. This is no
time for that nonsense.
But the monster would know things
that happened 4000 years ago, right?
It could reveal to us the
mysteries of ancient Egypt!
But of course, that's impossible.
None of us speak ancient Egyptian.
Of course... the hieroglyphs!
I see now. That's our key.
Taki.
Let's head to Doctor Goda's house.
The two victims were both historians.
Doctor Goda was an authority on ancient
Egypt with a similar level of renown.
That's nice work, Hayato!
Shocker will surely be after him.
Blasted Shocker...
I guess they're not here yet.
Taki, look at that.
Shocker!
Hold it, Egyptas!
We won't let you take Doctor Goda!
Transform!
Doctor! Doctor Goda!
Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
Doctor Goda...
Will you please tell us
why is Shocker after you?
I d-don't have the slightest idea.
But they were trying to take you
away just minutes ago.
Doctor... please, talk to us.
What is Shocker planning?
What are they using Egyptas for?
Egyptas?
You know about him, too?
Doctor!
Is that your son?
Yes.
He was taken by Egyptas last night.
Shocker kidnapped your child?
I couldn't find any clues.
"Papa, come save me.
If you don't come, they'll kill me."
- Taki!
- Hayato!
You're injured. I'll go.
You stay with the doctor.
He's here!
Not much to write home about...
My leg!
We've captured Taki.
"Ichimonji Hayato.
I appreciate all you've done for me.
And I'm sorry for the trouble you went
to, but I'm going to see them.
Please understand, Ichimonji.
This is the only option I have left.
If I don't go, Shocker may kill Yuji."
No one here...
You've returned, Egyptas!
Show me the way.
Why would the doctor...
Doctor!
Shocker! Open!
They've stopped.
Ten kilometers to the east-southeast...
Right!
- Yuji!
- Papa!
Doctor, kindly do your work first.
Now, doctor... interpret at once.
Now, talk!
Papa! Help me!
Papa!
There's nothing to worry about, Yuji.
You'll be safe soon.
"18th Pharaoh of Egypt, Thutmose III,
hid his gemstone hoard
in a country far to the north..."
Where? Where in that country?
"H-He respected the Tribe of Yezo
and showed friendship to them.
The hiding place of the gemstones
is known only to the head of the Yezo."
The Tribe of Yezo?
So the gems worth one billion yen
are with the Yezo people of Hokkaido?
Doctor... you've done your job perfectly.
What is the meaning of this?
You're no longer useful to Shocker.
And those who useless to Shocker must die!
What about Yuji?
What are you going to do to Yuji?
We'll kill him as well.
Taki!
Doctor... what happened to Hayato?
Where's Hayato, the man who was with you?
Damn you!
Egyptas!
Blow up this base, fly to
Hokkaido with the combatants,
and search for those gemstones.
Go!
I've been a fool.
Why did I knock out Ichimonji,
who was only trying to protect me?
No time for self-recrimination, Doctor.
Look at that!
Two kilometers left.
Let's go, Shocker.
Transform!
Doctor! What's that?
When did that get there?
Hayato...
Come quickly, Hayato!
Rider!
Rider, they're on their way to Haneda!
Cyclone could make it. Go after them, now!
I will.
I will defeat them!
It's the Kamen Rider!
Face me, Egyptas!
It's taking all my concentration
just to dodge his attacks!
I need to get in closer...
Now!
Rider Kick!
I won! I finally beat him!
Thanks a lot, mister!
We can't thank you enough.
Now, let's go.
What a nice family.
I sometimes forget how
brave parents can be.
Goodbye, mister!
You're a strange person, Hayato.
You always seem to look on the bright side.
Right, Hayato?
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen Rider,
defeated the mummy monster, Egyptas.
But more terrible battles with
Shocker would await him.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the poison gas Monster Torikabuto.
Shocker's vicious poison gas plan
puts Goro and friends in danger.
Kamen Rider struggles to keep up.
A deathmatch unfolds
on a high-rise apartment.
Join us next week for "Poison
Gas Monster Torikabuto's Operation G."
Poison Gas Monster
Torikabuto's Operation G
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!