KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Underground Monster
Mogurang
You are blind.
In exchange for sight, I will
give you retractable eyes
that will give you 360-degree
vision even while underground.
These electro-eyes.
Listen to me, Mogurang.
Your mission is to use all
the power at your disposal
to destroy the Kamen Rider
and see our plan through.
H-Help me!
You... You damned monster...
Colonel Zol.
The experiment was a roaring success.
Please, Mr. Tachibana!
My big brother Yutaka
is a real good mechanic!
He could even help Mr. Ichimonji win
this year's Motocross championships!
Right, Big Brother?
That's enough, Shinji.
Leave it to me, Big Bro.
You ask him, too, Goro.
Okay!
Please, Mr. Chairman!
Won't you let him try?
Please! Please!
C'mon, don't just stand there!
Please, please!
Well, if you insist.
You're hired, Yutaka.
Isn't that nice, Big Bro?
Thank you so much, Mr. Tachibana!
That chairman of ours is one swell guy!
I actually meant to hire
you from the start.
I've talked with Hayato about you two also.
But there's just one condition.
Yutaka.
Isn't it true that until six months ago,
you were aiming to be the
motocross champion yourself?
Then just because you took
a few spills during races,
you're suddenly afraid
to get back on your bike?
Next year, you race in Ichimonji's place.
That's my condition.
Doesn't that sound nice, Big Bro?
What happened?
You look a little flustered... what's up?
I just received a report that
a man was kidnapped by something
halfway between human and animal.
Is it Shocker again?
Shocker's latest cyborg, Mogurang, could
burrow freely through the ground.
He would pop up, kidnap someone, and
return them to Shocker's secret base,
where they would receive surgery that
would turn them into mole people.
Our current goal is to destroy
the Japanese economy.
Naturally,
our primary focus is Tokyo Harbor.
Our first target will
be the oil refineries.
We'll dump mass quantities of oil
from their tanks into Tokyo Bay
and then set the sea aflame!
We have left the execution of
this plan to the mole people.
Their intelligence has been
reduced through surgery,
so that they dig our tunnels day and night.
That makes forty kidnappings so far.
It sounds like Shocker's
doing something big.
I agree.
Aikawa, take a break once in a while.
The championship is two days away.
You can finish it tomorrow.
Of course.
But I just want to be as careful as I can.
Isn't that nice, Shinji?
Your brother gets to be a mechanic for
a motocross bike, just like he wanted!
Yeah! Do your best, Big Bro!
You said it.
Hayato is sure to win this one.
I guarantee it!
Okay, let's cheer him on!
Go! Go!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Mogurang, how is the plan proceeding?
Sir. We're currently here.
Good. At your current pace, we should
finish up tomorrow, as planned.
Yes, sir.
Mogurang.
Your slaves are starting to
work themselves to death.
Go and fetch some new ones.
Hold it right there, Shocker cyborg!
A mole monster...
The Rider Kick won't work on
an underground opponent...
I'll need to figure out a new move.
Now that we know we're
dealing with a mole monster,
we need to be as careful as possible.
Mogurang.
After our current plan succeeds,
I'll return your human form.
Yes, sir.
This is the restoration fluid.
But your work isn't finished yet.
Go and kidnap Yutaka Aikawa, who's
currently staying with Tachibana Tobei.
Aikawa.
I'm sorry to say it, but we might not be able
to take part in this year's championships.
Why not, Mr. Ichimonji?
You can't mean it!
I'm extremely sorry.
I can't apologize enough.
You're a liar, Mr. Ichimonji!
You made a promise to my brother!
That's enough, Shinji.
Hayato has other things in his life.
Now, let's go.
Darn it!
That's enough.
But I hate it so much!
Really, it's fine.
A monster!
Are you Yutaka Aikawa?
Big Bro! Big Bro!
Damn!
Shinji! Run!
Big Bro!
Hurry! Run away!
I'll call Mr. Ichimonji! Just hang on!
You gotta come!
Some weird monster got my brother!
Damn...
Where did it happen?
By the river!
All right...
Transform!
There you are, monster!
Rider, is it?
Get him!
That won't work against me!
What now, Rider?!
He's gone...
Where did he go?
Help me!
No!
KAMEN RIDER
Turn on the machine.
I think he's finally entered
the hypnotic state.
Yutaka Aikawa.
Your mission is to kill
FBI scum Taki Kazuya
at the motocross championships
two days from now.
Yes. I will kill Taki Kazuya.
Remember, failure means death.
Shocker must have gotten Hayato, too...
While he was trying to save Yutaka?
Then they got Yutaka, too?
I can't transform while
I'm tied up like this.
I need to do something...
Zol!
Just woken up and already
trying to escape, eh?
But it won't be that easy.
You've finally reached
the end of your rope.
Enough!
Where did you take the
people you kidnapped?
You want to know?
Yes.
I turned them into moles.
Turned them into moles?
What are you planning?
Since you're about to die,
I might as well tell you.
I'm going to drain all the oil from the
Kawasaki/Yokohama oil refinery into Tokyo Bay,
then set it on fire.
That's absurd...
It isn't possible!
Nothing is impossible for Shocker!
Tomorrow, the mole-people will arrive
beneath the oil tanks carrying bombs.
When I activate them by the remote control,
it will open holes beneath the tanks.
The oil that flows out will spread,
burning, through Tokyo Bay.
Well? Do you like my plan?
And one more thing...
I've released that Yutaka boy.
You've released him? Really?
Why would I lie?
But we've given him a mission of our own.
That's just the kind of
trick you would pull!
Say whatever you wish.
We've programmed Yutaka to kill Taki at
the motocross championships tomorrow.
"Taki, rest easy.
I foiled Shocker's plot and rescued Aikawa.
But there's something I need
to wrap up before I return.
If I can ask a favor, please take my place
in the motocross championships. Hayato."
Okay. Leave it to me, Hayato!
Give it your best shot, Taki!
I'll go tune up the bike, then.
Now, Taki will die...
When I press this button...
it will explode.
Have the cyborgs arrived under the tanks?
Yes.
Then, Colonel Zol, please
blow up the workers.
I'll press the detonation
switch in my room.
Switch remote control over to me.
Preparations for the
detonation are in place.
Then I'll blow up our secret base,
and Ichimonji Hayato with it.
Hayato.
This would be a good time
to say your prayers.
What was that?
Perfect!
Now I can cut through these chains!
Transform!
I see...
Imbibing this will turn them
back into normal humans.
And this will prevent the explosion!
How many left?
Just this one!
Mogurang, the oil refinery
detonation plan has failed.
Rider will be heading
for the motocross track.
Prepare to fight him there.
All-Japan Motocross Championships
Taki's looking good, huh?
You bet he is.
We'll win for sure at this rate!
Right, Yutaka?
Kill Taki...
That's Taki's bike!
Mr. Taki!
Taki!
Pops!
Taki! You okay?
Mr. Taki...
Die, Taki!
Rider!
Is Yutaka working for Shocker?
He's been hypnotized.
That hit I gave him should
return him to normal.
You jerk, Big Bro!
Shinji. That's enough.
It's not Yutaka's fault.
The fault lies...
with him!
Get him!
Rider... you've foiled
Shocker's plans yet again.
But for the last time!
He has the advantage, here on the soil...
I need to lure him somewhere
more favorable to me.
What's taking you so long?
Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him!
Damn... you unkillable monster!
Despicable Rider.
You won't leave here alive!
All right... I'll lure him over there.
Wait!
Come back here!
I'll knock him into that.
What's wrong, Mogurang?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to try to kill you, Mr. Taki.
I didn't know what I was doing.
No problem.
I know Shocker was just using you.
That's right.
Now's not the time for crying.
You made a promise to ride in
the race next year yourself.
Right?
Do your best, Big Bro!
Yeah! We'll totally win next year, right?
Root for him, everyone!
Go! Go!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen
Rider, defeated Mogurang
and protected Tokyo from an
attack on its oil refineries.
He renewed his pledge to fight Shocker as
he continued to wish for peace in Japan.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the electric monster Kuragedall.
Kuragedall appears and disappears at will,
kidnapping villagers and turning
them into electro-people.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "The Electric Monster Kuragedall!"
The Electric Monster Kuragedall!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!