KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Hongo Takeshi
Cannot Transform!!
The roads are clearer than I expected.
We should make it to the gorge
before nightfall at this rate.
It's been so much fun.
And it was going so well...
Really, construction this
deep in the mountains?
Well, nothing to be done.
Construction
Use Detour
That's strange.
This one's blocked off, too...
Something's wrong here.
I'm a little creeped out...
It's okay. Let's check it out.
Who's there?
Be honored!
You're the first to die to Leech Chameleon!
A monster! Run!
Your blood will be used to
revive Gel Shocker's monsters!
Run away!
Hey lady, you okay?
Are you all right?
H-Help me!
A t-terrible monster...
It said... G-Gel Shocker...
Gel Shocker?
Okay.
Rider Kid Corps, member number 505.
Gel Shocker spotted!
The experiment was a success.
We've brought Ganikomoru back to life
using an infusion of fresh human blood.
Ganikomoru... awaken!
Go and suck human blood, so that we
can restore more and more monsters!
Prepare for a grand Gel Shocker attack!
But there is something I
must deal with first...
I will defeat that perpetual thorn
in our side, the Kamen Rider!
Look.
There's no question.
It's a Gel Shocker base.
We'll have to thank the Rider Kid Corps.
That's the only way up, though...
Okay, let's go.
G6, G7. What's wrong?
We're on our way now!
Has something happened?
No, nothing to report.
All right. Time for a shift change.
Taki.
Listen, our target is General Black.
Right.
What is it?
General Black wanted to speak with us.
He's in the planning room.
Thanks a bunch.
General, emergency.
Hongo's motorbike was
sighted near the base.
And the ones who rode it here, Hongo
Takeshi and Taki Kazuya, are right before me!
You recognized us, General Black?
Sorry to say, but I'm not General Black!
Ganikomoru...
Damned Gel Shocker... they're
bringing monsters back to life?
This is merely a Gel Shocker frontline base.
Hongo, Taki... it's time for you to die!
Hongo... you will die at my hands!
Nonsense.
I'll make you tell me about
General Black's real base!
Now try me, Hongo Takeshi!
Transform into the Kamen Rider!
Very well...
I will transform!
Rider Transformation!
Are you all right, Rider?
I'm fine.
But there's something
else I'm worried about...
What is it?
The Rider Corps report said that the
Gel Shocker monster called itself Leech Chameleon.
But it was Ganikomoru that met us here.
And he was easily beaten...
You think it's a trap?
We should withdraw for now, either way.
Kamen Rider...
This film will reveal to
me all your weaknesses!
Stop!
Run that part back one more time.
Measure the length of the instant just
before he transforms into the Kamen Rider.
Twelve frames of film.
That's half a second.
Half a second, eh?
Great Doctor Dee of our science division...
In that brief span of time,
he is neither Hongo Takeshi,
nor the Kamen Rider.
He is nothing but a powerless puppet.
Excellent.
Research a way to fight him that
makes use of this weakness.
Yes, sir. At once.
Listen... have it finished
first thing in the morning!
Yes, sir.
It's an insurrection!
The prisoners have initiated a jailbreak!
All right... go!
KAMEN RIDER
We need to survive and find Kamen Rider!
You really think you can escape?
If we die, Kamen Rider will avenge us!
Hang in there!
You okay?
So many of our friends died for us.
That's why we have to keep fighting!
It's no use... they'll trace
us by our blood trails!
I'll distract the pursuers...
You... run!
I see a blood stain here!
They're here...
J-Just leave me here and go!
Damn... come and find me, Gel Shocker!
I won't let your death be in vain!
Leeches!
Wait!
Leech Chameleon...
You cannot escape!
I'll go to see Hongo Takeshi in your place!
Hongo!
Give me the Gel Shocker escapee!
Escapee?
You wasted your time. He's not here!
Damn...
Was that Leech Chameleon?
Hold it!
Kamen Rider!
Leech Chameleon!
Damn you!
Damn...
Get back here!
Show yourself, Leech Chameleon!
I'm not him.
Who are you?
Kamen Rider.
Avenge my comrades...
Destroy Gel Shocker!
Are you the Gel Shocker escapee?
I am. Please... avenge them!
Here.
Thank you.
Damned Gel Shocker...
Now they're using human blood to bring
their monsters back from the dead?
It's terrifying.
Mr. Hongo.
Mr. Taki.
I'm all better now.
I feel so much calmer.
I'll show you the way!
Maybe you should rest a little longer.
No.
While I stay here, they could be
sacrificing more of my imprisoned comrades.
We have no time to waste.
Taki.
We'll settle things with
General Black this time.
I'm ready.
Hongo.
Come back with good news, okay?
Just watch us.
Mr. Hongo.
Good luck, all right?
You think they'll make it
safely to Gel Shocker's base?
You know those two. They'll get it done!
This is Kamen Rider Kid Corps HQ.
Mr. Hongo? Mr. Taki?
Attention, members of the
Kamen Rider Kid Corps.
The Gel Shocker leader!
Gel Shocker is about to mount
a major attack on Japan.
But we intend to slaughter
all of our enemies first.
That includes you, of course!
Don't be ridiculous.
Try and beat us, if you can!
Wait!
If you think I'm lying,
look up at the ceiling!
Leeches!
Run!
Now, take them away!
This way.
Taki.
Back me up at the entrance.
Understood.
If anyone shows up, I'll stop them.
Mr. Hongo. Will you be all right alone?
I'll be fine.
You... get out!
You, too!
Please, spare me! Spare me!
I came to save you! Run away!
Run!
Hurry!
He's taking a while.
He certainly is!
What are you doing?!
I'll use your blood to
revive another monster!
Damn you!
Come on!
Mr. Hongo!
Did something happen to Taki?
Hongo Takeshi...
You're the last remaining
opposition to Gel Shocker.
What did you say?
Leech Chameleon...
It took you this long to see me?
What do you think, Hongo?
This was all a trap to
lure you into our base!
Leech Chameleon... What did you do to Taki?
It's not just Taki!
I've captured all of your allies!
Damn...
Look out the other window!
Can you see it, Hongo?
Well, Hongo... perhaps I'll show you.
Behold!
You got them all...
Their blood will give new
life to our monsters!
I won't let you do it, Leech Chameleon!
And how do you intend to stop me, Hongo?
Damn...
Well? Go ahead and escape, if you can!
You think you can hold me behind this wall?
Rider Transformation!
Now!
It's a Kamen Rider stoppage device
devised by Gel Shocker's science team...
Absolute zero!
I've done it!
I've captured Hongo Takeshi alive at last!
Learned your lesson?
Hongo?
Hongo!
Mr. Hongo!
Pops!
Watch, Hongo.
While you watch, I'll drain
their blood one at a time
and transfer it to my monsters...
And then I'll finish with you!
Yuri!
Begin the countdown!
Yuri...
Forty seconds.
Thirty-five.
Thirty.
It's no use. I can't transform!
Twenty-five.
Twenty.
Hongo Takeshi had fallen into
Gel Shocker's fearsome trap,
left unable to transform at a crucial time.
Will Taki and the others
fall prey to their plan?
Will Takeshi make it out of this crisis?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
At last, the leader shows himself.
At last, everything will be revealed.
Hongo Takeshi is trapped
immobile at absolute zero.
Leech Chameleon's fangs draw
towards Yuri's neck.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Gel Shocker Destroyed!
The Leader's End!!"
Gel Shocker Destroyed!
The Leader's End!!
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!