KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Having inherited the Kamen
Rider mantle from Hongo Takeshi,
Ichimonji Hayato has become
Japan's newest protector.
Kamen Rider is currently locked in
battle with the monstrous Sabotegron,
who was dispatched from
Shocker's Mexico Branch to Japan.
Sabotegron seeks to use powerful
bombs known as "Mexican Flowers"
to wreak destruction
around Japan.
Sabotegron Strikes Back
There he is...
the Kamen Rider...
Bloom, Mexican Flowers!
Rider!
Look out!
Rider Power!
Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
The cactus monster is gone...
Is that the end of it?
No, Sabotegron isn't dead.
I can hear him fleeing
deep into the earth.
That's right... the Kamen Rider's hearing
is over ten times better than ours, right?
Mr. Tachibana. Taki.
As long as Sabotegron lives...
No, as long as Shocker continues
to seek world domination,
will you work with me?
Of course!
You bet!
Thank you.
I will slaughter all
three of them together!
Just you wait!
Name: Ichimonji Hayato.
Special skills:
Superior athleticism.
Sixth degree black belt in
judo, fifth in karate.
We will turn this
man into a cyborg
and send him to
fight Kamen Rider.
Stop this! Don't do this!
That's no good.
I thought I'd given up on being
anything but a cyborg now...
Time to get it together,
Ichimonji Hayato!
I was altered to
fight the Kamen Rider.
But the Hongo Rider saved me,
and now I'm the Kamen Rider.
Shocker must be so
disappointed in me!
What are you doing?
What brings you here this
early in the morning?
And how did you know I was here?
I've got a mysterious
sense for these things.
For instance,
say I notice my cat's gone missing.
Then in a flash, I can tell
"Oh, it's under my bed!"
So I'm a cat,
as far as you're concerned?
So, what did you want?
Oh, right.
Please, won't you photograph me?
I already told you, no.
I don't photograph women.
Are you sure?
Most men would trip over themselves
to snap a pretty girl like me.
Look, the door is this way.
I haven't given up, okay?
Hey, you forget this.
Oh, but that isn't mine.
It was in front of your
door when I arrived.
In front of my door?
Open it, why don't you?
But it's mine.
Don't be such a square!
Fine, I'll open it.
Just don't blame me if it
literally blows up in our faces.
Oh, how thrilling!
Thrilling?
A Mexican Flower...
It's beautiful!
I wish it was for me!
Stop.
Don't move.
Why not?
If you touch its
thorns, you'll die.
How do you know?
Get down!
See?
Where was it again?
What?
I saw another package
just like that.
What?
Where was it? Try to remember!
It's harder to remember
when you yell at me!
Please. I'll photograph you, even.
Just try to remember!
I know! The club...
On the counter at
the Racing Club!
Mr. Tachibana's store...
Damn you, you Shocker cowards!
Tachibana Auto Corner
What's in it?
We get to open it and find out.
Hey, it's a cactus!
What a fashionable present...
I didn't know the chairman
had such good taste...
Shiro,
why don't you wake up the boss?
Michi's been waiting
for him to time her.
I want to learn how to
ride, too.
This is a heck of a racing
club, huh?
Nobody in it knows how to ride!
Stop grumbling.
Now, hurry!
Hurry!
I can't!
I haven't shown it
to the chairman yet.
But it's just a cactus!
That was a close call...
Too damned early for all this noise...
what's up?
Mr. Tachibana,
here's the source of the noise.
A Mexican Flower.
Th-That's a cactus bomb!
A bomb?
Who brought this here?
It was that man!
He was watching to see
if it would explode...
All right...
He'll pay!
Come on, let's show him!
Hey, girls!
Hold it!
Are you okay?
I'm fine...
Take this!
Michi! You okay?
I'm fine!
Someone help! Help!
Transform.
I see... I'd heard Shocker
was cruel and callous,
but I see you'll
even kill women...
Run!
Okay!
All right... where can I find
your commander, Sabotegron?
Let this be a lesson not
to charge off blindly.
Okay!
KAMEN RIDER
Hey, say something!
Stop it, Shiro.
He's not talking.
But it's just so frustrating!
We got ourselves a hostage,
but he won't even make a peep!
According to Hayato...
I mean, the Kamen Rider,
he's a cyborg
specialized for combat.
A cyborg specialized for combat?
Yeah, they're probably
designed to be mute,
just in case they
fall into enemy hands.
That's so creepy!
If Shocker conquers the world,
you think they'll do the
same thing to everyone?
Well,
given how worthless you are,
you'll be a cyborg specialized
for mopping floors.
That's a mean joke to make.
Let's see...
Chairman.
You're not going out, are you?
You can't leave me
alone with this guy!
I am, and I can!
I'm going to drop in on Hayato.
Don't worry!
Keep watch a while.
But, Chairman...
I hope they know
what they're doing,
leaving a precious hostage
unguarded like this...
Don't blame me if
something goes wrong!
They're here... they're here!
Oh, God, they're going to
make me a janitor cyborg!
Please, spare me!
Hey, what's your problem?
I think he's trembling!
Don't scare me like that!
What are you doing here?
Look, Yuri!
It's the bad guy hostage!
That's quite a face
he's got on him...
Is he the one you two caught?
Something like that...
right, Michi?
What a shame...
I wish I'd gone along.
Hey, Shiro.
Why don't we help
you keep watch?
Thank goodness!
Even girls like you are
better than nothing...
What's that?
Oh, nothing!
It really is a creepy face...
Definitely not an
"in" look at all.
Wow, they're not even scared...
What goes on in
these girls' heads?
Ow!
Look! There's a cactus thorn
sticking out of the floor!
Murderer!
Bring it on!
I'm scared!
Mommy!
Incompetent fool!
Normally I'd kill you for this,
but we need every combatant
we can get for Operation: Z.
So I'll overlook your
failure just this once.
Understood?
Now, come along!
I need to see your permit.
Security's pretty tight, huh?
Shocker's base must be
under that statue...
All right...
That was a close one.
One more step and I'd
have been roasted.
I'll have to take
the long way around.
Sorry about this.
This is some outpost
they've got...
Gentlemen.
I will now explain
Shocker's Operation: Z.
Operation: Z, huh?
Let's hear all about it.
The total destruction of
the prominent Sakuma Dam...
This is Operation: Z.
First, let's have a
look at the Sakuma Dam.
If the Sakuma Dam is destroyed,
it will paralyze the city of
Tenryu, which lies downstream.
In the ensuing chaos,
Shocker's forces will occupy Tenryu.
We'll make this a bridgehead
for Shocker in Japan,
so that our reach can spread to
encompass the entire country.
Commander.
What weapons will we
use in the destruction?
The Mexican Flowers I brought
from Mexico, of course.
Wait a minute.
What's a guard like you doing
here in the operations division?
Guess I put on the
wrong uniform...
Take off your mask!
Damn...
I didn't realize you had different
uniforms for different divisions!
FBI scum... catch him!
I'll kill you!
Wait.
We can always kill him later.
For now, use him as bait to
lure out the Kamen Rider.
Use this man...
to lure out the Kamen Rider?
And if I arrange the destruction
of the dam in the meantime...
Good.
Take him to the dungeon!
Rider!
Taki, the storehouse for
the Mexican Flower bombs
lies beyond that wall.
Stand back.
Hurry!
One more!
Sabotegron!
Rider!
I'll take these guys.
You handle that monster!
Kamen Rider. I will not flee!
Come to me! This way!
Show yourself, Sabotegron!
Rider!
Your interference with
my plans here in Japan
has tarnished the golden
reputation I earned in Mexico.
I am going to die...
But I won't go alone.
So that the name of Sabotegron can live
on in glory in the halls of Shocker,
I will take you with me!
My life won't be lost
to a Shocker commander
who sold his soul and
his body to devils!
I won't let you
leave the arsenal!
Rider Jump!
Rider!
That's right...
He's an invincible cyborg!
The Kamen Rider beat
the monstrous Sabotegron,
who had come to
Japan from Mexico.
But Shocker would sharpen its claws in
preparation for its next opportunity.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Pirasaurus.
The mighty pro wrestler Kusaka Noboru
is transformed into Pirasaurus,
who is controlled by the
female Shocker commander Maya.
Kamen Rider ends up in a series
of clashes against Pirasaurus.
Pirasaurus
The Devil Wrestler
Join us next week for "The
Devil Wrestler, Pirasaurus."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!