KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Namekujira's
Gas Explosion Plan
Is that the computer brain?
It looks so small!
How did you do it?
This is the smallest computer
brain in history, isn't it?
Doctor Yajima,
just what is it capable of?
Consider my computer brain
to be a miniature computer.
I've implanted the computer brain
into the head of this rabbit.
It can then make the rabbit capable
of understanding all human speech.
What?
Is that really possible?
A rabbit? No way!
- Seems unbelievable!
- Unbelievable!
The computer brain's
other function
is the ability to maximize an
animal's special attributes.
For instance, before this,
this rabbit was capable
of jumping approximately
one meter.
The computer brain, though,
allows it to jump five meters with ease.
Five meters?
There's no way!
You must be joking.
Show us, Doctor!
Yes, let's have an
experiment, Doctor!
Give us a big jump!
That's incredible!
Here.
Congratulations, Papa!
The experiment worked!
Think of what would happen
if you put that into a human!
There, there, dear.
This doesn't look good...
Why not?
Because Shocker's
gonna want that thing.
To defeat the Kamen Rider,
who stands in the way of Shocker's
plans for world domination,
I must create even more powerful
cyborgs than ever before.
To accomplish this,
you must steal Doctor Yajima's invention,
the computer brain!
Go, Namekujira!
Damn. A computer brain, huh?
A man could make a lot of money
with something like that...
Wanna try it?
What did you say?
I said, let's do it.
Yajima
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Heave-ho!
D-Damn...
A little higher!
Keep quiet!
Here!
There we go!
Here, right here.
Hey, Tetsu.
Is that the computer brain?
Right below us,
just as expected.
Thank goodness!
Time for the guided vacuum tube.
Do not interfere!
Damn!
Oh no!
Close it!
What was that monster?
That was just an illusion!
Let's get out of here, fool!
Right!
What is that?
The computer brain is protected
by an infrared sensor.
An alarm will go off the
second anyone touches it.
You mean,
someone was in this room?
Well... there's no sign
of anyone entering, but...
Hey, Bro. Let's call it off.
There's no way we can get
through security that tight.
Don't be a fool.
Listen.
We're gonna steal that computer brain
and sell it off to another country.
It'll fetch 300 million
yen, easy.
Upsy-daisy...
Bro, you okay?
You think this thing's
worth 300 million?
Yeah...
Just grab it and go!
Here we go.
We got away.
C'mon!
We lost them...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine...
Thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen...
That hurt!
Bro!
Run!
Catch them!
Hurry!
Who are you people?
It's coming!
Give me that artificial brain!
You gotta be kidding me!
There's no way we're giving it up after
we worked that hard to steal it! Right?
You want to die, then?
What should we do?
He says we'll die.
We'd better run quick!
- Right!
- Get them!
Oh no!
Bro!
Hold it!
You've shown yourself,
Shocker cyborg!
Get them!
Hayato! Are you all right?
Transform!
Withdraw!
That was close!
I thought if I implanted you with
that computer brain, Namekujira,
I could increase the power of your
liquid jets dozens of times over,
allowing you to even melt
through these steel gasholders.
But now that Kamen Rider has
arrived, our plans have changed!
You okay, Midori?
Go ahead.
I'm tired.
Don't you worry!
I'll get some food.
Get some for me, too!
No problem!
I always take care of girls!
Help me! Someone!
KAMEN RIDER
Open your eyes and look closely.
Excellent.
Now, listen closely to
what I am about to say.
When the clock strikes ten,
feed this tranquilizer
to Ichimonji and Taki.
We were all worried about
you, Midori.
Sorry!
Here you are.
Huh? You're not gonna have
some, Midori?
No, since I'm going to bed soon.
Go on, drink up.
Sure.
I must be exhausted from
all that worrying...
I'm suddenly very sleepy.
Well,
I think I'll get some rest.
Hayato, please continue
to handle security.
Certainly.
I'm going to bed, too.
- Good night.
A special FBI antidote.
It's probably just
a tranquilizer.
He'll recover on his own.
Yeah.
Now... time to see what they
have planned for tonight.
Taki.
The computer brain is gone!
Excellent. Well done.
Go.
Hold it.
You're going to let him go?
We should watch and see how
they're controlling Midori.
Damn...
Don't worry.
They'll slip up sooner or later.
What's the matter?
Is the surgery still in progress?
Yes.
We can't figure out how to
connect the computer brain
to his nervous system.
I don't think we can
perform the surgery.
That's fine. I've already
taken the appropriate measures.
Only I know how to use
the computer brain.
Who would take it?
And to what purpose?
I'm working now, dear.
Please leave.
Doctor Yajima.
No need to be
startled, Doctor Yajima.
Your daughter is currently
under Shocker's control.
If you don't want her to
die, follow her to our base.
Then the one who stole
the computer brain was...
Yes. Your very own daughter!
Very well...
How far must I go?
Turn right at the next light.
Ow!
Just where are we going?
We're getting a signal
from Taki's transmitter.
Damn you, Shocker...
I'll put a stop to this.
It's finished.
Well done.
Namekujira.
Your power should be
amplified by dozens of times.
Initiate our gasholder
detonation plan at once.
Gasholder detonation...
You're going to use my
computer brain for that?
Doctor Yajima.
Let me give you a demonstration
of Namekujira's power.
And now it's your turn!
I'm scared, Papa!
Don't do this!
Papa.
Hold it, Shocker!
Wait.
Let's move on to the next plan!
The next plan?
They said something about
blowing up gasholders!
Damn...
Now's our chance... blow it up!
Damn!
Transform!
I've been waiting for
you, Namekujira!
I won't let you touch
these holding tanks!
Get back here, Namekujira!
Taki!
Rider!
Rider Kick!
Rider Double Throw!
Rider! Rider!
Rider!
Rider's heroics kept Tokyo
from a gas detonation disaster.
But Shocker's evil
would not be dissuaded.
Rider renews his pledge to fight
whatever enemies tomorrow brings.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the snowy mountain
monster Bearkonger.
Exciting action unfolds
as Rider skids through the
Kusatsu Highlands on a snowmobile.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Showdown!!
Snowy Mountain Monster Bearkonger!"
Showdown!! Snowy
Mountain Monster Bearkonger
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!