KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Monstrous Inokabuton,
Defeat
Kamen Rider
With Insanity Gas
Keiyo Penitentiary
It's time for your execution.
Come along.
Any last words?
This isn't the end.
I will... I will crawl my way out of hell,
and murder all of you.
Who are you?
Let me go!
Where am I?
Where am I?!
No need to worry.
I'm here to grant your wish.
Who the hell are you?
General Black.
General Black?
I heard your call...
You wanted to crawl your way
out of hell and murder those men.
I've been searching for a man like you.
What?
General Black.
This is just the man
we've been looking for.
We must modify him, set him loose,
and turn Tokyo into
a city of corpses at once.
Hey. What are you going to do to me?
We saved you from execution.
You'd best do as we say.
These men are going to transfer
your brain to another body
to create a powerful rival
for the Kamen Rider.
Don't do it!
D-Don't...
Murayama Zoo
I guess it's gonna be dawn soon.
We'd better set things up fast.
Yeah, our animals do like
an early breakfast.
Can't say no to them!
- See ya!
- Yeah!
Hey! Kawasaki!
What's wrong?
One of the boars got out!
It got out?
Let's find it!
They say they breathed out some yellow
powder and they were both passed out.
Yellow powder?
What could it be?
The forensics lab is
investigating now, apparently.
But they said it had an
oppressively bad smell.
What about the boar that broke
out of its cage and escaped?
It didn't leave any tracks, they say.
It's like it vanished into thin air.
Oh, please. Animals don't just vanish!
But a boar went missing, and the
caretakers were found unconscious.
There has to be a connection there.
Pops, where are the caretakers now?
They were admitted to a
hospital close to the zoo.
- Going to visit?
- Yes.
Okay. Taki's not here,
so I'll join you instead.
- Sure.
- You handle things here.
Reporters, from a newspaper?
They're not allowed visitors now.
You should see their supervising doctor,
Mr. Sekiguchi, for interviews.
We're trying to investigate.
We'd really like to see them.
Where are they?
I'm afraid I can't reveal that.
Call 110!
Call the police... a patient's turned wild!
Are you all right?
What happened?
Hey, what's wrong?
Pops, this is...
Oh no!
We were too late...
Sekiguchi! What's wrong?
Don't touch the powder!
Carry him to the bed, but be careful.
Who are you people?
We'll explain later.
Now, hurry!
Bind his limbs to keep him from moving.
Hongo!
They're dead.
Wretched Hongo...
Experiments for our latest plan,
Operation: Tokyo Poison
Gas Extinction are proceeding well.
My leader. Did you see?
But General Black... do not
underestimate the Kamen Rider.
Be sure to finish him off before
moving the plan forward.
Are you Gel Shocker's monster?
That's right. I'm Inokabuton!
Hongo Takeshi... prepare to die!
Hongo!
Watch out, Pops!
Damn you...
Pops!
Well? Do you see what I can do now?
Inokabuton... we'll finish this later!
Get out of my way!
Damn you!
Kabashima Hospital
We've never seen a poison
gas like this before.
We're trying to analyze it
as fast as we can,
but I'm afraid there's nothing
we can do before then.
I see.
I need to destroy that
monster as soon as possible.
Mr. Hongo!
Naoki and Mitsuru sent this.
They said they saw the monster.
"In the forest in Tsukimigaoka."
Good.
Will you be all right alone, Mr. Hongo?
Yeah, I'll be fine. Look after Pops.
Right!
There you are, Gel Shocker...
I don't have time to deal with small fry.
Where is Inokabuton?
I'll face you!
Inokabuton!
Your life will soon be at an end!
Try me!
Rider Transformation!
I just have to disable his nose...
General Black.
Things seem to be going
poorly for Inokabuton.
How do you expect him
to defeat the Kamen Rider?
My leader.
I've given Inokabuton a terrifying weapon
in addition to his insanity gas.
Inokabuton... now's your chance!
Kill the Kamen Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
Inokabuton Horn Gouge!
Well, Kamen Rider?
How do you like my other weapon?
What did you...
That wound will never close.
You'll be dead soon!
Enjoy your final minutes on Earth!
Damn...
Mr. Takeshi!
I don't see him...
Yeah...
It's Mr. Takeshi!
Mr. Takeshi!
Naoki, Mitsuru...
You okay, Mr. Takeshi?
Mr. Takeshi...
Doctor, my blood type is O.
Please use my blood to save Mr. Takeshi!
Use my blood, too!
We've done everything we can.
Now we just need to wait
for his will to revive.
If only Mr. Taki were here...
Where am I?
Hold still for now.
Mr. Hongo!
Mr. Takeshi!
Is that you, Mitsuru?
Don't move yet, Hongo!
You're still receiving blood.
What's that?
Inokabuton is causing havoc
in an amusement park!
People are collapsing everywhere!
What did you say?
You can't move yet!
Inokabuton is in an amusement
park filled with people.
I can't stay here.
Doctor, please remove the drip!
I can't do that!
You don't have enough blood.
If you fight now, you'll die!
I'll be fine!
No! As a doctor, I cannot allow it!
He's right.
You shouldn't push yourself too hard!
Emergency! Mr. Tachibana broke
quarantine and stole a motorbike!
What?
Pops did?
Run away, everyone! Hurry!
Hongo! You never learn, do you?
But this time, you die!
Hongo... die!
Rider Transformation!
Die, Kamen Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
Pops...
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Tachibana!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Pops!
With my shining machine...
My poison gas has infected
Tachibana's mind, too!
Rider Jump!
Tachibana, kill him!
Rider Kick!
Kill the Kamen Rider!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
- Stop it, Pops!
- Kill him!
Rider, Rider!
Kamen Rider...
Shocker is coming,
You seem to have reached the limits
of what you can do with your blood loss...
with its armies made of demons
This is the moment I've been waiting for.
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
Kamen Rider... at last, I'll end you!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Die!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Tachibana...
Damn you... You betrayed me!
Don't underestimate me.
You think I'd sell my soul...
to a devil like you?
Shocker is coming
Pops...
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
Pops!
Darn it...
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Pops!
I'll be fine. Go!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Hold it!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Inokabuton Spike-Wheel!
Cyclone Attack!
Rider!
You're all right?
Pops...
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Gel Shocker's insanity gas plan
was successfully foiled.
But the Kamen Rider would
continue to face new challenges.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Kamen Rider.
I, General Black,
have sent you Isogin Jaguar...
Can you break free of his hellish trap?
Next week will be creator Shotaro Ishimori's
first time in the director's chair.
He'll give us speedy action
and a strong, awesome Kamen Rider.
We of Gel Shocker hate to admit it, but we do find it amusing.
Rider in Peril!
Isogin Jaguar's Hellish Trap
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!