KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Soaring Monster
Musasabeedle
Ready, Doctor?
Yes.
We've done it!
The explosive power
is incredible!
Doctor.
The explosive power of
this brand new liquid fuel
will let us power rockets
big enough to reach Mars!
Let's use it as fuel for the
rocket test tomorrow in Hokkaido.
Doctor.
Will a mere 100ccs of this new
fuel really power that rocket?
It will.
I know this will work.
We need it to work,
if we ever want rockets to get to Mars.
We did it!
The experiment worked, Doctor!
Its energy is truly amazing.
Incredible...
To get that much explosive power
from just 100ccs of fuel...
Rise, Musasabeedle.
Capable of 100 meter jumps
and 200 meter glides...
It's time for you to put those
skills of yours to the test.
Musasabeedle,
steal the liquid fuel
stored in the warehouse
at Osumi Laboratory.
If I may, Great Leader.
What do you want with that fuel?
The experiment Osumi
conducted this morning
proved the incredible
explosive power of that fuel.
The 700ccs still in the
warehouse possess explosive power
comparable to one
kiloton of TNT.
We will steal it,
and use it to destroy Sapporo!
Great Leader.
Musasabeedle.
Use that man as a guinea
pig to test your power!
A m-monster!
The slipstream phenomenon:
When Musasabeedle passes
overhead at supersonic speed,
it creates a momentary state
of vacuum in the man's body,
which tears his
organs to shreds.
Someone looks mad.
Where are Yuri and the others?
They're...
Off on vacation.
Who takes a vacation when
there's so much work to be done?!
Work?
I don't see any customers...
What's that?
Did you say something?
Whoops.
Where's Taki?
He went with them.
He said it was FBI orders.
The FBI...
I bet they've learned something.
All matched up.
Hey, clear the way.
What?
Here, Yuri!
Ow!
Boys be ambitious!
We should've come here
first, huh, Yuri?
We can see the whole
city like this!
Mr. Taki! A monster!
A monster?
Come on, don't tease me.
Shocker!
I'll take care of that monster.
Goro, Yuri.
Head back to the hotel.
Got it?
Okay!
Osumi Laboratory
Go on.
Shocker came in here
to get something.
What could it be?
You can't just come
barging in here!
And what, exactly, is Shocker?
We don't have anything that
anyone would possibly want here.
Hey!
Hey, you!
Where's the liquid fuel?
A m-monster...
Get back here, Shocker!
You've shown yourself,
Ichimonji Hayato!
Wretched cyborg...
Get back here!
Transform!
Kamen Rider!
What are you plotting
now, Shocker monster?
How about a test, Rider?
You can experience one
kiloton of explosives...
enough to blow up
the Diet building!
One kiloton?
That little case contains
one kiloton of explosives?
It must have come from
Osumi Laboratory, then...
Of course!
Give up and go home.
Very well.
I'll go!
But I'm taking this with me!
Why, you...
Wretched Kamen Rider...
I'll get you next time!
You must return with that
fuel, no matter what the cost!
We must turn Sapporo
into a wasteland!
And we need that liquid fuel to
bolster our battle power as well.
Hard to believe you could blow
up the Diet building with this...
But that's why
Shocker's after it.
I know it's crucial
for human advancement,
but it's a dangerous
thing you've invented...
Hayato, what is that?
A mini-transmitter.
We're dealing with Shocker.
We can't let our guard
down for a moment.
Taki.
You need to stop
running off without me.
But...
I have my duty to the FBI...
Hayato...
Taki, you don't need
to worry any longer.
If we break it down so it loses its
explosive capability, Shocker can't use it.
Doctor...
Are you abandoning
your own research?
Not abandoning.
We've spent the past three
years on nothing but this.
But I'm afraid I
need to destroy it.
To turn it into plain water...
Doctor...
Hello? It's me.
If a man from the Tokyo Radiation
Center arrives, send him to my room.
That's right.
Radiation Center?
He's bringing the special
radioactive material, 235,
which will convert
this fuel into water.
Yuri?
Hayato!
What are you doing here?
You, too, Goro!
We came here to
beat the monster!
What?
What did you say?
Shocker, in Hokkaido?
Damn...
So, how are things
going on your end?
I managed to recover the new
fuel from Shocker, but...
Hold on a minute.
If I leave now,
I can make Flight 105 from Haneda.
Okay, be there in two hours.
Listen, Hayato.
Take it easy until I get there.
Okay?
Ch-Chairman...
Let's see...
Sorry,
but you kids watch the store.
KAMEN RIDER
Chitose Airport
Japan Radiation Center
I'm from the Hokkaido Branch.
I'll show you the way.
That's strange.
Did someone contact them?
Get on in.
Hey, what's this smoke about?
Driver...
M-Monster!
We brought the special radioactive
substance, 235, that Doctor Osumi asked for.
Glad you're here. Come right in.
Who's there?
We're from the Radiation Center.
Good to see you.
I don't recognize you two...
And on the phone,
they said they'd be sending one man.
Shocker!
Hayato, this way!
Taki, you handle things here!
Transform!
Pursue Kamen Rider. Get him!
I'll track that monster!
Mari!
What are you lazing around for?
Why are you dressed like that?
What is this thing?
The Chairman asked me
to watch the store.
But I'm skipping out,
so I needed a disguise.
Okay, let's go!
Stay put for a while.
I know.
I've got a good idea.
Let's make the hostages
reveal Shocker's base!
I'm in!
Then we'll really
show up the Chairman!
Some people never learn!
You won't escape!
Strange...
the case is getting further away.
I need to turn back.
Of course... Musasabeedle
and the combatants split up!
45 degrees south, eh?
You'd better take us
right to your base!
And no funny business!
Mount Showa-Shinzan, eh?
Where'd it get off to?
There you are, Shocker monster!
Die!
It's not far...
Lake Toya, eh?
What's wrong, Tobei?
Aren't you going to fight back?
I'll just finish you
off, then...
There you are, Kamen Rider...
Why, you...
What's so funny?!
Kamen Rider...
look there, at Mount Usu!
- Shikotsu-Toya National Park
- Mount Usu
If you don't want them dead,
hand that case over to me.
Do it, Kamen Rider!
You leave me no choice...
Just do it!
Release them!
Darn you...
Now!
Goro! All of you, run!
Mr. Chairman!
Are you all right? Speak to me!
You won't escape!
Rider Kick!
He did it!
Is Rider dead?
No, he's just fine.
Kamen Rider isn't dead.
I'm so glad!
Yes, I'm sure he's all right...
But with idiots like you around,
even the Kamen Rider
might have a rough time...
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen
Rider, was able to stop
Shocker's terrible plan
to blow up Hokkaido.
And Ichimonji Hayato renewed
his pledge to fight Shocker,
with his wonderful
allies by his side.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the poisonous
monster Kinokomorg.
A creature covered in
poisonous mushrooms,
Kinokomorg attacks Kamen Rider
with his terrifying spores.
Their battle unfolds in a
factory deep in the mountains.
Join us next week for "Poisonous
Monster Kinokomorg Attacks!"
Poisonous Monster
Kinokomorg Attacks!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!