KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Deathmatch! The Monstrous Snowman
Versus
the Two Riders
The Alps, a mountain range near the
border between Italy and Switzerland,
echoes with bells
celebrating a new year.
Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year!
I'm going to read my
luck in the new year!
I'm gonna start
deciphering this code.
An unlucky card...
Your fortunes never come
true, Mika!
That's so rude.
Mr. Hongo said my fortunes
are very accurate!
Hold on!
I'm getting an
unusual message...
- An earthquake!
- Emi, look out!
Look, everyone!
What is that?
It's a volcano!
The Alps are erupting!
Look out! Mika, run!
The avalanche is
coming right for us!
A series of mysterious eruptions in
the Alps threw Europe into mass panic.
Congratulations.
The experiment was a grand success.
A toast...
to Shocker's great leader,
and to our conquest
of the world.
And a toast to Doctor Shinigami
and Shocker's Swiss Branch.
No... save that toast until I've removed
the greatest thorn in Shocker's side...
Until I've conquered Japan!
Tell me how you plan
to conquer Japan.
Japan is one of the world's
leading volcanic zones.
I will stimulate the magma
beneath those volcanoes,
causing them to erupt
one after another,
and throw them into chaos.
And what is your first target?
I'll start with the
south of Kyushu.
I'll dig a tunnel between
Kirishima and Sakurajima
and spark an eruption in the
Kirishima volcanic region.
Emergency!
Our Japan operation
plans have been stolen!
You fool! Catch the thief!
Then kill them!
We should be safe now...
Return the plans
you stole from us!
I don't know what
you're talking about!
We'll force it out of you!
Get them!
- Rider!
Wretched Kamen Rider...
He's come to save those
girls, has he?
But I won't let any of
you leave here alive...
Go, Snowman!
Burn Kamen Rider with
the power of magma!
- Get on!
- Okay!
Ready?
Hold on tight!
Another earthquake!
Kamen Rider!
Go on without me!
Right!
Rider!
Are you a Shocker cyborg?
I'm Snowman,
made from a modified Himalayan Yeti!
Die, Kamen Rider!
Snowman...
Feel the power of my Rider Kick!
Rider Kick!
I've killed Kamen Rider!
I, the great Snowman!
I don't stand a
chance like this.
Snowman, eh...
A truly powerful cyborg.
Well, viewers?
Do you remember this man?
That's right.
He's Hongo Takeshi, who once fought
Shocker as the first Kamen Rider.
He left the protection of Japan to
Ichimonji Hayato, the second Kamen Rider,
while he fought Shocker's
destructive plots in Europe.
- Mr. Hongo!
These two girls, Emi and Mika,
have been fighting Shocker as
Hongo Takeshi's assistants.
Kamen Rider saved us!
But this is serious!
Shocker's readying a major offensive!
A major Shocker offensive?
Here are the
classified documents!
They're planning on blowing
up Kyushu's volcanic zone?
Emi, Mika...
Take this,
and go to Japan at once.
What should we do
when we get there?
Go to the Tachibana
Racing Club in Tokyo.
Find a man named Ichimonji
Hayato, and give it to him.
I'll follow soon after.
Understood?
This is the Sakurajima Earthquake
Monitoring Station in Kagoshima Prefecture.
Hey, Okada! Look at this!
What's all the shouting about?
The movement of the needle
suggests new seismic activity.
Right.
We might see a major
eruption on Sakurajima again.
All right.
Contact the main office in Tokyo.
Hey! Hold the boat!
Wait for us!
We've got visitors
from Switzerland!
Wait for us!
Wait!
There!
We made it in time!
This way.
Thank you all for riding the
car ferry Saintpaulia today.
We'll be traveling 887
kilometers at 20 knots,
37 kilometers per hour,
from Kawasaki to Hyuga in Kyushu,
and will arrive in
twenty-five hours.
We hope you'll all enjoy
this journey with us.
Mr. Chairman, how'd it go?
No luck...
I was sure Hayato and Taki
got on board with us, but...
They're not on the
passenger roll!
What?
Think we should head back, then?
Don't be silly.
We already left port.
It's not going to stop
until we get to Kyushu.
Yeah, there's no swimming
home, I guess...
I know! Let's enjoy sightseeing
on the way to Kyushu!
Children are so irresponsible.
Did you say something?
It's a problem, isn't it?
Yes... We need to get those
documents to Hayato at once.
I knew those girls
would show themselves.
But why is Ichimonji
Hayato not with them?
Mr. Chairman.
Are Hayato and Mr. Taki
really on board?
Yes. But how will we find them?
Searching a ship of this
size is no easy feat...
What does that matter?
Let's check the
cabins, one by one!
Okay, let's go!
- Hey! Wait!
- Wait for me!
Let's look down here first!
This way!
Not here.
This one's a girl.
It's empty!
Let's see.
That's a locker, so...
This is the last room!
Royal room...
There's no way Hayato would
get such a grand cabin.
But we have to make sure!
Right.
Come in.
Excuse us.
May I help you?
We have the wrong room.
Nice weather we're having, huh?
I guess he's just not here.
But what a creepy old man!
Yeah, but don't sweat it.
Let's go!
This isn't good.
We'll have to be careful,
or they'll notice us.
That's right.
Hongo Takeshi's message
from Switzerland said
that Shocker was sending a
high commander to Kyushu.
So he's in that room, is he?
He has to be.
But maybe we should get the Shocker
documents from those Swiss girls first.
We can't, yet.
They're being watched.
If we show ourselves now,
Shocker will know what we're after.
Snowman! Snowman!
Show yourself!
Doctor Shinigami.
Shall I sink this ship?
Wait. Don't be hasty.
Your first mission is to retrieve
our classified documents.
And without being detected.
KAMEN RIDER
Mika, you do
fortune-telling with cards?
Quiet down!
She's trying to concentrate.
The ace of spades...
What's wrong?
I'm worried about this trip...
I won't be able to sleep until
we get these to Hayato...
I'll hold it, then.
But...
What, you don't trust me?
You may be Hongo
Takeshi's assistants,
but I'm Ichimonji
Hayato's assistant.
Go right ahead, then.
I appreciate it.
No luck again...
Taki!
Mr. Taki!
Hush!
What's wrong?
Get inside, quickly!
Where's Hayato?
We've been searching everywhere!
Circumstance demanded it.
But where are the secret documents
that Hongo sent from Switzerland?
Yuri has them!
- Yuri does?
- Yeah!
This is just wonderful.
I'm getting sleepy.
So am I.
Probably because I left the
responsibility with Yuri.
So mean!
But go ahead and sleep.
See you later, then.
See you! Let's go.
I think someone's there...
Why are you after that woman?
- Tell me!
- Never!
Damn...
Why, you... get back here!
Shocker was after Yuri.
Taki, take care of the others.
What will you do?
I'll head for the Ebino Highlands
the moment the boat pulls into port.
We'll meet up again there.
After 25 hours at sea, the ship pulls
into port at Hyuga Harbor, Kyushu.
Japan Car Ferry Hyuga Terminal
What will we do with that
Hayato, anyway?
He completely disappeared
without showing himself once!
He's probably waiting at the
hotel in Ebino Highlands.
Let's go, then!
You cannot hide from
me, Ichimonji Hayato.
I'll drag you out into the open!
Ebino Highlands
Awesome!
This'll make a great picture!
Hey, hurry!
This way!
- Wait!
Mr. Taki!
Why are you dressed like that?
I needed something
more comfortable.
So we swapped outfits!
You and who?
Well? Suits me, doesn't it?
Yeah. You look great.
I wish I'd worn jeans like
you, Emi.
- Lend them to me later, okay?
- Sure thing!
What's wrong, Mika?
Grab her!
Mika!
Someone help!
Mika! Emi!
Mika! Hey, Mika!
Goro...
Emi... Emi's gone!
Shocker must have...
Shocker?
Kill the girl.
But couldn't we
use her as a decoy?
Look carefully, Snowman.
She's wearing the clothes
of Ichimonji's companion,
but the face is wrong.
Doctor Shinigami,
I will kill this woman,
then bring Ichimonji's
companion at once.
See that you do not fail again.
You can't kill someone
for mistaken identity!
Emi!
Emi! Emi!
You're safe!
Thank goodness...
FBI brat!
Get him!
- Run away, fast!
- Okay!
Hurry!
Snowman...
the one you're after is right here!
Hayato!
I don't know what you're
plotting here in Kyushu,
but I won't let you
get away with it!
Ichimonji Hayato...
I will fight you!
Transform!
Snowman! Someone already
leaked your entire plan to us!
Kamen Rider...
This is why I must
kill you first!
Those were my orders
from Doctor Shinigami!
Doctor Shinigami?
A new Shocker commander?
Where is he?
Kamen Rider...
That voice.
That old man... of course!
Snowman, do it.
Kill Rider!
Magma from the deep...
burn Kamen Rider to death!
Another Kamen Rider?!
Rider Kick!
Hayato...
Hongo.
It looks like this new commander
may appear in Kyushu again.
Yes.
I'll work with you.
Shocker's attack has begun.
With the aid of Hongo Takeshi who
came from Switzerland to help,
Ichimonji Hayato will do everything
he can to stop their evil plans.
But what horrors does Doctor
Death have planned for them?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the magma monster Ghoster.
Shocker creates a monster capable
of withstanding up to 5000 degrees
and sends it to blow up
Sakurajima in Kyushu.
The two Riders must work
together to stop him.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "Magma Monster Ghoster
The Great Battle of Sakurajima."
Magma Monster Ghoster
The Great Battle of Sakurajima
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!