KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
No need to be scared.
Lightning won't strike a car.
But lightning
really scares me...
Rain, huh?
What's that?
What's wrong, Toshiki?
This isn't rain... it's sand.
Sand, falling from the sky...
But how?
It's no use.
Yukiko, take the wheel.
I'll push.
There's so much sand...
This is awful...
What's going on here?
It's too creepy.
I want to get out of
here as soon as possible!
We will.
When I give the
signal, slam the gas.
Toshiki, the car!
The car is sinking!
Run! Hurry!
I'm scared!
Toshiki, help me!
Help me!
Shocker's artificial
antlion pit is a success.
The antlion pits that
I, Jigoku Thunder, create
will tear apart
Japanese roadways.
Shocker will take advantage of the
chaos to begin its main offensive!
The Terrifying Antlion Pit
Why so timid, fools?
As long as the great Jigoku Thunder stands
among you, Shocker's Japan Branch will...
We have orders from our leader.
Leader?
Yes.
Colonel Zol has been dispatched to become
commander-in-chief of the Japan Branch.
Colonel Zol?
The most powerful
man in all Shocker?
Your uniform is sloppy.
Sloppy uniforms mean
sloppy soldiers.
Now that I'm here,
we'll be running a tight ship.
That's Colonel Zol.
Emergency orders from
FBI central headquarters.
"Colonel Zol, a high commander with Shocker
who we've been tracking for a while,
has transferred from Shocker's Near and
Middle East Branch to its Japan Branch.
We'll be on high alert."
Colonel Zol...
He's killed countless skilled FBI agents
who've pursued Shocker in the past.
All right...
It's time to avenge
my colleagues!
Unexplained cave-ins have been
occurring across major roadways
all over the Japanese mainland,
causing major traffic snarls.
The government has
launched an inquiry, but so
far, they're no closer
to finding a solution.
Seems fishy to me...
Right, Pops?
Yeah, there's no way those amateurs
will be able to find Shocker's trail.
I know! It's time for you two
to take action, then, right?
Good grief...
Nothing's going to happen
in an area like this.
I'd better take a break.
Taki.
Mr. Taki!
Hey, find anything?
No, nothing.
Well, want to hit a rest stop?
Sure.
This is so boring.
I'm a thrill-seeker, you know.
I came hoping for some excitement...
Enough of that, now.
Peace and quiet is always best.
Now, let's head back.
Money's on the table.
Thank you, sir.
Colonel Zol,
I have Taki Kazuya's voice on tape.
A picture of Taki and a
recording of his voice.
Now I have all I need.
Sending agents into
the enemy ranks...
It's how I crushed all resistance to
Shocker in the Near and Middle East.
Now that I'm here in Japan,
I will put an end to Shocker's hated
enemy, the Kamen Rider.
Money's on the table.
Thank you, sir.
No Entry
Reporting in.
Good to have you.
Stop!
Hey, you!
Wait!
- Get him!
- Right!
- Go that way!
- Yes, sir!
Hey! Wait!
Why, you...
Damn you...
Now,
have a good look at my face...
Damn...
I don't like the
look of those clouds.
I think it's more than
just the clouds...
I thought it was
raining, but it's sand!
You're right!
Taki, head back and stop any
other cars coming this way.
All right.
Traffic duty, huh?
I always wanted to try that once.
It's pretty cool.
Take this irresponsible
girl and head back.
What will you do, Hayato?
I'll see for myself
what happens next.
Damn...
I knew Shocker was behind this!
You think you can stand against Shocker?
You fool!
Transform!
Die, Rider!
Kamen Rider... plunge into the
antlion pit of Jigoku Thunder!
Kamen Rider.
Great though your powers may be,
they are worthless
in my antlion pit!
I know!
There we go...
I hope Taki and Yuri
are doing all right...
KAMEN RIDER
Stop!
You!
What are you doing,
directing traffic?
It's dangerous up ahead!
Not even police
should go through.
Right, Mr. Taki?
There's been a cave-in down the
road two kilometers from here.
Y-You!
Me? What about me?
You're under arrest for murder
and interfering with an officer!
Don't move!
What are you doing?
Don't play dumb!
We know everything!
What did he do?
He's the one who
attacked us earlier!
There must be a mistake.
I didn't do it!
Be quiet!
We'll get to the bottom of this.
We're taking you to the station!
You're really
going to arrest me?
Are you resisting?
There's been some
kind of mistake.
But an investigation will
clear my name easily.
I'll go along with you.
Mr. Taki...
Tell Hayato what happened here.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Come along!
Wait!
Taki Kazuya...
You can sate yourself on
prison meals for a while.
All right.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven.
One, two...
Stay out.
No visitors until the
investigation is over.
But it's ridiculous.
Mr. Taki can't be a murderer.
I was with him all day!
I was there on the scene.
I know he's the one.
Were you at the scene as well?
I was one of the men injured!
I'd never forget the face
of the man who did it.
Now get lost, before we charge
you as accessories to murder.
How rude!
I'm a lady.
I wouldn't hurt a fly!
Let's head back to
the club for now.
Come on, don't sulk.
But can't a murder conviction
lead to the death penalty?
Taki hasn't done anything wrong.
They don't put
innocent men to death.
But the witnesses...
I'm going to go see Taki.
You wait here.
How are you going to see
him, though?
I'll use a few drastic measures.
Looking good!
Not bad at all!
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three...
Taki!
Hayato!
You're looking well.
Did you come here
to vouch for me?
Yes,
but they wouldn't accept it.
They claim they saw your face.
What did you say?
This could be a Shocker trap!
Yes.
But why only set
the trap for you?
They must have a cyborg
that's copied your face.
Almost there!
It's obvious to us,
but they may not believe that
there's another man out there
who looks exactly like you.
Hayato, get me out of there.
I want to catch the impostor
and prove my innocence.
I can't do that.
If you escape now,
you'll look more guilty than before.
What if that Shocker cyborg
no longer looks like you?
How would we prove your
innocence, then?
But I...
Just sit tight for a
while, all right?
You insensitive fool, Hayato!
Hey. Are you trying to
break into the station?
No!
- Help!
- Sorry!
Good grief...
Yuri and Goro are
causing trouble again.
Hang tight, Taki.
H-Hay...
Damn you, Shocker!
Taki.
Mr. Taki!
I'm so glad! You made it out?
I'm sorry to worry
you, everyone.
See...
After you left,
I was attacked by Shocker.
What then?
They arrested him.
He looked exactly like me...
And so, they let me go.
I see.
They thought they could
divide and conquer.
But I'm glad you're safe.
We'll resume our highway
investigations tomorrow.
Now, go home!
I wanna come tomorrow, too!
Take me, too!
Time for women and
children to head home!
Don't be like that!
Please, Hayato!
Come on!
Good night.
Now, let's do some
prep work for tomorrow.
I'll destroy Ichimonji Hayato
with this time bomb.
Then, victory will be ours.
Are you so sure about that?
Hayato!
Only my friends call me that...
Shocker cyborg!
I... I'm not...
I've seen through your trick.
Look!
I see.
The resemblance is uncanny...
What are you doing here?
Taki Kazuya is part of the FBI's
Shocker investigation team.
They used their influence
to get him released.
If the jig is up,
I can abandon this face.
You!
Allow me to introduce myself.
Formerly head of Shocker's
Near and Middle East Branch,
now deployed to their Japan Branch...
Colonel Zol.
A senior Shocker commander?
All who hear my name
and see my face must die!
Damn you...
Wait!
I'll handle the small fry.
Good luck, Taki!
All right...
Again?
Ichimonji Hayato!
This time,
I'll finish your bike with you!
There's only one
way to escape...
Transform!
Rider Kick!
Rider!
Our highways are safe again.
Kamen Rider!
Jigoku Thunder will be avenged.
As long as I,
Colonel Zol, am here,
Shocker's conquest of
Japan is inevitable.
Mukadelas!
Begin preparations for
your operation at once.
What is the nature of this new
Shocker cyborg, Mukadelas?
And what is Shocker plotting?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Mukadelas!
The monstrous Mukadelas uses hypnotic
waves to kidnap intelligent children.
Goro is made to
join Junior Shocker.
Mukadelas attacks Ichimonji
Hayato and Taki Kazuya.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Mukadelas' Monster School!"
Mukadelas' Monster School!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!