KAMEN RIDER
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Garaox's
Flying Cars!!
Katsuhiko, this is so nice.
Yeah, the air really
is better outside of Tokyo.
Yes...
Is that mist?
Katsuhiko...
It's really thick... damn.
I can't see an inch in front of me...
Sanae, close the windows.
Right.
Strange... we should be
out of the tunnel by now.
But I can't even tell where
we are with all this fog.
I'm scared!
I'll get out and have a look outside.
You stay here, okay?
Right.
Katsuhiko!
We're in the air!
We're up in the sky!
No!
Help me!
Behold the power of the devil mist!
Katsuhiko!
Someone's falling from the sky!
Rider Transformation!
Taki, we must get to the
bottom of this at once!
Okay, got it.
Hey, speak to me! Hey!
A toll road...
Kamen Rider
Kid Corps Headquarters
Devil mist! Help! Help!
I can't make sense of it.
How could a person fall from the sky?
I know!
I bet he was skydiving!
Without a parachute?
Good point...
I see...
Thank you very much.
There were no aircraft passing
above at that time, they said.
So we know for sure
he didn't fall out of a plane.
This is a toll road ticket he had on him.
It's dated today.
What does it mean?
You mean he wasn't
in a plane, but in a car?
Then how did he end up in the sky?
What do you think, General Black?
My devil mist is fifty times more
powerful than hydrogen gas,
previously thought to be the
lightest substance on Earth!
It's perfect.
A victory of Gel Shocker's science division,
taking a hint from the dirigibles
of Nazi Germany.
We will use it to send all of Earth's
vehicles rising into the sky!
This will be enough to inspire
panic in the world below.
But that won't be enough
to satisfy Gel Shocker!
We'll then crash the
vehicles into the ground!
If this works, then all of Japan
will soon fall into our hands.
Go to it,
fusion cyborg of ox and
man-eating crow... Garaox!
Report!
The man in question survived.
What?
Where is that man now?
Sir. He was saved by the Kamen Rider,
and is now at the Rider
Kid Corps headquarters.
The Kamen Rider, eh?
That's perfect.
I'll use my devil mist to finish off that
man, and the Kamen Rider with him!
And you're sure this car fell from the sky?
Yes. There were quite a few witnesses.
Taki.
Hongo.
Is this it? The car that fell from the sky?
Yes.
Was anyone inside it?
A woman... I'm afraid she died.
That's awful...
A license!
This is the man I saved earlier!
Which means...
This man was definitely in this car.
Excuse me.
Do you really have to be in such a hurry?
Yes.
Could you at least wait for the
Chairman and Mr. Hongo to return?
What are you talking about?
It was Mr. Hongo who gave the order.
He did? Really?
He wants him conscious
again as soon as possible
to find out what he knows about Gel Shocker.
I see...
Goodbye, then.
Chairman!
What is it? Did the man wake up?
They just took him to the
hospital in an ambulance.
What?
Who did that?
They said they were
on orders from Mr. Hongo!
Impossible!
Contact Hongo at once!
Right!
There you are, Hongo Takeshi.
Get ready to go on the attack!
Stop! Stop this instant!
Hongo!
Hongo! The ambulance!
Rider Transformation!
You...
You've fallen for my trap, Rider.
I am Garaox.
And this is where you die!
Pipe down!
Garaox! You...
Die, Rider!
Behold the power of my devil mist!
What does this mist do?
You'll find out soon enough!
What happened to Rider?
The ambulance is flying!
Is Rider inside it?
Well, Rider?
Are you impressed
by Garaox's devil talons?
It's too cramped to fight in here.
Garaox, let's go outside!
Fool! Look out there first!
This is...
Do you now see what
the devil mist can do?
I see... the devil mist has the
power to lift anything into the air.
Die, Rider!
You'll crash into the ground,
still inside this ambulance!
No!
Rider! You will die in that form!
Wait!
It's no use!
Rider!
Rider...
KAMEN RIDER
Wait, Chairman.
Now's not the time to be
caught up in mourning.
Mr. Taki! How could you?
The Chairman thinks of
Mr. Hongo as his own son...
Choco. Enough.
Taki, I'm sorry.
I didn't consider your feelings in this.
Listen, everyone.
Gel Shocker is trying
to throw Japan into chaos
by lifting vehicles into
the air like hot air balloons.
And with Hongo gone... they'll
probably move their plan into full force.
Where?
I don't have the foggiest idea.
But we have to find it, no matter what,
and stop the attack from going forward.
Taki...
What if...
What if Gel Shocker received
news that Hongo was still alive?
That's our Chairman!
Then we could lure them to us.
Hey, Yuri!
Yes?
Open as broad a band as you can
and spread the word on radio.
What word?
"This is Kamen Rider Kid Corps HQ.
We have a patient in critical
condition. Name: Hongo Takeshi.
Prepare for surgery at once."
Got it?
Right.
Chairman. We'll avenge him.
Right!
We'll set out mines and lure them to us!
- Right.
- Let's go.
Now, destroy that bullet train!
Emergency communication!
It seems Hongo Takeshi is still alive!
What?
This is the message.
"This is Kamen Rider Kid Corps HQ.
We have a patient in critical
condition. Name: Hongo Takeshi.
Prepare for surgery at once."
Garaox!
Damn you, Hongo Takeshi!
I'll finish you off once and for all!
Hey, guys! Help us out!
Right!
Here, a blanket.
Wrap it up tight.
Right.
Okay, that should do that.
You'll look like Hongo.
Be careful!
Right.
Now, hurry!
- Right.
- Let him down.
Are you all right, Mr. Hongo?
Hang in there.
Hongo is on the road.
An emergency transmission
from headquarters?
I'll show you the power
of my talon missiles!
He's here, Taki!
Be careful.
Great. It's all going as planned.
You... You're Taki!
Where's Hongo?!
We knew that if you put
your plan into practice,
you'd throw Tokyo into a mass panic.
We put on a little act to stop you!
We did it!
Yes!
Taki! Look out!
You fool...
You thought you pitiful
weaklings could defeat me?!
Pops! Now!
Don't worry about me!
Just hit the detonator!
Pops! Do it!
Sorry, Taki...
Wait, Pops!
Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
Kamen Rider!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Garaox... your evil deeds
will not be forgiven!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Now, fight me!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
Garaox... you've picked
the wrong setting to fight.
with its armies made of demons
W-What?
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
You can only use your
demon mist in tight spaces!
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Damn!
Maybe so...
But I have one more power
to show you...
Go! Go! Let's go!
Gore!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
Rider Lunar Kick!
Hey! Takeshi!
Hey!
Pops! I'm sorry to worry you...
You idiot... if you're gonna
die, at least call first.
Pops, I'm not sure that's possible...
Hey, what do I care?
Why, you!
Garaox tried to use his terrifying
devil mist to throw Japan into chaos,
but Kamen Rider defeated him.
Still, Gel Shocker's
ambitions weren't foiled.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Next episode will feature
the monstrous Cactusbat.
Those hit with his poison needles
turn into cactuses immediately.
Gel Shocker wants to turn
all humans into cacti...
Including Hongo Takeshi!
Join us next week for "Hongo
Takeshi Becomes a Cactus Monster!?"
Hongo Takeshi Becomes
a Cactus Monster!?
The wind gusts across the wasteland
The Kamen Rider traverses it
Alone, all alone
Holding back my sadness,
I fight, I fight alone!
Despite my solitude,
I will do what it takes
to protect my friends and my home
I am the Kamen Rider!