KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Gel Shocker's Debut!
The Last Day of Kamen Rider!!
That won't be enough kindling.
Okay, Micchi, let's go get some.
Sure.
- Let's go wash the rice.
- Sure.
That should do it, right?
I'd say so.
What's that?
It's creeping me out...
Did you hear something?
It sounded like a person...
They're under the water!
They're trying to kill me!
H-Help me!
Take me to Kamen Rider's
Tokyo headquarters!
You can't escape us.
Shocker's replacement organization
has no need for the likes of you!
Sumiko!
Micchi!
Emergency!
We need to take down the camp!
Sumiko!
These must be the girls I heard screaming!
It's Shocker!
I gotta let HQ know!
What in the world is going on here?
There's too many for it to
be an execution of traitors...
Shocker's Leader said something
strange after I beat Rattlander.
He was going to erase Shocker
and create a new organization.
Then, the new organization doesn't
want the old Shocker combatants?
Yes.
Maybe they're killing
off their potential liabilities.
But... to even kill their
allies without mercy...
The new organization their leader
mentioned is a force to be reckoned with.
Yes.
We'll need to sniff them out ASAP,
or they'll surely get the better of us.
Their first mistake was
leaving the bodies behind.
Searching the corpses could give us a clue.
Stop!
There's construction here.
Please go around.
That's a pretty serious detour...
It went perfectly!
Hey, what's the matter?
I followed the detour exactly,
but it's just a dead end.
A dead end?
Okay, back up!
You're good!
You're still good!
Grab on!
Watch where you're going!
Wait...
Who are they?
Look out!
Is this the new organization
that took out Shocker?
Help me!
Hey, wait!
I knew it would be you...
Indeed. It's time for Ganikomoru to shine!
Tell us...
What's the name of your new organization?
Get back here!
Very well...
I'll tell you,
before you depart this world.
The entire Shocker organization
has been restructured!
What?
I knew it...
And Geldam, the secret organization receiving
rigorous training in the African deserts,
has been added to Shocker
as a shot in the arm!
Give us the name already!
The name is Gel Shocker!
What? Gel Shocker?
You think changing your
name will make you stronger?
Gel Shocker is an unstoppable force.
I don't even need to dirty
my hands with you.
Gel Shocker combatants, take care of them!
They're strong...
So much stronger than Shocker combatants!
Be strong.
The battle with Gel Shocker
has only just started.
They're here for the bodies
of the Shocker combatants!
Leave this to me
and take the truck!
Got it!
Gel Shocker... I will face you myself!
Kamen Rider!
Your struggles are pointless.
Ganikomoru...
I'll use those Shocker bodies,
to find your new Gel Shocker base!
You underestimate us, Kamen Rider.
Gel Shocker does not make mistakes!
What?
Did they do something to
the truck while we were fighting?
Damn you, Gel Shocker...
I will track you down!
It's too late.
In just thirty seconds,
the truck will blow up,
taking Taki with it!
Damn...
They put a time bomb on Taki's truck?
A... A time bomb?
Mr. Taki, you're in danger!
It's a time bomb!
A time bomb!
What's all this?
Not so fast!
If I'd been one second later...
Jonan University Hospital
Gel Shocker's not that hot after all.
They didn't even realize I smuggled
out one of those Shocker bodies.
My friend at the university will
have it analyzed by tomorrow.
That should give us a hint
as to Gel Shocker's whereabouts.
Not here...
Good, here it is.
Now all remnants of Shocker
are banished from this world.
Just as I expected.
Taki, Ganikomoru's on the way out.
Right. Got it.
Damn...
Where did he get off to?
KAMEN RIDER
Rider!
Gel Shocker's motorbike team, eh?
We're made up of top racers
from all over the world.
Kamen Rider... face us!
Let's see what you've got, then!
They just ran away!
Losing their commander paralyzed them.
I'm gradually coming to
understand Gel Shocker's hierarchy.
Look at that!
Talk!
Where is Gel Shocker's base in Japan?
And who's their commander-in-chief?
I d-don't know.
You think we'll buy that?
I-It's true.
The formation ceremony for Gel Shocker Japan
will take place on Sarushima
tomorrow morning.
General Black will appear for the ceremony!
General Black?
Their commander-in-chief?
I... I can't breathe!
The drug...
If we don't take the drug
every three hours... we die!
I... I'm done for!
Every three hours? What do you mean?
What a merciless way to
run an organization...
So even if we capture their combatants,
we won't be able to hold them long.
What do we do, Rider?
All right...
Let's interrupt their formation
ceremony at Sarushima.
And we'll see this "General
Black" while we're at it.
Hey. What do you see?
Strange... there's no sign of anyone.
You think they'll really hold the
Gel Shocker formation ceremony here?
You think he put one over us?
No, I don't see why he'd
lie knowing he was about to die.
We'll have to investigate to be sure.
That's true. Let's go.
We can't let our guard down.
Let's look in there.
Let's try further in.
What is this?
Pops!
Don't move!
Thank you for coming! Hongo, Taki!
Ganikomoru!
So Sarushima really was a Gel Shocker base?
Hongo. Taki.
You've saved us the trouble
of going to find you.
Get them!
Don't move, or Tachibana Tobei dies!
What are you going to do with us?
Kill you!
It will make a fine show for
the Gel Shocker formation ceremony.
Do what you want with us,
but let Chairman Tachibana go!
Chairman Tachibana, you say?
I think you need to have
your eyes checked.
Look closer!
Who are you?
I came all the way from the African desert
to manage the creation
of the Gel Shocker Japan Branch.
Remember my name... General Black!
So you're General Black?
Damn!
Hongo!
Take him away!
Wait!
Hongo!
This place will be your grave!
Ow!
Steam?
It's really hot.
We need to get out of here!
Okay.
It's no use.
Don't bother struggling.
You're not strong enough
to break through that door.
Not good... they outwitted us.
Taki, if we get rid of this
pipe, we can escape.
Hot!
We will now begin the Gel Shocker
Japan Branch formation ceremony.
Shocker, having acquired
the resources of Geldam,
is now Gel Shocker.
Gel Shocker will surely conquer the Earth.
To achieve this objective,
we will kill, rampage, destroy,
and perform innumerable acts of evil!
Kamen Rider!
But as long as Kamen Rider walks the Earth,
even with Geldam on their side,
Shocker will always suffer the same fate.
How did you get out of that room?
We destroyed the pipe in the boiler room!
Then we used the heat to open the door!
Hey...
Damn you!
I'll finish you myself!
Taki! Capture General Black!
Got it!
Gel Shocker will sow fear across Japan
at the command of General Black!
Kamen Rider... you will not interfere!
Wait, General Black!
Finish that brat off!
Rider Drill Shoot!
Rider...
Rider's been killed!
Kamen Rider seemed to die taking
out the Gel Shocker monster Ganikomoru.
Will we see him again?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
I am General Black.
Kamen Rider lies at the
bottom of the sea!
Now is our chance!
Go, Scorpiontokagesu!
Next week at this time,
watch Gel Shocker in action!
Kamen Rider Dies Twice!!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!