KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Doctor Insect
and the Shocker School
Catch rhinoceros beetles
with Kamen Rider!
Attention, sweet children
of the amusement park.
Good day to you.
I have some big news,
if you'll please gather around.
If you want to hunt rhino
beetles with Kamen Rider,
please get on this bus.
Just get on the bus.
We get to hunt rhino
beetles with Kamen Rider!
I'm more interested in Kamen
Rider than the beetles!
Now let's hunt rhino
beetles with Kamen Rider!
Get on, get on!
No pushing, now!
In order!
That's all for today.
That stinks!
Yeah, that stinks!
I know!
Kamen Rider has
his trusty Cyclone!
I'll catch up with the bus!
Let's go, Kamen Rider!
Out of the way!
Kamen Rider's coming through!
Kamen Rider.
Is there foul work afoot?
Are you going after Shocker?
Nah.
I'm going to hunt rhino beetles.
Rhino beetles?
Everyone went to go hunt rhino
beetles with Kamen Rider.
Hey, kid.
Did you say hunt beetles
with the Kamen Rider?
So who took them?
Shucks, it's gone!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Yeah...
Mount Takao Cable Car
Hey, it's Mount Takao.
You're right.
That's right.
We're on Mount Takao.
It's also called
Rhino Beetle Mountain.
Now, the Kamen Rider is
somewhere on this mountain.
Go find him, everyone!
Let's go, guys!
Where's Kamen Rider?
I don't see Kamen
Rider anywhere.
Not one rhino beetle, either...
M-Maybe we should go.
Mom's probably worried about me.
Look! It's a rhino beetle!
It's pretty big, huh?
Yeah, it's big!
It's a rhino beetle monster!
Don't run away, children!
You're going to be
students of Shocker School!
I will now educate you!
I am the insect
doctor Kabutrong!
Greet your teacher!
Good morning, Doctor Insect.
One,
our enemy is the Kamen Rider.
We've recruited a fine bunch of
students for our Shocker School.
I used both the Kamen Rider
and rhinoceros beetles as bait
and they came right along with
me, Ambassador Hell.
Once we produce the Shocker
School's first graduating class,
we'll create Shocker
Schools all over the world,
and really shock the adults.
If we make sure all the children
who inherit the world after them
are all members of Shocker,
then the world will easily
fall into Shocker's hands.
It's here.
Looks like they
weren't abducted.
Yeah...
Catch rhinoceros beetles
with Kamen Rider!
Make sure you do as I tell you!
Yes, Doctor Insect!
I'm going to follow
that microbus.
Try to talk to one
of the children.
Okay, got it.
Saki!
Hey, tell me!
Did you meet Kamen Rider?
Did you catch any rhino beetles?
Shut up.
I'm never playing with you
again, Koichi.
That's mean! Tell me!
I won't leave until you tell me!
Shut up.
Or I'll make you pay.
What are you doing?
Since you pretend to be the Kamen
Rider, that means you're our enemy.
Saki!
Kill the enemy!
Doctor Insect will
praise us for it!
Someone help me!
What are you kids doing?
What happened, Koichi?
Now, Kamen Rider can't go
crying when he's on his Cyclone.
It's not that...
Saki and the others said
Kamen Rider was an enemy.
They said they'd kill me.
They really said that?
Yeah.
I wonder if Shocker is planning
something with the children...
School bus. School bus.
You're being tailed. Be careful.
Understood.
You can't shake me off.
Wait!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Don't play dumb with me.
You sped up when you
realized I was on your tail.
If you hadn't done anything,
you wouldn't have tried to run!
I'm just...
Acting on orders.
Orders?
That sounds like a
confession to me.
Who's giving the orders?
Who's there?
Who did that?
It was me.
The iron man of
Shocker, Kabutrong!
Hongo Takeshi, can you hear me?
Show yourself, Kabutrong!
Open that door!
You come in here.
All right... as you wish.
Kabutrong!
Takeshi.
The Shocker School
bus cannot be escaped.
You're not capable of
breaking out of it.
Now I'll send you to hell!
It's no use...
It's not working!
All right...
Your struggle is pointless.
The bus' frame and windows are strong
enough to resist a blast from a bazooka!
There's a train coming.
If even a bazooka won't dent it...
the bus is as tough as a tank.
If the train hits it,
it will be a catastrophe!
That's right.
You hear the train
coming, don't you?
You claim to fight for peace, yet you're
about to become a terrible killer!
No...
All right...
Rider Transformation!
Rider Punch!
Rider, the train is coming!
Leave them to me!
Taki, thank you!
You're almost there!
Keep going, Rider!
Someone's pushing
from the other side!
I won't let you move it!
Damn you!
KAMEN RIDER
Let's see who'll win...
the iron man Kabutrong,
or the Kamen Rider!
What's that?
Look out, Rider!
Hold it, Kabutrong!
I almost had you...
Damn you, Kamen Rider!
Kabutrong... what are you
gathering those children together for?
For education...
as the first class of the Shocker School.
Shocker School?
In time, we'll build Shocker
Schools all over the world.
Then, all the world's children
will become Shocker's pupils!
And would you be their
teacher, Kabutrong?
I won't let you do it!
Don't make me
laugh, Kamen Rider!
You don't stand a chance against
the mighty cyborg Kabutrong!
Hold it!
Damn you, Taki!
You okay, Rider?
Yes...
Die!
Don't make a move, or Taki dies!
Taki...
No... Taki!
Taki!
Here...
Okay, this goes
here, and then...
Takeshi?
What happened to you?
What's the matter?
Mr. Takeshi...
Don't worry.
Taki's the one who...
What happened to Mr. Taki?
Shocker got him.
- Shocker?
- Is this true, Takeshi?
Yes...
Why don't we use Taki as
material for the Shocker School?
The Shocker School?
Yes.
We'll use him for the first
class' graduation exam.
Good.
Administer the graduation
exam tomorrow morning.
First class of Shocker School!
Doctor Insect orders you...
Assemble tomorrow
at eight o'clock.
Yes, Doctor. We'll be there.
It's a transmitter...
Goro...
Taki's fate depends on you.
You understand?
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Okay, go on.
How far are they taking us?
I hope this transmitter works...
Hey, 20 degrees,
20 minutes to the northeast.
Right.
Still driving down the
Koshu Kaido towards Otsuki.
Pops.
Where is Goro?
The Koshu Kaido.
Got it.
The Shocker School bus Goro
is on is headed for Mount Takao.
Mount Takao?
Of course...
that's where Shocker's base is.
Pops.
Right, I'll join you.
What's taking them so long?
We will now commence the
Shocker School graduation exam.
Prepare the test.
Students of Shocker School.
The rhino beetles I gave you are
wonderful weapons, miniature grenades.
Now, throw them at this man!
They're gonna kill Mr. Taki!
Let me go!
The brat who defies Shocker, eh?
We'll make you part
of the test as well!
Hang in there, Mr. Taki!
Mr. Takeshi and the
Kamen Rider are coming!
Let me go!
Fool!
The Kamen Rider has already lost
to the great Kabutrong once!
The next time he faces
me, he dies!
Don't be so sure, Kabutrong!
Kamen Rider!
Damn you...
Let's go!
- Rider!
- Taki!
Take care of the children!
Okay!
No use... it's a dead end!
Let's finish this!
Glad to!
Rider Kick!
What happened?
They're all sound asleep...
With Kabutrong gone,
the children should be back to normal.
That was a close call, huh?
But thanks to the three of you,
the Shocker School is closed for business.
Sounds about right.
Let's get the kids to safety.
See you.
Bye.
Goodbye! Goodbye!
The Kamen Rider has put an
end to the Shocker School.
But Shocker would find a
new target soon enough.
Keep fighting, Hongo Takeshi!
Let's go, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin
sent by Shocker HQ
is the monstrous Kamikirikid.
Flames crackle and burn.
Ambassador Hell chants
an eerie magic spell.
What is the terrible Shocker ritual
that uses Kamen Rider as a sacrifice?
Join us next week for "The Shocker
Graveyard: Monsters Revived."
The Shocker Graveyard:
Monsters Revived
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!