KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Mexico, part of the
North American continent.
The Palas River, host to the Palas
Dam, runs through its center.
The power this dam provides is an
important artery of the Mexican economy.
The Devilish Sabotegron
Attacks!
The destruction of the dam has
thrown all of Mexico into chaos!
Shocker will take advantage of
that chaos to conquer Mexico City.
Sabotegron.
The destructive activities of Shocker's
Mexico Branch are close to complete.
No, there is much more to do.
Our plans to conquer
Mexico are 90% complete.
Sabotegron.
It's time to put your spectacular
leadership to use in another region.
What region is that?
You must fly to Japan, where Shocker's
plans have been lagging behind.
Interesting. As you wish.
I'll finally get to meet this Kamen
Rider who's been giving our commanders
so much trouble, then?
Indeed.
Fight the Rider.
Then destroy all of Japan's dams,
and throw the country into chaos!
A message from the FBI's special
investigations department.
"A member of Shocker's Mexican
command team is heading for Japan.
I'll be arriving on
Flight 603 in Haneda.
Reference attached file six."
Flight 603 into Haneda, right?
I guess I won't make it to the
opening of the Tachibana Racing Club.
To Taki Kazuya
Tachibana Auto Corner
Sorry we're late.
I'll make some introductions.
This is...
I'm Mari.
Yuri.
I'm Michi.
We're joining the club. Got it?
Shiro, stop gaping and
show some hospitality.
We've got guests!
Come on in!
Take a seat in the back, everyone.
Right this way.
So cool...
Wow! It's so groovy!
Let's see...
Any experience?
I've got a little
experience with a 90cc.
I'm a first-degree.
A first-degree
blackbelt in karate.
I do fencing.
That's not what
I'm asking about.
I mean motorbike experience.
None at all.
Not a bit.
None at all?
That's why we need
lessons already!
International Arrivals
He should be out
of customs by now.
You got the message from HQ?
Yes.
What's this about a Shocker
commander from Mexico?
Well, he's a tricky one.
He shook off our attempts to tail him,
but we've managed to locate him in Japan.
Well, that's very impressive.
Maybe I'll join you, then.
Pops! Don't be a fuddy-duddy!
Have some fun with
the young people!
I'm gonna dance, too!
Hold this, Pops!
Is it like this?
Hey, you're good.
Yeah, I get it.
Kids these days, I swear...
Hongo, Taki...
they're just as bad!
Hongo!
Autopilot Remote Control
Hang on. Just a minute.
The fact that it started up on its
own means Hongo's calling it remotely.
I can sleep all the way to Hongo,
as long as I stay on board!
I'm not sure I like this guy.
And it's not good to take
someone completely at face value.
We have some news to report.
A body was found
aboard Flight 603
from Mexico City arriving at
Haneda at 2:00 this afternoon.
The body belonged
to an FBI agent...
Why'd you turn it off?
Ow!
Your hand...
I get it.
You're the Mexican
Shocker commander.
FBI scum...
your comrade is dead.
You'll die, too!
All who oppose Shocker must
be wiped from the planet!
Not a chance!
You're the one
who's going to die.
Your mistake was putting
me behind the wheel!
I did it!
Pops! You came to save me!
Taki!
It's a Shocker monster!
Well, obviously!
We're not safe here!
Let's make tracks!
Now, combatants of
Shocker's Japan Branch...
Prove yourselves to
the great Sabotegron!
Die!
So you're the Kamen Rider...
Rider Fight!
I'll crush all three
of you at once!
Be gentle, would you?
It's punishment.
You left your customers
behind to go off on a drive.
I'm hurting, too.
Where?
Don't be such a
baby, married man.
What, he's married?
What a rotten trick.
Go do it yourself.
There, all done.
But where's Hongo?
He should be here by now.
Well, that sounds like him!
Or maybe not...
It's not Hongo!
What?
Hey, everyone, hide! Hurry!
Shiro, turn off the lights!
Right!
Shiro, turn on the lights!
What?
Hey, get off!
Why, you...
Hey, now.
What kind of a welcome is this?
Who are you?
Me? I'm Ichimonji Hayato.
I'm a freelance photographer.
And what exactly do
you want with us?
Nothing in particular.
You forgot something,
that's all.
Forgot something?
Your motorbike.
Here, take this.
Hey, wait!
Oh, please!
Photograph me, would you?
Sorry, but I don't do women.
KAMEN RIDER
Sabotegron.
The combatants of Shocker's Japan
Branch are yours to command.
Embark upon wide-scale
destruction at once.
Members of the Japan Branch.
Before we embark upon
our reign of destruction,
I would like to show you an
experiment using the cactus bombs,
also known as the Mexican Flowers,
which I perfected back in Mexico.
They look exactly
like regular cacti.
But the spikes on the cactus
are extremely sensitive fuses.
Anything they contact will
be destroyed without a trace.
That is how Mexican Flowers die.
Soon, you'll all be able to see the
power of these bombs with your own eyes.
Our guinea pigs will be any humans foolish
enough to try to learn Shocker's secrets!
Hey, Taki. Slow down already!
I said you could sit this out.
You know I can't do that.
Now that I know you're going
out to find Shocker's base,
If I didn't come along,
I could never show my face again.
I can't be sure that their base
really is in these mountains, though.
Ah, don't sweat it.
Hey!
You're the guy!
It's not nice to strike at
someone the moment you see them.
Why are you following us?
Don't be so suspicious.
It's not like I
was following you.
I was walking ahead of
you, remember?
Well, that explains that...
Pops!
Don't fall for his nonsense.
Oh, right.
You're with Shocker, aren't you?
Shocker?
I'm more about shutters, actually.
Shutters?
We can't get a straight
answer from this guy...
We're not even
going the same way.
Look, you'd better not follow
us, okay?
Wait! Don't move!
Unusual to see this
cactus species here...
It originates in
Mexico, I believe.
What's it doing in
a place like this?
Don't scare me like that!
All that fuss for
a stupid cactus...
Pops, we're wasting time here.
Ignorance is bliss, I guess.
Let me see.
Pops.
Look at that!
As I thought...
we've finally found Shocker's base!
That's right.
What do we do now?
Now that we're here,
we don't really have a choice.
Yeah... we fight!
After nightfall, yes.
What is it?
That idiot!
Let me see!
What's he doing?
That amateur can't handle this!
Hey! I'm coming, too!
Hey, be careful.
These cacti are bombs.
If you touch their
thorns, they blow.
Bombs?
No way...
Well, if you think I'm lying...
That's odd...
Don't scare a man like that!
What are you doing?
The Mexican Flowers
don't bloom so easily.
I'll only let them bloom
once I use my decoys
to lure out Shocker's true
enemy, the Kamen Rider.
Take that!
It's a dummy!
Pops.
I think we might have
walked into a trap.
We'd better beat it, fast.
Why, you...
This isn't good.
We'd better leave for now.
I thought so.
Yeah, you were right.
They're here!
Damn... they've herded us
into a field of cactus bombs.
Out of the frying pan,
into the fire, eh?
I think Shocker's true target...
is the Kamen Rider.
What?
How did you know that?
Just who are you?
Enemy to Shocker...
And friend to humanity!
The Kamen Rider...
Are you...?
Hongo Takeshi left Japan to
stop a different Shocker scheme.
What, he's in another country?
Yes. Ruriko went with him.
Ruriko, too?
Now I protect Japan in
Hongo Takeshi's place...
As the Kamen Rider!
You mean...
You're also a cyborg?
Allow me to demonstrate.
Kamen Rider!
Transform!
Rider!
There he is... the Kamen Rider!
Bloom, Mexican Flowers!
Rider!
Look out!
Rider Power!
Kamen Rider is in peril!
Will he be struck down by
that Shocker devil, Sabotegron?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
Sabotegron Strikes Back!
is the devilish Sabotegron.
The devilish Sabotegron,
dispatched from Shocker's Mexican Branch,
uses cactus bombs known as Mexican Flowers
to drive Kamen Rider to desperation.
A deathmatch unfolds in
a field thick with cacti.
Join us next week for
"Sabotegron Strikes Back!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!