KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Eerie Owl
Man's Killer X-Rays
This is a standard
X-ray picture.
We've implanted a more powerful
version of this basic phenomenon
a killer X-Ray
emitter—into your eyes.
Owl Man...
Now...
go forth and test your power!
Go, Owl Man!
I never knew there
were owls around here.
I've never heard any.
And I go this way every day.
Yeah, it's a little creepy
to hear one in the daytime.
- Well, take care.
- Goodbye.
See you tomorrow, coach!
- Goodbye!
Who are you?
I am the Shocker cyborg...
Owl Man!
What did you say?
Give up and be my guinea pig!
Help me!
Isn't that the coach?
Feel the power of
my killer X-rays!
A smashing success.
Witnesses?!
No! Help me!
Take her away!
Officer! Please, help me!
What's the matter?
An owl monster...
What? An owl monster?
Hey, now.
I'm not about to fall
for a prank like that.
It's not a prank! It's true!
Stop being ridiculous.
I know you're just a kid,
but rather than playing pranks,
why don't you go home
and do some studying?
You get it?
Get real already...
Damn...
where did she run off to?!
Find her! Find her!
Help! Help!
What's the matter?
An owl monster appeared...
An owl?
Another Shocker plot, eh?
The monster got my tennis
coach, Mr. Tashiro...
I'll take the skeleton to the
university lab and investigate.
Was the test a success?
Excellent.
I hereby appoint you the head of
Operation: Clock Tower Detonation.
This is a map of large clock towers
in every city in the country.
Tomorrow at noon,
when Earth is closest to the sun,
and the clocks strike twelve,
we'll blow the clock
towers up all at once.
This will cause a chain reaction of
explosions in smaller clocks as well.
Magnificent!
A literal time bomb!
But how do we accomplish it?
The light from your eyes will emit a
frequency to trigger the detonation.
Our combatants have already affixed
receivers for that frequency
onto large clocks everywhere.
Then I must act immediately.
Wait.
One location remains
without a receiver.
You will go there tonight.
Incidentally, Ambassador Hell...
What should I do
with this woman?
Send her to work with
the other prisoners
to construct the
transmitter radar.
Here's an X-ray that Mr. Tashiro
had taken last year
after he was in a car accident.
Could I borrow this?
Hey. This picture
matches the skeleton.
Then Shocker used some
special method to kill him?
It's the same method. X-rays!
Especially strong,
killer X-rays.
The skeleton was
considerably irradiated.
You mean...
Yeah.
I'll go searching with a
Geiger counter in the morning.
Mukogaoka Park
Flower Clock
Unusual to hear owls
around here these days...
That little prankster girl
mentioned an owl monster, too...
Machinery Room
That should do it!
Wh-Who are you?!
Die!
This way!
Owl feathers!
It must have gone this way.
You've shown yourself,
Shocker cyborg!
Right...
Meddling fools...
Feel the power of Owl
Man's killer X-rays!
Hold it!
Taki!
Damn you...
Try me!
Die!
Rider Transformation!
Damn you, Owl Man...
Die, Rider!
Rider!
Taki!
Now!
This isn't over, Rider!
I'll get you for this, Owl Man!
KAMEN RIDER
Everyone's talking about
a skeleton they found
near the flower clock
in Mukogaoka Park!
What's this?
Damn Shocker...
what are they plotting this time?
Takeshi! What's wrong?
Owl Man got him bad.
Are you all right, Takeshi?
Takeshi...
we've got some bad news, too.
What happened, Goro?
Another skeleton appeared.
What?
Shocker's on the move again?
Stop. You can't handle it.
Hey... you okay, Taki?
The place he hit me before...
What? That's strange...
Is it broken?
It's no use. I think something's
jamming the radiation detector.
Damn.
Pops...
What? Is that their hideout?
Seems worth
investigating, at least.
Let's go.
Pops... I wonder if we
can lure him out here.
I have just the thing.
Look over here! Over here!
Damn it, we need to make noise!
All right...
Perfect.
C'mon, hurry! Hurry! This way!
Talk.
What's your plan this time?
Please, tell me! Please?
Damn...
Look at that!
Shocker thinks nothing
of killing their own!
Hey! Hey!
It's no use...
What's going on?
He can only write numbers?
One through twelve...
I get it! It's a clock!
The radar isn't finished yet?
Its completion is imminent.
If the prisoners
are slacking on you,
execute one as an
example to the others!
Perhaps a demonstration
of my power
will inspire you to work harder!
Understand?
This is what
happens to slackers!
Please, no!
Killer X-ray!
Mukogaoka Park
Flower Clock
Then the twelve in the
drawing means twelve o'clock?
So, what's the X?
It probably means an explosion.
Of the flower clock?
I'll check out the
machinery room.
Machinery Room
This is it...
Someone's removed the receiver
from the flower clock!
Hongo's caught our trail, then.
Damn...
They're going to trigger an explosion
using Owl Man's light-wave frequency...
Which means...
there's more than one location.
I see. All the clock
towers in the country...
Damn you... Shocker!
You'll pay for this!
I've laid the ambush
for Hongo Takeshi.
Good.
Only five minutes left.
Let's break through, Taki!
Okay!
Get them!
Rider Transformation!
Both the Kamen Rider
and the Cyclone
were designed to withstand temperatures
of several thousand degrees.
The radar is complete!
Excellent.
Thirty seconds to noon.
We must act before the
Kamen Rider arrives.
When I give the signal,
shoot the killer X-rays at this frame.
Twenty seconds to launch.
Ten. Nine. Eight...
Rider Crush!
You've shown yourself,
Kamen Rider...
Ambassador Hell.
I've crushed your
evil scheme this time!
Silence!
Kill the Kamen Rider! Kill him!
Taki!
You need to save the prisoners!
Got it!
Damn you, Rider!
Not so fast!
Hold it!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider!
Taki!
Shocker is coming,
Owl Man, fight me!
Let's go!
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Killer X-rays!
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Hammer!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Kamen Rider had
defeated Owl Man.
But Shocker would embark on
even more wicked schemes.
Ride on, Hongo Takeshi!
Let's go, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous
electrical Namazugiller.
Doctor Shinigami returns to Japan with
his 100,000-volt creation Namazugiller.
He and Ambassador Hell
instate a two-front attack,
putting Kamen Rider in peril!
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous
Namazugiller's Electric Hell."
The Monstrous
Namazugiller's Electric Hell
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!