KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Mount Rokko Pursuit of
the Monstrous Abugomes!
Kobe is the largest
harbor in Western Japan.
The FBI caught word of Shocker
operating here in Kobe,
and sent Hongo Takeshi and Taki
Kazuya to fly secretly to Western Japan
and investigate Shocker's activities there.
I trailed him here from Mexico.
This time, I'll find evidence
tying him to Shocker.
He disappeared.
That's impossible!
You're an FBI inspector.
I applaud your efforts to track me
all the way from Mexico.
Damn... you knew I was tracking you?
I know you're a Shocker liaison.
What are you doing in Japan?
You want to know, do you?
Japan's leading electronic
engineer, Doctor Kihara Michitoshi,
is staying at the Arima Hot Springs
for an academic conference.
We want to bring Doctor Kihara into
the fold as a Shocker scientist.
What did you say?
Bring Doctor Kihara, that Nobel
Prize frontrunner, into Shocker?!
Let me give you a warning.
I'm no mere Shocker liaison.
I'm a venomous horsefly cyborg
born deep in the Mexican jungles!
The venomous horsefly that
can kill a cow with one sting?
That's right.
They call me Abugomes!
I've told you my identity and my goal.
Are you ready to die now?
Because that's what's going
to happen, FBI scum!
A witness!
Help! Help!
Let me go! Let me go! Mama!
Hold it!
Shocker cyborg...
Taki! I'll send you to join
that friend of yours!
George?
You killed George?!
Hold it!
Hongo Takeshi...
Taki, take the child to safety.
- Right!
- I'll face you now!
Hongo Takeshi...
I'm just here to get your
measure this time...
The next time we meet, you will die!
Abugomes...
You fool!
Letting yourself be distracted
by such nonsense...
What if the child you let
escape heard everything?
Sh-She didn't!
Can you be sure?
If Kamen Rider learns of our plan,
we'll have trouble on our hands.
Finish off the child that
Abugomes let escape.
Shouldn't we finish off the Kamen Rider...
I don't need you to tell me these things!
Besides... defeating Rider
will require some planning.
Here we go.
Hey, what's all the luggage for?
It's a trip to Western Japan,
not a world cruise!
Even if it's not far, it's still a trip!
We need to impress Mr. Hongo and Mr. Taki.
Hold this, would you, Chief?
No way! The bus is about to leave!
Isn't this cool?
Yeah, it's very comfortable,
and the scenery is amazing!
No complaints here.
Or so I'd like to say...
But we're still stuck with the Chairman.
Well, excuse me for being old!
We'll be taking a ten-minute breather here.
Would you be the Tachibana Tobei party?
An acquaintance of yours
is waiting on the second floor.
Maybe it's Hongo and Taki!
Maybe so!
Tachibana Tobei. You won't
be getting back on that bus.
Shocker will take you the rest of the way!
Damn!
Take them to Shocker's
Western Japan Branch!
Kasuga Surgical Hospital
Cathy?
Abugomes nearly killed this girl.
Which means she must know
something important about Shocker.
Mama, I'm scared. I'm scared.
Are you all right?
Cathy, you're safe now.
There's nothing left to be afraid of.
Okay?
Do you remember what that monster said?
Mama...
You're a good girl, aren't you?
Tell us, will you?
They said they were going
to bring a doctor into Shocker.
Did he mention his name?
Um... um...
I don't remember.
Try to remember. Okay?
Look out!
Ma'am, take Cathy to safety.
- Hongo!
- That way!
I remember!
It was Kihara! He said Kihara!
Thank you, Cathy.
You handle things here!
Rider Transformation!
Rider!
I thought I told you... the next
time we met, I would finish you!
What's that?
Listen carefully... Shocker
has your friends in custody.
What did you say?
If you don't want to see them
dead, you'd better not move.
Don't move!
Abugomes.
Doctor Kihara is at the Arima
Hot Springs hotel.
Go kidnap him at once!
KAMEN RIDER
National Park Arima Hot Springs
Welcome.
I'd like to meet one of
your residents: Doctor Kihara.
Doctor Kihara?
He's out for a walk in Zuihoji
Park at the moment.
Zuihoji Park?
Yes.
Thank you.
Certainly.
Doctor.
Are you Doctor Kihara?
I am.
You see...
I'm interested in putting
your amazing brain to work.
My brain, you say?
Shocker is working on a
powerful radio wave scrambler.
We need your electronic
engineering skills to complete it.
A radio wave scrambler, you say?
Yes.
Shocker will block all communications
and alter them to suit our own purposes.
It will throw Japan into chaos.
I-Impossible...
I'd never go along with something so awful!
Doctor.
It's too late to refuse.
Who are you people?
Shut your mouth and come along.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Do you see that, Doctor?
What an awful thing...
I certainly dodged a bullet.
They don't realize they've taken a fake.
Don't worry.
But what will happen to
the young man taking my place?
No need to worry.
He's going to infiltrate
Shocker's Western Japan base
and rescue our captured colleagues.
I've learned Shocker's plan.
Now I just need to infiltrate their base
and save my friends from the club.
Doctor. Hurry!
How did they know I'd be here?
Ambassador Hell...
I, Shocker commander-in-chief,
Ambassador Hell,
has come here to escort
you personally, Doctor Kihara.
Now, won't you get in the car?
You won't have him!
Your resistance is futile.
Take him away!
Doctor Kihara.
Have a close look at that
cable car, would you?
What is it?
Taki! Doctor!
You've shown your true colors at last.
Hongo Takeshi!
You saw through my disguise?
Hongo Takeshi...
You underestimate Shocker!
Damn...
You won't leave here alive this time!
Damn!
Damn...
Fall! Fall to hell!
Hongo...
Take Doctor Kihara and Taki
to our base at Horai Bridge.
What do you think of the view?
I find it comparable
to America's Grand Canyon.
That tall, thin mountain will serve
as Shocker's broadcast antenna.
I won't be a part of it.
I won't help you undermine
Japanese communications!
Enough talking tough.
You'll come around soon enough.
Prepare for the execution.
Execution?
That's right.
All who oppose Shocker must die!
If I die here, everything I've
done will be for naught.
I have to go... I have to go!
Doctor... look closely!
Taki. Was Hongo really killed?
I saw it with my own eyes.
If he'd survived, he'd be here by now.
I don't want to believe it...
Are we really going to die?
I'm too young to die!
Push them into the ravine, one at a time!
Stop it!
I'll do whatever you ask!
Just forgive them!
Ignore him. Do it!
Doctor Kihara.
You must not bend to Shocker threats!
That voice...
It's Rider!
Where are you, Rider?
Show yourself!
Show yourself, Rider!
You coward... show yourself!
I'm right here!
Kicking off the ground
with a Rider Jump,
There he is!
Abugomes!
- Rider!
- You came!
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
- Rider!
- Rider, save Doctor Kihara!
Got it!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Stay here, Pops.
Okay. Good luck out there!
Hold it!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Swimming through the
oceans with a Rider Swim,
This time, you die!
a great dive flitting through the sea!
Calling up whirlpools with a Rider Screw!
Dragging enemies down with a Rider Lung!
Oh, oh Rider!
Rider Knee Block!
Kamen Rider!
Doctor, Shocker's plan has failed.
You're safe now.
I'm so glad. I truly am...
We'll get you back, then.
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Mr. Taki!
What about us?
This is Arima Hot Springs.
Why don't you take a nice rest?
What a nice idea!
I'm so glad we came.
But how do we get down from here?
Kamen Rider's deathmatch with
Shocker at Mount Rokko in Arima
ended with justice prevailing.
But Shocker would target Japan
with their evil once more.
Fight on, Hongo Takeshi,
the Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
I am the blood-sucking monster Mosquilas!
I was sent from South
America to kill Rider!
I'll kill Rider this time,
and throw him into the
plunge pool of Nachi Falls!
Next time, "The Blood-Sucking
Mosquilas Versus the Two Riders."
The Blood-Sucking Mosquilas
Versus the Two Riders
It'll be fun!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!