KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Elekibotaru's
Fireball Attack!!
Elekibotaru.
It's time to show your potential.
You must use your power
to reduce Japan to ruin,
so that we may erect a Shocker Kingdom.
This will be the final charge.
With this, I give you life.
Give it your best!
C'mon, Naoki! Get your head up!
Hang in there! Come on!
Hang in there!
Come on!
You're almost there!
Keep kicking your legs!
Look alive!
Give it your best!
Okay, well done.
That's enough for today.
Get up, everyone!
Yes, sir...
Thank you.
How did I look, Coach?
You've got a long way to go.
Aw...
Another power outage?
Rise, Elekibotaru!
Steal all of Tokyo's electricity,
and become the deadly Elekibotaru!
Go!
Coach...
What's that light?
What could it be?
- Let's check it out.
- Right.
I think it came from around here.
Let's go.
Coach! There it is!
It's like a firefly...
It can't be.
Fireflies don't grow that big...
It's a bit eerie, isn't it?
We should really go back.
Right.
Shine! Fly! Dance the dance of madness!
What's going on?
I will now inflict my hypnosis
upon these foolish humans!
I can't... I can't see!
How do you like my electric hypnosis?
Does it hurt?
Now I'll kill you all!
This electric fire will burn you to death!
You know Hongo Takeshi,
so I won't kill you.
I have a greater purpose for you!
My dance of hell will make you my slave.
Now, go!
You must destroy Hongo, enemy of Shocker!
Chairman!
Oh, Yuri?
These are friends of mine.
I was wondering if they
could join the Racing Club.
Well, of course.
I'm Yokko.
I'm Choco.
This is the club Chairman,
Mr. Hongo, and Mr. Taki.
A pleasure.
Nice to meet you!
Well, I'm going to show them around.
- Sure.
- Let's go!
But it doesn't make sense.
The power outage yesterday
was completely unexplained.
It said enough electricity
was diverted in an instant
to power Tokyo for ten days.
Ten days?
Yes.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
I know what happened.
Naoki?
I saw it. The firefly monster.
Shocker is behind it all.
Is that true, Naoki?
Where is it?
Next to the third sluice
gate of the Tama River.
We should investigate, anyhow.
Hey, be careful, okay?
This is it, right?
Okay, I'll look this way.
Nothing out of the ordinary here.
But who but Shocker could
do something like that?
There must be a clue somewhere.
You think it was really a Shocker
monster that Naoki saw?
What else could it be?
But then... why didn't
he come to us last night?
Yeah...
Hey, Hongo. What's that?
This is...
It suggests a considerable
discharge of electricity.
Hey... What's going on?
You've come, Hongo! Taki!
You fools!
You walked right into my trap!
Are you a Shocker cyborg?
Indeed.
My name is Elekibotaru!
Elekibotaru?
That's right. Get them!
Taki! You okay?
Damn it...
Rider Transformation!
Taki!
Taki...
Elekibotaru,
we'll finish this another time!
Are you running from me, Rider?!
Sorry about that, Hongo.
Hey, it's no problem.
Let me see.
Please, I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
We should focus on
finding their base instead.
Don't be hasty, Taki.
Listen.
The real problem is
Elekibotaru's electricity.
It seems to contain unimaginable power.
The only way we can win is if we
figure out how to steal that from him.
What's this?
Why did you let Hongo escape?
You fool!
Shocker does not suffer failures.
I'm terribly sorry.
I swear I will defeat Hongo next time!
Enough.
I've already taken our next steps.
Mr. Hongo and Mr. Taki
have been out a while...
Hey, Naoki.
What's wrong? You look down.
And grouchy, too...
Shucks. He hasn't said
a word to me all day.
Think he's sick or something?
Naoki, do it.
Attack your comrades!
What's wrong, Naoki?
What's wrong?
Naoki!
Hey, knock it off.
What's going on?
Naoki's acting strange!
Naoki! Stop it!
Run away!
KAMEN RIDER
Hongo!
Pops!
- Pops!
- Pops...
Yuri and the girls... kidnapped by Shocker!
Shocker?
Damn you, Shocker...
Let's go, Taki!
I see...
The electricity in his body was grounded.
What's wrong, Hongo?
I need a stake and a rope.
Pops, I need a stake and a rope.
Okay...
Meet up with me later.
The third sluice gate on the Tama River.
Got it!
Hey...
Okay.
Taki, I think it's that way.
Let's go.
It's our club badge.
I knew we'd find something here...
Could that be it?
You have an important task ahead of you.
Hongo and Taki will soon
come here to save you.
But when they do come, they will die!
Taki, this must be it.
It definitely looks like
Shocker architecture...
Okay.
This way!
Yuri!
We've been waiting for you, Hongo, Taki!
I've prepared a grave just for you.
What did you say?
Hongo.
You've met your end at last.
Get him!
Taki. Take the others and go!
Right!
Hey, speak to me!
Speak to me, everyone!
Elekibotaru.
Show them your dance of hell.
Dance of hell?
Hongo... watch closely!
Kill Hongo and Taki!
Fight them! Kill them!
They're so strong!
They've all been hypnotized!
Get them! Give them all you've got!
Stop this, Yokko, Mitsuru!
Taki, we can't afford to harm them...
Taki!
It's no use, Taki.
We have to knock them out.
Right.
Hongo Takeshi!
Right...
Taki!
Hongo!
Rider Transformation!
Feel the wrath of my electric fire!
Hold it!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Rider! I brought it!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Throw it to me!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Take it!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Right... now!
Shocker is coming
Elekibotaru,
I will steal your electricity!
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
You're finished now!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Fight me!
With my mask of green...
Rider Throw!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider!
What were we...
Hey, it's okay.
You're okay now, right?
Come on, let's go!
- Let's go.
- Let's go home.
Once again, Kamen Rider was able to
defeat the terrifying killer Elekibotaru.
But Shocker would surely
send a new cyborg soon.
Ride on, Hongo Takeshi!
Fight, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Next week is the first episode
of an amazing location shoot series.
Set on Mount Rokko in Arima, Kobe,
Rider pursues the Mexican
monster Abugomes.
The action on the Rokko Ropeway
suspended 130 meters in the air
will prove especially thrilling.
Join us next week for "The Mount Rokko
Pursuit of the Monstrous Abugomes!"
The Mount Rokko Pursuit of
the Monstrous Abugomes!
It's going to be amazing!
Be sure to tune in!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!