KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
I need to get myself together by the
All-Japan Motocross Championships.
That wretched Hongo...
we'll show him.
You are our most talented
combatants, re-modified and
brainwashed for our
third attack operation.
Look at this.
The cyborgs shown here have successively
been defeated by the Kamen Rider.
We've run their data through
our Shocker computers
and created a new one by combining
all of their strengths: Gebacondor.
But Gebacondor is
not yet awakened.
Gebacondor requires the
blood of young women to live.
Blood-Sucking Monster
Gebacondor
C'mon! C'mon!
Amen.
Hello, there.
I know it's a bit sudden, but we'd
like to get married at this church.
Could you accommodate us?
I take you to be my spouse,
in richness and in poorness,
in sickness and in health,
until death do us part.
Help me!
I brought fresh blood
from that young woman.
Drink deep, and become a
loyal soldier of Shocker.
Gebacondor... rise!
Disrupt humanity's
peaceful lives
and do all in your power to
help Shocker conquer the world.
Now, go and test your power!
Rise, Gebacondor!
That foolish Rider...
He's dead for sure, this time.
"To my dear comrades at Snack Amigo.
Taki Kazuya."
Hey... wasn't he the winner of last
year's All-Japan Motocross Championships?
That's right.
Takeshi's perpetual rival.
He must be confident, getting married
with the championships on the way...
Whereas Takeshi's out there...
That reminds me...
I haven't seen Takeshi for a while.
I wonder what he's up to.
Some kind of important
research, I think he said.
He wants to dedicate all his time to
driving in the run-up to the championships,
but his research is
important, too.
I guess living a
double life isn't easy!
Jonan University
Biochemistry Laboratory
Hey, Hongo.
Aren't you going to
your friend's wedding?
You'll be late.
Where's Takeshi?
Are you sure he
said he was coming?
It is strange...
He said on the phone
that he'd be here.
You want that woman's
blood, do you?
But hold on.
Not inside.
There are too many
people in attendance.
Congratulations, Yoko!
Congratulations!
Good luck at the
Championships, too!
That's right!
Hooray!
She'll get an interesting honeymoon
from her new racer husband, I'm sure.
But I guess Takeshi
didn't make it...
Yoko? Yoko!
Am I too late?
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Rider Kick!
Now's your chance!
Take the girl and go!
Yoko!
KAMEN RIDER
Poor Yoko...
Do you think she'll
ever recover?
Damn that Shocker...
What an inhuman act...
But it's a wonder
things didn't get worse.
I'd given up,
assuming it was hopeless.
That's when the Kamen
Rider rode in and saved me.
What?
The Kamen Rider did that?
Phone
That's strange...
I wonder what Takeshi is up to.
I'm going to head out for a bit.
Sure thing.
Are you getting married
too, mister?
You really shouldn't do it
here, though.
Why is that?
Do you know something?
Oh, it's you, Mr. Tachibana...
Taki!
What are you doing here?
I've been scoping
out this church.
Something seems off here.
Are you trying to avenge Yoko?
Yes.
When I look at her in that
condition, I get so angry,
I just need to take action.
After what that boy said, too...
There's definitely something strange
about it, but we still can't prove it.
Hey.
When we went, there was just that
one old woman playing the organ.
The creepy one?
Yeah.
That's right.
Maybe there's a Shocker
base under that church,
and that woman is
standing guard there.
I bet that's it!
I did think there was something
fishy about that priest.
But I didn't spot anything that seemed
like it could lead underground...
Of course, the old woman being there
made it was hard to look around.
Then let's try again.
We need to make Shocker pay
for what they did to Yoko.
No, hang on a minute.
Could it be...
Could what be?
Yes! I have a perfect plan!
Investigate as thoroughly as
you can during the ceremony.
But listen up.
If things get
dangerous, make tracks.
Right.
Do you, Jiro, take Kazuko to
be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
Don't go taking this
seriously, now.
Do you, Kazuko, take Jiro to be
your lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
Run!
Get going!
We need to go faster!
They're in danger!
When did he get here?
Well, I'll finish you this time!
Kamen Rider!
Rider can't beat him...
I'll going run out of
power at this rate...
That's right.
Rider!
Use the Cyclone to get away!
Are you running away? Coward!
Damn!
All right...
H-Hey!
I need to get back, too!
Wait for me!
The danger had
passed once again.
Kamen Rider's heroics had protected
another precious young life.
But as long as Shocker was out
there, modifying
humans and plotting
to conquer the world,
Hongo Takeshi's—the Kamen
Rider's battle would never end!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
The Murderous Yamogerus
is Yamogerus.
Shocker steals the Danger Light
just developed by Doctor Shirakawa
and uses it to engineer
humanity's extinction.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Murderous Yamogerus."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!