KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Poison Gas Monster
Torikabuto's Operation G
Hey, wait for me!
Koji!
What is it?
Look!
Isn't it pretty?
Isn't it?
It's certainly an unusual plant!
The plant is making smoke!
The plant is making smoke?
Did someone's car break down?
What's the matter?
Hey.
Hey, hang in there!
Hey! Hey!
They're dead...
What is that plant?
M-Monster!
I pity your fate,
but anyone who sees Shocker's latest
weapon, the killer plant, must die!
Die!
H-Help me!
A monster!
That monster killed someone!
Mitsuru! Where are you?
Mitsuru!
Mama!
Mitsuru! You're incorrigible!
I've been looking everywhere.
Mama, we gotta go to the police!
The police?
Where's this coming from? You silly boy.
A monster... a monster killed someone!
That's not funny at all.
You can't scare me that easily, you know.
But a monster really did kill someone!
I see. Well, I'm going home.
You can stay here if you want.
But don't blame mama
if the monster kills you, too!
Mama!
The child saw it all...
After him!
Gentlemen.
The day of Operation: G draws near.
We will soon put our new weapon,
the killer plant, to work.
But first, Torikabuto...
You must silence the boy
who witnessed our experiment.
Colonel, sir. I have a report.
The witness's name is Kimoto Mitsuru.
He lives in Machida, Tokyo.
Go, Torikabuto!
Silence this Kimoto Mitsuru permanently!
The day Torikabuto silences that boy
is the day Operation: G goes into action.
Gentlemen. Come this way.
I will hereby explain the plan.
Just what was Colonel Zol's Operation: G?
Shocker's plan revolved around their newly
developed weapon, the killer plants.
They would set them around populous
venues such as theaters and music halls,
and use the gas the plants emit
to murder thousands of people at once.
This monster killed someone
There it is!
You're right!
That makes five.
They're all of the same monster.
Something's wrong here...
I'll put one on this pole, too!
Mitsuru?
Mama!
I knew you were behind this, Mitsuru.
Why are you drawing this strange monster?
And why are you taping them
to electric poles and mailboxes?
Tell me the truth!
But I really saw it!
I really saw this monster kill someone!
Mitsuru.
You're not feeling well.
Let's have a doctor look over you.
I'm not! I'm not sick!
That monster really killed someone!
Mitsuru!
Whatever.
I hate you, Mama! I hate you!
Mitsuru!
Mitsuru is the one drawing this monster?
And he says it killed someone...
Tachibana Racing Club
No use, eh?
Incidents, incidents...
Just two traffic accidents.
Yeah, it's pretty boring.
No sign of Shocker activity
for the last twenty days.
No, that's for the best.
Blue skies in Tokyo and no sign of Shocker!
That's right.
But I feel a little like I'm going soft.
It's suspicious.
There's something to this.
What are you mumbling about, Goro?
A Shocker monster killed someone!
What are you talking about?
Look!
"This monster killed someone," it says.
It's just a child's picture!
But it's very good.
It looks almost alive...
But Mitsuru's mom thinks
he's sick or something!
And no wonder.
Any mother would,
who cares about her child.
She must be worried.
But he says he saw it all!
Goro. Where is Mitsuru's house?
I knew Hayato would believe me!
Motomachi Block 17, Machida!
Right.
Hayato!
You really believe the boy's story?
I do.
I don't think a child's mind could
conjure up a monster like that.
All right. I'll join you.
Hey!
I'm borrowing this.
You FBI cheater!
I'm going!
I wanna tell Mr. Ichimonji the truth!
Stop this.
You're sick.
Remember what the doctor
said? You need rest.
Mama!
Enough.
Open up! Mama!
Darn it...
This monster killed someone
Lying?
He's lying about everything?
Did Mitsuru say that?
Well, it's just... monsters
like that don't exist.
So Mitsuru didn't say he was lying.
Ma'am, is Mitsuru really sick?
Yes...
But the doctor couldn't
find anything wrong.
I just can't believe
he really saw a monster.
Monsters exist.
My allies and I are fighting
hard against those monsters.
Ma'am, let me speak to Mitsuru.
Ma'am!
Mama!
Mitsuru!
Oh no!
Hold it, you Shocker cyborg!
Help me!
Wretched Shocker...
Take your time fighting him.
I'll be taking the child!
You won't escape!
You've arrived, Rider!
I won't let you have that child!
Take this!
- Taki!
- Rider!
Look out!
Oh no!
I'm sorry, Rider.
If not for me...
It's nothing, Taki.
I promise I'll save Mitsuru.
But Shocker...
"Poison gas plant"...
Hayato, did you learn anything?
Just this.
A plant that emits poison gas.
I'll analyze it.
What about me?
Stay here, please.
Hayato, contact me the
minute you learn something.
I feel like it's my fault that
Mitsuru was kidnapped.
I will, of course.
KAMEN RIDER
Gentlemen.
Kamen Rider may have
learned of our killer plants.
Hurry!
Initiate Operation: G at once!
Initiate Operation: G!
Colonel Zol. What about the boy?
Kill him alongside Goro
Ishikura and his friends.
What? Goro and his friends?
I've already taken measures
to deal with Goro and his friends.
You need only follow my orders.
I don't know about the florist
that sold us this thing...
Don't you agree, Goro?
Three o'clock!
I hope Mari and Yuri show up soon!
Goro, why are you so
concerned about the time?
The monster autograph
session is starting at four!
Monster autograph session?
Let's go!!
Monster Autograph Session
Ticket
Oh, I see.
We're ready to head out, Goro.
You're late, you two!
Just 30 minutes left! I gotta go!
Hey, Goro!
Beautiful! What a lovely flower!
Yeah!
Looks like the chairman
is finally thinking about us.
Isn't that right, Mr. Chairman?
I guess...
What? Poison gas?
I'm sure of it.
Shocker is experimenting with
plants that emit poison gas.
Taki. Would you mind putting
in one more call to Mr. Tachibana?
Sure thing. Just hang on.
Hello, Pops?
Hello?
Hello? Pops!
Strange...
Hayato. Something's wrong at the club.
I think something's happened!
Taki, hurry to the club!
Right.
Tachibana Auto Corner
Taki, open the window!
Right!
Hang in there! Mari!
It's okay! They're not dead!
Getting them to fresh
air should save them.
Really? Great.
Yuri!
You made it out alive, Racing Club.
But it's too late to stop our plan.
Stage one of our plan will
commence at four o'clock.
The children you count as your friends
will die holding hands together...
Like the children they are!
He must mean Mitsuru, Goro, and the others.
Ten minutes until then.
Taki, we can't give up.
We need to save Mitsuru and Goro.
I know that!
But where do we start looking?
Pops!
Do you know where Goro went?
Damn... I knew there was
something off about that florist...
Pops! Do you know where Goro went?
Yes... I do.
The Sky Building.
He went to some
monster autograph session...
When's it scheduled for?
Four o'clock, he said...
Five minutes left.
Taki, I'm on my way!
Transform!
This way! This way!
Come on! Come on!
There's lots of monsters to be seen!
So many monsters!
Hurry! Hurry!
Monsters, monsters!
This way!
Right here! Right here!
This is the place!
I'm gonna get his autograph.
I'm gonna get this one!
I'll get this one, for sure!
They're here!
Lots of scary monsters right here!
Monsters!
They look familiar...
Can I get your autograph?
Darn it!
Take this, you jerk!
Cry, scream, suffer!
Let's get going.
You can die with them!
Only one minute remains!
Goro!
Mitsuru... Th-They got you, too?
They're gonna kill us with
that poison gas plant!
Fifty seconds left...
Hey!
Thirty seconds remain.
Kamen Rider!
I'll kill the children
right before your eyes!
Rider!
Try me, Shocker!
If it's a fight you want, you've got it!
Taki!
Goro! Is everyone okay?
It's a plant that makes poison gas!
Get out of here, now!
This way, everyone!
Damn it!
Hey, guys! We can get out this way!
After him!
Rider! Where are you, Rider?
I'm right here!
Oh no! He's about to spit that toxic fluid!
Oh no!
Now!
Rider Kick!
Rider Punch!
This way!
He did it!
- Rider!
Mitsuru! Mitsuru!
Mama!
- Mitsuru!
- Mama!
Mama!
Rider!
Rider! Thank you, Rider!
The battle had ended.
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen Rider,
had saved many young lives this day.
But he had no time to rest.
He had to always be ready,
preparing to fight new monsters
that could appear at any time.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the lightning monster Eiking.
Shocker summons lightning to put the
Worldwide Blackout Operation into motion,
but the Kamen Rider will
rise up to stop them.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Lightning Monster Eiking's
Worldwide Blackout Operation."
Lightning Monster Eiking's
Worldwide Blackout Operation.
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!