KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Pirasaurus
The Devil Wrestler
Hey, this is my stop!
Stop the bus!
What's that driver doing?
Hey, what's going on here?
Hey, did you hear us?
Your destination... is hell!
What did you say?
You're talking crazy.
This bus is a mobile
Shocker testing lab.
And you're all the guinea pigs.
Now... experience the terror
of Shocker's death mist!
Run!
Someone help!
It was a roaring success!
Hey, answer me!
He's dead...
He wasn't strong
enough to withstand the
death mist generator
implanted inside of him.
We'll need a stronger
human specimen.
The Pirasaurus is a
creature theorized to
have existed deep in
South America long ago,
capable of emitting
venom from its body.
Its poison mist was a thing of
terror, capable
of killing even giant
dinosaurs in seconds.
Shocker managed to find a pirasaurus and
fused it with a human to create a cyborg.
But their human specimen
lived only a few days
after being imbued with
the pirasaurus' venom.
In order to create a
more perfect cyborg,
Shocker's most brilliant
scientists began a new analysis
of the pirasaurus
from various angles
to acquire new data.
They then put that data
into their computer.
Soon, the computer used
the data it was given,
to give them the
name of a human.
This human would be capable of
enduring the pirasaurus' venom.
This computer's cold diagnosis
did not take into account
whether the person in question
would want this or not.
My scientists,
Shocker's pride and joy.
Has your analysis produced a
satisfactory response from the computer?
Sir.
The computer has named a man
with the power to become a
pirasaurus cyborg from the million
stored within its memory banks.
Nationality: Japanese.
Name: Kusaka Noboru.
Age: 28.
Occupation: Pro wrestler.
Excellent.
Maya. Hurricane Joe.
Take our welcoming team
and bring this professional wrestler
Kusaka Noboru into our fold at once.
Today's main event...
A 61-minute best out of three.
In the blue corner...
the challenger!
At 245 pounds, Mr. Jinbaori!
In the red corner...
the Ocean League Champion!
At 230 pounds, Kusaka Noboru!
The champion Kusaka Noboru, also known
by his ring name "the human machine"
flashes a victory sign into
the cameras again tonight.
I think that v-sign is meant
for his little brother, Kiyoshi.
See? It's true.
My brother flashed me a v-sign!
That's so cool!
Get me his autograph, okay?
Now, the 61-minute best
of three match has begun.
Will the winner be the
champion, Kusaka,
or the challenger, Mr. Jinbaori?
Get him!
What's all the noise about?
That wrestler is his brother!
Let's all root for him!
He's pretty cool!
Go! Go!
Hey, now, keep it down!
One, two, three!
The champion Kusaka
takes the first match!
Yeah!
I see Kusaka's still on top.
Hey, Chairman.
He's this kid's big brother.
Oh... yours, eh?
Hey, that's Hayato!
I was wondering where
he'd gotten off to!
I'm going to see him.
Me, too!
Me, too.
Hey, you!
Sorry about that.
What's gotten into them?
Have a look.
Ichimonji Hayato?
Nice one!
Why, you...
Right there!
There goes my precious film...
Use the Ultra Punch! Get him!
Great job!
Make it a little more exciting!
Why, you...
One, two, three!
Kusaka Noboru wins
the second match!
I think we've all seen
why he's the champion!
Yeah! He did it!
He's strong, isn't he?
In fifty matches, the champion
Kusaka has 48 wins and two ties.
And that Ultra Punch
of his is unbeatable!
I'm with the Maicho Shimbun.
Can I get your
picture, Mr. Kusaka?
Maicho Shimbun?
Of course.
Something like this?
Who are you?
What... what are you doing?
Damn you...
You...
That venom would take down an African
elephant in less than ten seconds...
But he endured it for twenty!
No wonder the computer
chose this man.
His stamina is incredible!
Excuse me.
What is it?
That's an unusual
camera you have.
Could I have a look at it?
Sorry, but I'm busy right now.
Just a few minutes.
I'm obsessed with
cameras, you see...
Certainly not.
Hey, what's the big deal?
Leave me alone!
I didn't think that
was a normal camera...
Looks like I was right.
Joe, I'm being tailed.
Leave it to me.
You don't look like a
Shocker cyborg to me...
I'm Hurricane Joe.
I train Shocker cyborgs
and guard their commanders!
Why don't you show
me what you've got?
You're certainly strong enough
to be a Shocker trainer...
But not strong
enough to beat me!
Damn you...
Rider...
I've had enough for today.
I see...
They put on a performance
to throw me off her trail.
KAMEN RIDER
They'll be convinced that pro wrestler
Kusaka Noboru died in a car accident.
Just as I thought...
What was she doing here?
The pro wrestler Kusaka
and his little brother...
Hey, son.
Son.
Why don't you head home?
I don't think your
brother is coming.
Hey, I'll get him home.
Upsy-daisy.
That's weird... my brother
never broke a promise before...
I wanna check the arena.
Big Brother!
See? He's not here.
I'm sure he's just gone home.
Wrong!
My brother wouldn't do that!
Something must have happened!
Happened?
Hey, Kiyoshi.
He's the best wrestler in Japan, right?
Don't you worry.
Kiyoshi... Kiyoshi...
Kiyoshi!
Big Brother!
Kiyoshi...
Kusaka Noboru's memories
have now been purged.
Good.
Now begin the cyborg surgery.
Maya. Hurricane Joe.
The cyborg surgery
was a success.
Now take command of him, to help him
use his cyborg powers to their fullest.
Yes, sir.
I will train him into a champion
cyborg, I swear it.
Listen. You're a fusion
of pirasaurus and human.
Put your powers to the test!
Go on, try it!
Step back!
Fire!
You're an invincible
cyborg champion!
We'll run Pirasaurus Man's final test
tomorrow at the motocross racetrack.
Okay. Who goes first?
Not me!
What's wrong with you kids?
Not me! You do it!
Go on, clear the way.
What's up, Hayato?
Giving up photography
to be a racer today?
Pretty much.
I was hoping you could time me.
I don't have time to
deal with amateurs.
Don't be so cold, Chairman.
I might just have to quit.
Me, too.
What's with you girls?
Why side with Hayato over me?
Well, fine...
Go on, drive.
Okay, I'll do a light lap.
Far out!
Wretched Shocker cyborg...
Challenging me again?
This is no challenge.
Kamen Rider...
you've been chosen as my guinea pig!
What was that?
Guinea pig, you say?
He's taking a while...
Kamen Rider!
You are no match for me!
Rider Kick!
Ultra Kick!
I have won!
That punch, powerful enough
to break through steel...
It seems to have fouled up the
Kamen Rider's internal mechanisms.
Three hours, 27 minutes, huh?
Come on. Cheer up, everyone.
I'm sure Hayato
will come back safe.
I know. Let's do some go-go
dancing to cheer ourselves up.
Sounds good.
How can those guys
can be so calm?
A man's missing out there.
Yeah, it's not cool at all...
In the red corner,
the Orient League Champion...
At 235 pounds, Gomeito Ota!
It's pro wrestling.
In the blue corner,
the challenger...
At 230 pounds, Satan Mask!
Did he say Satan Mask?
He crippled ten men at the
pan-American championships.
The eyes behind that mask...
I know that's my brother!
Okay!
Speaking of pro wrestling...
What happened to that kid whose
big brother was the champion?
There he is! That's the kid!
Big Brother! It's me!
Why won't you come to see me?
Even with that mask on,
I can still tell it's you!
Big Brother!
I don't know you.
Finish that child off!
All right.
What are you doing?
You're mean, Big Brother!
The Kamen Rider!
Passing off a cyborg
as a pro wrestler...
What is Shocker plotting now?!
Kiyoshi!
Take the child to safety.
Right!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
will be Pirasaurus
again next week.
Shocker's plot is to advance
Pirasaurus as a professional wrestler
then use his death mist,
the S-gas, to destroy humanity.
The clash between Rider and
Pirasaurus plays out in the ring.
Join us next week for "Deathmatch
in the Ring! Defeat Pirasaurus!"
Deathmatch in the Ring
Defeat! Pirasaurus
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!