KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The secret organization Shocker,
in their quest for world domination,
chose professional wrestler Kusaka Noboru
to become a fusion of human and pirasaurus,
a monster capable of killing
a woolly mammoth in seconds.
But Noboru's little brother Kiyoshi
has been searching fervently for him,
unaware that he has been
turned into a merciless cyborg.
Now, the cyborg Noboru
Kusaka has appeared
in the ring as the mysterious
pro wrestler Satan Mask,
and the boy Kiyoshi pursues him,
convinced Satan Mask is his big brother.
Deathmatch in the Ring
Defeat! Pirasaurus
Try me!
Ultra Kick!
Running, are you, Kamen Rider?!
I'm not running.
I'm just putting off the match until
I can find out what you really are.
Wait!
Don't bother.
You can't stop him.
C'mon, Kiyoshi.
Just drop it already.
I keep telling you,
Satan Mask isn't your brother!
Yes, he is!
I can see it in his eyes!
You're being pretty
stubborn about this!
I gotta say, I dig it!
But seriously, think about it...
Satan Mask is from
America, remember?
My brother could've gone to
America without telling me.
I won't give up until I see
underneath Satan Mask's mask.
Boy, oh boy. Kids these days!
Fine, I'll help you out!
Help me out?
Listen up...
Okay, kids.
I've got a real feast
for you tonight.
Open up!
Did they fall asleep
while they were waiting?
Did those kids...
Goro... you got me this time.
I heard Satan Mask is in
room 1742 in this hotel.
But how are we
supposed to get inside?
I have my ways.
Now wait for my next trick!
Where'd you get those keys?
Remember what Mr. Taki said?
These keys can open up any door!
He's gonna yell at you...
Don't you worry!
When he hears I'm doing it for a
friend, he'll forgive me.
That's the mean lady who
wouldn't let me see my brother!
So if she's out of the room...
That means Satan Mask
is alone in there!
Yeah.
That's great news for us!
Wow!
Listen to that snoring!
This is just perfect.
My brother snored really
bad, too.
Hold your horses already.
We're about to find
out if it's him!
I'm gonna do it!
J-Just be careful!
It's not my brother!
Hey...
What are you doing here?
You're Satan Mask fans
who want an autograph, eh?
Y-Yeah! We want an autograph!
No! You're not the
real Satan Mask!
Hey, Kiyoshi!
Give up on this already!
We're really sorry.
He's a little slow
on the uptake...
Goodbye!
It went perfectly.
No, we can't rest easy yet.
We'll need to silence that
child for good sooner or later.
Now... where is Pirasaurus?
As planned,
he's gone to test the death mist.
I wonder what's
keeping Hayato...
It's not right to break
a promise to a lady!
Maybe I should call him...
It's hard to look cool
with just women around...
Agreed.
Public Phone
You go in first.
No, you first.
No, really.
No, you.
Come on, let's go.
Welcome, sir.
What can I get you?
Your life.
Give me your life.
That's really not funny, sir...
It's just creepy.
It's true.
What I've come for is your life!
Knock it off, you...
M-Monster!
Hiromi? Hey, is Hayato with you?
No...
I haven't seen Hayato all day.
What's this about Hayato?
Mr.
Chairman, it's Mari and Yuri.
Those two? Forget it.
I don't even know why those kids
even joined the racing club!
I see the generation
gap at play.
You shut up!
We heard all of that.
You can give the Chairman
a message from us.
That's right!
Tell him we joined the racing
club to improve our figures!
There is no way out.
You will all become guinea
pigs to test my death mist!
Public Phone
Wasn't that just so rude?
Let's put everything on
Hayato's tab tonight.
Mr. Bartender!
We'll have a soft
drink and a rice bowl.
I wonder what happened here...
Yeah. It's like everyone
fell right to sleep.
What happened, Mr. Bartender?
Come on, talk to us!
Mari, Yuri, speak to me!
They're pretty cute
when they're asleep.
You're weird, Mr. Chairman.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I don't have daughters of my
own, so...
What's up?
Is it true, what they saw?
We can't talk here.
Yeah.
Should we go into the back?
Hiromi, look after
them, won't you?
Right.
It's clear that Shocker's
pulling the strings here.
It's almost exactly like an
incident two weeks ago in Kawasaki.
The one where everyone on a bus
was bleached down to their bones?
That's right.
But I'm not sure how things
will develop from here.
It's that pro wrestler's role in
things that's tripping you up, right?
Yeah.
If he's really Kiyoshi's
brother, that complicates things.
Not again...
Better give it a rest before
something worse happens to you.
He's right.
You only made it out alive
because you're lucky.
It's more than luck!
We're just more
careful than most.
So, what did you want?
You have a visitor.
Come on in.
Goro!
Here...
I'm really sorry.
What did you do with these?
Kiyoshi just wouldn't lay off...
He wanted to see behind
Satan Mask's mask...
We've got a real pack of
daredevils in this club, I see.
So, what happened?
It really wasn't him!
It was someone else!
So Satan Mask wasn't
Kiyoshi's brother?
He wasn't the professional
wrestler Kusaka Noboru?
But Kiyoshi said he wasn't the
Satan Mask from the ring...
I couldn't believe it!
It wasn't the Satan
Mask from the ring?
I can tell...
The Satan Mask I saw yesterday
isn't the same person.
The eyes under the mask
weren't the same...
Pirasaurus.
You're becoming famous all over the
world under your pro wrestling identity.
The people go into a frenzy
over your superhuman feats.
And today, Pirasaurus will fight the
title match for the championship!
The arena will be
packed with people.
Among them will be important members of
the Japanese political and economic worlds.
We'll murder them all in
seconds using the death mist.
Japan will fall into chaos!
And Shocker will use that
chaos to take control of Japan.
Go, cyborg champion!
I will.
The poison gas my body emits can
kill tens of thousands at once.
That's right.
The champion...
I am the champion!
KAMEN RIDER
Is that him?
Okay... I'll tail him.
Why do you get to do everything?
There's also the woman.
You can have her.
The woman, huh?
Don't underestimate her.
She's still a member of Shocker.
I know, I know.
Good luck.
I guess I'll
infiltrate the hotel...
Is that you, Kiyoshi?
Mr. Taki!
If you were waiting for Satan
Mask, I'm afraid he just drove off.
I know that.
But that wasn't the real one.
What did you say?
Look! That's the real one there!
It's just like I thought.
That's my big brother!
If you would, please.
Wait, Kiyoshi.
Listen, Kiyoshi.
You're a big boy, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Then I have a favor to
ask, man to man.
What is it?
Quietly follow that Satan
Mask to his destination.
And then what?
Once he's arrived,
call the Tachibana Racing Club.
Call the Tachibana Racing Club?
Yes.
Hey, it's Satan Mask!
Now, now...
Foolish people...
lining up for the executioner's block.
Show yourself, Ichimonji Hayato!
I knew you would follow me!
Well, I guess you got me.
But I know who you really
are, too.
The pro wrestler Satan Mask...
You're really the Shocker
cyborg, Pirasaurus!
Impressive, Ichimonji.
Now, fight...
And prove your worth to me!
If you insist.
Let's go!
A sold-out house of fools.
As we hoped, it's full of people from the
Japanese political and economic worlds.
The champion...
I'm the champion!
Five minutes from now,
the bell will ring.
The infernal bell that will
lead them to their deaths!
Pirasaurus...
just what are you after?
Taki!
Hayato! He's a fake!
Look!
Then where's the
real Pirasaurus?
Call the club.
I'll take over here.
You're late... too late.
Pirasaurus will already be in the
arena, slaughtering the Japanese elite!
I won't let that happen!
Good luck, Taki!
Right. Go to it, Hayato!
Transform!
So cool!
There's no accounting
for taste...
People really think he's cool?
He sure is!
Kiyoshi,
don't tell me you still...
Yeah.
Go! Big Brother!
One minute until the bell rings.
Right...
Pirasaurus is at the arena.
One minute until the bell
rings to start the match.
I'm not going to make it!
It's time for
today's main event.
A 61-minute best out of three!
In the red corner,
the World Ocean Champion!
At 230 pounds, Satan Mask!
Pretty cool.
And the challenger...
Kamen Rider!
Go, Kamen Rider!
Pirasaurus...
your challenger is the Kamen Rider!
What did you say?
Everyone, evacuate the arena!
It's not safe here!
Escape!
Kamen Rider...
Run away!
Run, everyone!
Run!
That woman...
Let's get her!
Hey, wait!
Hey, wait up!
Kiyoshi!
Pops! Where's Kiyoshi?
I lost sight of him!
Kiyoshi!
What are you doing
to my brother?
It's not safe! Get away!
No! Stop being
mean to my brother!
Kiyoshi... look!
Do you see now?
Die!
Kiyoshi!
Taki! Get him away! It's gas!
Right!
Let me go!
What is this thing?!
The death mist!
It doesn't work on you?
Looks like you
used up your stock.
Ultra Punch!
Rider Kick!
I won! I'm... the champion!
Big Brother!
Kiyoshi!
Does that mean that
monster was my brother?
No.
The monster's death has brought
your brother back to life.
Wait for us!
Bye-bye!
No fair!
They left without us!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the fossil man, Hitodanger.
Fossil man Hitodanger
repels the Rider Kick,
and flies like a ninja
star to attack our Rider.
Hitodanger wreaks havoc in the
rapids deep in the mountains
where he clashes
with Kamen Rider.
Join us next week for
"Fossil Man Hitodanger."
Fossil Man
Hitodanger
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!