KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Worm Man
of the Bottomless Swamp!
Hey, it's pulling hard.
- Help me out!
- All right!
Why you...
Hey, look! Look!
A monster!
What is this?
It's a monster!
You've learned the location
of Shocker's secret base!
We haven't! We don't know
what you're talking about!
You think you can stumble on our
secret base and leave here alive?
Fools!
Those are my killer rings!
That should teach you a lesson!
The intruders are disposed of.
No one must be allowed
to approach this base.
Worm Man.
We will soon begin the
cobalt bomb radiation plan.
An explosion caused by
conventional Cobalt 60...
This is what it looks like.
Cobalt 120, which contains ten
times the destructive power,
will be arriving in Japan soon.
You were modified from
a brandling earthworm,
the only organism
known to survive
the hydrogen bomb
experiments on Bikini Atoll.
Thus, you are the only one
who can carry out this plan.
You carry a heavy burden.
I understand, sir.
I will conduct the handover of the
Cobalt 120 at the 51st Wharf today.
You will then take command.
Two more men have gone
missing at Persimmon Swamp.
You think they fell
into the swamp?
Oh, please!
There were two of them!
It's not like it's bottomless.
But isn't Persimmon Swamp
the place they found those fissures
in the ground six months ago?
Am I right, Chairman?
That's right, I remember now.
They thought it was a sign of
a big earthquake coming, right?
I was thinking of that myself.
Sorry, Taki, but could you investigate
deeper into the patterns they saw then?
You think the disappearances
are connected?
I'm not sure,
but investigate as much as you can.
Okay.
Please move swiftly and pay
attention to the signals.
This is the scramble crossing.
If you intend to cross, please move
swiftly and pay attention to the signals.
Boss! Boss!
You idiot!
Don't scare me like that, Sabu!
Hey, Tatsu. How'd it go?
Y-You're creeping me
out, Boss...
Total success!
Ready?
Feast your eyes!
Wow, awesome!
Boss, how much do you
think it'll fetch?
In my opinion...
ten million at the very least!
Ten million!
You idiot! Keep your voice down!
You're the stupidest
man I've ever known!
Hurry up and drive! Drive!
Right!
You idiot!
Watch where you're
driving, jerk!
What was that?
Get out here!
- Take that!
- Why, you...
He got me...
Hey, let's go!
Let's go!
Wait a minute!
Hey, wait a minute!
Damn you! You'll pay for this!
Boss! Boss!
Good morning.
We're way past morning!
Take it, Boss!
What? It's gotten lighter!
What's in there?
What is...
A chocolate bar?
What is it?
It's too hard to be chocolate!
You idiot!
You got the wrong case!
They went that way, Boss!
Look, don't let that
car out of your sight!
Just you wait, you jerks!
Persimmon Swamp is
close to the ocean,
so people thought it could be the influence
of something happening on the sea floor.
That's all we know.
And by the time investigators came
by, the rumblings had died down.
Pops.
This topography... it's the kind of
place they might set up shop, right?
Shocker, you mean?
Yes.
You mean... Shocker could be
behind the disappearances?
I can't help but think so.
Taki, let's go.
You let some strange men get
their hands on the Cobalt 120?!
You will pay for this!
Who are you people?
That's them!
That's the man
who took our case!
What? Get him!
Now, now, now.
No need to fret, now.
What is this, a masquerade ball?
What was that?
We'll be taking our jewels
back, if you don't mind.
Shut up! Give us that case!
The hell I will!
I thought we could just trade
cases and be on our way,
but I think you need
to learn some manners!
Sabu, take this.
Right.
Look at you,
wearing that worm monster mask...
This isn't a carnival, y'know!
Take it off now.
Hey, it's not a mask!
It's not a mask!
Help me!
H-Help me!
Monster!
Hongo, this way.
The swamp we're looking
for is this way.
Help!
It's a monster!
Help me!
I knew it was Shocker...
Monster!
Hongo Takeshi!
Shocker!
What are you plotting here?
Shut up! Hand over the
case that man is carrying!
Case?
Never!
Get them!
Help me!
Wait!
Rider Transformation!
The more you struggle,
the tighter it becomes.
Hard to breathe,
isn't it, Rider?!
KAMEN RIDER
I lost... he beat me completely.
But why did the ring come off?
How did I get it off?
I commend you for
defeating the Kamen Rider.
But how could you have
lost the Cobalt 120?!
I beg your forgiveness.
I will retrieve it!
And how will you do
that, exactly?
The Kamen Rider is dead.
I'll use this man as a hostage to
lure that hoodlum Saburo to us.
Spare me, please!
Do it at once.
Wait!
Ambassador Hell,
the Kamen Rider survives.
Wh-What did you say?
And the stolen Cobalt 120
is with Hongo Takeshi.
You must retrieve it
from him at any cost!
Hongo Takeshi is alive?!
How did I get the ring off?
I need to figure out how I removed
this ring as soon as possible
or the next time we
fight, he'll kill me.
Hongo.
Did you figure out
what was in the case?
Yes.
Stand back. It's dangerous.
It's incredibly radioactive...
What the...
It's Cobalt 120, whose radioactivity
greatly outstrips that of Cobalt 60.
Shocker is going to use
it to create a new bomb.
It's clear that we must keep
it out of Shocker's hands.
Hey... what's gonna
happen to Boss Nogami?
Hey, don't worry.
We'll save him. Right, Hongo?
Give me a little bit more time.
Saburo.
If you don't want to die,
bring us the Cobalt 120.
No! I don't want to die!
Then go and steal the cobalt.
If Hongo and Taki try to stop
you, make them drink poison!
Look inside your hand.
Poison... in my hand?
My entire nervous system was focused on
my neck, as I tried to get the ring off.
Of course... in that instant,
I hit my power switch.
I used Rider Power
to break the ring.
What's wrong, Saburo?
Why the long face?
Oh, I'm fine...
You're an odd duck.
Hey, Saburo.
Hey, calm down.
Stop crying and tell us.
What's going on here?
Sh-Shocker gave me...
this poison...
Damn you, Shocker...
I'll finish them this time!
Save me...
Saburo betrayed us.
What? Saburo betrayed us?
Then I'll kill this man and
take back the Cobalt 120 myself!
Please, spare me!
Taki, I'm going on ahead.
Right. Good luck!
Rider Transformation!
This time, you die!
I'm a goner!
Not so fast!
Rider!
Did you come here to die?!
Shocker. Fight me!
Silence!
Get him!
Hold it!
Help me! Help...
Shocker is coming,
Rider, the monster is
heading for the ocean!
with its armies
straight from hell
Understood.
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Hold it!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Get him!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider!
Let's go, Worm Man!
Rider, Rider!
Die!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Killer ring!
Victory is mine!
Now... Rider Power!
Rider Power!
Rider Power! Rider Power!
How dare you!
Rider Kick!
Sorry about all the trouble...
Boss!
Saburo!
Boss! I'm so happy!
I'm so glad you're safe!
What's with those two, Pops?
No idea.
But it's quite a moving
reunion, isn't it?
I guess they must've known
each other a long time.
Male friendship, I guess?
I hope they learn their lesson and
give up their life of crime. Right?
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
So happy! So happy!
The heroic actions of the Kamen
Rider, Hongo Takeshi,
prevented Shocker from
realizing their radiation plan.
But Shocker's attacks
would continue.
Keep fighting, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the eerie Owl Man.
The explosive energy of the
X-rays built into his eyes
causes clock towers all
over the country to explode.
Join us next week for "The
Monstrous Owl Man's Killer X-Rays."
The Eerie Owl
Man's Killer X-Rays
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!