KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Blood-Sucking Mosquilas
Versus the Two Riders
H-Help me!
Capable of draining not just the blood,
but all fluids from the human body,
the terrifying cyborg Mosquilas
was Shocker's newest weapon.
Go forth, Mosquilas.
Erect a new Shocker base.
Your target is Katsuura Port
in the southern Kii Peninsula.
"Kumano is at the center of the east
side of Yoshino-Kumano National Park.
Enjoy views of the Kuroshio
Current in the Kumano-nada Sea
and beautiful green mountains."
Goodbye to those smoggy skies, huh?
Hey, isn't Nachi Falls
the tallest waterfall in Japan?
They have that special candy there, right?
Oh Choco, are you talking about food again?
But I hate that stuff.
I just want a soak in those
Katsuura hot springs.
Listen to you talk, like it's a vacation!
We're not going there to play around.
That's right. We're hunting bugs
for our summer homework!
Right?
Welcome
Nachi-Katsuura
Tourism Department
Okay, almost there! A little further!
Okay, there we are!
Hey, Uncle!
Hello!
You're growing like a weed!
Hello.
Thanks for having us.
- Thanks for coming.
- Hello.
Hello, this way.
All around there is Katsuura Port.
It's where the hot springs all bubble up.
It's as grand a view as I'd imagined.
It's easy to forget about Shocker
when you're in a place like this.
Shocker?
Oh, nothing...
Right this way.
I didn't even know they'd be here.
This should make things very interesting!
What a view!
Awesome! You can't
see this stuff in Tokyo!
There's lots of rhino
and stag beetles, I hear.
Yeah.
Let's climb a little higher!
I want Mr. Hongo to see this place!
Yeah. But I dunno where we'll find them...
Let's ask that monk!
Excuse me, Mr. Monk.
We have a question for you...
How can I help you?
Monster!
Darn it... you're Shocker, aren't you!
Let me go!
Hey, why aren't you guys eating?
Those two have been out for a while...
They should be heading
back to eat around now...
You think they got lost?
Good point...
Okay, let's go find them.
Excuse me.
Hello, there.
What? Why aren't you eating?
Naoki and Mitsuru haven't come back yet.
That's no good. Naoki was with him?
We were just thinking
of going to look for them.
I'll have our clerk guide you.
Come along.
Over there!
It's Naoki's hat!
Something must have happened here.
We should split up and search.
We'll go this way, then.
Excuse me, sir!
Have you seen two boys pass this way?
Why yes, I have!
M-Monster!
Help me!
Hey, where's the clerk?
I was waiting for him, too.
That must be the scream we heard...
Let's go!
There you are!
I knew Shocker was behind this...
And I'll do the same to you!
Run!
Hurry!
Stay together, everyone!
I knew you'd come, Rider!
Okay...
Run, everyone!
Okay!
Why, you...
Damn. He got away!
Rider, where are you going?
It's been too long.
Hayato!
It was you...
What's happening?
I got hold of some information that
Shocker was sending its cyborg
created deep in the Amazon,
Mosquilas, to Japan.
So I pursued.
I see...
We came here for summer vacation...
We weren't expecting
Shocker to show up here!
They're trying to establish a base
here in the southern Kii Peninsula,
with access to the Pacific Ocean.
That explains a great deal.
Oh no!
What's the matter?
Naoki and the others are in danger!
Ambassador Hell...
Impressive indeed, Ichimonji Hayato...
You tracked us down.
Grab him!
Transform!
Hold it!
Stay where you are...
Or the children die!
Help!
KAMEN RIDER
Get him, Mosquilas!
I've killed Rider!
So this is the entrance to their base...
Investigate the plunge pool!
Find Ichimonji Hayato's
body and bring it to me!
Well? Any luck?
I couldn't find them.
Where could they have gone?
I'll go to pray to the gods!
I'll buy a shrine fortune!
Please let us find the boys safe and sound.
Please!
"Those whom you seek are near.
Wait and they shall arrive."
Look, look, look!
I got best luck!
You're right!
Excuse me.
Are you looking for boys
about ten years of age?
You know them?
You really know them?
Tell us where they are!
There were two of them!
I thought so.
I found them collapsed in the mountains.
We're caring for them
in the great hall there.
Really?
This way.
What a lovely hall...
Come along.
Take the girls to our underground base!
Impressive as ever, Hongo...
It seems he sniffed us out.
Go, Mosquilas.
Someone saw a monk
lead three girls in here.
I don't like the look of it.
- Yeah.
- Let's go in.
All right...
Don't move!
You've showed yourself... Shocker cyborg!
Try to transform and your friends die!
What?
We have all five of them in custody.
I'll show you. Come along!
Look there.
Naoki!
Mitsuru!
Mr. Hongo!
It's pretty hot...
Damn...
Naoki, hang in there!
Hey! Are you guys all right?
It's boiling hot...
Naoki!
Hang in there!
Well, well...
Thank you so much for coming.
We've awaited your arrival.
Damn you, Shocker...
What are you going
to do to these children?
If you want to save them,
let Mosquilas feed upon you.
Do it, Mosquilas!
Hongo... it's time to die!
Hongo, don't resist, or the children die.
Damn...
Hongo!
Stay where you are, Taki!
Mr. Hongo!
We're finished!
It stopped!
Who turned it off?
Hongo!
Turn it back on at once!
Kamen Rider is here!
Hongo, leave this to me!
You survived, did you?
Finish him!
What are you doing? Kill him at once!
Taki, get them to safety!
All right.
- Hang in there.
- I'll be fine!
Hayato, I'm going to join you!
Hongo, are you sure?
Rider Transformation!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Damn...
Rider... this isn't over!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
He's heading for Dorokyo Gorge.
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Okay, let's go!
Rider, Rider!
Mosquilas... you won't escape!
Look behind you!
What?
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Rider Knee Block!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Double Kick!
Damn you, Kamen Riders...
But I haven't given up yet.
Just watch me!
I will establish a Shocker base
on the southern Kii Peninsula!
We have yet more tricks in store.
I'm counting on you, Siomaneking!
See the Kamen Riders dead at last!
Hongo Takeshi and Ichimonji Hayato had
defeated the blood-sucking monster Mosquilas,
and stopped Shocker's
awful plan in its tracks.
But Shocker wasn't finished yet,
as it sent a monster called Siomaneking
to the southern Kii Peninsula.
Fight on, Kamen Riders!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next monster that I, Ambassador Hell,
will send in is Siomaneking!
He'll use the deadly foam that he shoots
from his mouth to melt down both Riders!
I will create an underwater Shocker
city no matter what it takes!
Now, tune in next week for "Defeat It, Double Riders!!
Siomaneking."
Double Riders!! Siomaneking
Defeat It
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!