KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Mantis Man
Central Earthquake
Research Facility
Hello? Central Earthquake
Research Facility.
Yes, I'm Chikako Amemiya of the Academic
Society for Earthquake Prediction.
Yes, we have all the
latest equipment.
Yes,
it's all utterly cutting-edge.
Even the newspapers
were interested.
Hello?
Excuse me,
but might I ask who's calling?
Hello? Hello?
That's strange...
A power outage?
I think it's around here...
There it is.
Who's there? The security guard?
Dear me...
Did a fuse blow out somewhere?
Is that you, Mr. Guard?
Hey! You okay?
Yes...
Must've been an earthquake.
Yeah... it scared me.
We've had a lot of them
lately, haven't we?
We might have a
big one coming up.
Would you put that
as a 5.0 magnitude?
Magnitude refers to the energy
emitted at the quake's epicenter.
What we feel in each location is
measured in terms of seismic intensity.
I guess even you mix them
up, Mr. Tachibana.
I see!
So the intensity is lower as you
move away from the epicenter...
I never realized that.
So by creating a distribution plot
of seismic intensity readings,
and tracing back to
where it's the strongest,
you can learn the
location of the epicenter,
and that tells
you the magnitude.
Got it?
That's right.
Oh, no...
I get it now.
Takeshi is the one who taught
you about epicenters, right?
But at least we know that catfish have
nothing to do with earthquakes, right?
The usual, please.
Hey, Takeshi.
Speaking of earthquakes...
remember Chikako Amemiya?
She was a childhood friend of
yours, wasn't she?
Yes.
A sweet girl from my hometown,
three years older than me.
I believe she's become a
respected seismologist.
Why did you bring her up?
Look. She's gone missing!
What?
Hey, these aren't human cells!
They're insect cells!
Looks like part of a spine
from a serrated insect leg.
But it would have to
be one big insect...
What would something
like that be doing on
the floor of an earthquake
research center?
You picked it up because you
thought it was suspicious, right?
Yes. But...
I feel like there's a clue in the link
between that insect leg and this map.
There's a lot of symbols
and numbers written on it...
Yes.
It's like a series of recent
earthquakes and their epicenter.
What are we supposed
to learn from that?
Look closer.
Isn't it strange to have
earthquakes occurring
on the outskirts of
a city like this?
Even if they are weak ones...
There have been seven
already this year.
Well, that is strange, but...
There's only one
conclusion we can come to.
They're the ones behind this.
It's considerably irradiated...
Damn you, Shocker...
I bet they're detonating small
nuclear payloads underground
and disguising them
as earthquakes.
Which means...
They're tests!
They've done seven tests so far,
and the scale is
gradually increasing.
Which means...
They're plotting to
engineer a major earthquake.
Hongo here.
What? Chikako?
Takeshi...
I need your help with something.
I've found the main base of the people
trying to engineer an earthquake.
Please... come quickly. Alone.
The location is...
Who's there?
Chikako!
Takeshi...
I knew you'd come.
Thank you so much.
Not at all...
I'll explain why I
invited you later.
For now, we need to stop them!
Right. Show me the way.
Inside that hole.
Takeshi!
Chikako!
Takeshi, help me!
Takeshi!
Damn...
Hongo, you're helpless now!
There's no way out of that hole.
Listen up...
you have only two minutes to live!
Damn you...
There's no way you
can reach this.
No need to finish the
modifications on scum like you...
Better to rid ourselves
of you entirely.
And this bomb will be
the perfect way to do it!
Hey! Wait!
Just ninety seconds left.
I can't give in.
I'll struggle to the very end.
Damn...
If I die here, Shocker will be free
to cause a major earthquake in Japan.
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Wait!
How did you survive that?
The wind from the explosion
triggered my belt!
Give Chikako to me!
Stay back or I'll kill her!
Wait!
Get him!
Find him!
Find him quickly!
Go! After him!
KAMEN RIDER
You must retrieve that
woman at all costs!
The success of Operation:
Artificial Earthquake
depends on the aid of
that earthquake expert!
Find her,
no matter what it takes!
Sir!
Takeshi's late today.
He'd normally be here by now...
He must be caught up
in his research again.
Is there something
you're worried about?
Not really...
What's wrong, Shiro?
Just outside... a monster!
Oh, honestly.
I think you've been
watching too much TV?
No, I really saw it!
A giant mantis monster!
I'll check it out.
Ruriko!
There's no one here.
She's waking up.
That's a relief.
Poor Chikako.
Chikako was just great at tag.
The neighborhood kids would
run, but she'd always catch us.
You played tag, Takeshi?
You must have been
an adorable child.
But now it's Shocker that's
chasing the both of us.
That reminds me...
will they come back to get her?
Yes...
I need to do
something, and fast.
No...
No.
It's too awful...
No, no, no!
Chikako. Get a hold of yourself!
An earthquake...
A major earthquake!
An earthquake?
Egg...
Mantis egg...
What are you talking about?
Shocker... at
4:00 PM...
Chikako! Chikako!
You're awake at last!
Where am I?
Takeshi's apartment.
You're safe now.
Chikako...
Can you explain what you
were saying just now?
A major earthquake
and a mantis egg...
I don't know what
you're talking about.
4:00 PM... was that today?
I don't know anything.
Chikako isn't even my name.
You have the wrong person.
I'm leaving!
Wait a minute!
That hurts!
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry...
I'm a cyborg.
Shocker modified my body,
giving me strength beyond my control...
Return her.
Return the woman!
Never!
Go, get to safety!
Well done.
Finish preparations for Operation:
Artificial Earthquake at once.
I've calculated
the nuclear energy
needed based on
detonation sites,
crust vibrations, and necessary
magnitude, and finished the placement.
In order to destroy a city,
we must target locations in which
overuse of underground water systems has
created land subsidence,
which will amplify the dislocation.
Only thirty minutes left...
You've shown yourself, Mantis.
Wait!
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
The tests are now complete.
The earthquake will occur the moment
the detonation lever is pulled.
Good. Now sleep and
wait for further orders.
Soon, Japan will be destroyed!
I have you now, Mantis Man!
Those who rob others of their freedom
and threaten the peace must pay!
Tell me! Where is the switch
to initiate the earthquake?
M-Mantis... egg...
The mantis egg...
is that the term for the nuclear bomb?
Where is it?
It's...
Is that it?
Rider Kick!
Chikako.
Chikako... don't wake up yet.
I'm no longer little Takeshi,
the neighborhood boy you knew.
I'm not the grown-up Hongo
Takeshi, either.
I am a cyborg, forced into a battle
with Shocker that may never end...
I am Kamen Rider!
Enduring the sorrow
he felt as a cyborg,
Hongo Takeshi found new resolve
to live on as the Kamen Rider,
and fight Shocker's evil.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the elusive Chameleon Man.
What does he want with
Lieutenant Commander
Sunada of the former
Imperial Japanese Navy?
It's a struggle with Shocker over a
steel box left behind by the Nazis.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Shinigami Chameleon"!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!