KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Three Electric Monsters:
the Seadragons!!
Things have been too quiet
lately. It's boring!
The Kamen Rider Kid Corps
haven't had anything to do.
I'm getting soft!
Don't be so snotty.
I'm sure something terrible
will happen very soon!
Come on by!
We've got monsters straight
from America, fresh in a can!
Come on by!
Monsters in a can?
Let's check it out!
It's a monster in a can!
A monster in a can...
You think it's legit?
How much is it, ma'am?
I'll give you a great price.
200 yen apiece.
I only have three, so how
about you take one each?
I'm not sure.
It sounds fun, so maybe I'll buy one!
- Sure.
- I'll get one, too!
- Me, too!
- Here's your change.
Thank you.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Put them in water and they'll grow.
I hope you'll show me once
it's big and strong.
We will, ma'am!
I'm gonna bring it back
once it's this big!
Don't be silly.
It says here they don't
get bigger than one centimeter.
Right, ma'am?
No,
if you raise them very carefully,
they could even get this big!
Liar!
I'm gonna put mine in an aquarium!
Thank you for coming.
Huh? What's going on?
Is the monster gonna be born?
Help!
All finished.
Two o'clock, huh?
Got done earlier than I thought.
C'mon, hurry up!
Right.
M-Monster!
Help!
Hongo.
Look.
That's not how you'd
expect it to burn.
There's nothing left of the car.
It's just a heap of scrap metal...
A normal fire wouldn't do this.
Is this it?
What happened to the three workers?
That's the real mystery.
It's as if they just disappeared.
They weren't the only ones attacked.
The same thing happened to Choco.
I was really scared!
It means the three who bought
the monsters in a can were attacked.
What?
Monsters in a can?
What's really strange is that all the aquariums
the monsters were put in were broken.
Naoki.
Where did you buy those cans?
Stop!
Right over there!
Excuse me.
That's odd...
Okay, let's go around back.
Mr. Takeshi, help!
Taki!
Help!
Naoki!
That way!
What a dirty trick...
What now, Hongo?
Help me!
Scream!
Scream louder, Hongo Takeshi!
You've interfered in Shocker's plans
of conquest time and again...
but you're helpless now.
Ambassador Hell.
Your latest cyborg, Seadragon,
seems to be functioning just as expected.
Yes, my leader.
Electric monster Seadragon will
electrocute any who resist it
with the high-voltage electricity
stored in its antenna.
Wherever Seadragon goes,
mountains of the dead will follow!
Hold it!
Hongo, I am Shocker's cyborg, Seadragon.
Take one more step, and the child dies!
You damned Shocker monster...
I'm the one you're after, right?
Let the child go!
In exchange...
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'll kill this child, and then you!
What?
KAMEN RIDER
Watch carefully.
It hurts! Help!
Taki!
Taki, get him to safety!
Right! This way.
Grab them!
Not so fast!
Jump!
Hold it!
Well? Lost your nerve, Hongo Takeshi?
12,000 volts run through these antennae...
I'll turn you to ash
instantly, just like that car!
I see... it's this electricity.
He must have immolated
the workers along with their car.
Rider Transformation!
Kamen Rider... this is your end!
His legs are his weak point.
Ambassador Hell.
The Kamen Rider has identified
Seadragon's weak point.
Use the other two Seadragons
to destroy the Kamen Rider.
My leader.
I've fixed Seadragon's weak point.
The Kamen Rider's life
will soon be extinguished.
Mr. Hongo's coming!
Help!
Someone help!
Hang in there!
I'm on my way now!
Help!
Hey! What's going on?
Hey!
Die, Hongo Takeshi!
You'll never get in my way again!
That looks bad!
Mr. Hongo disappeared!
We'd better tell HQ!
Well done, Seadragon II.
Ambassador Hell.
The electrocution has rendered Hongo
Takeshi in a state of near-death.
Let's finish him off now!
Not yet.
I couldn't stand the thought
of killing him so easily.
He's destroyed too many of
our precious cyborgs in the past.
He's foiled more Shocker
plans than we can count.
Hongo Takeshi is our mortal enemy.
Today, I will make him an evil incarnate,
from the top of his head
to the bottom of his toes.
Open a hole in the top of his skull.
We'll replace his cerebrum
and cerebellum with an evil AI.
Hongo Takeshi.
Today, you will be reborn
as Shocker's greatest servant.
That's odd...
Damn you...
I was only playing
possum to find your base.
Ambassador Hell...
Your plans won't succeed,
as long as I'm alive!
Catch him, quickly!
Rider Transformation!
Seadragon II... show him your power!
Damn you, Rider!
Seadragon III, show yourself!
What?
Seadragon III is here, too?
Get him!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider... die!
Rider Kick!
Rider!
Taki!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider... I will burn you to a crisp!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
What now, Rider?
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Mr. Taki!
Rider!
It's dangerous. Get out of here!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Damn you, Rider...
Go! Go! Let's go!
Where have you gone?
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Punch!
Rider!
Look out! Get down!
He did it!
Rider!
I finished off all three Seadragons...
Hey!
Mr. Taki!
Everybody safe here?
All three Seadragons are gone now.
Good.
But how did you know I was here?
I owe that to the boys here.
By the way, how many of the
Seadragons did you beat, Mr. Taki?
Well, see...
Rider didn't beat all three
himself, did he?
What?
Where did Rider go anyway?
He was just there...
The Kamen Rider beat all three
Seadragons that Shocker was so proud of.
But Shocker was already
creating its next terrible cyborg!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Its long red tongue snakes out creepily.
Rider's body burns in red.
Wretched Rider...
The flaming-hot tongue of
Imoriges will melt you into goo!
Stay tuned to this channel next week for "Showdown at Hell Ranch!"
The Monster Imoriges
Showdown at Hell Ranch!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!