KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Shocker high commander Doctor
Death formulates a plan
to erupt all the world's volcanoes
simultaneously at the dawn of the new year.
He plans to run his first
test in Kyushu, Japan.
On advice from the first Kamen
Rider, Hongo Takeshi, in Europe,
the second Kamen Rider, Ichimonji
Hayato, has headed for Kyushu.
Doctor Shinigami sent the
mighty Snowman after them,
but the Rider team of Takeshi and
Hayato put an end to Snowman for good.
But Shocker wasn't finished
with the volcanoes of Kyushu.
Magma Monster Ghoster
The Great Battle of Sakurajima
How'd it go?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
All right.
Let's search this area.
Right.
It's not enough.
I need bigger eruptions.
Call Ghoster!
The Shocker cyborg known as
Ghostar is a terrifying monster
that can move freely in temperatures
as high as 5000 degrees.
Shocker seeks to use this
heat-resistant monster
to control the flow of magma.
- Be careful.
- Right.
Let's go!
Hey... this earthquake
is really something.
Something really is going
on in this volcanic region.
Yeah.
Ghoster.
Have you completed the tunnel between
Sakurajima and the Ebino Highlands?
It's too hot in there.
The workmen can't take it.
If you're running out of
humans, just find some more.
This is the Earthquake
Monitoring Station.
There's a high chance of an
eruption in Sulfur Valley.
Attention, hotel residents.
This is the Earthquake
Monitoring Station.
There's a high chance of an
eruption in Sulfur Valley.
Hotel residents,
please board the bus at once.
This is an extremely
dangerous situation.
Please board the bus at once.
Hurry up!
This is the Earthquake
Monitoring Station.
There's a high chance of an
eruption in Sulfur Valley.
Wait please!
Please hurry!
Please board the bus at once!
Take us with you!
- Mom!
- Mr. Taki!
Mr. Taki!
Hey, stop this bus!
- Let us on!
- Mom!
Mr. Taki!
- Let us on!
- Mom!
Mom!
Darn it...
I bet they're with Shocker.
I know. I gotta let Hayato know.
You wait here, okay?
Please, let that child on board!
Shut up! We have no use for
children or the elderly!
Hey. What are you
planning to do with us!
Silence!
Are you Shocker errand boys?
I knew it...
Foolish humans.
From this day forth,
you serve the great Shocker!
Please, take me back to my son!
You monster... darn it!
I'll kill all who oppose me!
- I can't go on.
- Move.
This is too awful...
- Tatsuji...
- Hang in there, ma'am!
Just hang in there,
and I'm sure help will come.
Be quiet!
Increase our speed!
Take us to Shocker's
underground tunnel!
Mom!
Ow...
I wonder where Mom went...
What's the matter, son?
Got a stomachache?
A man shouldn't sulk like this.
They took my mom away.
Your mom?
Could you tell us just
what happened, son?
Hayato!
It's an emergency!
I wonder where he went off to...
Damn. It sounds like
something Shocker would do.
Wait, Hayato!
What is it?
I won't stop you,
but only one of us needs to pursue.
Understood.
Then how do we decide?
You or me?
You choose.
Now, now.
You're not going to get me with
a double-headed coin, are you?
Trust me.
All right. Heads!
Too bad.
I'll take the boy home.
Where should we meet up?
Let's say the overlook
on Sakurajima.
All right.
Come here, son.
I'll contact Taki and Pops
too, all right?
Right.
Good luck!
Ichimonji, nothing personal.
But both sides of
the coin were tails.
- Hurry up!
- Help me!
Get walking!
Hurry up!
Keep walking!
Stop lagging behind!
Hey... what have you
brought us here for?
You're going to dig us
a tunnel to Sakurajima.
- What?
- But...
Please, let me go home!
Shut up!
A suspicious figure
is approaching.
What?
Shocker must have a base nearby.
Hongo Takeshi...
He came all the way
from Switzerland...
Blow him away with
the land mines!
He's not here.
Find him!
I'm right here!
Over there!
The Kamen Rider!
Show me to your base, would you?
No! I'll never tell!
Speak!
Kamen Rider... die!
There you are, Armadillong!
Die, Kamen Rider!
Come back here!
Are you Shocker's
newest monster?
My name is Ghoster!
Kamen Rider... try me!
On my way!
Rider Kick!
Your Rider Kick
won't work on me!
Damn... that's hot!
Damn...
Behold my power to endure
up to 5000 degrees!
It's hot...
Not even my cyborg body would
last one minute down there.
Too hot for you, Kamen Rider?
Die, Kamen Rider!
Damn...
Damn!
KAMEN RIDER
Why don't you kill him?
I have a use for him.
The Kamen Rider was originally
a cyborg created by Shocker.
Yet he prattles on about justice,
peace, and love for his fellow man...
Such absolute nonsense.
Those made by Shocker
must serve Shocker.
Behold... the power of the mind
control device I've attached to him!
Now we can control
him subconsciously.
Then you mean to make the first
and second Kamen Riders...
Let traitor fight traitor.
Sakurajima
I wonder where
Hayato got off to...
What'd he even come
to Sakurajima for?
You're hopeless, Hayato...
Hey.
What is it?
Can I have a look?
There's another
telescope over there!
That one's out of order.
I'm looking for
someone important!
So am I! Don't hog it, okay?
You jerk! You'll pay for that!
Now you've done it!
It's your fault!
- Take this, you jerk!
- Come on!
Ow!
Say uncle, you jerk!
You stupid little...
Give up yet?
- You jerk!
- Dang it!
Hayato!
Well, if it isn't Goro.
What's all this fighting about?
What, you know him?
This is Goro.
Tatsuji here is looking
for his lost mother.
That's right! You were the kid who
was crying in front of the hotel!
Oh, I remember you!
Where are Pops and Taki?
They were taken by Shocker,
along with Tatsuji's mom!
What?
Yuri, too...
They were all taken away.
I see.
Maybe I could use this to
get in touch with Taki...
Ichimonji Hayato.
If you wish to save your allies,
come to the island's caldera.
The island's caldera?
I, Ichimonji Hayato,
accept Shocker's invitation!
Don't go, Hayato! It's a trap!
Goro.
There are times when, for the greater
justice, a man must walk into a trap.
You'll understand
when you're older.
Tatsuji,
I will save your mother.
You'd better, mister!
Both of you, wait here.
Okay!
Work! Hurry!
- Stop slacking off!
- Ow!
- Hurry up!
- Stop this!
- Get up!
- Don't touch her!
Damn it!
Stop it! Don't do it, Taki!
Just hang in there
until Hayato comes.
I've got you.
Don't give up hope!
Shocker! Death!
I've come, just as promised!
Hongo! You had me worried!
Hongo!
You both betrayed Shocker...
Now, let the traitor
kill the traitor!
I get it...
Shocker is controlling
your mind!
All right, then...
Transform!
Hongo, it's me!
Don't you recognize me?
Fight me!
Rider Kick!
Hongo... regain your senses!
Switch over your brainwaves!
Almost there...
Now it's down to you.
Get him!
Damn you...
Damn!
I guess that didn't go
the way you hoped...
Even thousands of kilometers
apart, we're linked by telepathy!
I used that to restore Hongo
back to his right mind.
Now, try us!
Die!
What's your plan now, Rider?
Die, Rider!
Talk!
Where did you take the
people you kidnapped?
Where are they?
They're all in the tunnel...
where they're about to die!
Rider Kick!
It's about to explode!
We did it!
Hongo, let's go save the people!
To the underground tunnel!
Help us!
Took you long enough, Rider!
Taki, get the people outside!
- What about you?
- I'm going to find Death!
Hurry, everyone!
Get out of here! Hurry!
- Hongo.
- Ichimonji?
Where's Death?
It looks like he's
abandoned this base.
Any luck in the tunnel?
They're all out safely.
All right, let's join them.
I'd like to speak to
Mr. Tachibana and Taki again...
But it would be harder
to leave Japan if I did.
I belong in Europe.
Remain well, all of you.
The other man who fights
evil, Hongo Takeshi.
You are...
You are the true hero!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Fly Man.
The capsules dispersed by the
fly-robots that Fly Man controls
makes the members of the Tachibana
Racing Club try to kill Ichimonji Hayato.
Kamen Rider is in peril!
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Demonic Assassin,
the Eerie Fly Man!"
The Demonic Assassin
the Eerie Fly Man
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!