KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Bird
Pranodon Attacks
Listen closely,
all you young ladies
Don't go falling
for a mountain man
If he gets lost in the mountains
You'll end up a young widow
I wish Hayato, Taki,
and Mika could have come with us...
Akira's father will be
back from America soon.
They'll be busy with that.
Akira.
Aren't you glad to get to see
your father again after a year?
Yeah, he said he'd
buy me a toy rocket!
That's nice.
Don't be like that.
You can't go around littering just
because we're out in the mountains.
What's the big deal?
What a hopeless kid...
Huh? What's a tunnel doing
in a place like this?
What could it lead to?
Let me go! Please!
Now, let us begin the surgery.
No! Let me go!
Good. Begin.
No! Don't do this!
No!
Begin!
Shocker implanted a receiver
capsule into Emi's ear.
Doctor Shinigami.
I can now control this girl
with the radio waves I emit.
Emi! Emi!
Emi!
She's not here.
I guess not...
I wonder where she
could have gone.
There she is!
Emi!
Where have you been, Emi?
We've been worried!
Have you?
We found her.
That's what matters.
Now, let's head home.
Yeah, let's go!
Now, the fun will begin...
A Shocker cyborg...
Come to me. Now!
Help me! Please, stop!
That's what you get
for refusing my orders.
Stop it!
Please, I'm going mad!
From this moment forward,
you will do as I tell you.
Do you understand?
Doctor Namikawa,
a world leader in rocketry,
was returning to Japan following
a two-year joint research project
in the United States.
Welcome Home!
Papa!
Taki, on orders from the FBI
in case something went wrong,
was assigned to guard
Doctor Namikawa in secret.
Hayato would also be there,
in his role as a photographer
to take pictures
of Doctor Namikawa.
Having a brilliant scholar
like Doctor Namikawa back in Japan
will prove detrimental
to our plans.
Turn on the TV!
Watch now, Ichimonji...
You will kill the
doctor yourself.
I've rigged Ichimonji's camera
to fire a miniature rocket
when he presses the shutter.
Akira!
Papa!
You...
An assassin!
You're under arrest!
He was caught in the act.
You can't talk him out of this.
I swear to you, he's innocent.
It's an emergency,
so I might as well tell you.
I'm actually...
You mean... you're FBI?
Doctor Shinigami.
Your assassination of Doctor Namikawa
appears to have failed.
A regrettable coincidence.
But Ichimonji cannot meddle
from within a jail cell.
Very well.
Take advantage of the situation
and move the plan forward.
Meanwhile,
at the Namikawa home...
Was he injured?
Light injuries to the left arm.
He was pretty calm about
the whole incident.
I see.
And I told them that
this morning's incident
was just a malfunctioning
flashbulb.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Taki.
Emi, is that you?
What are you doing here?
I need to speak with you.
Emi, what's this all about?
You've shown
yourselves, Shocker!
A monster!
Feel the force of my wind!
Taki!
Transform!
I've been expecting you, cyborg!
The Kamen Rider!
You won't escape!
Damn...
Damn!
KAMEN RIDER
Taki.
We've planted a receiver
capsule in your ear.
Now Pranodon will
control your every move.
Hayato... where have you been?
A policeman came by earlier.
- A policeman?
- Yes.
The truth is,
right after the police released you,
Taki went missing.
He made it sound like
you were a suspect.
Taki was kidnapped by Shocker.
Shocker?
- By Shocker?
- Of course...
They're the ones
behind all of it.
They must have swapped my
camera, too.
But why would they
be so circuitous?
Why not just attack
Doctor Namikawa directly?
They want to both kill him,
and frame me for the murder.
I see.
That does sound like Shocker.
Is that why Taki was taken, too?
Who's there?
It's me. Can I come in?
What's wrong?
My head hurts.
I see. Sorry to hear that.
Tobei and the
others are worried.
They says you've been acting
strange since you went hiking.
You went missing in the mountains
for an hour, didn't you?
Did something happen to
you during that time?
Is it possible...
you ran into some kind of winged creature?
I knew it!
You were under
Shocker's control!
You're the one who
swapped my camera.
Emi!
What's wrong, Emi?
Taki, I've heard you're the
FBI's greatest marksman.
To test it,
see if you can hit those targets.
But can you pull the trigger?
You cannot refuse me.
Do you see that now?
Now, stand! Stand up!
Point that rifle at the target
and fire!
Now the eye!
Our plan is now
all but complete.
Give this man his next
mission assignment.
Taki, this man will
be your next target.
Doctor Namikawa is heading for Mount
Ikuta.
You will set an ambush
for him on the way,
and kill him with that rifle.
Meanwhile, Doctor Namikawa and
Akira were leaving the city
on a drive to Mount Ikuta.
Doctor Namikawa's car is heading for
Ikuta Driveway across Route 246,
traveling at 60
kilometers per hour.
His car will reach the
sniping point in ten minutes.
Look at this.
There's something
strange in her ear.
Could you look a little deeper?
There it is.
This capsule was inserted right
next to her tympanic membrane.
It's a receiver.
A receiver?
An extremely delicate receiver.
But what in the world...
Taki, Doctor Namikawa has just
entered Ikuta Driveway.
He will reach the sniping
point in seven minutes.
Six minutes.
Doctor Namikawa's car.
Sniping point...
I see. No!
Doctor Namikawa has five
minutes left to live.
Transform!
Rider!
Taki!
You tried to exploit Taki, Shocker...
now you must pay!
Rider... witness my power!
Damn you, Pranodon!
Die, Rider!
What now, Rider?
Damn...
All right. Now!
Rider Kick!
Forgive me, Hayato.
I'm not entirely sure what
I was doing back there...
Same here! I don't know
how to apologize to you!
It's all right.
It's not your fault.
- It was this.
- Here.
This receiver.
I'm just glad Doctor Namikawa
is all right.
A young man sent
this for the child.
Who was it?
He didn't give his
name, I'm afraid.
Excuse me.
It's a toy!
It's a rocket!
"This is for Akira
from Ichimonji Hayato.
Kamen Rider."
Kamen Rider!
This is so cool! Really neat!
Thank you, Kamen Rider!
The Kamen Rider,
Ichimonji Hayato,
managed to protect Doctor Namikawa
from Shocker's evil scheme.
But what will they
send after him next?
Don't let them beat
you, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the graveyard
monster Kabibinga.
He seeks to use young twins to spread
Operation: Mold everywhere in Japan.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
Graveyard Monster Kabibinga
in "Graveyard Monster Kabibinga."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!