KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Shocker broke a violent criminal
on death row out of jail
and doused him in
poison mushroom extract
to create the monster
you see before you.
Kinokomorg is a formidable
cyborg who breathes out spores
that puts humans in a state
of suspended animation.
When our Kamen Rider confronted him to
bravely put a stop to Shocker's scheme,
he too was bathed in
the spores and captured.
Defeat Kinokomorg!
At last,
we'll be rid of the Kamen Rider.
Now, Kinokomorg!
Cut him in two!
Wait.
It won't be fun to
kill him like this.
We must restore his consciousness
so he'll experience the pain.
Rise and shine.
I'm about to slice
your body in two.
And I'll take my
time doing it...
We're looking forward to
hearing your screams of agony.
Now, turn it on!
Die, Ichimonji Hayato!
What are you doing?
Hayato, it's me!
Y-You're...
Thanks.
I owe you one!
Oh, please.
You'd do the same for me!
I'll be taking this.
Taki. We need to get out of
here, fast.
Okay. I'm in your hands!
The exit is that way.
Right!
Ow! What's going on here?
I see...
it's a special optical barrier.
Damn... we can see out,
but we can't pass through.
How did you get inside?
I was clinging to the
roof of their truck.
Damn... they're on the way!
You can't escape us now!
Damn...
there's nothing we can do!
Taki. This might hurt a
bit, but try to bear it.
Okay.
Speak to me!
You really are something, huh?
What's in this bottle?
It's what they injected
into you to wake you up.
I thought it might be
useful, so I snatched it.
I see...
I won't know until
I run some tests,
but it looks like the
chlorophyll from a plant.
What does that have
to do with mushrooms?
Nothing whatsoever.
Nothing?
Yes.
Mushrooms are a kind of plant, but they're
a lower species with no chlorophyll,
and can't assimilate
carbon dioxide.
They absorb nutrients from other
plants and animals instead.
That means...
What is it?
I want to try injecting this
into the paralyzed children.
It's too reckless.
We can't experiment on humans.
I know that.
But they have no hope of
recovery as things stand.
Please, take the chance!
What if you increase the dosage?
This is all I have left.
What will we do about
the other children?
We can't just use it all up.
Koike.
I want you to analyze that
substance and create more of it.
In large amounts!
What?
But...
We may yet see more
victims like them.
Please!
They seem to be feeling
a lot better, huh?
But Goro's still unconscious...
Haven't the boys
found a cure yet?
Hiroshi!
What's wrong, Hiroshi?
Speak to me, Hiroshi! Hiroshi!
Speak to me, Hiroshi!
What's wrong?
Kimiko! Kimiko!
Oh, no!
We need to call an ambulance!
Will she be all right, Doctor?
It doesn't look good...
their heart rates keep dropping.
Isn't there any
way to treat them?
Please... you have to save them!
We finally saved
them from Shocker...
Shocker?
He's not going to know
what you're talking about!
What should we do?
I just don't know...
Hiromi? What's wrong?
Hiromi!
What's the matter with you?
What's wrong?
Doctor!
She's acting strangely, too.
Oh no... it's contagious!
Call an ambulance!
Doctor! We can't call an
ambulance to a hospital!
But... still...
Can't breathe!
Someone help!
Help! Help us!
Help!
If I stay in that
hospital, I'll die...
C-Can't breathe...
The epidemic previously confined to the
Kanto Region is now spreading nationwide.
Those who come in contact with a carrier
will contract the disease within one hour.
The infected can be seen lying in the
streets with nobody to treat them.
All lines of transportation
will be closed in
order to prevent further
spread of the disease.
Hayato,
this is really getting serious...
Well? Nothing yet?
I'm almost there.
I need to cause two
more chemical changes,
then add chlorophyll
to the extract.
I see...
Well done.
Just leave it to me.
I really want to save those
children, too, after all.
It worked!
Really, Koike?
Thank you!
Great. This just might work...
Hayato,
I need your help as well.
All right!
Our experiment was a success, but Ichimonji
Hayato foiled our plans once again.
Go, Kinokomorg!
Destroy Ichimonji Hayato!
Destroy the Kamen Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
Hello.
Thanks for your patronage.
One of our clients sent
these flowers for you.
Why, thank you.
Here you are.
Please shop with us
again in the future.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Look! Aren't they beautiful?
Who could have sent them?
I think there's
something inside.
You're right.
To the Members of
the Racing Club
Ichimonji Hayato
Hey, they're from Hayato!
Hold on a minute.
What does it say?
"Congratulations on your
recovery, ladies.
I hope you see now that Shocker
is a force to be feared.
Why don't you lay off the tomboy antics
and start bridal training already?"
Oh, that nasty jerk!
He's absolutely right, though!
Don't be rude.
We're not that weak.
Right?
That's right.
We can beat Shocker easily.
Okay!
It's time for some payback!
Hey, now.
You girls just got
out of the hospital.
Why can't you be more
ladylike, like Hayato says?
I agree!
Hey.
Over here.
Okay.
Let's go!
Hey! Where are you going?
We're gonna eat
all of your cake!
What's wrong with those girls?
Darn it...
You don't think...
Hello?
Mr. Tachibana?
What?
Why, those tomboys...
They're hopeless.
I understand. I'm on my way.
What is Hayato off doing at
an important time like this?
Is that you, Hayato?
Why, you...
What a creepy place...
Yeah.
There must be a secret entrance
somewhere around here...
Let's start looking!
What is it?
What's that mushroom?
Don't do it!
It might be poisonous!
Right...
Go on, Hiromi!
Yuri!
Hurry!
Learned your lesson
yet, tomboys?
Not a chance!
You idiots... stay close to me.
This way!
Damn... we're trapped!
Kinokomorg was here...
You'll never interfere
with my plans ever again!
Damn...
Take them away!
Hayato will be here soon!
At last, we'll witness the
end of Ichimonji Hayato!
Damn.
I'm too late...
Ichimonji Hayato.
Your allies will soon be dead.
Look!
Hayato!
I'm sorry! They got us!
Damn...
You're a stubborn one!
Have you forgotten the power
that the Kamen Rider wields?
Get him!
Mari,
there's a knife on my belt.
Try to get it!
Okay.
Okay, hurry!
Mr. Taki!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
You're all better now.
Come on, look alive, now!
Get home quickly, everyone!
Thank you, Kamen Rider!
Rider!
Wait!
Wait! Rider!
Rider!
And there he goes...
I really wanted to thank him...
What a shame...
Ichimonji Hayato,
the Kamen Rider,
defeated Kinokomorg after
a long and difficult battle.
But this has only increased his
resolve to stand against the
powerful monsters that
Shocker continues to send.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Jigoku Thunder!
The monster Jigoku Thunder creates
antlion pits that gum up traffic,
which they plan to
use to conquer Japan.
Jigoku Thunder's
commander, Colonel Zol,
targets Kamen Rider by disguising
himself as Taki Kazuya.
Join us next week for more Kamen
Rider in "The Terrifying Antlion Pit."
The Terrifying Antlion Pit
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!