KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Cobra Man
Cobra Man.
Put those fangs into your mouth.
When Substance A,
integrated into those fangs,
combines with Substance
B from your ears
and is forced out by
the pump in your heart,
it will allowing you to
dissolve any substance at will.
Try it.
Spare me! Please, spare me!
This man is no longer
useful as a combatant.
He'll make a perfect
test subject.
Gentlemen.
We will use Cobra Man's powers to
acquire all of the world's gold.
We will start with the
Japanese gold repository,
then move onto
America, then England,
then the gold repositories of
every country in the world.
Go, Cobra Man!
To the Japanese gold repository!
Ministry of Finance
Gold Repository
It's me! It's just me!
That's odd...
Is something the matter, Kondo?
No, I'm fine.
It's time for a shift
change, Kondo.
Of course.
I'll leave it in your hands, then.
Good evening.
See you tomorrow!
Hey, there.
Nothing out of the
ordinary in front.
I'm going to take off early.
Of course.
Get home as fast as you can.
I'm sure your boy is lonely.
No, when he's with our dog,
he doesn't care what
his old man does.
See you.
Dummy?
Hey, there.
S-Someone... come help me!
Dummy! Where are you going?
I guess he needs to pee...
This gold will all
belong to Shocker...
Damn!
Gold Reserves Attacked Last Night!
No Gold Bars Taken!
Investigation Regarding
Death of Security Guard!
Shocker must be behind
this latest incident, too.
What could they be after?
If they're targeting gold
in various countries...
They must be trying to
take over the world.
If that's true...
It's very serious.
Oh, hello there.
Hello.
Ruri, if you would.
Hiromi, coffee please.
Okay.
Mr. Tachibana.
What is it? Are you going
to the gold reserve, too?
Yes.
I'll catch Shocker's
trail this time.
Here.
What?
What's this?
There's a charm of
protection in the locket.
It's a bell for the cat.
Because we never know
where you might run off to.
Who would have done this?
Who's there?
I know your dog
brought my fangs here.
Give them to me!
Fangs? I don't...
know what you're...
Don't give me that. Talk!
Please, don't...
Where is your dog?
My dog is dead!
And what did you do
with its corpse?!
Here Lies Dummy
Poor Dummy...
I hope you're in heaven
now, Dummy!
A monster!
Help!
Let me go!
All right...
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Return the child!
He's done nothing wrong!
We require the child.
Where is the child?
Shut up!
Die, Rider!
Oh no!
Kamen Rider's ears can hear sounds up
to four kilometers in all directions.
He could tell exactly which direction
the underground Cobra Man was moving.
All right, I've got it.
KAMEN RIDER
One kilometer west-southwest.
I'm almost there!
Let me go!
I want to go home!
Tell me where the fangs are!
I told you, I don't know!
I really don't know!
Did you see that?
Your body will burn just like
that when it touches that fluid.
Now,
tell me where the fangs are!
I told you, I don't know!
I really don't know!
It's the Kamen Rider!
The Kamen Rider is here!
What? The Kamen Rider?
Like a moth to a flame.
But I've planted mines
all around the grounds.
Return the child!
Shut up! Die!
Cobra Man! Return the child!
Get him!
I'm scared! Someone help me!
Not one step closer,
Kamen Rider...
Stay back, or the child dies!
Help me!
Does the child's life
mean nothing to you?
Surrender now, Kamen Rider!
Help! Someone help me!
Help!
Now,
surrender to me.
Hands up! Now!
That Takeshi really knows
how to worry a guy...
Which way is it, now?
There it is.
There's the cat's bell.
Meanwhile, the Kamen Rider had
fallen into Shocker's hands.
He'd been brought to Shocker's laboratory
to complete his Shocker brainwashing.
Kamen Rider...
Once the surgery is finished, you'll
become a cyborg acting at my beck and call.
And once that's done, there will
be no one left to stand against me.
I won't let you do it!
Takehiko!
Boss.
I ran the child through a lie detector, and
he really doesn't know where the fangs...
Silence!
It will take six more months
to create new fangs for you.
You will need to
wait until then!
But without those fangs...
I destroyed those fangs and
threw them in the ocean!
You'll never find them, either!
Damn you...
I'll kill you!
Takeshi!
Hurry!
Thank you, Mr. Tachibana!
Now escape, quickly!
Takeshi, hurry!
Now, let's go!
So cool!
Watch over him!
Cobra Man...
I can't let you go after this!
Silence!
Rider Kick!
There he is!
Hooray! Hooray!
Kamen Rider beat the
guy who killed Dummy!
Where's the Kamen Rider going?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Bye-bye, Kamen Rider!
See you again!
Here Lies Dummy
So Cobra Man's fangs were
here the whole time...
Come on, miss! Hurry!
Huh? I wonder who came
to visit Dummy's grave...
It must have been
the Kamen Rider.
Oh, right!
I wish I could see
the Kamen Rider again.
Where do I have
to go to see him?
Tell me, Mister!
Takehiko.
I'll bring the Kamen Rider
to meet you some day.
Okay...
but you'd better not be lying!
Why don't we go home?
But I wonder why Takeshi
didn't come with us.
Don't you worry.
I know exactly where Takeshi is.
How?
I put a transmitter into the
good luck charm you gave him.
Is that a receiver?
It's a bell for the
cat, after all.
Come on.
And so the Kamen Rider, Hongo
Takeshi, foiled Cobra Man's plans.
But his rage, hatred, and determination
to fight Shocker only grew stronger.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next monster sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the revived Cobra Man.
Having failed to steal
the gold reserves,
Shocker brings Cobra
Man back from the dead.
Kamen Rider fights to keep the
gold safe from Cobra Man's ambush.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Reborn Cobra Man"!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!