KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Electric Monster
Kuragedall
Washigaki
Lighthouse
Poochie! Poochie!
Hey, mister!
Looking for your dog, eh?
Yeah.
He ran that way.
Really? Thanks so much!
Poochie! Poochie!
Poochie?
I guess it wasn't him...
Poochie! Poochie!
Poochie!
Poochie?
Poochie! Poochie!
That hurt...
Say... is that an alien?
It is an alien!
An alien!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hey, don't pull so hard!
What do you expect?
Anyone would be scared
after seeing what I saw!
What's the big emergency, anyway?
I saw an alien!
Oh, please. That's stupid.
But it's true!
I thought you'd seen a
dead body or something.
I don't have time for this!
Come on! You gotta hurry!
I think you watch too many
Hollywood movies on TV.
Fine! I saw a dead body!
Don't you change your story now!
Just hurry already!
Hurry! Hurry!
It was right here!
But there's nothing here.
It was an alien with a big head.
It looked like a jellyfish!
It attacked the guy like this!
Stop that! It's a crime to
tease an officer of the law.
You adults never believe us kids.
Fine!
I really did see it, though...
It was an alien with a huge head.
You're a liar.
There's no such things as aliens.
You liar.
It's so silly.
Fine, I'll show you proof!
Kota's such a liar.
He's just lying!
Let's forget him and go play!
Yeah, let's go!
Damn it...
Damn it!
Nobody believes me!
What's all the fuss about?
None of your business!
You're acting very strangely.
Did you really fall off a cliff?
Did you hit your head? Are you okay?
Mom, where's Big Brother's camera?
Don't you dare.
He'll be furious with you!
Washigaki
Lighthouse
It's not here...
There's someone!
I knew it!
It's that monster!
Okay...
Hey, kid.
What are you doing?
Damn it!
Just the one we've been looking for.
Leave it there.
It's better that way.
You'll see soon enough...
Wait. Leave the child there, too.
My electric shock will
put him out for an hour.
Now, go!
Space-obsessed Kota
Kawamoto, ten years old,
saw a jellyfish-like alien
near Washigasaki Lighthouse.
"Experts agree that it's an extremely
well done trick photograph."
I see... a jellyfish alien, eh?
Still, that's a pretty convincing fake
photo that ten-year-old kid made.
"It's true that several
villagers have gone missing,
but family circumstances are
believed to be the cause."
I see...
You think it might be Shocker?
Don't be silly!
Honestly, children these days.
Why do you guys always have to pick on me?
No...
I think Goro might be right.
You mean...
It's a Shocker monster?
I'd like to speak to that boy.
Told you!
Goro.
Hayato, good luck.
You want to see our Kota?
I want to ask him about
this morning's article.
I'm so sorry, it's really
quite embarrassing...
I understand.
But I was hoping to
speak to him directly...
He came home yesterday in sort of a daze.
He's with a guest right
now, as a matter of fact.
Another visitor?
Yes, that's right.
Taki?
Oh, it's you...
You know each other?
Yes.
Hey.
This is...
They look just like Shocker combatants.
Really, Kota.
It's not nice to lie, you know.
But it's true!
Kota, would you show us to the place?
You mean it?
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go!
Can I get you something to drink?
We have to be going.
Hey, mister! They're here!
Looks like Shocker's shown themselves...
Taki, look after Kota.
Right!
Ichimonji Hayato will make you pay!
You've shown yourself, Shocker Cyborg!
Ichimonji Hayato...
Die!
Transform!
Kamen Rider!
At last, you will die!
You electric jellyfish monster!
You're the one who'll die!
It's the Kamen Rider!
Don't move!
I am Kuragedall!
And now, I will kill you!
The Kamen Rider's body can withstand
50,000 volts of electricity!
Rider!
Kamen Rider... we shall meet again!
Thank you, Rider!
KAMEN RIDER
Hey, it's Hayato!
Hey.
I got separated in all the trouble.
If Kamen Rider hasn't shown
up, we might have died.
Washigaki
Lighthouse
Meanwhile, in Shocker's base
beneath Washigasaki Lighthouse...
We'll find humans who can
withstand 5,000 volts
and turn them into electro-people.
Do it!
2,000 volts.
3,000 volts.
5,000 volts!
He fails!
Dispose of him!
Next!
Those who pass will be given
massive electric charges,
so that all who touch them will die.
We'll use these electro-people to
kill Japan's political leaders!
And in time, we will kill all of humanity!
Bring me the woman!
Proceed!
No! Please, spare me!
Now we can lure out the
Kamen Rider and finish him.
Then no one can stand in our way.
The Kamen Rider is nothing!
I'll dig out his heart myself!
Don't cry, Kota!
It's just awful.
Even Kota's mother was taken...
That's right. It's unforgivable!
I wonder why they took his mother...
To lure out Hayato, maybe?
Several people in that village
have already gone missing.
They're holding Kota's mother
at Washigasaki Lighthouse...
To take a child's mother...
It's unforgivable!
It seems totally abandoned...
Strange.
No one here!
When Rider moves to save
her, trigger the dynamite!
Rider hasn't appeared yet.
What should we do?
Knowing them, they must have
some trick up their sleeve...
That fool Rider's run away!
Do it the second he gets
close to the woman!
He's FBI scum. Just as good.
Do it!
All right... no matter the
danger, I have to save her.
That's my mission!
All right...
Get down!
Run away, quickly!
Right!
This way!
Hurry!
Rider!
Rider Kick!
Stand back.
Help us! Please!
Get out of there, now!
Run to safety!
All right...
Mom!
Mr. Taki!
Kota!
Goro!
Mom!
Mr. Taki!
Kota, isn't that nice?
But where's Hayato?
Hey, Hayato!
Hey,
sorry I'm late.
Where have you been?
What were you off doing?
Come on, let's go!
Sure!
Come on.
Wretched Kamen Rider...
next time we meet, I will kill you.
I will kill you!
The persistent Colonel Zol
will attack Japan again.
And evil organization Shocker will
continue to create new cyborgs
in their efforts to conquer the world
and disrupt our peace once more.
Keep fighting, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is a blood-sucking trilobite.
Shocker, in its quest to conquer the world,
threatens the world-renowned
trilobite scholar Doctor Shimura
into creating blood-sucking trilobites,
which they intend to send
all around the world.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
Reborn Fossil:
The Blood-Sucking Trilobite!
in "Reborn Fossil: The
Blood-Sucking Trilobite!"
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!