KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Jaguar Man's
Deadly Motorbike Battle
Huh?
He's been standing there
for two hours now...
Excuse me, sir.
It's closing time,
so if you don't mind...
Leave me alone.
Please, sir...
He and I aren't
finished speaking yet.
He? You mean the tiger?
Don't be absurd.
Really, you have to go...
Emergency!
Where's that phone...
Dial 119...
No, it's 110...
What's the matter with you?
I saw it...
a monster, like a jaguar man!
What's so funny?
It's true.
You have to believe me!
I believe you. I saw it, too.
Where? When?
Every day, in the mirror.
This is what he looked
like, right?
That's... that's him!
Someone come!
Your partner is
asleep under the desk.
Murderer!
Have patience.
You'll get to run
wild soon enough!
The terrible Shocker created a
man-jaguar hybrid called Jaguar Man.
How would Shocker use Jaguar Man to
forward their plans for world domination?
Meanwhile,
at Tachibana Motocross...
Hongo Takeshi is also known
as the first Kamen Rider.
While the second Kamen
Rider, Ichimonji Hayato,
is off fighting Shocker
in South America,
Hongo Takeshi is in
Japan, filling in.
It is a long-awaited return.
What's my time, Pops?
45 seconds.
I thought you might have lost it after
so long in Europe with no practice.
I spent my free time polishing my
skills against Europe's best racers.
That's what I like about you.
Well,
have we had enough for the day?
I'm going to make one more lap.
I can shave three more seconds
off, I think.
Don't work yourself so hard.
That Takeshi...
But having him back in Japan gives
me the chance to dream again.
To win a World
Grand Prix race...
I don't want to be the old man
who runs the Racing Club forever.
Pops...
Winning the grand
prix is my dream!
But first, I need to wipe the evil
organization Shocker off of the map!
Foolish Hongo Takeshi!
It is you who will be
wiped from the map!
Show yourself, Shocker!
Are you a Shocker
cyborg as well?
Indeed I am!
I am Jaguar Man,
master of all animals on Earth!
Jaguar Man... what's the
mission that Shocker gave you?
To destroy Kamen
Rider, of course!
Get him!
Shave three more seconds off?
Please!
He's already two minutes over...
Strange...
You don't think...
it couldn't be!
Hey, Taki!
You're looking pretty
green in the gills, Pops...
Where's Hongo?
You're asking me?
He was due back already!
What did you say?
I hope he wasn't
in an accident...
I'll go check.
Please do!
Get him!
Rider Transformation!
Kicking off the ground
with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning
with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Get him!
Withdraw!
Calling up tornadoes
with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider! It was Shocker, then?
Taki,
we need to keep after them.
Right. I'll go this way.
Right!
Damn.
I was right on their heels...
Where did they get off to?
Calm down, Taki.
Oh, it's you?
You got thrown off the trail
and ended up here, too?
You mean, you did, too?
Wait a minute.
If we split up to
go after Shocker,
and I ran into you
when I lost them...
That means...
Shocker's base must
be in this area!
Watch closely.
The driving technique
of Hongo Takeshi,
and the driving technique
of the Kamen Rider.
You must study Kamen Rider's
technique very carefully.
Ambassador Hell.
I'm counting on you
to get things done.
Great Leader.
I, Ambassador Hell, have wreaked
havoc all across Southeast Asia.
Since you chose me to
come here to Japan,
I shall defeat the Kamen
Rider without fail.
Your current plan is
Operation: Animal Panic...
You must not allow the Kamen
Rider to learn its secret.
I am aware, my leader.
This is why I have sent my killer
rider team after the Kamen Rider
to hold his attention.
Change the video feed.
Hongo!
Anything?
No sign of anything
like a Shocker base.
Time to settle in for the long
haul, I guess.
Lure them to the base,
then spring into action.
Jaguar Man!
Initiate Operation:
Animal Panic.
Recently, a number of city
pet owners have been injured
when their dogs and cats
abruptly lashed out.
We ask owners of cats and dogs to
be on the lookout for such behavior.
And we've just gotten
a new story in.
Zoo animals are
abruptly lashing out,
as if they've become
wild animals again.
Riot police have been
dispatched to zoos as a result.
If you live near such a location,
keep your doors tightly locked,
and pay attention to your TV
or radio for more information.
Hear me, animals!
Hear the orders of Jaguar Man!
Let your wild blood race,
and devour all the
humans you find!
KAMEN RIDER
This is no fun...
I can't believe they
told us to leave,
just because a lion
or tiger might escape!
I'm hungry. Let's get going.
Oh, wow!
Just because a few dogs and
cats are running wild...
But I think we're
probably fine here!
Oh, please!
You act all tough, but you're always
the first to turn tail and run.
Yeah, let's get going.
That way!
Okay, let's go!
I'm gonna call Takeshi!
We don't have time!
Another one! Let's go!
Help me!
What's wrong with you?
I saw it... a monster!
A monster?
It had a face like a jaguar.
You think a jaguar
from the zoo got loose?
- Where was it?
- Over there.
Let's check it out.
Right.
I hear growling...
That's just your imagination!
I'll take care of all of you!
Darn it... you monster!
Take them away,
and feed them to the animals!
Hold it, Shocker!
Stop it!
Takeshi!
Hongo...
trying to interfere again, eh?
Get him!
Run!
Hongo... it's not safe alone.
I'll be fine.
Watch Goro and the others.
Strange...
there must be something here.
That's right, Hongo Takeshi!
Is that you, Shocker?
Show yourself!
All the way from Southeast Asia.
Remember my name...
Ambassador Hell!
Ambassador Hell?
That's right.
I'm one of Shocker's high commanders,
on equal footing with Doctor Shinigami.
Sorry to disappoint, but you won't
have your way while I'm here!
Hongo Takeshi...
You really think you
can stop Shocker?
What?
Are you so eager to get
your friends killed?
You mean...
Taki, Goro, and the girls...
It's far too late.
Ambassador Hell!
Was Ambassador Hell
telling the truth, then?
Hongo...
resist, and all your friends die!
All right...
take me where you will, then.
Behold!
Takeshi!
Taki! Goro!
Listen.
I am Jaguar Man,
master of all animals.
On my command, that lion will
eat the humans in that cage.
I see, Jaguar Man...
You're going to make the world's
animals do Shocker's bidding?
Hongo. Don't worry about me.
Crush Shocker's plans!
I've made my peace.
Let the lion eat
me if you have to!
I'm right here,
but I can't save them...
Hongo. What's stopping you?
Take Hongo away!
Put him to death at once!
Hongo...
don't bother struggling.
I don't intend to.
But will you really release
the people in that cage?
Taki... have a good life.
Hongo!
Taki, please escape, quickly!
Now, burn him to a crisp!
A little more to the left.
To the left!
A little more forward...
Ow! Hot!
Hold off a little longer, okay?
We're almost out!
Burn him to death!
Taki, what are you doing?
Haven't you escaped yet?
How do you like it, Hongo?
Is it hot up there?
Suffer!
Hongo!
Taki!
Shocker...
I don't need to hold back now!
You coward!
Rider Transformation!
Fight me, Jaguar Man!
Taki!
Rider Head Crusher!
Rise, beasts!
Give in to your rage...
and come save Jaguar Man!
Wow, so cool!
Look at that!
Yeah, really!
Shocker's Operation: Animal
Panic has failed, I see.
We won't let Shocker
disrupt our peaceful world.
Rise, beasts!
I am Jaguar Man!
I am your master!
You've got it all wrong!
I-It's all a misunderstanding.
Don't roar at me!
Goro,
I think he might remember you.
You're popular.
Not bad.
Aw, who wants to be
popular among lions?
Shocker's plot has been foiled,
and peace has returned to the zoo.
But when would Hongo Takeshi,
the Kamen Rider, find peace once more?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Sea Snake Man.
The powerful light
emitted by Sea Snake Man
can change the scenery
around him on command.
It throws people
into mass confusion.
Join us next week for "The
Sea Snake Man of the Ghost Village!"
The Sea Snake Man of
the Ghost Village
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!