KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
How did you get in here?!
Fusion of cat and gecko, Catgecko.
For Operation: F to succeed,
you must first lure out Hongo Takeshi.
Eerie
The Bloodthirsty
Black Cat Paintings!
Is Big Brother still working?
Everything's fine in the day.
But when night falls...
So that's why you came
to ask for our help, huh?
Yeah.
The point is, he's acting really weird.
Okay, we get it.
We'll come by and stand watch.
Sure!
The black cat paintings, painted
with the blood of devils...
You can use your self-replicating
cells to travel freely between them.
Go!
Big Brother! Big Brother!
- Monster!
- My name is Catgecko.
Hongo will have heard of the
locked-room murders by now.
Catgecko!
Hongo Takeshi is your next target!
Hey, Hongo.
Good morning.
Good morning!
What's wrong, everyone?
Naoki, why don't you tell
Mr. Hongo the whole story again?
Okay.
What's going on?
Satoru's big brother...
His big brother, see?
He was acting weird,
then suddenly he collapsed.
He was mixing his blood in with paint to
paint all these weird black cat pictures.
How awful...
Yeah...
Hey, Pops. Where's Taki?
We haven't seen him in three
days, actually.
Hey. A minute.
What is it, Pops?
You're the only one I can tell this to,
but Taki's on orders from the FBI.
From the FBI?
Yes.
Today at four o'clock at Nishiatami Hotel
they're going to hold a peace conference with
famous scientists from all over the world.
I see.
So Taki's running security...
Yeah.
It's no exaggeration to say
that world peace lies in the
hands of the scientists.
If Gel Shocker attacks them,
awful things could result.
And now for the news.
An investigation on the mysterious serial murders
that occurred last night has hit a wall.
The lead investigator, who will hold a
press conference at three o'clock today...
What is this picture...
A cat?
A Gel Shocker cyborg!
My name is Catgecko!
Die, Hongo!
Catgecko!
Are you the one behind
the locked room murders?
Of course!
What are you after?
Isn't it obvious?
We mean to kill our enemies...
Hongo Takeshi, and the entire Rider Corps!
I see...
Catgecko can travel through
those paintings at will.
He was mixing his blood in with paint to
paint all these weird black cat pictures.
Satoru's brother?
Who's there?
Hongo Takeshi.
Why have you come?
You're working for Gel Shocker.
Take me to Catgecko's hideout!
The one you seek...
is right before your eyes!
What?
Don't tell me, you...
That's right.
I am Catgecko!
Rider Transformation!
Cat Fire!
Kamen Rider... we'll
finish this another time!
But the next time we
meet, I will kill you all
by slipping through a black cat painting!
KAMEN RIDER
This is the security layout for the day.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Conference Room
Hey.
What's that?
It just seemed awfully plain in here...
Let me see.
I don't see any time bombs...
Nothing else out of the ordinary.
Here.
Thank you.
Preparations are complete.
It's time to execute Operation: F.
In other words, our plan to kidnap
the world's greatest scientists.
Ready, Catgecko?
Leave everything to me, General Black.
I will now attack the
Rider Corps headquarters!
The Kamen Rider, Hongo Takeshi,
is sure to appear then!
Then, in accordance with
your orders, General Black,
I will travel to the
conference room's painting.
It will take two minutes!
Rider travels fast,
but it will still take him twenty minutes
to reach a location eighty kilometers away.
In the meantime, you'll be
able to kidnap the scientists.
Go!
So that Japan...
no, all of Asia can be ours!
Go on in.
Doctor! Everyone's here.
I see. Thank you very much.
Certainly.
Hello? Kamen Rider Kid Corps headquarters.
Yes?
Chairman, phone call from Mr. Hongo!
Hey, Hongo? What's up?
Pops.
Did someone send you a painting?
Yes, they did.
It's an interesting painting.
What are you talking about? Destroy it!
The black cat in that painting is alive!
A monster will leap out of it!
What are you talking about, Takeshi?
There's no black cat in the painting!
What did you say?
Fine... just stay where you are.
I'll be there right away.
What's he talking about, a black cat?
See, Mr. Hongo?
There's no black cat here.
That's strange...
Rider Corps... I'll kill you all!
Nonsense.
You won't have your way while I am here!
- Hurry!
- Pops, take Yuri and the others to safety!
I hope, with confidence,
it'll be important.
Thank you.
General Black, preparations are complete.
We can be combat-ready at any moment.
Good.
All preparations are in place.
Catgecko... now!
Hongo!
Hey...
Mr. Hongo...
Are you all right?
Why did it disappear?
That was close...
I believe our inventions are best
when used in the interests of peace.
One minute left.
Pops...
What's the matter?
The peace conference Taki
is doing security for...
It should be in progress as we speak.
That's what they're after!
What?
That's why they wanted to draw me here!
But, Nishiatami Hotel is
80 kilometers from Tokyo!
Catgecko can travel between cat paintings,
even if they're a hundred kilometers away!
Taki! Taki!
It's Hongo! Respond!
Taki!
Taki here.
This is Hongo. Listen closely.
Is there a picture of a
black cat in that room?
Yes, there is.
There is?
You have to destroy it!
The black cat works for Gel Shocker!
What did you say?
Hurry! Hurry!
All right!
Everyone, please remain calm...
Hongo! A Gel Shocker monster!
Oh no!
Hold it!
Rider!
Rider! How did you get here?
I'm always getting stronger, Catgecko!
What did you say?!
Let's go!
Taki!
Save the scientists!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
Got it!
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider Throw!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
Die!
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Rider Punch!
Calling up tornadoes with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Cut!
I'll finish you!
Oh, oh Rider!
Rider Chop!
Kamen Rider!
You fool! I have another weapon!
My Gecko Sucker Feet!
Rider... I will suck
out all of your energy!
Swimming through the
oceans with a Rider Swim,
a great dive flitting through the sea!
Calling up whirlpools with a Rider Screw!
Dragging enemies down with a Rider Lung!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider Kick!
Rider!
What a fearsome plan...
Is that...
That's the boys' friend's brother.
It should cheer Satoru up
to see him back to normal.
Gel Shocker's ambitions were
foiled by Kamen Rider.
But Gel Shocker wouldn't
be easily dissuaded.
Fight on, Kamen Rider,
in the name of justice and peace!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
General Black.
The first phase of Operation: Pet involves
using Canarycobra's venom to
make the people of Tokyo go mad.
Go, Geldam!
Fill the Earth with death!
Gentlemen, let's meet again for
"The Terrifying Operation:
Pet - Send Rider to Hell!"
The Terrifying Operation: Pet
Send Rider to Hell!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!