KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
In their quest for
world domination,
Shocker created a new
cyborg, Dokugander,
but the Kamen Rider defeated
it in valiant combat.
But then, Dokugander sealed
itself inside a giant cocoon,
and disappeared without a trace.
Shocker had already disposed of Professor
Koizumi, who had learned their secret.
Dokugander
Battle at Osaka Castle!
Hanshin University of Science
Mr. Yoshioka.
Did you really find a man-sized
caterpillar at the base of Mount Fuji?
Unbelievable...
Is it true? Do you have proof?
You must have pictures, right?
Let us see them.
Hurry up, would you?
We're on a deadline, here!
Hang on, now.
I'll bring them soon.
Please do!
They're gone...
The pictures I left
on my desk are gone...
Yoshioka.
Professor...
You survived?
I got lost on the way back
and couldn't get in touch.
I'm so glad...
I felt sure that you were dead!
Please! Bring us those pictures!
I'll speak to them.
Excuse us...
Gentlemen. Yoshioka here
said he saw a man-sized
caterpillar near the base of Mount
Fuji, but he was mistaken.
What?
But he just said
he had pictures!
It's a publicity stunt. He's just
trying to get his name into the papers.
Sir, please!
I really did see it!
You be quiet.
Big news!
It turns out Professor
Koizumi is alive!
What's this?
"Assistant Professor Yoshioka
Driven From Hanshin University."
"The groundless rumors about a giant
caterpillar was a publicity stunt
to get his name out
in the newspapers."
That's strange.
We saw the caterpillar
ourselves.
That's right.
You think that Professor
Koizumi is an impostor?
Professor Yoshioka is in danger.
I'm going to Osaka!
What is this?
A drug I've been researching.
It's a growth serum that accelerates
the development of cocoons.
A growth serum?
What do you think?
It's quite impressive...
Would you mind coming by my
laboratory to investigate further?
I have a secret laboratory.
You'll help me, won't you?
Of course.
Isn't that...
I have returned to life...
and this time, I'll kill you!
Hayato!
Taki!
Look out!
I was just feeling
you out this time...
We'll meet again!
Damn!
Taki, what brings you here?
Orders from FBI headquarters.
They think Shocker's
planning something in Osaka.
Okay, let's go.
Just 45 kilometers left!
Mr. Yoshioka!
What's that?
Shocker...
It's too late, Ichimonji Hayato.
Yoshioka is already
in our custody.
What?
Damn...
Is that why you tried
to delay our arrival?
Precisely.
There is nothing that
Shocker cannot do!
You do research in
a place like this?
Professor...
Go on.
Professor! What are you doing?
Open this door!
Professor!
What is the meaning of this?
Please, let me out!
Thank you so much for coming.
I will now explain the
work I'll have you doing.
I've never seen
such big cocoons...
Surprised, are you?
Each contains a new
cyborg created by Shocker.
But it will take several
months for them to develop.
We require these cyborgs
as soon as possible.
What do you want
me to do about it?
Use that cocoon growth
serum you invented
to make them fully-grown
Dokuganders as quickly as possible.
No.
Never!
You think you have a choice?
Professor Yoshioka...
look carefully!
Miki...
We can kidnap your daughter
any time we choose.
Just think it over carefully.
Yoshioka
We're terribly
sorry to bother you.
We're the paper goods exchange.
We'll trade old newspapers and
magazines for toilet paper.
I can't believe this is
Hayato's "big job" for us...
Yeah. Paper exchange in Osaka...
This is no job for a young girl.
I should have stayed home
like Michi and Hiromi.
But do you really think
Shocker will be after Miki?
Of course they will!
Taking Miki hostage is the best way
to threaten Mr. Yoshioka, right?
Look. A suspicious vehicle!
Too bad. It's a woman!
Miki.
Your father was in an accident.
He's been taken to the hospital.
Come along now.
You can't fool me!
Child... you tricked us!
Stupid! You can't fool me!
Stupid rotten lousy jerk!
You're amazing, Goro!
You bet I am!
Not like you guys at all!
Spare me the ego trip!
The plan worked!
Now let's take him to Hayato!
Where is your base?
I'll never tell!
Where is Mr. Yoshioka?
You want another karate chop?
Enough with the feminism.
Miki needs your attention first.
We'll play with you, dear.
Don't worry,
I'll save your papa.
Butt out!
Us kids are in this together.
Right, Miki?
I hate boys.
Burned...
Quiet down, all of you.
I'll look after her.
Taki.
Stop selling out your
friends for points.
Now, tell me!
Where is Mr. Yoshioka?
Oh no!
Damn...
Quick, take care of Miki!
Wow! That's some monster!
You monster! Come down here!
You cannot escape me any longer!
Wait!
Hayato!
There you are...
Transform!
This isn't over!
Taki, are you all right?
I'm fine. But we should check on
the others back in the apartment!
KAMEN RIDER
It's not working!
I can't find my dad!
It's just like I told you!
Osaka is big!
You'll never find your father
with some little kid's telescope.
You're mean.
This is why I hate boys.
You're no fun!
I'm taking the picture.
Look this way.
That's good, everyone.
There.
Take care on your way home.
Okay, see you.
Excuse me, Mr. Photographer.
Have you seen a girl
with a red ribbon
and a very snotty-looking
little boy nearby?
I have not.
I wonder where Goro and
Miki could have gone.
I certainly hope Shocker
didn't get them...
Shocker is more likely
to get the two of you.
Sir, do you know about Shocker?
I certainly do.
Hey, it's the Chairman!
I got so worried,
I came rushing right from Tokyo!
Ye of little faith, huh?
Well? Pretty good way to
keep tabs on Shocker, right?
I know. How about a picture
to remember this by?
Monster!
This place belongs to Shocker!
How dare you!
Don't start crying!
You'll make me cry, too!
Spare the women and
children, please!
What kind of coward
would torture a child?!
Shut up.
You will all die.
Dad! Save me!
Is this really how I die?
Ready?
Kamen Rider!
Okay!
Rider!
Boss...
Yoshioka has completed
the cocoon growth serum.
All right. Pull out!
Get a move on already!
So there was an entrance
here, eh?
This is the growth serum, then?
Well done...
Get to work at once!
Mr. Yoshioka, don't do it!
Who are you?!
Something terrible will
happen if you do. Stop!
We'll kill him off later.
Take him away!
Don't do it, Mr. Yoshioka!
We can't afford
further interruptions.
Do it at once.
What is the meaning of this?!
It's a chemical formula
for dissolving cocoons.
You won't be making
any more cyborgs now!
Stay quiet.
It's some kind of signal...
They must have Taki in
an underground cell.
It's coming from that way.
"I'll save you soon. Rider."
I knew he'd come!
Rider!
Taki! I'm glad you're safe!
Hey, are you okay?
Pops!
Rider!
Dokugander...
It's finally time to end you!
Professor!
Is my daughter all right?
Don't worry.
We have her somewhere safe!
Now, hurry!
Rider!
Rider Fight!
Rider Kick!
You can't outrun me!
Wait up, Goro!
Come visit me in Tokyo some
time, okay, Miki?
You can come back to
Osaka some time too, Goro.
Sure!
What, not us?
Us kids are in it together.
Adults can butt out.
You heard her.
Well, bye-bye! Let's go!
See you, Miki!
See you. Take care, okay?
Okay!
Why won't Hayato and Taki be
taking the plane back to Tokyo?
Apparently, they don't trust something
made out of steel to really fly.
Motorbikes are
more their speed.
I'm glad to be leaving
those wild women behind.
Now,
let's take a drive to Tokyo.
Yes!
The battle was over,
but with Shocker still
aiming for world domination,
they would surely send more
cyborgs to Japan in the future.
In that moment, Ichimonji Hayato
renewed his pledge to fight Shocker.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous
merman, Amazonia.
The terrifying fish-man Amazonia
seeks uranium on the ocean floor.
Kamen Rider will fight a steaming
midsummer battle near the sea.
Prepare for thrills, suspense,
and underwater action!
Join us next week for
"Monstrous Merman Amazonia."
Monstrous Merman Amazonia
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!