KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Poison Flower Bararanga
Secret of the Terror House
Having received word from
a member of the Rider Kid Corps
that Shocker combatants were
spotted in a Tokyo suburb,
Taki Kazuya was racing to the scene.
Wretched Taki.
He doesn't realize that we intentionally
let the Rider Kid Corps see us
in order to lure him out.
Let's see what he gets...
What's that?
A Shocker cyborg!
This smell...
Now, take him away!
A Shocker monster!
We need to let them know!
Koichi, the pigeon!
Good luck!
It disappeared!
Darn it...
I hope my pigeon makes
it back to HQ safely...
Kamen Rider Kid Corps Headquarters
Hey, we have a pigeon in.
I'm on my way.
Isn't that Koichi's pigeon?
But there's no message attached...
What is this?
I found this in its wing.
What's this?
Smells nice...
Chairman!
Chairman! Are you all right?
Chairman! Speak to me!
Mr. Hongo...
What's the matter?
It's the Chairman!
Pops! Pops!
He collapsed after smelling the thorn
I found in the messenger pigeon's wing.
Thorn?
A thorn from a rose...
Awakened, have you?
How are you feeling?
Where am I?
The Rose Estate.
Rose Estate?
You were collapsed in the road.
I brought you here to let you rest.
I appreciate it.
I'm sorry about all the trouble...
You mustn't force yourself.
You must rest.
But... I need to get back.
My comrades will worry.
But, we were just getting
to know each other...
You're leaving already?
I'll come back again to
give a more proper thanks.
Well, then...
Could you take this
rose, to remember me by?
Certainly.
It's a lovely rose.
I am very proud of my roses.
This smell...
No, it's a very fine smell.
Strange.
The smell of that rose,
the way she was acting...
When did you...
It's very rude of you to enter
my room without permission.
This is yours?
You aren't shown reflected in that mirror.
You caught on, did you...
Taki Kazuya?!
Excellent work, Bararanga.
I see...
Yes...
Don't kill him.
We'll use him against Hongo and his allies!
Be on your guard!
Someone's found us and
they're on their way.
Go!
The smell of these roses...
So you've shown yourself, monster!
Get him!
Rider Transformation!
Rider! Come down here!
KAMEN RIDER
I knew it. It's a powerful tranquilizer...
When it enters the human
body, it addles the mind.
Damned Shocker...
Oh, Chairman. You're feeling better?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Boy, that was something...
He said there was a powerful
poison in that thorn.
What? Poison?
I'll make some tea.
Sure.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Oh, Naoki?
Yeah. Yeah.
Nothing out of the ordinary for now? Okay.
If you find anything, contact us at once.
Okay! We will!
I'm a little worried about Taki.
I'm going to visit Hongo.
Right.
A monster!
Oh, Choco.
I can't believe you're eating
while Mr. Taki's missing!
Yeah!
Are you ever not working
that mouth of yours?
Leave me alone!
I'm really beside myself
with worry right now!
What's with you guys?
You're looking kind of pale...
What's wrong with you?
- Yeah...
- You're acting so weird...
Hey, what are you doing?
Naoki and the others...
What happened to their hands?
Look out, Pops...
Clear the way, everyone!
What's going on here?
Bararanga must have gotten to them.
Take them into the back.
Right!
Hongo.
Taki!
You made it back safe?
Yes.
What happened to you?
We've been worried...
Taki!
They got to you, too?
Remove the boys' roses, too.
Right.
This is it.
This is what did it.
I see...
I don't remember anything after
she attacked me in the Rose Estate.
The poison in those roses addled
the minds of you and the boys.
Damn you, Shocker...
Okay, I'm going back to the Rose Estate.
Hey, wait a minute!
Chairman, they used me
to attack you guys.
I can't let this stand.
I get how you feel,
but you need to calm down!
Besides... she doesn't
know I've recovered.
I can pretend to still
be under her control,
and infiltrate Shocker's base.
Taki.
Is there nothing I can say to stop you?
No.
All right. Just a minute, then.
This is an antidote I
designed for the rose poison.
Inject it and the roses' smell
won't affect you.
Sounds good. Give it to me.
But it only helps with the smell.
You won't survive a prick from the thorns.
I get it. Go ahead.
All right.
Inject us, too!
What, were you listening in?
We have our own pride.
We want to help Mr. Taki, and restore
the honor of the Rider Kid Corps!
All right, I get it.
Taki, just don't forget to
contact me if things go south.
Right.
Okay. If I'm not back in thirty
minutes, contact Headquarters.
Right.
So, you've returned.
Did you dispose of Hongo and the others?
Yes.
Thank you. You've done well.
You're truly one of us now.
Come with me.
Ambassador Hell, the plan was a success.
Taki is now one of us.
I see.
That's truly worth celebrating.
All right.
You are henceforth a member of Shocker.
Come right this way.
Wait!
Do not trust that man.
Hongo Takeshi lives!
Wh-What did you say?
You...
You betrayed me, Taki!
Damn you...
After him!
Wait a minute.
I cannot let a traitor
leave this place alive.
Captain Taki is in danger.
Contact HQ!
Right!
Taki!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
Taki, are you all right?
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Wait!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Screw Block!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
The terrible flower monster
Bararanga was defeated.
But Shocker wasn't about to give up.
Hongo Takeshi and Taki
Kazuya's fight was far from over.
Fight on, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
I am the monstrous Seadragon!
I'll use the 8,300 volts that
flow through my body
to put an end to the Kamen Rider!
My brothers Seadragon II
and III will appear as well.
Stay tuned to this channel next week
for "Three Electric
Monsters: the Seadragons!!"
Three Electric Monsters:
the Seadragons!!
Kicking off the ground with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!