KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Graveyard Monster
Kabibinga
Rock-paper-scissors!
It's a tie!
Shin's it!
C'mon, let's hide!
Jun, Mako!
Don't go into the graveyard!
Shima Family Grave
Monster!
Help me!
I am Kabibinga!
What are you doing?
Behold, the power of Kabibinga!
I cannot afford to be seen.
Find them!
Monster!
I'm scared!
What shall we do
with the children?
Kill them.
No, wait...
We might get some use
out of these twins.
Take them away.
No! I'm scared!
Let me go!
Please, let me go!
This is the Shocker base
beneath the graveyard.
Doctor Shinigami.
The test was a success.
Here.
Put it into the mold cultivator.
Shocker's plan was
to incite mass chaos
by cultivating mold and
releasing it into the city.
In other words, they were planning
to use mold as a deadly weapon.
Kabibinga.
We need more of your powerful mold
that propagates by feeding on humans.
Continue to attach
your mold to people.
I shall see to it that Japan
falls under Shocker's control!
Monster!
Take one of me, too!
Looking good, everyone!
Mr. Chairman!
Hayato won't let me join!
Haven't seen you working as a
photographer in a while, Hayato.
Taking advantage of this
brief peace and quiet.
Hey.
What's that supposed to mean?
I feel like Shocker's
due for an attack soon.
That's right!
I haven't seen Taki
for a few days.
That suggests he's gotten
a tip from the FBI,
and he's running
an investigation.
Damn you, Shocker!
Shocker!
They won't let this
peace last for long.
They're planning
something, for sure!
See to it that the Kamen Rider does
not catch wind of Operation: Mold.
Doctor Shinigami.
It's time we took the initiative.
Bring in the twins!
No! Help me!
Kabibinga, what are you plotting?
I'm going to make
them my messengers.
Doctor Shinigami.
If you use your powerful
hypnosis on them...
I'm certain it will work.
No! Let me go!
Let me go!
Very well.
Then I shall.
Watch.
Watch...
You are now members of Shocker.
You will do anything
Shocker commands.
Okay!
We're members of Shocker now!
We'll do anything
Shocker commands!
What is Shocker planning?
Yes? This is the
Tachibana Racing Club.
There we go!
I see.
Tell him to contact me
the minute he gets back.
Yes, thank you.
That Taki. Going off
without so much as a word...
Hey, there!
How's everyone doing?
Hey, Taki. You're leaving
us in the lurch again.
You have a lead, don't you?
You got me, huh?
But I guess it's time to own up.
There's a certain graveyard that's
seen a lot of disappearances nearby.
- A graveyard?
- Near the graveyard?
Can we help you?
It's an emergency. Please help.
Help?
My sister was
kidnapped by Shocker.
Shocker?
They'll kill her if
we don't save her.
Is this true?
But how do you know that
I know about Shocker?
It's dangerous, Hayato.
It could be a trap.
They're gonna kill
my big sister Junko.
Where was your sister taken?
Near the graveyard.
Anyway, let's check it out.
Let's do it.
Mako, is this the place?
Yeah.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure.
Let's go.
Now we'll fool them.
We'll send her to the Racing
Club with this box of candy.
I hope those two are
taking this seriously!
Don't be ridiculous.
You worry too much, Goro.
This is Shocker we're dealing
with, after all.
Oh, you're that girl.
Say,
did they save your big sister?
Yeah!
And where are the nice
men who went with you?
They said they'd be back soon
and I should take this to you.
Soon?
All right. I'll take this, then.
Hey, guys! Let's all have some!
- Move please.
- Let's all have some.
I'll make some tea.
Why don't you join us?
I have to go. Goodbye.
She seemed a little different...
Someone! Come and save me!
What a fantastic guinea pig.
The mold will absorb the moisture
in this cave and multiply.
When it reaches her
feet, it will devour her.
This will be a valuable test.
The mold!
The mold is gonna eat me!
I'm scared! Help!
I'll search this way.
Where'd all this fog come from?
You were brought here through
Doctor Shinigami's hypnosis!
Take that sword and stab Taki.
Mako!
A Shocker cyborg!
Now... face me!
That mold will melt
my body on contact!
Hayato! Where have you gone?
Transform!
KAMEN RIDER
Damn you... Kamen Rider!
Are you frightened,
now that I'm Kamen Rider?
Please!
I'd never lose to
the likes of you!
I'll coat all of humanity in
mold, and lead them to extinction!
Attack him!
Pursue him!
Fight me, Kamen Rider!
Damn...
It's filled with a tranquilizer!
Kamen Rider is no match for me!
Hold it!
Get back here!
Wake up!
Come on, wake up!
She's hypnotized!
Wake up!
That hurts!
Take that!
Taki!
Speak to me, Taki!
I see...
The mold is vulnerable to oil.
Wake up, everyone!
Wake up!
Don't move!
Touching that mold will kill you!
Hey!
You did this, didn't you?
You filled the sweets with tranquilizers!
It wasn't me!
Returning here while the Kamen Rider still
lives... I should execute the lot of you!
Kabibinga.
I will permit you
one more chance.
Defeat the Kamen Rider,
and make Operation: Mold a success.
If you fail again, you will die.
I swear, it will be my ears
that hear Rider's final scream!
But first,
the combatants who failed must die.
Go, Kabibinga!
I see. I didn't even
realize they were twins...
Shocker's stooping to exploiting
young children... it's disgraceful!
They must have a base
near the graveyard.
Hanging in there?
Yes!
Hayato will be here soon.
This time, I will finish him.
When he passes under the bell, I will
blow up the belfry, and him with it!
But what about the base below?
The explosion won't be powerful
enough to reach that far down.
Now, take your places!
Just where is the
entrance to the base?
Knowing them,
it'll be somewhere unexpected.
I could hear that bell inside the
base, I think!
All right. Let's go.
Wait here,
in case things go badly.
Good luck.
It's here...
Hayato, thrown into the
air by the explosion
transformed using the
wind from the blast.
Fight me, Kabibinga!
How could you have survived that?
You cockroach!
Get him!
So that was the
entrance to the base!
Help me, mister!
Damn! Too much mold...
Impudent fool!
Die!
Rider!
Die, Rider!
I brought oil!
All right...
Now!
Rider Kick!
The mold disappeared!
Hurry, mister! Hurry!
It all disappeared!
Yeah!
Pops!
They're both safe!
Sounds like a perfect
outcome to me!
Hey, there!
Where did Mr. Kamen Rider go?
Well, he's...
Oh? Where did he go?
Goodbye, mister!
- Goodbye!
Hey. Which one is which?
That's Mako and that's Junko.
Wrong.
I'm Mako!
Goodbye!
- See?
- I see.
Honestly,
I can't tell them apart!
Shocker even tries to corrupt even
the most trivial of human happiness.
Ichimonji Hayato burns with
hatred for their evil deeds.
Don't let them beat
you, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Namekujira!
Shocker transplants a computerized brain
invented by Doctor Yajima into Namekujira,
in a plot to blow up gasholders.
Can Kamen Rider stop
their dirty plan?
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Namekujira's
Gas Explosion Plan."
The Monstrous Namekujira's
Gas Explosion Plan
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!