KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Eighteen million years ago,
Earth was inhabited by a
creature called the trilobite.
Reborn Fossil
The Blood-Sucking Trilobite
Doctor Shimura is hard at work
trying to find a way
to restore this ancient creature
from its fossilized form.
But can the trilobite be awakened
from its 18 million year slumber?
It worked. I've finally done it...
We've been waiting for that experiment
to bear fruit for some time.
I want to combine that ancient organism
with a cyborg that drinks
human blood to live,
and send this new monster
out into the world.
This will further our plans
for world conquest.
Name the trilobite cyborg Zanbronzo.
Finish the human's modifications
by 6:00 tomorrow evening,
then perform the blood swap with
the trilobite at 2:00 in the morning.
Papa, Mama.
I'm heading out on my overnight hike now!
Right. Take care, all right?
Don't be too rambunctious, now.
No problem.
And Papa, I bet you'll get
to do a lot of research
with me out of your hair, right?
You got me there.
The kid's got my number.
Hear me, my brother.
Listen well.
All who stand in the way of
our world conquest are enemies.
It is your duty, as the chosen one,
to kill those enemies.
It's gone...
I wonder where it could have gone.
It shouldn't have been
able to go anywhere.
There's no one here
to take the trilobite away...
Begin the blood transfusion.
Who are you people?
Inhabitants of a world
you know nothing about.
What do you want with me?
We have business with you.
I'm giving you one chance.
Leave, or I'll call the police.
We won't kill you.
We're going to take you somewhere.
Where?
When did this appear
underneath my house?
Welcome, Doctor Shimura.
I understand how you must feel...
But don't forget that
you've been kidnapped.
What do you want with me?
This.
A trilobite fossil?
What about it?
I want your help to
bring it back to life.
Why?
To bring peace to all of humanity.
Liar. I refuse to help you.
You're in no position
to refuse, Doctor Shimura.
Natsue!
Darling...
Do as we say,
or we'll have this
trilobite suck your blood.
Ridiculous. Trilobites can't
drink human blood.
Yes, that's been the scientific
consensus up until now.
But we've used our science
to break through that barrier.
Liar!
Are you prepared to be test subject one?
How... How could you?
Shimura! It's time to drop
that idealism of yours.
Well? I want your answer now.
Damn you!
What are you doing?
All right... begin the test.
Shocker's plan was to create a monster
that grew as it drank human blood,
use it to throw humanity into chaos,
and thus conquer the world.
Additionally, their first targets
would be the Kamen Rider
and FBI agent Taki Kazuya.
It worked!
Hey, Mr. Taki!
I read something in a book yesterday...
It said there's a doctor working
to bring ancient creatures back to life.
Ancient creatures?
Sounds like a fantasy.
You think so?
I think you adults need
more fantasy in their lives.
The best you can manage is sinking
15 years' pay on a new dream house.
Don't be a brat!
You gross litterbug!
You could learn something from kids.
The Seventeen-Article Constitution says...
Huh?
Look at that creepy bug...
What is it?
Goro!
Damn... the Racing Club, then...
No husband until I'm 30, huh?
Tachibana Racing Club
Colonel Zol.
We failed in our plan
to attack FBI scum Taki.
I'm going to put Plan B
into operation now.
That's nice.
This one says I'll get a date next week...
Drain her! Drain her dry, Zanbronzo.
Tachibana Auto Corner
You're Ichimonji Hayato!
You damned monster!
Wait!
Mari...
Speak to me!
Mari! Mari!
You can't hold out on us forever.
Agree to work with us,
and we'll restore your
wife to good health.
And if you refuse...
Don't tell me...
My son, Wataru...
Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
These scales might be
the key to solving all of this.
You might be right.
Taki, look after Mari.
I'm going to the university lab
to investigate these scales.
Come to me, Rider!
Transform!
Where did it go?
Rider doesn't realize I've shrunk myself!
KAMEN RIDER
Well, that's nasty...
All that garlic is enough
to drive a man mad.
But it keeps vampires away!
I know, but...
Damn Shocker for doing this to her.
I feel the same way.
I couldn't stop thinking it
when I was looking after her.
How'd things go at the university?
They said it might be an Earth
organism that went extinct long ago.
Hey, it's like that thing I read...
What are you talking about?
Um... there's a guy named Doctor Shimura.
He's doing research to bring ancient
organisms back from the dead.
Doctor Shimura?
I'm so glad you've agreed
to help us, Doctor Shimura.
I have your word, then?
We won't harm Wataru.
You have my word.
Welcome your visitor.
We can't afford to draw suspicion.
But don't forget that
I'm standing right here.
Stalling won't get me anywhere.
I'm sorry to interrupt your work,
but I was hoping you'd
show me your trilobites.
Of course.
But I'm afraid you're too late.
I don't have them here.
You don't?
No.
The laboratory at Johoku University
wanted them back, and took them away.
That's quite a shame...
- Well, have a seat.
- Certainly.
You're looking a bit
green around the gills.
Is something troubling you?
No, it's nothing...
Strange. There's somebody
else in this room...
Is somebody after you?
Excuse me.
If there's a Shocker monster
behind these curtains,
it could spell tragedy
for this household...
Where's Mom?
Mom's not here right now.
Oh, yeah?
Wataru... say hello to our guest.
Hello.
Taki.
I think Doctor Shimura's trilobites
are involved in this somehow.
The Johoku University laboratory
said they never asked for them.
What did you say?
Then someone stole them from the doctor,
and then threatened him not to tell?
Yes. Let's go.
There's no time to lose...
Contact the Chairman.
This wasn't the deal.
Change of circumstance.
Stop dragging your feet and get to work.
Doctor Shimura, it seems your
part is done here.
What?
Do you want to experience
Zanbronzo's blood-sucking for yourself?
Wait a minute.
I'm not a fool, you know.
I thought you might try this.
And?
I shortened the trilobite's lifespan.
Which means you'll need
me again very soon.
Wh-What?!
I must protect my family and myself.
You dare...
We can discuss the rest after
you restore my wife to good health.
Damn you!
What are you doing?
Move the plan to the next stage
before the Kamen Rider arrives.
Is anybody here?
I don't see the kid around...
Get back here!
They're fast, I'll give them that.
Right. Let's go inside.
There it is. The way into Shocker's base!
Yeah. Let's go.
Hold on. It's a time bomb!
Where is it?
Taki! Hurry!
Come on!
Doctor!
Hurry! We're getting out of here!
Hurry!
Damn. They planned for
the fact that we might escape.
I'm sure of it.
Doctor. Where has he gone?
Haneda. With the trilobites
I restored to life.
Damned Shocker... they're going
to send them all over the world!
They're absolutely inhuman!
Taki. You handle things here.
Right.
Transform!
Tokyo International Airport
Hold on.
Kamen Rider!
Give me that bag this instant!
Listen.
Let Zanbronzo drink your
blood and send it to fight.
Yes, sir!
There you are...
Rider!
Rider.
Taki, watch out for that monster.
Strange.
I'm getting weaker...
The doctor... he did something to me!
All right, time for my last resort!
Rider Kick!
Serves you right, Zanbronzo!
Yes. He was a fearsome opponent.
This is my end...
I'm returning to my original form.
The antidote that Doctor Shimura
created seems to be working.
Where am I?
Mari, hang in there.
Hang in there!
Well, then... Cheers!
Cheers!
I only wish Ichimonji could have joined us.
He's an odd one, really.
He gets uncomfortable
in cheerful settings like these.
I think he's just very bashful.
Dear, why don't we have another
toast, to Mr. Ichimonji's health?
That's a fine idea.
Then let's have another toast.
Cheers!
Ichimonji Hayato saved everyone
from the blood-sucking monster.
But what will he
be forced to face next?
Don't lose, Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the ant-eating devil Arigabari.
Arigabari seeks to use a deadly bacteria
known as "The Curse of the Amazon"
to conquer Japan.
Ichimonji Hayato picks up on their
scheme and heads for Shocker's base.
Join us next week for more Kamen Rider
in "Deathmatch! The Ant-Eating
Devil Arigabari."
Deathmatch! The Ant-Eating
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!