KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
Ambassador Hell!!
His Fearsome True Form?
What's that sound?
Release the water from the dam!
I can't do that!
It would wipe the
city downstream...
Hoshino City... off the map!
All two million people who use this
lake as water supply are going to die.
I, Rattlander, have filled
the lake with my deadly venom!
What? Venom?
Well? Open the sluice gates!
No!
The Kamen Rider!
Shocker monster, Rattlander...
You won't get away with this!
H-How did you learn of my plan?
A member of Shocker informed me.
What?
There's a traitor in Shocker?
That cannot be!
I hardly believed it...
but it seems the tip was correct.
But who could have
leaked the information?
Let me go!
What are you doing?
I am your commander!
Ambassador Hell.
My leader!
What is the meaning of this?
I think you already know!
I... I have always followed
your orders loyally!
Silence.
Rattlander reported that
there is a traitor in Shocker
who leaked our plan
to the Kamen Rider.
What did you say?
And you think that was me?
Operation: Poisoned Reservoirs
was a top Shocker secret.
The only ones who knew
about it were you and me.
Ambassador Hell... you are the traitor!
No, it wasn't me!
Let me go!
My leader!
Keep him in a cell until his execution.
My leader...
My leader!
So, what I said was...
Who is it?
It's a pigeon we haven't seen before!
Registry number 0001.
That's strange...
We don't have that number.
What's that?
Let me have a look.
What's this thing?
My dearest Hongo Takeshi.
That's the voice of Shocker's leader!
Leader?
The execution of your mortal
enemy, commander-in-chief
of Shocker's Japan branch, Ambassador Hell,
has been scheduled for September 30th
at 4:00 PM in the 8th warehouse at Harumi.
You are hereby invited to attend,
to serve as a witness to
Ambassador Hell's execution.
For the time of your attendance,
Shocker pledges not to lay a hand upon you.
Ambassador Hell's being executed?
It's a trap!
We'd be fools to take
Shocker at their word!
It might indeed be a trap...
But I can't let them kill Ambassador Hell.
What are you talking about, Takeshi?
After everything he's
put us through? He's a villain!
Why should we object
if they turn on their own?
Hey, Pops.
Ambassador Hell might've been the one who
leaked the plan about the reservoir last night.
It's entirely possible that Ambassador Hell
could have turned on them for some reason.
Hongo, you mean...
You want to save him?
You must wear a blindfold
from this point onward.
I suppose you and I have
a truce today, too...
Hey. Don't be rough.
Now, come with us.
All right. Here we go!
Welcome, Hongo Takeshi!
We will now commence the execution
of the former Shocker
commander, Ambassador Hell!
Traitorous Ambassador Hell.
Do you have any last words?
Yes.
Hongo.
You were a worthy foe for a long time,
yet you came here to serve
as my witness today.
Let my last words be an
expression of gratitude.
Thank you.
Ambassador Hell...
I consider it an honor to
serve as your witness as well.
Commence the execution!
Remain calm!
Retrieve Hongo and Ambassador Hell!
That way!
Hongo.
Where is Ambassador Hell?
He may be a traitor to Shocker,
but I still need him.
I can't just let you kill him!
Where is Hongo?
No need to worry.
If he's just against combatants,
he'll be by soon enough.
Well...
I hope it's just combatants, but...
Then... You think Rattlander might show up?
No...
Our leader created a mystery
monster without my knowledge.
A mystery monster?
Indeed.
It is the reason I betrayed Shocker.
Ganikomoru...
You're a Shocker monster, too?
Think that, if you wish!
Our last battle taught me
all I need to know about you!
Let's go!
Rider Transformation!
All right...
What is he, really?
KAMEN RIDER
You were their commander-in-chief!
How can you not know
Ganikomoru's true identity?
Forgive my ignorance.
What is world domination worth,
if your leader doesn't trust you?!
I've grown sick of Shocker's methods!
That is why I leaked Rattlander's
poisoned reservoir plot to you.
About that.
I'm worried about that unknown monster,
but we need to take care
of Rattlander first.
Ambassador Hell.
What is Rattlander's next target?
He spent all of his venom
in the reservoir last night.
He's probably gone to restock his venom.
But where?
Rattlander is a cyborg based off
of that desert snake, the rattlesnake.
He would live in the desert.
Is there anywhere like
a desert in the area?
Hamamatsu.
That's right.
I'll show you the way!
Wait a minute.
You should stay here.
We want to learn more about Shocker, too.
I leave myself in your hands, then.
Uh, we'd rather not
have you in our hands...
Pops, we're heading out.
Good luck.
Um...
Hey.
What are you whispering about?
We're worried.
It's okay.
Takeshi pulled his neck
out of the guillotine.
He's not a Shocker commander anymore.
But Colonel Zol was
actually Wolf Man, right?
And Doctor Shinigami was
secretly Squidevil, remember?
Shocker commanders-in-chief
have always been cyborgs.
Yes, that's true...
Hey, Ambassador Hell!
Yes?
The pigeons are afraid!
Maybe a rat or a cat is stalking them?
What's that sound?
The animal pigeons fear most
is the sound of the snake.
And not just any snake,
but a rattlesnake.
What did you say?
Don't tell me! You...
The women were right.
All Shocker commanders are cyborgs.
And the true form of Shocker's
greatest commander-in-chief...
Ambassador Hell, is...
Rattlander!
Then the execution was all an act?!
To deceive your enemies,
you must deceive your allies!
And even Hongo and Taki
now trust me implicitly!
It's so big. I wouldn't even
know where to start...
Let's start with the center
of the dunes, at least.
Hey. Look at that.
Is this...
Ambassador Hell...
What's going on here?
What do you think?
Look!
- Yuri!
- Pops!
Stay back!
I see.
Ambassador Hell...
you were never a traitor!
I am Shocker's high commander.
I would never betray Shocker!
Now, stay still!
That was a dirty trick...
Cry and suffer...
Now, the real execution will begin!
Have you gone mad, Hongo Takeshi?
What are you laughing about?
What's so funny?!
Do you really think we
came to these dunes blind?
We prepared for this!
W-What did you say?
Watch carefully...
Look out!
Disperse!
Damn you...
Hongo.
It's finally time to end you!
He's gone...
Where is he?
That is the power of Rattlander!
Ambassador Hell's true form...
Rider Transformation!
Jump! Dive!
Slam into them!
Give it all you've got! Rider Kick!
Hit them with the force of a storm!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Mr. Taki! Help!
Rider! Rider!
Hey! Be careful!
Kamen Rider!
Mr. Taki!
Pops!
He came here in a roar...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of lamentation,
who brings evil plots to light?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for strength!
Fly! Run!
Get the dynamo humming!
Rider Throw!
Full charge! Full charge!
Hit them with an engine's roar!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider Kick!
Curse you, Rider...
I will return from the
dead and destroy you!
Shocker forces... are eternal!
Kamen Rider.
Shocker's Japan Branch is hereby disbanded.
I can now create a more
fearsome organization.
We shall meet again, Kamen Rider!
A more fearsome organization, eh?
It's finally time for
us to show ourselves...
Kamen Rider... I shall destroy you!
Ambassador Hell was secretly
the Shocker cyborg Rattlander.
And the monster Ganikomoru
was about to lift his veil of mystery.
What is the new organization
that will replace Shocker?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
Geldam has joined Shocker
to create Gel Shocker!
Let us celebrate the merger.
Gel Shocker will surely conquer Earth
and destroy the Kamen Rider.
Go, General Black!
Gel Shocker's Debut!
The Last Day of Kamen Rider!!
Go, Ganikomoru!
Kicking off the ground
with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning
with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!