KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the
Kamen Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil Shocker, a secret
organization plotting world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to fight
Shocker and free humanity!
The Monstrous Girakorogi's
Nails of Death
Girakorogi.
Let's see what your killer
sound waves can do.
Kamen Rider... I'll do the
same thing to you, very soon!
You've shown me your power.
Now that I've seen what you can do,
I must put you to work.
Then... Then let me
fight the Kamen Rider!
Not so fast.
You can fight the Rider any time.
Girakorogi...
For now, you must use your
terrifying nails of death
to send all of Japan into a panic.
Bring me a combatant
who has outlived his usefulness!
P-Please! Spare me!
Silence.
Girakorogi.
Show me what your nails of death can do.
But the real show is what happens next.
Quite impressive indeed.
Do you see the power of my red nails?
Anyone pierced by these nails
will return to life with these
same red poisoned nails!
Go!
Enough!
Listen to me, all of you.
Girakorogi's nails of death
will spread his mysterious disease
through the population exponentially.
Kids these days.
They've never even seen a cricket.
This is my pride and joy.
Wow.
Kids who've never seen crickets, huh?
You can't help but feel sorry for them.
That's why I'm going to teach them
some bug-hunting tricks tomorrow.
When that's over, I'll take
them bug-hunting with me.
Oh, that reminds me.
I'll bring two kids I know tomorrow.
Will you look after them?
Sure.
I have to go now.
Oh?
Yes, goodbye.
What's that sound?
My head... my head's splitting in two!
M-Monster!
I am Girakorogi!
G-Girakorogi?
You must do as I say!
I... I won't obey some monster!
Get up, now. Rise!
My lord, Girakorogi...
Your wish is my command.
Nine o'clock already?
Where could he be?
Calm down a little, Mitsuru.
You're pacing like a bear in the zoo.
I just wonder where Naoki is.
He's gonna be late for Sunday class.
Oh... Naoki's not here yet?
After Takeshi went to all that trouble...
Okay, Mitsuru, you go on ahead.
I'll drop Naoki off on my motorbike later.
That's right, go on ahead.
Okay, Mitsuru?
Speak of the devil.
You're late. What were you doing?
Naoki. That's not nice to do.
Sorry, I ended up sleeping late!
Good morning!
Okay, come on in.
Now, everyone.
Go into that room.
Okay!
Good.
Today I'm going to teach you about insects.
This is a model of a cricket.
Did you all bring notebooks?
Yes!
Good.
See if you can make a good
drawing of this while I'm gone.
Got it?
Mr. Teacher, today's not a drawing day.
You were gonna teach us
how to hunt bugs.
Yeah! You said you'd teach us
how to hunt bugs!
Yeah!
Shut up!
Mr. Teacher! Mr. Teacher!
Help!
Let me go!
I won't let you go.
You'll be the first victim of my red nails!
Help!
Now I just have to sit back and watch.
What's going on?
Help!
Okay, let's go.
A monster!
He's gonna get everyone!
Help! Help!
The experiment was a roaring success.
The children will live only three days.
In that time, they will spread
the red nails to more and more people!
This is bad!
We'd better tell Mr. Hongo!
Hello? Tachibana Racing Club here.
Yes, it's me.
What did you say?
What's going on?
My colleague Ogawa is attacking
children with a monster.
You don't think...
Hey, is this true?
It's true!
That Ogawa guy is working for Shocker!
Hello? Hey, Naoki!
What's going on? Naoki!
Taki, something's wrong.
What's wrong with you kids?
Hey, kid...
Taki! What's wrong?
Hey, Taki!
I'm going numb...
Taki...
The children's red nails...
Hey, Taki! Speak to me!
Hey, Taki!
Hold it!
I knew I'd find Shocker here...
All right... I'll face you myself!
Rider Transformation!
Let's go, Rider!
Try me, Girakorogi!
KAMEN RIDER
Let's go!
Combatants, you've done enough for now.
Withdraw!
Girakorogi... what's your game?
I just don't want to kill the combatants.
What did you say?
Take this... killer sound waves!
And another blast!
Damn you, Girakorogi...
Stop it! Stop it!
Don't get in my way!
I've almost killed the Kamen Rider!
Stand back!
Help me!
Ah, damn!
Rider... now I'll finish the job!
Stop it!
Damn!
He got away... damn him!
I almost had him, too!
Those stupid combatants!
I can't stand it!
Hey, Naoki!
Naoki, Mitsuru!
What is this?
Naoki, Mitsuru... forgive me!
Hey!
Hey, what's going on here?
Pops, look out!
Hey...
Takeshi, what's going on here?
Damn. Those Shocker bastards...
They're going to use these red
nails to throw the city into chaos.
What?
You've finally come, Hongo.
Girakorogi.
Use Ogawa to lure him into our base.
Ogawa! Ogawa...
Are you... working with Shocker?
Wait a minute. I just
escaped from Shocker's base.
- Base?
- Yes.
Will you come back with me, Hongo?
I know where to find the
antidote to cure everyone.
All right. Show me, then.
Okay. Follow me.
Ogawa... is the medicine in here?
Yes.
Hey, Ogawa!
What's wrong, Ogawa?
No... it was a trap?
Damn...
Damn!
All right... I'll have to break through.
It's no use...
All right...
Rider Transformation!
All right... I'll break through and escape!
Rider Punch!
It's no use.
All right... now a kick!
Rider Kick!
It's no use.
The Rider Kick isn't working...
All right.
I'll jump through that window!
It's no use.
I can't even jump?
Ambassador Hell!
Shocker's great scientists
worked hard to create these...
Absorbing mats that absorb
any force directed into them.
You can't use any of your
precious jumps or kicks.
Now, die!
Now, face my sound waves!
There's no absorbing
mat on that high window...
If I could hit that window with
my kick, I could escape...
Wait. I know what to do.
Girakorogi.
You have a chance now
that will never come again.
Use everything you have
to kill the Kamen Rider.
Kill him!
Screw Kick!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies straight from hell
Their black shadows threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Not so fast!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Hold it!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Damn...
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Their black shadows threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Damn! You destroyed my transmitter!
Rider, Rider!
Girakorogi...
Without your killer sound waves,
you're just like any other monster!
Rider Kick!
Look! They're all back to normal!
- Isn't that nice?
- Hongo!
What about the others, then?
They're fine, of course.
Then untie me already!
I'm sorry!
Ogawa...
I'm sorry, Hongo.
This was all my fault.
The actions of Hongo
Takeshi, the Kamen Rider,
kept the city safe from
Shocker's evil plot.
But Shocker will send more
new cyborgs to attack your city!
Fight on, our Kamen Rider!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Elekibotaru!
A swarm of fireballs burns hot and red.
When one of them lets out a flash,
people catch fire in an instant.
Go, Kamen Rider! Beat your foe!
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider in,
"The Monstrous Elekibotaru's
Fireball Attack!"
The Monstrous Elekibotaru's
Fireball Attack!!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!