KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
What's that there?
It's a big one!
It's gonna tip us over!
The Monstrous Crab Bubbler
Appears in Hokkaido
Japan Meteorological Agency Otaru Branch
"The minor tsunami that
occurred yesterday in Osaka Bay
is the third this month, following
similar incidents in Kyushu and Shikoku."
"Undersea earthquakes are
believed to be the cause,
but sabotage to seismometers in the
local areas prevent their epicenters
or scales from
being determined."
Damn... what's going on here?
Don't get so mad.
Japan's always had earthquakes.
If that was all this is...
But why would someone
sabotage the seismometers?
And I've heard talk
throughout the agency
that there's been damage to
their electrical rooms, too.
Electrical rooms?
Electrical Room
The seismometer's down.
Some kind of malfunction?
Did we lose power?
And he's been gone a while...
Could it be...
the electrical room...
Who are you people?
Why, you...
I'm telling you,
we don't do four-wheelers.
Motorbikes only.
That's right.
So...
Don't make me say it again!
We don't do that!
Hey!
Something's off around here.
Hiromi, where are the girls?
What do you think's got the
Chairman in such a bad mood?
They ran off!
Babbling about summer break...
I think they went to Hokkaido.
I see.
Where's Taki, then?
Taki's the one who set it up.
Taki's just as much to blame.
After all that complaining
he does about the girls...
Mr. Chairman,
it's not good for you to get so angry.
You're too old
for this nonsense.
What was that?
But I wonder if they know they
won't do much swimming there.
You mean how swimming's off
limits because of the tsunami?
Exactly.
Investigator Taki Kazuya
of FBI Tokyo Branch.
FBI number 5021.
Reporting in as scheduled.
Over.
Nothing to report
as of August 7th.
Roger.
Okay, we're through. Go on.
Taki-san?
Hey, this place is so great!
It's totally groovy!
Blue skies, fresh air!
We're about to go for a swim!
Sorry to tell you,
but you won't get to show
off your swimsuits after all.
What did you say?
We can't even go swimming?
Don't shoot the messenger.
The newspapers said swimming
is off limits for a while.
Mr. Kanda?
What is it, Taki?
Good luck babysitting.
Roger.
Babysitting? How rude...
Are you gonna come join
us, Mr. Taki?
When I'm done with work, I will.
See you, everyone.
Gentlemen.
I've just received a report
from Crab Bubbler that he's
destroyed the seismometer at
the Otaru JMA branch office.
Our preparations
are now complete.
Based on our successful trials in
Kyushu, Shikoku, and Osaka,
we'll use our new underwater bombs,
more powerful than a nuclear explosion,
to create a tsunami on
the Muroran Peninsula.
Until our plan is
successful, we must not let
anyone learn the secret
of this operation.
Have Crab Bubbler continue his
surveillance on the surface.
Hey, no diving allowed.
The water's off limits.
Stay out of my business.
It'll be your life
on the line...
Crab Bubbler,
orders from our leader.
You're to kill anyone who
gets close to our base.
Damn you...
This is no fun...
It's such a shame. The water's so
calm, but we still can't swim?
I spent 3500 yen
on this swimsuit!
Like anyone cares.
Am I right, Mr. Kanda?
Yes.
What's that?
C'mon, let's go back!
Sure, let's go.
Come on, girls.
We just got here.
Now we have to go?
No fun at all...
Damn...
they took my Shocker transceiver!
What's that?
You're sure the diver was dead?
I'm sure.
And what's this mini-transceiver
you said you found?
It has an odd-looking
eagle symbol on it.
Mr. Kanda, please stay
where you are for a while.
I need to tell Ichimonji
Hayato about this.
Ichimonji Hayato? Who's that?
He's like a modern
superhero, I guess you'd say.
You...
Any who learn about our
underwater earthquakes must die.
But I won't kill you.
We'll convert that able body of yours
and put you to work as a cyborg!
Underwater earthquakes?
You mean
you're the one
behind the tsunamis?
Don't be absurd...
I'm going to stop you!
Mr. Kanda!
What's happening, Mr. Kanda?
I had a feeling Shocker was
behind those mysterious tsunamis,
and what do you
know, here they are!
Hurry!
Transform!
Rider!
Keep driving! Go!
The Kamen Rider!
Rider Jump!
Shocker HQ! Shocker...
Kamen Rider.
They're the ones behind the tsunamis!
Amazing work, Mr. Kanda.
If we can trace this
transceiver's frequency...
Get down! It's about to explode!
Rider, we won't be able
to find their base now.
Don't you worry.
We'll find their
base, no matter what.
KAMEN RIDER
Crab Bubbler.
Kamen Rider stole your
mini-transceiver, did he?
Yes.
But I detonated it immediately!
Fool! Do not
underestimate Kamen Rider.
What if he were to listen
in on our communications?
What would happen
then, Crab Bubbler?!
He could easily find this base's location
through the use of a directional tracker.
I see, my leader.
Hurry.
Kamen Rider is on our scent.
We have not one moment to lose.
You must destroy the seismometer of the
Sapporo Central Weather Station at once!
As you just heard,
my scientists,
now that the Rider is on our
trail, we must hurry.
Prepare for the
detonation at once.
We need but two
hours, my leader.
Good.
Spark a massive tsunami in the
sea near Otaru in two hours.
Mr. Kanda!
Mr. Taki!
Mari, where's Kanda?
Taki...
Mr. Kanda,
where's the transceiver?
I have Hayato looking into it.
Hayato?!
So he really is here, huh?
Yeah.
If I can locate the special
communications signal they're using,
I can inevitably determine
the Shocker frequency.
I've got it!
Extremely short
waves, 384 megahertz!
Hayato!
Taki.
Mr. Kanda explained everything.
I'm so glad you're here.
So, did you determine
Shocker's frequency?
Did you find it, Hayato?
Extremely short
waves, 384 megahertz.
Great.
If we use our directional tracker, we
can find the location of Shocker's base.
Wait.
I'll have you do that, Taki.
Shocker will be feeling the heat and
racing to destroy that seismometer.
I'll investigate the Sapporo
Central Weather Station.
I'll contact HAM radio enthusiasts
in the area and try to trace back
the source of the waves.
Go to it, Taki.
Will you help us, Mr. Kanda?
Of course.
You guys, too.
Listen. We're going to contact
HAM radio operators in this area
and ask about the directionality
of the mystery waves.
Then we chart the directions
on the map, right?
CQCQ.
This is JA8AGN.
Emergency transmission.
Please report the direction in
which you hear the extremely
short wave 384 megahertz signal.
I repeat...
Sapporo District Meteorological Observatory
Damn... was I too late?
It's them! They did it!
All right. Thank you.
You won't get away!
This is JA8BIX Hakodate.
Direction is north-northwest.
Got it.
Hakodate, north-northwest.
Hakodate, north-northwest...
Now, talk! Where is your base?
West-northwest from Kushiro.
North-northwest from Otaru.
We seem to have our
general direction.
Fifty kilometers north-northwest
into the sea off Otaru.
Rider Kick!
How is the explosion coming?
Preparations are complete.
The large tsunami will occur in
the sea off Otaru in ten minutes.
Well done. Evacuate, all of you!
Hayato, any luck?
Did you trace back the signal?
Right here.
You're a life-saver, Taki.
Tell the other three, as well...
that Hayato says thank you.
Good luck, Hayato.
Is this it?
All right...
Hurry! The bombs will
go off in seven minutes!
We must evacuate at once! Hurry!
The Kamen Rider!
Looks like I arrived with
seven minutes to spare!
Well? Can't see now, can you?
Rider... die!
Rider Punch!
Feels great out here!
It's just wonderful!
Such a romantic sight!
I guess even our girls can feel
romantic from time to time.
I guess so.
Hey!
Hey, Pops!
What's wrong, you guys?
Aren't you going to swim?
I thought swimming
was off limits.
It's safe now. Right, Hayato?
Yes.
Okay then, let's have a swim!
I'm gonna grab my bag!
Me, too!
Hayato, shall we join them?
All right. Let's race!
With his wonderful allies by his side,
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen Rider,
foiled Shocker's
artificial tsunami plan.
And then...
Shocker, do your worst!
I'm not in this alone.
I have wonderful
allies by my side.
Allies!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the fire-breathing caterpillar
monster, Dokugander.
The man-eating caterpillar
that appears out of the blue
turns out to be the Shocker
monster, Dokugander.
When Kamen Rider
pursues the beast,
it leads to a tempestuous
confrontation with Dokugander.
Join us next week for "The Fire-Breathing
Caterpillar Monster, Dokugander."
The Fire-Breathing Caterpillar Monster
Dokugander
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!