KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Fossil Man Hitodanger
Listen closely,
all you young ladies
Don't go falling
for a mountain man
If he gets lost in the mountains
You'll end up a young widow
Well, we're almost there.
How are you doing?
I'm just fine!
That's my little brother.
Once we get to the top,
we'll report to the others at
the base through the transceiver.
Okay!
Okay, let's go!
How are you doing?
Hang on, Big Bro.
What is it?
Oh, I see...
Maybe I'll join you...
What happened?
Oh, you just slipped, huh?
Don't scare me like that...
Hey, Big Bro! What's that?
They look like starfish...
Don't be silly.
Starfish live in the ocean.
They keep going that way...
Let's follow them!
Hey!
Boy,
you've got weird interests...
Hey, what's that?
I'll bet you it's
some secret base!
Masaru, you read too much manga.
Take a picture of me with it!
How about here?
Looks good.
A little more to the right.
That's right.
A little further back.
That's it.
Get a good one, okay?
Ow!
Hey, you okay?
Ow...
What's this thing?
It looks like a starfish...
Snow and rocks will be our home
We're not cut out for the city
We're just not cut
out for the city
Yuri, do you know how
much water we need?
Don't worry.
I've done this before.
You're sure?
I can't stand undercooked rice.
Don't be mean.
What are you up to, Goro?
Catching a fish for dinner!
You don't stand a chance!
Tobei here.
Hiromi, do you read me?
Yes, Hiromi here. Over.
I thought you might be
feeling lonely. Over.
Hayato and Taki haven't dropped
by, so I'm all alone.
I wish I hadn't caught
this stupid cold.
It's so boring. Over.
I read you loud and clear.
We'll bring back a souvenir,
so just wait for us there.
Over.
What was that sound?
Interference from something?
Over.
Hiromi here! Over!
That's strange...
Next to Tengu Rock...
a starfish...
A starfish monster!
Starfish?
Hello? Can you hear me? Over.
That guy said he saw
a starfish monster!
What could it be?
Tengu Rock?
Where would that be?
You monster...
Take this!
Masaru! Run!
Don't you hurt my brother!
Why, you...
My glasses...
Big Brother!
Big Brother! Where are you?
I can't see anything
without my glasses...
Are you okay?
This isn't a mountain a boy
should be climbing alone.
A starfish monster took my
brother into some weird building.
A starfish monster?
It must be Shocker...
What's Shocker?
I'll take you to the town at the foot of
the mountain, then look for your brother.
This might be a
strange question,
but does Foggy Peak have
any connection to starfish?
Oh, most certainly.
What kind of connection?
It all started last month.
They found a starfish fossil
that was just enormous!
A fossil, eh?
That means this whole area used
to be under the ocean, right?
But they say it was alive!
Alive?
No way...
But it's not impossible.
Starfish are hardy animals that
can even regrow their own limbs.
So? Where is this fossil?
As a matter of fact,
it's gone missing.
We all ran around searching,
thinking it'd run away, but...
Shocker must have stolen it
and turned it into a monster.
Shocker's plans for world
domination are proceeding smoothly.
Once the underground missile base
here on Foggy Peak is complete,
we will be unstoppable!
Shocker will cause widespread
destruction and take over the world.
Hitodanger, remain alert.
Until this base can use its missiles
to sow destruction across the world,
you must not let a
single person approach.
Capture anyone who gets
near, and execute them!
You people are inhuman!
You monster!
Take him away!
I sure do love the mountains.
Fresh air, clean water...
But there's something
to that building...
I've traced the mystery
radio waves that
FBI headquarters picked
up back to this area.
I bet it's connected to
the recent disappearances
of local mountain-climbers,
too...
Why, you...
Shown yourselves, have you?
Rider!
Kamen Rider...
Rider,
this thing's body is tough!
The body of Hitodanger,
hardened over tens of thousands of years,
was stronger than steel.
Rider Kick!
Rider...
Damn you...
KAMEN RIDER
Rider should have left a body...
Search the area!
Who's there?
That hurts!
Pops!
That wasn't nice!
I came running because I
thought I heard you down here...
I'm so sorry.
I thought you were one of
that starfish monster's gang.
Starfish?
I knew it...
You know something about it?
I got a strange
message on the radio.
It was talking about a starfish
monster, so I came to check it out...
I get it...
If our favorite FBI
agent is snooping around,
that means Shocker's
involved, right?
It's incredibly powerful.
It knocked Kamen
Rider for a loop!
Rider? That's not good...
Don't head out yet.
They're still
searching the area.
Does that mean...
they haven't caught Rider yet?
Of course not!
If he went to Tengu Rock...
that's here...
Still,
he's been gone way too long.
He could have fallen
into a crevasse!
I hear something!
Let me hear!
Hello? Hello?
Stop it! It's not a telephone!
Hello?
This is the camp for the
Tachibana Racing Club. Over!
C'mon, let me do it!
Quiet down!
It's Tobei and Taki here!
Oh, Mr. Taki is with you?
Is everything all right?
I'll explain later.
Has Hayato been down your way?
Let me have it!
Hayato hasn't been by! Over!
That's odd...
But all right.
I wonder what's going on...
Over there?
Is this where Rider was beaten?
Get them!
Taki!
Why, you...
Pops!
You won't beat me this time!
What the...
Taki!
You stay in there
until we find Rider.
You jerk!
At least take off the ropes!
Pipe down.
Did they bring you in, too?
Here, I'll untie you.
Their cruelty is unspeakable...
Thanks.
Boy, that was rough...
That's quite a
monster they have.
Yeah.
Come on, look alive, you two.
Let's work together
as mountain men
and find a way out of here.
Sounds good to me!
I'm really worried
about my little brother.
Okay...
Can you open it with that?
Yeah, leave it to me.
Hey,
it won't open!
Need a hand?
Hey. Aren't you...
Hey... Hayato!
I knew it was you.
Shocker's going to regret
catching this mountain man.
Just unlocking the door
won't get us anywhere.
Security is too tight to escape.
But I have an idea.
Listen. Get into a fight.
But what good will that do?
I think I get it.
Okay... let's try it.
Well,
I think I'm good in a brawl!
I'm sorry!
Don't do it for real!
Why, you! That really hurt!
Take that!
Hey! Quiet down, you fools!
Didn't you hear me?
Why, you...
Hey, they're here!
Didn't you hear me?
I said quiet!
Hey! Come over here!
Are you going to
pipe down or not?
Quiet down, you!
Get him!
You stupid little...
All right, get them!
Let's go.
You seem a bit old for
a Shocker combatant.
Oh, shut up!
I'll disconnect the alarms.
Will you be all
right on your own?
Leave it to me.
I'll flick the lights three
times to show it's safe.
When I do, run.
Let's see...
this would be the alarm.
Okay.
What are you people doing?
They're imposters!
Acetylene, eh?
I know what to do with this...
Oh no... they've found us out!
A fire! There's a fire!
What?
Let me through!
Now's our chance to escape!
Wait, we can't go out
dressed like this...
There we go!
Now, hurry!
Transform!
Sound the alarm!
If we don't put it out quickly,
the building will explode!
Be careful!
Don't get it on me, you fool!
He seems afraid of the water.
Of course...
Absorption of water will
restore the fossil to normal.
We did it! We did it!
Not so fast!
I'll lead you all to your doom!
Rider!
- Get in there!
- Right!
You won't beat me this time...
Hitodanger!
Your body will have
absorbed that water,
making you soft!
What was that?!
Rider... die!
Damn you...
Go down, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato, the Kamen Rider,
had defeated the fossil monster Hitodanger
and foiled Shocker's
evil schemes.
The fight only made him more determined
to fight Shocker and protect the peace.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Crab Bubbler.
A series of mysterious
tsunamis on the Pacific Coast
leads the gang to Hokkaido.
The fight between our brave
Kamen Rider and Crab Bubbler
unfolds amidst the
bounties of nature.
Join us next week for "The Monstrous
Crab Bubbler Appears in Hokkaido."
The Monstrous Crab Bubbler
Appears in Hokkaido
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!