KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
The Man-Eating
Monster Isoginchack
In the south of the vast
continent of Africa,
countless diamond
mines are to be found.
The area also contains veins
of diamonds not yet discovered.
This man, Kenzo Nakayama,
recently discovered a new diamond vein.
He was writing a letter to his
only relative, a grandson in Japan.
Hiroshi.
I've never done
anything for you before,
but today,
I am sending you a wonderful gift.
The package will
arrive to you soon.
Who are you people?
You found a new diamond mine!
You should give your map to us!
I just sent the
map to my grandson.
What?
To Hiroshi in Japan, you mean?
Yes.
Damn!
A monster!
I am Shocker cyborg Isoginchack!
Then get back in the
ocean where you belong!
Tell me the location of the
diamonds, or I'll suck you in!
Don't be ridiculous!
Do you see my power now?
You can suck this in!
Hey! Hey!
He's alive...
Hey, what happened to you?
Hey!
Are you Japanese?
I'd better get
him to a hospital.
Who's that?
Hongo Takeshi.
A persistent pest.
Contact the Japan
Branch at once.
I'll have my revenge for this.
What's this?
What's that?
Some kind of medallion?
Hey, isn't there
anything else in there?
Well?
I wonder what the
pattern means...
Let's have a look.
What could it be?
Looks like a
Christian cross to me.
Give me a break!
The letter said he'd
send something wonderful.
Well, it's nothing!
Just a child's toy...
I bet that medallion
contains some kind of secret.
Well, let's take it anyway.
It could be useful later.
No!
This is mine!
How dare you! Give that to me!
Come back here!
Mr. Policeman, save me!
They're thieves!
What? Thieves?
Our little Hiroshi
is such a liar!
Liar?
Are you the policeman who just
took over our local police box?
Yes, that's right.
Then I'm sure you
haven't heard yet,
but our boy here likes
to play pranks by lying.
It's not true!
But it is true.
Thank you for your help.
I see we need to be a
little stricter with him.
What do you mean?
You see...
He's not really our son.
He doesn't have any family,
so we took him in.
It's not nice to lie.
Try to be more
truthful, all right?
We're so sorry to bother you.
See you.
Thank you for all
your hard work!
See you again!
Now, Hiroshi.
Get going on your
delivery job already!
I thought he might send some diamonds,
but it was just that hunk of junk.
I'll have to put him
to work for this.
However he might look,
Hiroshi's still useful enough.
What in the...
Help me!
What is that thing?
Hey!
Help!
Help me!
What? An anemone?
Yes.
This telegram Hongo
sent from Africa says
that he'll be coming after a
boy named Hiroshi Nakayama.
A boy?
Hongo will be arriving
in Haneda today.
Really?
Hongo's back from Africa?
I guess this must be a
pretty big deal, huh?
Most likely.
Taki, will you come
with me to see the boy?
See you.
Begin.
Dentures, eh?
None of this clothing
is Hiroshi's.
No, sir.
But there was this.
The remains of an
opened package...
It likely contained the
map to the diamond mine.
Which means Hiroshi has it now.
Isoginchack, go after him once more.
Yes, go!
All the diamond mines of
Africa must belong to Shocker!
Uncle? Auntie?
Where'd they go?
Auntie? Uncle?
That's Hiroshi, is it?
Give us the contents of
your package from Africa!
No! No way!
If you don't,
I'll swallow you down and digest you!
Well?
Wait, you! Wait!
You can't escape me, you brat.
Now I'll show you!
Sakura, help me!
Hiroshi!
Help me, Sakura!
Isoginchack! Wait!
Transform!
Rider...
you'll pay for your meddling!
Taki will soon die.
Witness the power of
African poison darts!
What?
Taki! Taki!
Damn it...
KAMEN RIDER
An antidote Hongo sent me.
It should prove effective...
Hey, mister!
Hiroshi wanted me
to give this to you.
Where's Hiroshi now?
"They seem to want the medallion
my grandfather sent me,
but it's very important to me,
so I won't let them have it.
I'm going to go somewhere
they'll never find me."
I see...
But there's nowhere Hiroshi can
hide that they won't find him.
Do you know where
Hiroshi's hiding?
I don't.
But we have to find him.
Sakura,
look after the nice man here.
Okay, sure!
Excellent.
Now, we must find Hiroshi
before they do at all costs.
And to do so...
The place where
Hiroshi is hiding...
To the northwest of his home,
a place of forests and shrine gates.
The rest I leave to your
instincts, Isoginchack.
I believe you can
catch his scent!
It shall be done!
What's wrong, mister?
I need to help Hayato.
I smell the child!
He's not here.
Find him!
There he is! Get him!
After him!
Mr. Policeman!
Jonan Police Umemura Station
Help me!
Oh, you again?
-What's wrong?
-They're after me!
Who? Your auntie and uncle?
No, an anemone monster!
An anemone monster?
Is that another silly lie?
It's not a lie! It's true!
You should go home now.
Don't lie again,
or I'm taking you down to the station.
Excuse me.
Have you seen a boy
about ten years old?
Ten years old?
You mean 'the boy
who cried wolf'?
His name is Hiroshi Nakayama.
Oh, he played a little
trick on me and ran off.
He said an anemone monster was after
him, and ran off.
That wasn't a trick.
Which way did he go?
Taki...
are you sure you're up to this?
- All right.
- I am.
I'll search this way.
I'll go a little further down.
Hongo to Ichimonji.
Hongo to Ichimonji!
Is that you, Takeshi?
Are you in Japan?
I'm on my way to the scene.
I'll meet up with you soon.
Okay.
Hiroshi's destiny is
leading him to danger.
"Danger in a high
place," it says.
A high place?
Yes.
Up a tree, maybe?
We almost have him!
Catch him at once!
Just try and climb up!
I'll ring the fire bell
and bring everyone running!
Damn... that little brat!
Hit him with a dart!
Darn it...
Damn them...
How dare they harm Hiroshi!
They'll pay!
Transform!
Wretched Kamen Rider...
Hiroshi, hang in there!
All right...
Get him! Get him now!
Get him! Destroy him!
Take this!
Fight me, Shocker!
You've arrived, Hongo Takeshi...
Ichimonji!
Hongo!
Now, face us!
Taki, look after Hiroshi.
Right.
How do you like this?
Try me! Come on!
What now?
All right...
Rider Wheel!
Rider Throw!
All right. Now!
Rider Double Kick!
Thank you, Kamen Riders!
This is where we part ways.
You're leaving already?
I have a new mission
waiting for me in Europe.
You stay well, Hiroshi.
Get Hayato to spoil you like
a real big brother, okay?
Okay.
See you.
Another time.
Let's go.
I've got it.
The numbers represent
coordinates on a map.
Come in.
My name is Kenzo Nakayama.
Grandpa? Are you my grandpa?
Hiroshi?
I got your medallion.
Medallion?
I don't need that any longer.
I sold the diamond mine I found
to return to Japan.
And I'm going to use the money
to create a children's home
to help all the sad
orphans of Japan.
That's a wonderful idea.
I'm going to create a
lovely children's home.
And I know Hiroshi will help me.
Isn't that great, Hiroshi?
Yeah!
Shocker's plans to steal the diamond mine
that Kenzo had discovered had been foiled.
But Shocker would continue
seeking fresh opportunities to
advance their goal
of world domination.
What would they send next?
And how will Kamen
Rider fight them?
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Kamestone.
The strange beams
emitted by Kamestone
create a deadly aurora.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Kamestone's
Killer Aurora Plan!"
The Monstrous Kamestone's
Killer Aurora Plan
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!