KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Hongo Takeshi is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
Poison Butterfly of the
Amazon, Gireela
That's strange...
Is it a breakdown, Papa?
I'm not sure...
Monster! It's a monster!
Papa, I'm scared!
Koji, run!
Open up!
Please, help us!
Is anybody here?
Papa, I'm scared!
Don't worry. Papa's here.
In the past month, three cars have
been found at the bottom of this cliff.
But none of the vehicles'
occupants have been discovered.
No one would go to that trouble
just to throw out a junker...
Want to check it out?
Yeah.
This is the cliff.
They must've done something
with the people inside
then sent the car off the cliff.
The question is,
why'd they choose here?
Because it's deep in the mountains...
and no one would see them?
Hey. How do you get
a driver to stop?
Good question.
If you see a girl waving, maybe.
Or you're about to
be in an accident.
That's it.
What?
They rigged something on the
road to cause an accident.
You think Shocker's behind it?
I can't be certain yet, but...
What's that?
That doesn't look
like car paint.
Stop!
You need to be careful.
What if it's toxic?
Fair point.
Let's take it home
and analyze it.
These are Japan's
main reservoirs.
They flow with potable water
to quench humanity's thirst.
In other words,
if we poison this water,
we can purge large amounts
of humans all at once.
Listen well, Gireela!
Fill these capsules with the
poison scales from your wings,
and drop them into the
reservoirs from above.
This is Shocker's
Operation: Poison Water!
If we wish to sow enough
chaos to conquer Japan,
I will need to drop a large
number of capsules all in one day.
Go, Gireela!
They're scales from
a butterfly's wings.
And very unusual ones, at that.
A non-native species?
Yes. Look.
The shining part there
is a deadly toxin.
I had a close call, then.
You said it.
You could have had
a seizure and died.
Wait a minute...
There was a butterfly collector
who brought a rare poison
butterfly from the Amazon recently.
I read about that in the
newspaper, too!
All right.
Let's find that
newspaper and ask them.
These are the prisoners
I've collected so far.
Well done.
Put the prisoners to work as slaves,
making poison capsules at once.
Use the child as a guinea pig.
What are you planning here?
A glass, if you please.
Drink this, as a test.
Drink it!
A perfect success.
It's not in this one, either.
Hey, don't put it back with the
ones we haven't sorted through.
It's not in this one, either.
Are you sure you saw that article?
Yes, I'm sure.
I just can't find it.
Maybe it ran off somewhere.
Move, Goro.
I bet it was Goro!
You used it for something!
Aw, why do you blame
everything on me?
Forget you!
I quit!
Goro!
Hey, that's...
Here it is!
Hey, this is it!
I knew Goro had it!
Goro!
- Hey.
- Sorry...
Well done.
That's strange.
The address is
close to that dam!
Hey. Something's bothering me.
Maybe we should split up here.
Okay, I'll go on.
You wait for me here.
Will you be all right?
Will I be all right?
You're asking me if
I'll be all right?
I've got this.
I call this butterfly
from the Amazon "Gireela,"
but it doesn't have
an official name yet.
Because it's the
first one ever caught.
Does it have any
special properties?
Yes.
When pursued, it fights back.
It stings its pursuer
with poison needles.
Those pierced by the needles
immediately die from the venom.
They call it the "devil
butterfly" there,
and even if they see it,
they give it a wide berth.
Knowing it's so rare just
makes me want to see it more!
Could I please have a look?
Yes. But I...
Well, just wait one moment.
What a pretty lady.
This is...
These are just like those
scales from before...
Which means...
What's going on in this house?
It's too late to run.
I knew Shocker would
be behind this...
What did you do with the
person who lived here?
Shocker gave my life to the
poison butterfly of the Amazon,
to create a cyborg Gireela!
Wait!
Open up!
Open this door and fight me!
Set the bomb to go
off in five minutes.
We'll blow away the
house, and him with it!
Damn.
They set a time bomb, did they?
With just five minutes to go...
Taki's been gone a while...
It's an S.O.S.
There you are, Shocker cyborg!
I am the poison butterfly
of the Amazon, Gireela!
Rider Transformation!
Rider... Taki is crying inside.
Go find him!
What?
Taki, where are you?
Taki!
Rider, it's a time bomb!
It's going to explode soon!
Run!
Damn...
Let's move on to Plan B!
KAMEN RIDER
Hello?
Tachibana Racing Club here.
Would this be
Mr. Tachibana Tobei?
Yes, that's me.
I heard you were looking for
a butterfly from the Amazon.
A butterfly from the Amazon?
Oh, that?
Well I'm sorry,
but could you tell me who you are?
Miwa Kujo.
Kujo?
Actually, my friends were
on their way to see you.
They haven't arrived yet?
Oh, they certainly arrived.
I am the demon
butterfly Gireela...
And now,
I'll show you my true face!
Shocker...
Capture that man!
He'll be our hostage.
Take him away!
I think she ran away.
That's not their way.
Keep your guard up.
- Should we check it out?
- Yeah.
Hey. Let's wait
here a little while.
Be careful.
This is the kind of room where the
lights go black and a monster jumps out.
It's here!
You've survived, but not for much
longer, Hongo Takeshi.
Be quiet!
Come finish our fight!
Get out here, monster!
You've lost.
The capsules for Operation:
Poison Water are complete,
and the countdown has begun.
Operation: Poison Water?
What is that?
Silence!
Here's your explanation!
That hurts!
Taki, you okay?
This is their underground
base, huh?
Damn...
Pops!
You fell for our trap.
Hongo! They're planning
to poison the dam!
What?
Is that Operation: Poison Water?
Stop it!
Do you want him to die?
I'll die if I have to!
Just stop him!
Throw Hongo into a cell!
Take him away.
Wait, Gireela.
It's time to put the
plan into motion.
All right...
Round up all the prisoners!
Bring them!
Right.
First, we'll drop a
capsule into Okutama Dam.
Then we'll tie weights to them,
and drop them into
the poisoned water!
Go, Gireela!
Hongo.
I have a special way to finish
you off when this is all over.
If I could only destroy those
poison capsules from here...
I know!
All right!
Rider Transformation!
Damn...
Wait, you!
Papa, I'm scared.
We'll be all right.
What are you going
to do with us?
Help me!
Before I kill you, I'll let you watch
as I drop these capsules in the dam.
Stop it!
- Hongo!
- Rider!
Rider?
Go!
Kicking off the ground
with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning
with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider... watch,
as I throw these capsules into the dam!
Get him!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
Rider, leave these to me!
Calling up tornadoes
with a Rider Jet!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Cut!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Swimming through the
oceans with a Rider Swim,
That won't work on me!
a great dive flitting
through the sea!
Calling up whirlpools
with a Rider Screw!
Dragging enemies down
with a Rider Lung!
Rider Kick!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Rider!
Goodbye!
Rider! Goodbye!
Shocker will spare no method in
their quest for world domination,
from a stab in the back to
a poison butterfly's flight.
Ride on, Kamen Rider!
Shatter Shocker's next plot!
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is Tsuchigumo Man Dokumond.
Ambassador Hell uses Dokumond,
who appears from the ground,
drags people down,
and reduces them to skulls,
in an attempt to steal a liquid
explosive that can melt any metal.
Kamen Rider tries
to stop it all.
Join us next week for more Kamen
Rider in "Tsuchigumo Man Dokumond."
Tsuchigumo Man
Dokumond
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!