KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Mukogaoka
Flower Orangery
The flowers here
are all so creepy...
Let's go home, Ken.
No way!
Big Sis!
What's this flower called?
What will I ever do with
you, Ken?
"Sarracenia, or pitcher plant.
A carnivorous flower."
King Pitcher Plant
A pitcher plant, huh?
Originated in North America,
they grow in subtropical regions.
The Man-Eating Sarracenian
Someone help!
Big Sis!
Kenji! Ken!
Ken!
Big Sis!
Hiromi,
they have a flower orangery!
Want to check it out?
Yeah.
What's wrong, little boy?
My sister... my sister...
What happened to her?
She was eaten by a flower.
What?
Eaten by a flower?
Did you ask the staff
to look for her?
The things Kenji said were all so strange,
they said they couldn't trust him.
Kenji.
Where did you lose track
of your sister, Yukie?
In the greenhouse.
You shouldn't tease
grown-ups like that.
In the greenhouse?
I don't think the boy is lying.
Six people have already disappeared
near that botanical garden.
Kenji, I'm sure your
sister is already home.
Why don't you head home?
I'm sure your mother
is worried about you.
I don't have a mom!
And your father?
He's dead.
I'm sure your sister
just went home.
That's right, Kenji.
Where do you live?
Seishun Estates in Ikuta.
All right. Then the three of us
will take you home, all right?
Okay!
Big Sis?
Those two are doing their
best in this little apartment.
And Yukie was like a
mother and father to Kenji.
She's all that little boy had.
Yukie...
What happened at that
botanical garden?
Kenji.
I swear to you,
I'll find your sister.
So don't cry anymore, all right?
That hurts! It hurts!
Let go of him!
They're so red and swollen...
I'm sure it hurt very much, Ken.
Has...
Has Shocker taken even my
ability to soothe a crying child?
Where are you going, Takeshi?
Mister! Wait, Mister!
Hey, Mister!
You can have my model
if you want it...
Just please, find my big sister!
Find my big sister!
I will.
I promise you, I'll find her.
I promise!
The cyborg Hongo Takeshi...
As the one man who knows the
extent of Shocker's evils
he is putting his life on
the line to fight them.
King Pitcher Plant
The pitcher plant is gone.
Someone pulled it out.
Did Yukie disappear
with the pitcher plant?
Damn you... wait!
Damn... nerve gas.
When wind spins the turbine in
cyborg Hongo Takeshi's belt,
he transforms into
the Kamen Rider.
Where am I?
Hongo Takeshi caught
one of our men.
It's the boss.
Is Rider on your trail?
Number 3 was captured.
Pitcher-Plant Man,
in accordance with Shocker's laws,
you must eliminate Number 3.
What is this place?
The underground fortress of
Shocker's Pitcher-Plant Man.
Shocker?
We've given this man a
preliminary injection.
He will soon undergo
tests to prove that he
capable of handling
our cyborg alterations.
Run 50,000 volts
through the man's body.
If he proves able to endure it, he will
be sent to the cyborg research facility
and serve us,
as Shocker's latest cyborg.
Start the flow of electricity!
Increase it to 100,000 volts!
Enough. He's dead.
That's awful. How could you?
You'll undergo this test
yourself, at noon.
No! Please, return me to Ken!
Ken! Ken!
The preliminary injection.
Big Sis!
What's wrong?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You're in your sister's house.
Big Sis...
Big Sis was eaten by a flower.
You were dreaming, right?
Poor thing.
But don't worry.
Takeshi said he'd find your big
sister, remember?
KAMEN RIDER
Did anything happen
while I was out?
No.
Lock it.
Okay.
I brought us a visitor.
He's a member of Shocker.
Shocker?
Yes.
I think they were the ones
who kidnapped Kenji's sister.
Now...
tell me where your base is!
Tell him!
No! Let me go!
Initiate the test!
All right...
The monster left...
It was told to kill the hostage!
What's wrong?
A strange monster...
outside the window!
There's nobody there.
I was sure I saw it!
A plant-like monster...
It was peering in the window!
It's him...
the one who ate my sister!
What?
Rider Kick!
Who was that?
Ken... that nice man
was the Kamen Rider!
Kamen Rider?
Thank you, Mr. Rider!
Kenji!
Big Sis!
Ken!
Takeshi...
Hey.
Yukie's back, I see.
Ken!
Big Sis!
It must be wonderful
to have siblings.
Jonan University Biochemistry Laboratory
Mister!
Hey, mister!
Kenji!
Hey, you're just
like the Kamen Rider!
What do you mean?
Mr. Rider patted my
head just like you did!
I'm afraid I'm not as
strong as the Kamen Rider.
But you still kept
your promise...
Because you got my sister back!
I can't thank you enough.
Not at all.
It's Kenji who made sure you
came back safe and sound.
You searched hard for
her, didn't you?
You even let your
precious model go.
It's okay!
You don't regret
it, even a little?
It was a promise between men!
I see.
That's good thinking.
Kenji gave me his model
to ask me to search for you.
Did he, really?
Ken. I'll buy you a new model.
Really? That's great!
Yippee! Yippee! Yippee!
We'd better go quick, then!
Bye-bye!
Everyone has someone
to support them:
a sibling, a
partner, or a spouse.
They're all bound together
by different kinds of love.
But for now, Hongo Takeshi
is allowed no such luxury.
As a cyborg,
Takeshi's future would remain consumed
by his dark and lonely
battle with Shocker.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the monstrous Mantis Man.
A series of mysterious
earthquakes...
Could Shocker be behind
these, too?
With a bigger earthquake on the
way, Rider rises to stop it.
Join us next week
for more Kamen Rider
in "The Monstrous Mantis Man."
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!