KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming,
with its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadows
threaten us all
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Ichimonji Hayato is the Kamen
Rider, a cyborg.
He was modified by the evil
Shocker, a secret
organization plotting
world domination.
Kamen Rider has pledged to
fight Shocker and free humanity!
And... go!
You're losing speed!
Pick up the pace!
Fifteen seconds left!
Hey, what's going on?
A swimmer practicing for the Olympics
disappeared in front of his team's eyes.
Days passed with no sign of this
strange mystery ever being solved.
Monstrous Merman
Amazonia
Shocker has to be behind this.
But why would they
go after a swimmer?
I didn't see anything
out of the ordinary.
You?
Nothing off here, either.
That's strange.
You think HQ got their
information wrong?
Definitely not.
This is definitely the place the
mystery sound waves were coming from.
I see.
If the FBI sent an
expert like you,
they must be sure of it.
Let's try another dive tomorrow.
Sure.
Ready, Miyuki?
Watch carefully how your
big brother does it.
Stay very calm and move
your arms and legs slowly.
But deep water is scary...
Don't talk like that.
You can't learn to swim
properly in shallow water.
Go on.
Ready?
He's such a good swimmer.
Come on, Miyuki!
Swim over to me!
Don't worry! I'll be right here!
Miyuki? What's wrong?
Swim to...
Big Brother!
Someone help!
That's not fair!
I'll get you for that,
you filthy tomboys!
Catch me if you can!
Wait for me! Wait up!
Wait! Wait up!
Hey!
What's wrong with you, Mari?
You're looking kind of down...
You homesick or something?
I'm fine. Just leave me alone.
See? She yelled at you.
Kids should stay out
of grown-ups' business.
Come on!
Cut it out! Hey, cut it out!
Hey!
I think it's time for lunch.
Taki and the others
should be back soon.
Who cares what Mr. Taki does?
He went off with another girl.
That woman's a co-worker.
Don't sweat it, all right?
But Mr. Taki promised he'd
teach me how to dive next time
we were at the beach...
Taki, I see someone over there.
That's strange...
Let's go look.
Hey, what's wrong?
My brother's gone!
Don't cry, now.
Did you get separated?
He was eaten by a monster!
What did you say?
Tell us more!
This man possesses
considerable stamina.
We should transform him
into a worker at once.
Amazonia.
Is your mission, Operation:
507, proceeding as planned?
It will surely be
complete by the deadline.
But the workers are exhausted
by the labor on the sea floor.
Continue to catch humans
with exceptional stamina
and complete the operation
as quickly as possible.
And when it is done, there will be none
who can oppose the power of Shocker!
Evil organization
Shocker had set its eyes
on a large uranium deposit
in the ocean near Japan,
and were advancing a plan to
build an undersea factory.
They refer to this
plan as Operation: 507.
Meanwhile,
believing the swimmer's mysterious
disappearance to be
the work of Shocker,
Ichimonji Hayato was
out investigating.
I thought so...
The water from the pool
flows directly to the sea.
They kidnapped that swimmer to create
a cyborg proficient in the water.
Damnable Shocker...
What are you scheming
for our oceans now?
It showed up around here, then?
It has to be a Shocker cyborg.
We need to get to the
bottom of their plans.
A sea monster this time, eh?
We'll do an early dive tomorrow.
I'm sure we'll learn
something useful.
I'll start from the
opposite side as Taki.
Between the undersea monster
and the mysterious sound waves,
they clearly have an
underwater base in the area.
But I wonder what our
Hayato's getting up to...
Hayato should join us soon.
Take care, all right?
There you are, monster!
Transform!
I'll face you, Rider.
Come to me!
Hayato should have
been here by now...
KAMEN RIDER
We'll meet back here
in twenty minutes.
Okay. Take care.
You, too.
Don't forget the emergency
signal if there's trouble.
All right, let's go.
Hey, where's Hayato, anyway?
I wonder where he could be...
Do you think something
happened to him?
Don't be ridiculous.
There he is!
It's Hayato!
Hey, Hayato. You sure took
your time getting here...
Yes,
I ran into Shocker on the way.
What?
They showed themselves already?
It was a fearsome
foe, a fish monster...
It completely had the
advantage in the water.
A fish monster?
But then Taki and his
partner are in trouble...
Where have they gone?
They went for an
early morning dive.
That's not good.
Taki doesn't stand a
chance against that thing.
I'm heading out.
Mr. Tachibana, all of you.
Stay in the hotel room.
All right.
Mister...
You'll save my big
brother, won't you?
Miyuki, was it?
Yes.
I promise,
I'll bring your brother back.
Pinky swear?
Pinky swear.
Don't you worry.
He'll save him, no sweat!
Within the next 24 hours, you'll be
ready for labor on the ocean floor.
Damn you...
what are you doing to me?!
Let me go!
You... are you with Shocker?!
Taki's in danger...
Where's Taki?
Bad news!
He activated the
emergency signal!
Was I too late?
Okay, leave Taki to me.
I'll find him.
You return to the hotel
and protect the others.
They'll be in danger, too.
Transform!
We've captured the spy.
You dare to stand against
us, do you?
So it's the uranium
you're after?
Do you work with the Rider?
Amazonia.
That man is Taki of the FBI.
His partner and the Kamen
Rider are both on the move.
Capture them at once!
Put that man into the capsule.
Damn... they captured her, too?
Put that woman in the capsule.
We'll lure the
Kamen Rider to us.
The Kamen Rider is
inside the base!
Hold it! All of you, stay here.
Let him come to us!
That's odd...
What are they planning?
Rider!
Taki! Where is he?
I don't know.
But they seem to have something planned.
Be careful!
Right...
Rider!
Are you all right?
Taki, I'm going to
break your capsule.
Now her!
Thank you.
There you are, Kamen Rider...
This place will be your grave.
What's that?
Do it!
Be careful!
Rider... are you sure
you want to fight here?
Bring it!
Strange... it's hard to breathe.
Having trouble, Rider?
I've set the oxygen in this room
to one-third of its usual levels!
Die, Rider!
Those switches...
Rider...
we'll finish this later.
Withdraw!
I'll find Mr. Aoyagi.
You get out of here.
Okay. Thanks.
I'll detonate their base.
Hurry up and escape!
Thank you!
Hey!
Taki!
Pops!
Mr. Taki!
Taki, you're safe!
I managed to make it out.
What about my brother?
Don't worry.
The Kamen Rider is going to save him.
Really?
Are you all right, Mr. Aoyagi?
Yes.
We'll jump straight
to the surface.
Kamen Rider...
I've been waiting!
Mr. Aoyagi, Miyuki is waiting.
Hurry!
Rider...
finally giving up the ghost?
Rider Kick!
He did it!
Kamen Rider won!
Miyuki!
Big Brother!
I'm so happy...
Miyuki!
I knew you were alive!
I'm so sorry to worry you.
The Kamen Rider saved me.
Isn't this nice?
I'm really glad your brother's
back, Miyuki.
You'd better spoil her for a
while, okay?
That's right.
She was really worried about
you, you know.
Thank you, all of you.
You've got me crying, too!
Hey, it's Hayato!
Hayato!
Ichimonji Hayato has defeated his
latest unspeakably powerful foe.
But Shocker's unwavering persistence
only renews his will to fight.
To be continued
Next Episode Preview
The next assassin sent by Shocker
HQ to kill our Kamen Rider
is the soaring monster
Musasabeedle.
When Hayato and the others catch wind
of Shocker's plan to blow up Sapporo,
they head to Hokkaido.
They arrive at Lake Toya on Mount
Showa-Shinzan.
It's a fabulous location
shoot in midsummer Hokkaido!
Join us next week for "Soaring
Monster Musasabeedle."
Soaring Monster
Musasabeedle
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the
villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with
all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
Kamen Rider!