KAMEN RIDER
Shocker is coming
With its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadow
threatens us all
But I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's Go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Daidouji Geophysics
Research Institute
Kamen Rider
Versus
Shocker
Ano, the experiment
was a huge success!
I'm really happy for you, professor.
Thanks.
If the artificial gravity device GX was larger,
it could be strong enough to shift the Earth's axis!
It would be a disaster if it fell into the wrong hands, though.
That's right.
Even world conquest would be an easy task.
- All right.
- Let's go process the experiment data.
Get the data ready to be
inputted into the computer.
Yes.
Ano, hurry up and help me gather the data!
- Right!
A power outage?
Maybe because of the lightning.
Professor Daidouji!
I want to congratulate you on
completing your research.
Who's There!?
Who are you!?
We are Shocker, and we have waited
patiently for your research to bare fruit.
What do you want!?
I am Doctor Shinigami, The Commander
of Shocker's Japan branch.
We will now gratefully take
the fruits of your research!
I won't hand it over!
Get out of here, Ano!
- Right.
- Hurry and run!
What's the matter, Ano?
Ano!
Professor!
Help me!
What's going on?
You shall not escape.
If Shocker holds the power has the power to shift
the Earth's axis, we will be able to subjugate the world!
Ano!
Say something!
What'd you do with Ano?!
Release him!
Begin constructing the artificial
gravity device using the data at once.
We will alter the Earth's axis, and sink the
Japanese archipelago into the bottom of the sea!
Excuse me, Doctor Shinigami?
What is it?
This data is missing it's most
vital part, the GX equation!
What?
I see...
How dare he!
That damn Daidouji must have hidden
the most crucial piece of the puzzle!
However, we will not give up here!
I will never hand it over...!
I will not let my life's work be used for world domination!
Hey!
Help!
Ano?!
Ano!
Hey Ano!
Hang in there!
Are you all right?
Ano! You've gotta get up!
Is that you, Professor?
So you're alright?
I've put you through a lot, so please forgive me!
We've got to get you to a hospital.
It must have been hard to escape.
I'm so glad that you're okay.
Well...
While they were shocked learning that the GX
equation wasn't included in the data they stole
I took a chance and escaped.
Pr-professor...
Just where where in the world
did you hide the GX equation?
To tell you, I entrusted it to my daughter,
Tamami, in case anything happened.
It's with Tamami...
Ano?
Who are you?
I am Fly Man!
I'll thank you for blabbering the truth!
With it's location confirmed,
we have no more use for you, Daidouji!
Help!
You cannot escape us!
Please! I only ask that you
spare my daughter, Tamami!
Let her go in peace!
I beg of you! please spare my daughter!
I'll only consider it if you hand over
the GX equation willingly.
Stop right there, Shocker!
Don't tell them anything!
So you've shown yourself, FBI brat!
This way!
Shocker! We won't let you take Professor Daidouji!
Ichimonji Hayato, how did you know where we were?
The FBI headquarters deciphered
your encrypted transmissions!
You're aiming for Professor Daidouji's research
in order to flood the world, aren't you?!
Get them!
Taki, take care of the Professor!
All right! Hurry!
Wait!
Come at me, Ichimonji Hayato!
So you're here as well!
Sabotegron and Mogurang!
Transform!
Let's go, Shocker cyborgs!
How dare you do that to our comrades!
Take me on if you dare, Fly Man!
Rider Kick!
Hayato!
We arrived just in time, didn't we?
It's all right now, Professor.
It's not. We might be too late.
For what reason?
Why are we too late?
I already told them that the secret of my
research is being held by my daughter.
With your daughter?
Daidouji
Thank you for coming, everyone.
Tamami, here's something on behalf of everyone.
Happy birthday!
- Thank you!
- Congratulations!
But don't you feel lonely without your father here?
Tamami's father is a famous scientist,
so it can't be helped.
It's fine. I've gotten used to it.
Even if my Papa's not around,
all my friends are here!
Also, he didn't forget,
because he sent me a present.
See?
Your doll is cool and all,
but the cake is even better!
Oh! That's right!
I still haven't cut it yet.
Don't you want to blow the candles out first?
Hey, close the curtains.
It'll give off a nice glow!
Blow it all out with one breath!
Ready? Here goes!
The cake's on fire!
We need to get out of here!
W- What are you doing?
- But what's wrong with it?
- The door's stuck!
The only option left is to go
through the windows, let's hurry!
Oh no! Shocker cyborgs are here!
Let me go!
You're Arigabari and Dokugander, aren't you?
This is bad...
Let go of me!
Someone save me!
Stop that!
It hurts!
Let go!
Why you!
- You brat!
- Let go of me!
- Crap.
- Let go!
Speed it up!
Hey, sleeping on the job, are you?
Hey!
He's unconscious.
Who knocked him out?
It's Hongo Takeshi!
Shocker cyborgs!
Put down that girl and leave immediately!
Silence! If you dare to interfere
then your life is forfeit!
It seems like you couldn't hear me.
Here I go!
Transform!
Kamen Rider!
Stay behind me, alright?
Save me, Rider!
Help!
So you're an all new cyborg?
My name is Zanjioh! I'm a man-eating
salamander from the Japanese Alps!
The girl is ours, Kamen Rider!
Get him!
Die!
Let go!
Good timing, Ichimonji!
We've captured the girl!
Help...
This is bad!
They've taken the Professor's daughter.
He's a fearsome Shocker cyborg.
Please cheer up a little, Professor.
You should too, Pops.
You look very distraught.
I'm sure Hayato will come back with Tamami soon!
A parent can't help but be concerned
about their child's well being.
Though, I don't expect you girls to
understand what that feels like yet.
They're back!
W- What happened?
He suffered a light concussion, that's all.
Goro.
Aw man...
Why those Shocker creeps!
Where's the Professor's daughter?
We were too late.
What?
She was taken by Shocker.
It's as we feared...
Yes, this is Tachibana Racing Club—
What? Doctor Shinigami?
Deliver this message to Professor Daidouji.
If he values his daughter's life,
then he will hand over the GX equation.
The exchange will be held at Hell Valley.
Tomorrow at noon.
Shocker!
I've brought Professor Daidouji as requested!
Are you going to return Tamami?
So you've finally come, Ichimonji Hayato!
The exchange will be done
in the middle of the valley.
On the count of three, we will begin!
If you try to do anything,
we'll kill the girl!
One!
Two!
Three!
Go.
Tamami wake up!
Papa!
Tamami!
Ichimonji Hayato.
Did you think that Shocker would
let you just walk away?
Look!
You fell right into our trap!
Mukadelas!
Kamestone!
Armadillong!
Namekujira!
Zanbronzo!
Egyptas!
Ghoster!
Unicornos!
Crab Bubbler!
Wolf Man!
Todogiller!
Dokudalian!
Antlithunder!
Spider Man!
Gamagiller!
Dokugander!
Yamogerus!
Eiking!
Snowman!
Scorpion Man!
Isoginchack!
Bat Man!
Torikabuto!
Gebacondor!
Chameleon!
Arichimedes!
Musasabeedle!
Sarracenian!
Even if you consider yourself invincible
you stand no chance against our great army!
Have you gone mad, Ichimonji Hayato?
Doctor Shinigami.
It seems that your over confidence has made you blind.
Take a good look at the Professor Daidouji you have!
What?
Now!
Doctor Shinigami.
You'll be coming with us until we reach safety.
You planned this, didn't you, Hongo Takeshi?
Tell that group of ravenous monsters
to get out of our sight!
- Now...
- Hongo...
- Let's take a walk, shall we?
- Let's go.
- Hold on tight!
- Are you all right?
Okay!
Damn it!
Wait!
None of you will leave here alive!
This is bad.
We messed up!
Tamami!
Damn!
Don't be afraid, Tamami!
Keep your eyes closed no matter what, okay?
Okay.
I'll do like you say!
All right.
Hongo! It's time to Transform!
All right!
Transform!
Rider Hammer Kick!
There you are, Shocker cyborgs!
Hayato, leave them to me!
Will he be all right alone?
Rider!
Taki!
What good timing!
Take care of her!
Alright!
- All right!
- Let's go!
Rider Kick!
Let's move on!
Right.
Have you prepared yourselves, Riders?
Get them!
Kicking off the ground
with a Rider Jump,
a great turbine that
whirls through the air!
Calling up lightning
with a Rider Kick!
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Chop!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Ichimonji.
- Let's do this.
- Hongo.
Get them!
Tearing through the
air with a Rider Plane,
a great flight that
skates over the ground!
That was the last of them.
Calling up tornadoes
with a Rider Jet!
Strange. Zanjioh wasn't with them.
Striking down enemies
with a Rider Cut!
All right, let's go!
Oh, oh Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Tamami!
Papa!
I was so scared!
But I stayed strong for you Papa.
I'm sorry. I never wanted to put you
in danger because of my research.
Professor, about your research...
How exactly did you leave the
secret information your daughter?
Actually, it's in the doll I gave Tamami as her birthday present.
In a doll?
So, where is that doll?
It's still at home.
What?
Kamen Rider!
I won't let you have this doll!
Give me the doll!
Never!
I'm here as well!
When we were attacked, we didn't see you anywhere.
we assumed that meant you were secretly
following us to get the secrets of the GX equation!
Get them!
Hongo!
Oh no!
Hongo! Go after him!
You won't escape, Zanjioh!
Here I go!
How's that, Riders?
Die, Riders!
Over there, Hongo!
All right!
Rider Double Kick!
Shocker is coming
With its armies made of demons
Their black shadows threaten our friends
But I'll fight to maintain the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's Go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
THE END