Kamen Rider
Versus
Ambassador Hell
Shocker is coming
With its armies
straight from hell
Their black shadow
threatens us all
But I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's Go!
With my shining machine...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
East Japan Road Race Championship
Organizer: JAO     With Support From: Suzuki Motors
- Go for it!
- You can do it! You can do it!
Start
- Do your best!
- You can do it!
Do your best!
Taki!
Go for it!
You can do it!
- Do your best!
- Go for it!
You gotta get first place!
Taki!
Go for it!
Taki! Hongo! Don't lose, ya hear?!
Do your best!
Start!
Taki, let's go!
All right!
Hey.
Hongo and Taki are nearing the target location.
Excellent.
Failure will not be tolerated.
Aim carefully
and get rid of Hongo and Taki in one foul swoop!
How strange. It seems that we've gone off course.
Is that a helicopter?!
What was that sound?
We have an announcement regarding the race.
I repeat, we have an announcement regarding the race.
The two racers in the lead, from Tachibana Racing Club,
appear to have gone off course, and are missing.
Pops!
Taki Kazuya and Hongo Takeshi of Tachibana
Racing Club were in the lead, however...
Let's go!
They're not here!
I'm pretty sure we hit them...
Looking for me?
You're still alive?
Hold on a minute, Pops!
There's tire tracks heading that way!
- Let's check it out!
- Let's go that way!
All right!
Did the attack go as planned?
Yes sir.
We've confirmed the deaths of Hongo Takeshi and Taki Kazuya.
Good. Return immediately!
Roger!
So this is Shocker's Tokyo branch?
Time to stop whatever their new plan is!
Damn it! They're on to us!
Taki, don't let your guard down!
You fools!
Hongo and Taki, you've done us
a favor by coming right to us.
Ambassador Hell!
Shocker's hidden cameras have captured
your every movement! Now stay still and die!
It's poison gas!
Taki, we need to open that escape hatch!
Someone's holding it down!
That's right!
Try to open it if you can!
That voice, it's Kabutrong!
This isn't good, I can't breathe!
Taki!
Hang in there!
Taki! Damn!
Good!
With this, the two of them
should be completely melted!
It went well!
They've both turned into soup!
Is that right, Kabutrong?
What? That voice belongs to Kamen Rider!
Have you forgotten my abilities?
So you live, Kamen Rider?!
Kamen Rider's alive!
Come out, everyone!
where are you, Ambassador Hell?
Nut's, so he's fled?
Ambassador Hell!
I have not fled .
Shocker has successfully built an
impenetrable stronghold in a secret location.
And pnce we set up our Super Destruction Beam there...
...we will be able to call forth lightning all
over Japan, and reduce it to ashes!
Listen up!
In 30 seconds, the base you're
in will be blown to smithereens!
They've set a time bomb!
Taki, let's get out of here!
Rider!
Kamen Rider!
Your strength alone can't break through it!
We built that door in accordance to
calculations made by Shocker's computers!
You have 15 seconds left.
Farewell, Kamen Rider and Taki Kazuya.
Taki, there's no other way to escape
besides finding that time bomb!
He said there were only 15 seconds left?
Shh.
Rider, there's no time left!
Ambassador Hell, The bases
self-destruction was successful.
Kamen Rider's been wiped
off the face of the Earth!
You're wrong.
There's a minuscule chance that they survived.
Surely you jest...
We must take the necessary measures.
Until we transport the Super Destruction Beam device
to our impenetrable stronghold at Mount Fuji,
do not let your guard down even for a second.
Takeshi and Taki sure are late.
They're probably busy
beating up Shocker right now.
Should I cook something while we wait?
Here you go.
- And a strange one at that!
- It's an earthquake!
What's going on? I'm scared!
Pops, the floor...
The floor's glowing.
What?
A new Shocker monster!
The name's Kamikirikid!
Now come with me!
What kind of idiot would come with you?!
You dare to fight back?!
Eat my sleeping gas!
Someone's coming!
Hurry up and carry them out of here!
Pops, I'm here!
Are they not here?
Yuri?
The cups still warm.
Where did they go?
That's odd.
Pops isn't the kind of person
who leaves his pipe lit.
Go!
Emi!
- Hongo!
- Tokko!
Hurry and get out!
It's dangerous! Run!
Wait!
A new Shocker monster?
The name's Kamikirikid!
Now eat this!
Rider Transformation!
There you are, Kamen Rider!
Get him!
Talk!
Where's Shocker's great stronghold located?
It hurts...
I'll talk! I'll talk, so let me go!
Now talk!
It's in Fuji...
Where in Fuji?
Why did you attack me?
It's what you deserve, you imbecile!
How vexing...
He's gone.
Taki!
Rider.
A truck with a Shocker crest is heading towards Mount Fuji.
I see. All right!
Take care of Emi and Tokko.
Where are they?
They're over there.
I'll tail Shocker all the way to their stronghold.
You'll realize soon enough.
How foolish you are, Kamen Rider.
That smoke...
Did you think you'd be able to escape with that?
Rats! I lost them.
Race, race, machine! Run like lightning!
And carry all our hopes with you!
Take out those dastardly Shockers!
Dive, Cyclone! Straight into the sea!
Hurricane Jump! Hurricane Jump!
We're counting on you! Cyclone! Cyclone!
Race, race, machine! Speed like a fireball!
Become the limbs of the ally of justice!
Reclaim the cheerfulness of our towns
Soar into the sky, Cyclone!
Hurricane Jump! Hurricane Jump!
It's a victory! Cyclone! Cyclone!
So the entrance to Shocker's stronghold is in this field?
Kamen Rider!
If you resist, even for a second,
then your friends' lives are forfeit!
Look over there!
Rider!
Pops! Yuri!
Rider, don't worry about us!
That's right! I'm prepared for this!
How's that, Rider?
Are you willing to defy us now?
I can't do it.
I can't just sit by and watch them die.
Get him!
How's that?
You can't do a thing to us!
Secure the ropes!
How's that?
Are going to give up, Rider?
Drag him around!
Continue fighting, don't give in!
Please, Rider!
Rider, I'm coming!
Taki!
Damn you, Shocker!
You'll pay for this!
It's Taki!
Rider, I'll take care of the Pops and Yuri!
Shocker is coming
with its armies spreading fear
Get him!
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my mask of green...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Retreat! Retreat!
The Rider's gone.
No way! He was there
just a second ago.
Rider! Rider!
Damn.
I'll tear down Shocker's stronghold
on my own if I have to!
I see.
So Shocker constructed their great
stronghold inside of Mount Fuji?
In that case, I'll have to force my way through enemy lines!
- Hongo!
Be quiet.
Don't rush, Taki.
Look.
That's the objective.
We have to use the element of
surprise and destroy that first.
You all right?
Be careful.
Monsters!
Sea Snake Man!
Worm Man!
Eiking!
Ghoster!
Pranodon!
Kinokomorg!
Zanjioh!
Dokumond!
Musasabeedle!
Zanbronzo!
Beaded Lizard Man!
Hongo Takeshi, you've done well coming here!
But alas, this place will be your grave!
Get them!
Are you ready, Taki?
Ready as ever!
Taki, You go and blow up the stronghold!
Sounds good!
Rider Transformation!
Rider Punch!
Kamen Rider!
While you were busy fighting us, we finished installing
the Destruction Beam device on our stronghold!
It should be fired at Tokyo in a matter of seconds!
What? In a few seconds?
Rider, this time Shocker has won!
Target of attack, Tokyo Tower.
Laser firing in 30 seconds.
What a fine mess I've stumbled into..
Just watch.
Soon, the Tokyo Tower will be blown to smithereens.
Taki!
When did you get in here?
- Taki!
- Rider!
- Right!
- Those dials are the controls!
If you try to fire the laser now,
the entire stronghold will blow up!
We have to stop it quickly!
It's too late!
This stronghold's about to blow!
- Right!
- Taki, let's get out of here!
What's going on?!
Kamen Rider has destroyed the power room!
What?!
Curse you, Kamen Rider!
All units, evacuate!
Shocker is coming,
with its armies made of demons
Their black shadows
threaten our friends,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
With my scarf of red...
Rider Jump!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Shocker is coming
Rider Reversal!
with its armies spreading fear
Come at me!
Their black shadows
threaten our towns,
but I'll fight to maintain
the peace of our world!
Go! Go! Let's go!
How's that, Kamen Rider?
I'll make it so you can't
defy Shocker ever again!
With my mask of green...
Damn it! His power's are in his horns?
Rider Jump!
Rider Punch!
Rider Kick!
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
Rider, Rider!
Rider Kick!
He came here on a storm...
Who is he? Who is he?
Who is this man of storms,
who sends the villains scattering?
Kamen Rider!
His mask stands for justice!
Start it up! Rev it up!
Get that engine running!
Give me top speed, Cyclone!
Hit them with all of your anger!
Put an end to Shocker's evil!
Rider! Rider!
THE END
Kamen Rider!